[TWELVE] Because they put
it on a plane instead.
I can't get out!
Please, you have to help me!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hold it.
You'll be taking
orders from me, now.
[LISA grunts]
Here!
[LISA screams]
[TWELVE, LISA grunt]
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[SHIBAZAKI]
Damn you, Sphinx.
[FIVE]
Lisa, you won't get away again.
[NEWS ANCHOR 6A]
We have some new information
regarding the bombing
incident at Haneda Airport.
The explosion occured
on an unoccupied runway,
fortunately resulting
in no injuries.
Based on suspicious
text messages,
the attack is suspected
to be connected
to the terrorist cell, Sphinx.
[SHIMADA]
"We're supposed to stay here."
It's called direct
order, gentlemen.
In spite of that,
you lot somehow got into
a fight at the airport,
and even managed
to significantly interfere
with the investigation.
Was it worth it?
Because you're all now
suspended. You're off the case.
I don't want to see you
for three months.
[HAMURA]
Three months?
If you even piss
without orders again,
you'll be out permanently.
We clear on this?
Won't be terribly easy
to find another job.
Don't punish them. The whole
thing was my idea, sir.
And I'm prepared to
take full responsibility.
Oh, I don't need
you to tell me that.
You are getting
special treatment.
Mister Shibazaki, at this point
you are suspended indefinitely.
Indefinite?
So basically you're
saying he's fired?
Look, you need to know I saw
Sphinx with my own eyes.
They're not guilty
of that bombing.
Whoever set up the
whole airport thing
was just trying to frame them.
[SHIMADA] Don't dig yourself any
deeper than you already have.
[SHIMADA]
Shibazaki. Leave your badge.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Tch!
[KURAHASHI] I get what
you're tryin' to say. I do.
But you have to understand
you still got off easy.
[SHIBAZAKI] That girl
was behind this, right?
Pretty much, yeah.
Seemed she was the only
one who wanted you out.
You said she was a nuclear
physicist or somethin'?
Nice story, but what
is she really?
I actually put out a
few feelers about that,
and looks like she was
transferred from the ISA.
Intelligence Support Activity?
So this chick came from
US Army Special Ops?
You got it.
Why are we working
with a former spy?
And why do they care
about our stolen plutonium?
[KURAHASHI] Because the
situation may be much worse
than we could ever have assumed.
[LISA grunting]
[doorbell rings]
Okay, what's wrong?
Why are you visiting
out of the blue?
What? Oh, you know.
[HARUKA]
How's Mom doing?
Dunno. Fine and
at home, I guess.
Wow, Dad.
I take it you're too
obsessed with work
to notice her or some
cliché like that?
So I'm payin' for you to study
somethin' along the lines
of physics at this school.
[HARUKA] I'm in the department
of science and engineering.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Then you should know about
nuclear power stuff, too, right?
Come on.
Are you worried I'm not
studying hard enough, or what?
No, no, I just have a couple
o' questions for ya is all.
Like how plutonium's
used to make a bomb.
For real? Don't tell me
this is for an investigation?
Oh. No.
[HARUKA]
You can't smoke in here, Dad.
[SHIBAZAKI sighs]
[HARUKA] It's a precision
machine, so the right tools
would be necessary.
Can't imagine it'd be easy for
amateurs to pull off, though.
But in theory, it's possible.
That's what worries me.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, but there's more to it
than just building the thing.
Whoever's handling the material
would be exposed
to serious radiation.
[HARUKA] Your investigation
must be pretty serious.
'Cause that's a heck
of a look on your face.
Oh, no.
I was just thinkin' how
weak your barley tea is.
[HARUKA growls]
[LISA] Now to let the
curry simmer for a bit...
[doorbell rings]
You Lisa Mishima?
There's a package for you.
Really, for me?
[DELIVERY MAN 8A]
Thank you!
Who coulda sent it?
[LISA]
Wha-- Bomb?
[TWELVE] So we're gonna
move out of the hideout?
[NINE]
She's been seen, now.
We have to. They can't find us.
We're too close to risk it.
I really liked that roof.
Man, this totally sucks.
[LISA panting]
[LISA whimpers]
[CLARENCE] Even for just a
threat, this was too far.
You know our
government's orders.
Securin' the object
is our top priority.
If the worst were to
have happened today--
Nine would never hide it in
his own apartment, please.
[CLARENCE grunts]
[FIVE] In the end, all they
want are results, right?
My point is you need
to show some restraint.
Ya need to realize there's
only so much I can do
to hold off the local police.
[FIVE gasps]
This isn't funny anymore.
I've actually never
found this funny.
I didn't think we'd
end up using this spot.
[TWELVE]
Cool!
We can play all the
games we want in here.
They're all super retro,
but still.
[NINE] You know whose
fault this is, don't you?
It's mine.
And I'm sorry.
[SHIBAZAKI] The top officials
at all the buildings
where bombs have
been placed took part
in a seminar led by a group
called the Rising Peace Academy.
They had previously implemented
something called
the Athena Plan.
Athena, the goddess of wisdom,
appears in Greek mythology.
Just like the Sphinx.
[door clacks]
Hello? Oh, Shibazaki!
Hey.
I thought I had
heard that you were
gonna be out of the
office for a while.
Stopped by to say hi,
and figured I could
look somethin' up.
You want one? It's a chocolate.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hm?
I also got some of those
pink ones you like.
If that's your idea of
a farewell gift, keep it.
Hey, wasn't there a recent
thing where the son
of some bigwig in
the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare
injured someone?
Yeah. Heard about that.
I think they settled
the case out of court.
[SHIBAZAKI] Hate to ask,
but think you can
find the paperwork?
Oh, and uh...
"Oh, and uh" what?
You better save me one
of those Pon de Rings.
[TWELVE] Whoa. You seriously
wanna go there already?
[NINE] We didn't take Five
into consideration before.
Accelerating the plan's
our only choice.
I guess so.
But?
[TWELVE]
Nothin'. Except. Well...
[NINE gasps]
I was just thinking,
maybe we should
stop this whole
thing altogether.
[CHILD 8A]
I'm hungry.
[MOTHER 8A] I gave you
a snack five minutes ago.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Let's get straight to the point.
About ten years ago,
there was a project
created called the Athena Plan.
Their "goal" was to properly
educate gifted children.
However, the specifics of the
project cannot be found
anywhere on the public record.
But I do know members of
the Rising Peace Academy
spearheaded the project.
And since you were
one of those members.
I'm assuming you must have
known about this plan?
I'm very sorry,
but I don't know
what you're talking about.
Although, even if I did,
I certainly wouldn't be able
to divulge classified
information regarding it.
I'm assuming a detective
must have known that, though.
[SHIBAZAKI]
How's that son o' yours?
Behaving any better?
Now, why would
you bring that up?
It has already been resolved.
[SHIBAZAKI] Yes, and I'm
sure you're relieved.
But it seems he didn't
quite learn his lesson.
[FUJIKAWA] You bastard.
A detective using extortion?
How dare you? You should
know your place.
Funny how one can change when
they're about to be fired.
[SHIBAZAKI] Turns out I don't
give a damn about "my place."
[NINE]
How can you quit?
[TWELVE]
Because if we keep this up,
there's every chance we'll...
Are you scared?
[TWELVE gasps]
[NINE]
Is it Lisa?
[LISA gasps]
[NINE]
Twelve. Think back.
Remember where we came from.
We're only doing what
we have to, here.
Or have... have you
changed your mind?
[NINE] I get it, I do.
That bomb almost killed her.
Okay. We'll stop
involving Lisa, then.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
[TWELVE] But I'm afraid it
still won't keep her safe.
[LISA whimpering]
Thought I'd help you
investigate today.
How'd you find me?
It wasn't very hard.
Just had to bribe someone
with some ramen.
You'll be fired if you
disobey orders again,
or did you forget? Got a job
lined up if you lose this one?
Folks own a grocery store.
Always got that to fall back on.
[HAMURA]
Orphanages?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah.
According to that politician,
they tested the children
at all the orphanages in
the country, then gathered up
the ones they considered
the most "gifted".
[HAMURA] So what, you're
gonna check 'em all out?
One by one?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah.
Probably ought to act like
a detective at some point.
[PRINCIPAL 8A] Yes, I believe
there was a test like that.
Far as I recall,
though, no children
from our institution passed it.
[YOUNG MAN 8A]
Well, I was only five.
So I don't remember
what was on the test.
But I do remember
being interviewed.
What's that?
[YOUNG MAN 8A]
Oh. I love those Sphinx guys.
They're legit.
[SHIBAZAKI] Okay, so
afterwards, the boy was taken
by a government official?
[NUN 8A] That's right, and we
never heard from him again.
[SHIBAZAKI] By chance,
do you happen to remember
anything about that official?
Sorry, but I think he
gave me a business card.
This is definitely weird.
All of these places and not
one person we talked to
has a clue where
those kids ended up.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah.
Almost like they're
ghosts or something.
They just disappeared.
But at least we've got this guy,
and we know he's no ghost.
[KINOSHITA]
The Athena Plan?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Right. Get me whatever you can
about the project.
Check the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare.
Look into their past
employees, too.
You should be able to find this
Aoki guy's address there.
If I'm caught, I won't get
off with just being fired.
Isn't hacking the cybercrime
division's specialty?
No you ass,
we try to prevent it.
[SHIBAZAKI] To be clear,
if we don't figure this out
a lot of people are gonna die.
[KINOSHITA'S WIFE]
Mm-hm.
Ooh! I can feel it moving!
[KINOSHITA] Gimme a bit.
I'll call you back later.
[LISA panting]
[FIVE] ♪ London Bridge
is falling down, ♪
♪ falling down,
falling down.♪
♪ London Bridge
is falling down, ♪
♪ my fair lady. ♪
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hey, Hamura.
That young guy we talked
to who's a "fan" of Sphinx.
You know what's happening there?
[HAMURA]
Oh yeah. Seems a lot of kids
are startin' to treat
them like heroes.
Course, they conveniently
forget the truth.
You know, that they're
just criminals.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Interesting.
Years ago, when I was
young like them,
there were these teens
who threw rocks at cops.
Fought against the government.
Sphinx may be called
terrorists, now,
but in a different time.
These boys might've been
thought of as somethin' else.
Just my opinion.
[feet shuffling]
[LISA gasps]
[KINOSHITA]
Yes, I've found Aoki's address.
Also. I've got some goods
on the Athena Plan.
Pharmaceutical companies,
neuroscience researchers,
and medical organizations
were involved, too.
No kiddin'?
[KINOSHITA] The plan itself
was terminated 7 years ago.
I see.
Oh, and, there's one
more important detail.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Of course.
[LISA gasps]
[FIVE]
Poor thing.
You should take better
care of your nails
or they'll get weak and break.
Lisa Mishima.
Supposedly living with
her caring mother,
just the two of them.
I researched everything
about you, Lisa.
I even know you've run away from
the guys because you think,
rightfully so, that it would
be better for them that way.
You didn't want
to distract them
any more than you already have.
Isn't that right?
You're just so sweet.
Please, understand. I actually
want to help them, too.
[LISA]
Huh?
[FIVE] They still have a chance
to atone for their crimes.
However, if they carry out
the next part of their plan,
they will be tragically
beyond redemption.
You can still help.
Tell me what you know
and save them.
Why were you even
with Nine and Twelve?
By accident.
I saw them at the Tokyo
government office building.
They told me I had
to choose between
becoming an accomplice
and dying, so...
[FIVE]
You should've chosen to die.
[LISA gasps]
[FIVE] That was stupid.
Unbelievably stupid.
To have an idiot girl
following them around.
I can't imagine how annoying
that must have been for them.
[LISA] I don't... I don't
care what happens to me.
But please, please let them go.
[FIVE]
Why would I do that?
Surprise sweetie, I don't care
what happens to you, either.
You are nothing.
I care more about
a roach than you.
[FIVE]
Back to the point.
You don't honestly think those
boys have a future, do you?
[LISA gasps]
[NINE]
Where are you going?
[TWELVE] I'm gonna
find Lisa. I'll be back.
Is that a good idea?
What if she's ratting
us out to the cops.
[TWELVE]
She would never!
[NINE] And that's not just
what you want to think?
[phone rings]
[TWELVE]
It's from Lisa's phone.
Lisa!
From Five. There's no doubt.
Twelve. Wait!
This is a trap.
[TWELVE]
I know it is.
Then why go? We can't
afford to take chances.
We're running out of time!
[TWELVE]
I know that, too! Don't you see?
I'm going because
I'm out of time.
[NINE]
Twelve...
Don't do this.
I'm sorry, Nine.