[police sirens blaring]
[NEWS ANCHOR 11A]
We have a special news bulletin.
According to the information
we just received,
the serial bombing terrorists--
[NEWS ANCHOR 11B]
terrorist group, Sphinx,
have made a proclamation. The
government and related agen--
[NEWS ANCHOR 11C]
An announcement was made stating
a nuclear device will go off
at 10 o'clock this evening.
[NEWS ANCHOR 11A]
Upon hearing the proclamation,
the Chief Cabinet Secretary
held a press conference.
[CHIEF CABINET SECRETARY]
Earlier this evening
at precisely 8:21,
The government declared
an official state of emergency.
The entire Kanto region
has been designated
an emergency danger zone.
To maintain public order,
we have requested
that the ground Self-Defense
Force be dispatched.
We ask that all citizens
within the danger zone,
and surrounding areas,
evacuate immediately.
[LISA gasps]
You're alive!
Hey!
Oh no! Are you okay?
Talk to me! Twelve!
[HAMURA] Those guys are
seriously gonna do it,
aren't they? This is the
revenge they've been after.
[SHIBAZAKI]
No. I don't think so.
[HAMURA]
Huh?
[VOICE 11A]
We're sorry.
Your call cannot be
completed at this time.
Think about it, man.
They haven't
killed anyone, right?
What?
[SHIBAZAKI]
During the bombing at the Tokyo
government office, they rigged
the fire alarms to go off
so they could make sure
everyone evacuated
before the building collapsed.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Roppongi Station, too.
They put in a webcam
and detonated the bomb
when no one was around.
And at the airport,
they even went so far
as to disarm the device
planted to frame them.
Sphinx is no ordinary
terrorist group.
They have a specific goal.
Something important they
want the world to know.
[phone rings]
[HARUKA]
Dad, are you there?
Haruka! You got a sec?
I got a question for you.
Where are you, Dad?
Please, tell me
you're evacuating.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Calm down. I'll be fine.
What d'you mean, fine?
[SHIBAZAKI] Listen to me.
I promise I'll get out of here.
I just have to finish up.
Good. Now, what did
you want to ask me?
Is there a way to
use an atomic bomb
without killing anyone?
[HARUKA]
What?
Like, an atomic bomb explodes,
but without a single casualty.
Is something like that possible?
I think so. I've uh,
I've heard of like,
a high-altitude
nuclear explosion before.
Sorry, I missed that.
Oh, high altitude.
It'd be a nuclear explosion,
but instead of on land,
it's in the stratosphere!
The stratosphere?
[HARUKA] During an experiment
in America, though,
there was a large-scale
power outage.
[SHIBAZAKI]
How would they get a bomb
into the stratosphere
in the first place?
I know how. With a balloon!
Saw it once in college.
They put a camera on one.
Buncha students sent it up
to take pictures of Earth.
I'll hafta call you back!
[MUKASA] Shibazaki!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were fired.
[SHIBAZAKI]
You're comin' with us.
What? No, wait, aw, Shibazaki!
[phone ringing]
Nothing. I can't get through.
[LISA whimpers]
Twelve. Wake up. Please.
[OKANO] That the
National weather service?
Yes, sir, but they
don't know anything, yet.
Hamura, any reports
of a balloon?
Checking on that, now!
The roof! I'll head
up there now!
[KINOSHITA gasps]
Guys, take a look at this.
[OKANO]
Huh?
[KINOSHITA] This footage is
from about 43 minutes ago.
It's from a camera
inside the city.
Went up the same time as
the bomb announcement.
There's no question.
The explosion
will be in the sky.
Roger.
Understood.
[OPERATOR 11A] This is from an
information-gathering satellite.
The balloon is
currently ascending
to 10,000 meters
above the Kanto area.
Good work.
Request dispatch of the
Air Self-Defense Force.
A high-altitude nuclear blast.
So the explosion will be
in the upper atmosphere.
The radiation will disperse out
into space, but in exchange,
it will most likely generate a
strong electromagnetic pulse.
[KURAHASHI]
And that means what?
Well, to put it simply,
if the pulse is strong enough,
it means it will
probably destroy
most of the electronics
in the country.
I hope you're
wrong about that.
Or we're all hosed.
Japan will be paralyzed.
Then what's the goal?
Why knock the whole country
back into a literal Dark Age?
[KURAHASHI] Contact the
cabinet's crisis center.
To start with, get all the
nuclear power plants shut down.
[OPERATOR 11A]
Yes, sir.
Hold on, what'll
happen to aircraft?
That would depend
on if the plane
has Anti-EMP equipment or not.
Those without it will crash.
And how many have
the necessary equipment?
Zero. Unless you count
the U.S. forces.
Right now, they have the only
planes in Japan with Anti-EMP.
[TWELVE grunts]
Twelve!
[LISA sobbing]
[LISA]
I'm so glad you're okay.
[TWELVE]
Lisa...
[KURAHASHI] Contact all
planes and helicopters
currently in the air. We need
them on the ground, now.
[WORKER 11A] We're counting
over 250 aircraft flying, sir.
It'll take at least an hour and
a half to land them all safely.
Not soon enough!
You have 30 minutes!
[KURAHASHI] Call the Welfare
and Transportation Ministries.
Put all medical
and transportation
facilities on alert!
[OPERATORS]
Yessir!
[AIRCRAFT OPERATOR 11A]
Echo 0-1.
Target 0-6-0.
Decrease 4-8 miles.
Altitude 6-6-0.
[PILOT 11A]
Roger, it's on my radar.
12 o'clock, 4-8 miles.
Altitude 6-6-0.
[AIRCRAFT OPERATOR 11A]
That's your target.
[PILOT 11A]
Roger.
[AIRCRAFT OPERATOR 11A]
Echo 0-1, target dead ahead
1-8 miles.
[PILOT 11A]
Roger. Tally-ho.
Target. Approaching
the mark, now.
Roger. Tally-ho.
Another, no stranger.
[OPERATOR 11A] Air Self-Defense
Force has made
visual confirmation.
[LISA] So, is Nine really trying
to destroy the whole world?
When the atomic bomb explodes,
will it kill everyone?
[PILOT 11A] Rising sun,
Echo 0-1 aborting mission.
Reaching climb limitation.
[OPERATOR 11A]
Balloon's going beyond
the plane's altitude limit.
We won't be able to
follow it any farther.
Where we were raised,
no one had any parents,
let alone family. It was a
dark place. A lonely place.
[TWELVE] Even after we escaped,
we were still always alone.
Just us two. Nine and me.
Neither one of us was
ever needed by anyone,
except each other.
[OPERATOR 11A] Less than
three minutes until the blast!
[KURAHASHI]
The aircraft?
[OPERATOR 11A]
Four still to land!
That's why.
[OPERATOR 11A] They'll be on
the ground momentarily, sir.
Oh, Lisa. Thank you.
I'm glad we met. You saved me.
[NINE gasps]
[NINE grunting]
Nine. I, uh--
The grenade.
It was you, wasn't it?
Uh--
[NINE]
You're the only one who would
pull something like that.
Guess I owe you one.
[music playing]
[SHIBAZAKI] Took long enough,
but I finally made it here.
This is your hometown, isn't it?
The place Sphinx
wanted everyone to see.
Well, you've definitely got
the whole world's attention.
They all wanna
know who you are,
where you came from.
Hell, media outlets
across the planet are
desperate to find out.
If you're caught,
everything that happened to
you will come out in the open.
It would have to.
At this point, you've created
such a fire-storm
no one can ignore it anymore.
So the world is ready to listen.
Which, I'm assuming was
your goal the whole time.
Am I right?
Were you planning to be caught
from the very beginning?
Yeah, but we needed something.
Well, needed someone.
We couldn't be captured
if no one figured that out.
You were our Oedipus,
Shibazaki. It was always you.
All right, then. Sphinx,
you're under arrest!
About her, she's just a hostage.
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE]
Please protect her.
[helicopters humming]
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
Americans?
What do they want, now?
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
I am holding a detonator.
While, the atomic bomb
may be no more,
there are countless others
like it in this country.
They're all over.
The one this detonator
is connected to,
is in a nuclear power plant!
[LISA gasps]
Tch!
[NINE] If the U.S. forces
do not withdraw.
I will set this off!
[COMMANDER 11A]
Correct, sir.
That's what he's claimin'.
[TRANSMISSION 11A]
Carry out your duties.
But if we do--
[TRANSMISSION 11A]
The mere existence of someone
who knows the truth
about the airport
and the Shuto Expressway
incident puts us
at a disadvantage.
Even if the bomb is real,
nothing can be done
about it now.
Yes, sir.
[TRANSMISSION 11A]
Don't kill the detective.
If he accuses the
Japanese government,
it will turn attention
away from us.
[COMMANDER 11A]
Understood.
[gun fires]
[NINE grunts]
[NINE sobbing]
[NINE screaming]
No, wait! Don't do it!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hold fire! Hold fire!
Please, let me
talk to him first!
[SHIBAZAKI]
I will make sure everything
comes to light in court.
That's why you put your
lives on the line.
That's all you really wanted.
I promise. The world
will know the truth.
[NINE] All right.
I'll let you finish it.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[high-pitched ringing]
[NINE grunting]
Thank you. But, I have
one more favor to ask.
Remember us.
Remember that we lived.
[LISA] I saw the entire
thing with my own eyes,
and I still couldn't
believe it was real.
A lot of people
came to ask me about it,
but I couldn't talk
about anything.
I thought for a while
I wouldn't be able to talk
for the rest of my life.
I was so sure about that, too,
but, gradually,
I got used to it.
And then, before I
knew what had happened,
a year had passed.
[LISA gasps]
Hey, there.
Guessing you were
just visiting the grave?
[LISA]
Yes.
[SHIBAZAKI]
I'm headed there now, actually.
[LISA] I, um, I just wanna
thank you for everything.
[SHIBAZAKI]
You're very welcome.
I'm always here if you need me.
Did I, did I tell you about
how Nine loved music?
[SHIBAZAKI]
No.
Well one time.
I asked him what he
was always listening to,
and he said it was music
from a "cold place".
Then, he told me it
was from Iceland.
V-O-N. It's an Icelandic word.
Have you heard of that before?
Nine told me it means "hope".
Of course.
[LISA]
Well, see ya.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah. Be well.