[NINE] The bomb is set
to blow at eight sharp.
We have to personally
retrieve it before then.
[TWELVE] What is this,
Mission: Impossible?
[NINE]
It's her. She's back.
You pulled us off the bomb
so they could deal with it!
[KURAHASHI] I was given
every assurance they would.
[phones ringing]
Hey, Nine, is this?
[NINE]
There's no doubt.
Five is back.
[FIVE] ♪ London Bridge
is falling down, ♪
♪ falling down,
falling down. ♪
[CLARENCE] You've never
behaved like this before.
You seem excited. It's weird.
[FIVE]
Excuse me for having fun.
I've been so bored playing
this game by myself.
I don't even care
about winning anymore.
I just want an opponent worthy
of my attention. And now...
...the prodigal
son has returned.
Let the games begin, Nine.
[LISA]
Whoa.
[OKANO] Our initial subway
bombing report is complete.
Although there
were no fatalities.
72 people in total were injured.
More than any of the
prior Sphinx attacks.
My men are currently analyzing
surveillance footage from
the Shuto Shinjuku Line,
as well as bomb
fragments we recovered.
We also have people
looking into the connection
between the bombings and
the recent interruption
in cell phone service
across all networks.
[KURAHASHI] That should
just about do it, people.
But before you leave.
Let me say one thing.
Go ahead, Chief.
[KURAHASHI] The United States
Government made
an offer to provide assistance
with our investigation.
From this point on, we will
coordinate our efforts
with the FBI's
Counterterrorism Division,
to bring an end
to these attacks.
We'll work with them,
and put their experience
to good use. Any requests they
make should be prioritized.
Dismissed.
[YOUNG FIVE panting]
[YOUNG FIVE cackling]
[NINE gasps]
[TWELVE]
Nine? Are you okay?
Why don't you get some rest?
I can't. Five's not
gonna wait for that.
[TWELVE]
So what?
Is she holding some kind
of grudge against us?
I don't understand.
[NINE]
Neither do I.
If she had wanted to escape
with us, she could've.
I think she just likes
playing the game.
Now she wants to pick up
where she left off.
She's quite the adversary.
[TWELVE] Somethin' tells me
she's not gonna go easy on us.
[LISA]
Um...
I don't mean to eavesdrop,
but maybe I could help out?
What the hell could you do?
U-Uh, I am capable
of things, y'know!
[NINE]
Like what?
I could, uh...
Blow up buildings?
Hurt bystanders?
I don't know.
[NINE]
Could you do that?
No. I couldn't.
[LISA gasps]
[NINE] 'Cause this is what
we're doing. Look at them.
[TWELVE]
But Nine, we didn't detonate
the bomb in the subway--
[NINE] So just stay
out of our way, alright?
You wanna help? Do that.
[SHIBAZAKI] Their offer of
support is just a front.
The Americans are planning
to take control, aren't they?
If that happens, we're gonna
have a real hard time
getting a single thing done.
I'm afraid you're right.
From here on out, my hands
are effectively tied.
This have anything
to do with you
getting called out of
yesterday's meeting?
Where'd you run off to?
The Chief Cabinet
Secretary's office.
Something seemed off
the minute I walked in.
All the Department
heads were sitting there
waiting like whipped pups.
That's where I met
our new "partners."
[INSPECTOR GENERAL]
Kurahashi. Let me introduce you.
This is Special Agent
Clarence, from the FBI.
[CLARENCE]
It's a pleasure, sir.
[KURAHASHI] I'm First
Division Chief Kurahashi.
They've kindly offered
help getting a handle
on this Sphinx situation.
The FBI? You're sure?
[CHIEF CABINET SECRETARY]
Absolutely.
The cabinet has already
approved our decision.
One thing. This is
a domestic incident.
Why bring in the FBI?
Surely their capable personnel
have better things to do
than worry about bombs in Japan.
There's a bit more to it.
[CLARENCE] Six months ago, a
nuclear fuel processing facility
in Aomori was infiltrated
by persons unknown.
[CLARENCE]
The United States Government is
"extremely interested" in the
item that went missing.
We're here now
'cause we've reason
to suspect the ones behind the
attack at the Aomori facility
are the same as your
serial bombers.
[FIVE] More than just
"reason to suspect."
We have proof.
What kind of proof
are you talking about?
If you don't mind sharing that
information, we can arrest--
[FIVE laughs]
[FIVE] On top of allowing those
silly boys to wreak havoc
across your beautiful city. You
let them leak sensitive intel
about the case to the public,
and now you have the gall
to puff your chest and talk
about making arrests?
That's the funniest joke
I've heard all year.
[KURAHASHI]
From what I gathered,
the woman is a researcher with
the American Nuclear
Emergency Support Team.
NEST for short.
[SHIBAZAKI] A researcher?
That doesn't seem right.
[KURAHASHI] I confirmed
her official job title.
[SHIBAZAKI sighs]
I'll be damned.
Apparently the FBI
believes Sphinx
stole that Aomori
plutonium as well.
Yeah.
[SHIBAZAKI] Seems to make
'em think they've got
the authority to mess with
those kids however they want.
Like that crap that
went down yesterday.
[SHIBAZAKI]
What happens when they back
the perps into a corner?
They gonna force
that joker into play?
[TWELVE] Your voice is
like the color of straw.
A pale yellow.
What?
[TWELVE]
Oh, sorry.
Y'see, I have this condition
known as synesthesia.
I experience sounds as colors.
[LISA]
Colors?
[TWELVE]
Yeah. It's funny.
There're lots of blues,
greens and reds.
But I hardly ever hear yellow.
Oh.
We're talkin' rare. Unique.
I'm in the way. I know I am.
[LISA] It would be better
if I just left, wouldn't it?
What? No way. Nine was
just bein' grouchy.
[TWELVE] He may say mean things,
but he doesn't hate you.
[LISA]
But he said-- Huh?
[TWELVE]
That's just mild sadism.
[LISA giggles]
Makes sense.
I guess you know him
pretty well by now, huh?
[TWELVE]
Hm?
I'll admit. I'm a
little bit jealous.
Well we've been together
for most of our lives.
[TWELVE]
Just the two of us.
[NEWS ANCHOR 6A] We interrupt
with live, breaking news.
The serial bombers called
Sphinx have resurfaced.
Once again antagonizing
authorities through riddles.
[TWELVE] Nice! Looks like
we've got an impostor.
Guess that's one way to
know we've hit the big time.
She's made the first move.
Okay, "Gaius Julius
Caesar gone to Arab."
"Gone to Arab?"
But he went to Egypt. I think
I know what this means, though.
It's a simple Caesar cipher.
So does that mean it
needs to be changed
to Arabic numerals?
[SHIBAZAKI]
The Caesar cipher is an ancient
substitution coding system
that shifts each letter
a fixed number of places
down the alphabet.
If there isn't an assigned
shift, the default
is three letters to the left.
Since there was
no assigned shift
sent with the message,
we'll have to hope
the default does the job.
[NINE grumbles]
No dice. Maybe, coordinates?
Could be.
[TWELVE] Haneda Airport,
International Terminal.
Yeah. It's one of our targets.
[OKANO] All right! Get a hold
of the airport right away!
Yessir!
So what's with the
twenty at the end?
[SHIBAZAKI] The time the bomb's
set to go off, most likely.
[phone chimes]
[HAMURA]
"VON voyage"?
As in "Have a nice trip"?
They're just messin' with us!
Also, they've misspelled it.
No. It's intentional.
"VON voyage?"
They're really trying
to make this look like us.
This is it. Her message to us.
[NINE] Her way of saying that
she's seen through everything.
[MANAGER 6A]
Yes.
I have already been briefed
on the situation by the MLIT.
[CLARENCE] Thing is,
this is very hush-hush.
Every single operative involved
has top-tier security clearance.
What we need from
you is discretion.
Therefore, any communication
with the terrorists
should be through us.
An' we'll pass the
info onto the police.
I understand. I'll make
the necessary arrangements.
Do you really think
those two are gonna bite?
They gotta be smart enough
to realize this is a trap.
They will come.
[CLARENCE gasps]
They will come to see me.
[TWELVE] Isn't it possible
the bomb's a fake?
[NINE] If it's Five, and she
never does anything half-assed,
she'll blow it up for real.
Because she has nothing to lose.
She knows the cops
will blame it on us.
Let's put out a video
saying it wasn't us!
The word of a mysterious
fringe group, or Metro PD.
Which one would you buy into?
[TWELVE]
So messed up.
Try to stop the bomb and
get caught. Or option two:
we ignore it, and are implicated
as murderous psychopaths.
'At's one hell of a trap!
[NINE]
It's summer vacation,
so the airport's
gonna be packed.
Depending on how strong the
bomb is and where it's placed.
Hundreds of those
people could die!
[TWELVE]
She's gone insane.
[NINE] You know there was never
any sanity to begin with.
Not for her, and not for us.
[INVESTIGATOR A]
Detective! Over here!
[INVESTIGATOR B]
Sir! On my way!
What's buggin' you?
I don't think this is
really from Sphinx.
Yeah? Why do ya say that?
The clue's too cut and dry.
Doesn't feel like
there's a message hiding
below the surface.
Look, we don't
have time to think
about that stuff right now.
We only have four hours
to find and disarm the bomb.
Let's go earn our
salaries, old man!
[SHIMADA]
Attention! Everybody listen up.
We have orders
straight from the top.
The Explosives Ordinance
Disposal team is en route
to remove the bomb.
We're supposed to stay here
and await further instructions.
But, wait a sec! Director!
This was a challenge
issued to Metro PD!
Please let us go!
[KATO]
C'mon, sir!
[KINOSHITA]
We want some payback!
[DETECTIVE 6A] Yeah!
Why do we have to stay put?
[DETECTIVE 6B]
What the hell is this?
[OKANO]
Everyone, calm down!
Director. You said these
orders came from the top?
From the Superintendent
General's mouth.
[SHIMADA]
I shouldn't have to say this,
but renegade cops
will not be tolerated.
No one get cute.
Uh, yo, Shibazaki.
Where're you going?
[SHIBAZAKI]
To grab some food.
I have a feeling we'll all be
stuck here for a while.
[TWELVE]
This is gonna suck.
The international terminal
is freakin' huge!
[NINE]
Yeah.
[TWELVE] So, how are we
supposed to find the bomb?
Well most likely,
we'll receive the next riddle
once we get there.
I counted about 1500
surveillance cameras
spread throughout the terminal.
[TWELVE] And naturally,
Five'll be monitoring
every single one of 'em.
[NINE] Which means we need
to act under the assumption
we'll be apprehended.
No way. We just
need someone new.
Someone whose face
hasn't been tied to us yet.
[LISA screams]
No! Sorry. I thought I'd
make noodles. You hungry?
No way in hell.
To what? The noodles?
[car beeps]
[HAMURA] Where do you
think you're going?
It's against the rules
to use official vehicles
for personal food breaks.
Or were you planning to get
yourself into trouble again?
[HAMURA]
Times have changed, gramps.
The lone wolf
shtick's kinda done.
[car beeps]
[OKANO] That goes for
you too, Hamura.
Sorry, boys. 'Bout
those "dinner" plans?
We'll be joinin' ya.
[NINE]
Impossible.
[TWELVE] Think about it.
Wouldn't someone amateurish
be useful in a
situation like this one?
[LISA]
Amateurish?
[NINE]
Let's go.
Wait. Kokonoe. Uh. Nine!
It's just that.
I want to be one of you.
Let me help your cause!
And maybe I can't
handle the bombs.
Or any of this other
stuff yet, but please!
I'll study hard!
[LISA gasps]
[NINE sighs]
We'll move separately.
[LISA gasps]
To avoid the security cameras.
[NINE] Take the train
out to the airport.
[LISA gasps]
Ah, the irony.
Here we are, a couple
terrorists, heading out
to try and prevent a bombing.
[CLARENCE]
Everything's in place.
[FIVE] Pull up the
"Runpass" activity log.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Yes, ma'am.
[FIVE] Filter down to users
active in the last 15 minutes.
[OPERATOR 6B]
Yes, ma'am.
[FIVE] Check with all
airport personnel lists.
Sure, one moment.
[FIVE]
Move!
[OPERATOR 6B]
My apologies.
You're getting careless. Nine.
[FIVE] Show the camera C15
feed from ten minutes ago.
[MALE OPERATOR 6A]
It'll take about three minutes
to transfer the data.
You're kidding me.
Bring up F12 to G6
on the main monitors.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Done.
[TWELVE]
S'about time, isn't it?
Yeah, let's move out.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Target confirmed.
A chessboard?
That's crazy.
You think she wants to
continue the game from before?
Uh-huh. She's planning to
use the airport as the board
and us as the pieces.
[TWELVE]
And lemme guess.
If we win, the position
of the last piece
will match the bomb's location.
Yeah.
[NINE grunts]
King's Knight to F6!
Good luck!
[FIVE] It's been far too
long since we last played.
Run, Nine.