I was just thinking,
maybe we should
stop this whole
thing altogether.
[SHIBAZAKI] To be clear,
if we don't figure this out
a lot of people are gonna die.
[LISA]
I don't care what happens to me
[FIVE]
Surprise sweetie,
I don't care what
happens to you, either.
Back to the point.
You don't honestly think those
boys have a future, do you?
[TWELVE]
Lisa!
[NINE]
We can't afford to take chances.
We're running out of time!
[TWELVE]
I know that, too!
I'm going because
I'm out of time.
[doorbell rings]
I'll make the old man spill
everything he knows.
[footsteps]
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
I'm Detective Shibazaki,
Metro P.D.
Might we have a few minutes
of your time, please?
[SHIBAZAKI coughs]
Oh. Yeah, um.
[AOKI grunts]
Right this way.
[phone rings]
[HAMURA gasps]
[AOKI] Haven't used
this tea set in a while.
When you get to be my age,
visitors are few
and far between.
Especially now, ever since
my dear wife passed away.
I'm not surprised.
Always knew someone like you
would come for answers one day.
Well, get on with it.
I'll get straight
to the point, then.
Tell me what you know
about the Athena Plan.
[SHIBAZAKI] Your organization
gave an intelligence test
to all orphans in the country
under the age of five.
You gathered the top performers,
and erased all traces
of them from the record.
Or am I mistaken?
Have you ever heard the name
Shigeru Yamamoto before?
The former under-secretary
for Health and Welfare?
Yeah, he passed away
about three years ago.
[AOKI]
That's correct.
He died unexpectedly right
before he could report the truth
about what happened
to the authorities.
[HAMURA, SHIBAZAKI gasp]
[AOKI] If you'd still like to be
able to walk the streets
safely at night, it would be
prudent to go home now.
Hamura, you should
do as he says.
What, are you crazy?
After all this, there's no
way I'm wussin' out now!
[recorder beeps]
[AOKI] Are you familiar with
savant syndrome, detectives?
[SHIBAZAKI]
I think so.
Isn't that where someone has
extremely high brain function,
but only in specific areas
due to injury or autism.
[AOKI] Savants are known to
excel in mental arithmetic,
memorization, music, as well
as art and spatial skills,
to name a few.
Although these
abilities far exceed
an average person's in very
specific areas, many are unable
to reliably complete mundane
tasks, or even communicate
with the outside world.
To artificially reproduce
the exceptional abilities
found in these savants,
but without the deficits
commonly associated
with the syndrome.
That was the goal that
lead to the creation
of the Athena Plan.
Under government directive,
26 children total
were collected.
They were processed and
became test subjects.
Test subjects?
How is that kinda
thing even possible?
[AOKI] The theory behind
the whole experiment
was based on a new drug
accidentally developed
in the mid-90s by a Japanese
pharmaceutical company.
They stumbled across it while
researching brain function.
The Rising Peace Academy
saw the results
of the drug research.
Then, they pulled the strings
to set the
Athena Plan in motion.
That's right.
[AOKI] Funds were allocated
to create a remote facility,
where the test
subjects were kept.
It was known as
"The Settlement".
Ridiculous sums of money
were poured into that place.
Along with dozens
of the most talented
researchers in the country.
[AOKI]
The caveat,
this new "wonder drug" that
had fallen into our laps?
It was only effective on
the still-developing brains
of children under
the age of five.
Unfortunately,
the serum proved to be
highly volatile to the
biological systems
of the majority
of test subjects.
The bodies and minds
of these children
were severely
ravaged by the drug.
Most of them died
shortly after infusion.
I've heard enough!
How can you talk about this
--like it was nothing?
--[SHIBAZAKI] Hamura!
In the end. Athena was
labeled a complete failure.
The U.S. government
had become aware
of the program and intervened.
They shut the whole thing
down seven years ago.
Oh.
[AOKI]
Seems the tea's gotten cold.
[SHIBAZAKI]
So why?
Why did you wait until
now to come clean?
Honestly, if you
hadn't come along.
I'd have taken
everything I knew about
the Athena Plan to the grave.
Although, in all likelihood,
I imagine those
children would probably
not allow it to end that way.
[HAMURA, SHIBAZAKI grunt]
The moment I told you
'bout that damn project,
I painted a target
across my back. However,
I'm getting old and tired.
My body gets weaker every day.
I can feel it.
Not much time left.
And the children at the
Settlement. Where're they?
When it was shut down,
only one girl
had managed to survive
the various experiments.
One girl, taken into custody
by an American agency,
and the files sealed.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Interesting.
[AOKI]
Although...
[SHIBAZAKI]
"Although" what?
[AOKI] Apparently,
there was a report saying
two of the children managed
to escape the facility.
[HAMURA, SHIBAZAKI gasp]
Do you know their
names, by chance?
The subjects were
never assigned names.
Too empowering. Instead,
they were called by a number.
[AOKI] One of the boys
was number Nine.
The other was number Twelve.
They managed to start a fire,
then took the security systems
down to make their escape.
Clever little buggers.
When did all this go down?
Must've been eight years ago.
If those boys are still alive,
I guess they'd be about 17.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
It's gotta be them.
[AOKI] I'd like to think
they're still alive.
Going to school in
a nice, quiet town,
playing sports
and chasing girls.
Enjoying their lives before the
drug's side effects take over.
[HAMURA growls]
You don't have the
right to say that!
Using children as your
guinea pigs? You bastard.
You can't even be called human!
[AOKI] Yes. I stopped being
human a long time ago.
I was a pawn, a cog
in the great machine.
The orders came down from above.
I just followed them.
Yeah, the guards conducting
inmate selection at Auschwitz
said the same thing.
So you can save that
tired old bullshit.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Tell me who was in charge.
[AOKI sighs]
[AOKI]
It was Doctor Mamiya.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
Wasn't he--?
[SHIBAZAKI gasping]
[HAMURA] Shibazaki.
[SHIBAZAKI]
It can't be.
[HAMURA]
Shunzo Mamiya, right?
Isn't that the crotchety
old bastard who got you
demoted in the first place?
They call him the monster
of Japanese politics.
What are you gonna do?
[SUBORDINATE 9A]
This is Alpha One.
We have visual confirmation.
[CLARENCE] Five, should we
move in to apprehend?
[FIVE]
Of course not!
I mean, what's the point
if can't have some fun?
[TWELVE grunts]
[TWELVE panting]
Lisa.
[TWELVE]
Lisa!
[LISA]
Oh, Twelve! I, This...
The-They-They're all bombs.
I don't--
W-What do I do?
[TWELVE]
Just be calm, 'kay?
[LISA]
I'm scared.
Damn her.
[TWELVE] I bet she
thinks this is hilarious.
[FIVE] It looks like he's
enjoying himself to me.
What're you doin', Five?
We're supposed to capture 'im.
He can't very well
tell us the location
of the item if he's dead.
Don't be such a
downer, Clarence.
No one likes the loser who
shuts down a party early.
[LISA]
So do you have a plan?
Hold still.
[LISA]
Twelve?
It's gonna be fine.
Don't you worry.
[FIVE groans]
[TWELVE]
Tch.
[LISA whimpering]
[TWELVE]
All right.
That's one down.
[CLARENCE]
What exactly are you hopin'
to accomplish here?
I know professional EOD guys
who couldn't disarm
that many devices in the
time you've given him.
If the kid buys it,
it'll be harder to
secure what we need.
It appears you've
lost sight of our goal.
Shut up!
[CLARENCE gasps]
[LISA gasps]
I'm sorry.
[LISA] If I hadn't left, those
people wouldn't have grabbed me.
I was just trying to stay
out of the way for once,
but I ended up
making everything worse!
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
No. You don't
have to apologize.
What?
It's okay.
This isn't your fault.
[LISA gasps, whimpers]
[TWELVE]
I'm the reason you're here.
Let me apologize.
[TWELVE]
Nine was right.
If I hadn't gotten you
involved at the airport,
none of this would've happened.
[TWELVE]
In fact,
I never should've given
you a ride that night.
No, before that.
I shouldn't have talked to
you from the very beginning.
I knew it would be dangerous.
Getting to know somebody.
But...
I had to.
Thank you.
But it's all right.
I'm okay. Leave me.
[TWELVE gasps]
Lisa...
You should go now,
while there's still time.
[TWELVE]
I'm not going anywhere!
Nine's waiting for you.
[TWELVE gasps]
[LISA]
Please don't worry about me.
You know he still
needs your help.
[LISA] You two still have
something important
you need to finish.
The reason you came to Tokyo.
Go, now. Make people
see the truth.
[TWELVE gasps]
[phone ringing]
[TWELVE]
Tch.
[FIVE]
Hey! You having fun yet?
Five!
I propose a trade.
Your girlfriend for the A-bomb.
[TWELVE gasps]
[FIVE] The cops seem to think
you boys stole a little
plutonium from Aomori, but we
know what you really took
was Japan's first in-house
developed prototype atom bomb.
Tell me where you
stashed that sucker,
and I'll disarm your
damsel in distress.
[TWELVE gasps]
[FIVE] C'mon! It's not
a bad trade, really.
Say no, and you two die.
Say yes and you betray Nine.
But you've already
demonstrated that's something
you're willing to do,
so give it up!
Stop it, Five.
[FIVE] You've already chosen
that doe-eyed girl over Nine.
After all you've been through,
how could you let
Lisa down, now?
Who cares about
all that other stuff?
[TWELVE growls]
[FIVE] Of course,
Nine won't understand.
But you should know that.
He'll never forgive you.
Why would he?
You're an untrustworthy,
cowardly traitor!
If you don't talk, she will die.
[FIVE] But at least she can die
a lover's death with you.
Eyes! Look your last!
Arms, take your last embrace!
[FIVE]
Goodnight, Romeo.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
The school! The bomb's
in locker D-12!
Congratulations,
you saved your Juliet.
[NINE gasps]
Damn it, Twelve.
[SUBORDINATE 9A]
We've lost visual.
[CLARENCE]
Roger that. Fan out and search.
[FIVE grunting]
[NINE grunts]
I've regained visual!
Wait, take him alive!
No! Stop!
[CLARENCE]
Five, what--?
[NINE panting]