[VOICE 4A] Even though
you answered correctly,
these friends of yours
decided to cheat.
Which means. Uh oh!
The hidden bomb
cannot be stopped!
[TWELVE giggles]
[LISA]
The entire planet?
Do you, like,
wanna blow it all up?
[TWELVE gasps]
[TWELVE, NINE]
Huh?
[LISA grunts]
[NINE]
Are you crazy?
You shouldn't have
brought her here.
[TWELVE]
A runaway wandering around?
The cops almost caught her,
and she could identify us.
She's helpless, Nine.
We should keep an eye on her.
The girl is an outsider.
She stays, and
everything we've fought
to achieve is jeopardized.
[TWELVE] The thing is. She
hasn't got anywhere else to go.
And when she talked about making
her escape, it really hit home.
[TWELVE] Lisa isn't that
different from us.
[NINE] I seem to
remember you promising
you wouldn't get involved.
It's for her own good.
Getting all mixed up with us?
You know that only
leads to more misfortune.
[phones ringing]
[TWELVE gasps]
[LISA gasps]
I was, that is, I'm sorry!
[TWELVE]
Wow. Talk about lucky.
What?
This little guy's
no ordinary phone.
[TWELVE] See, that
extinguisher is packed
with plastic explosives.
[NINE] And that phone serves
as the detonation switch.
If the fuse had been connected,
we would all be dead.
Ka-bang!
[LISA shrieks]
My bad. I forgot about the
whole "you being sick" thing.
[CLARENCE] Looks like the
weather's held after all.
[FIVE] Oh no. You're wrong.
A storm's on the way.
[LISA sighs]
[NINE] Make sure she cleans
the filth from the tub
when she's done.
[TWELVE]
Chill out.
I think it's been a while
since she last had a bath.
This girl isn't planning on
gradually moving in, I hope.
[NINE] Anyway. Once her fever
goes down, she has to go.
[TWELVE]
Now, hold on!
[NINE] Keeping her here
is absolutely pointless.
She'll just get in the way.
[KURAHASHI]
The data leak caused by Sphinx's
recent attack exposed
the progress of our
current investigation
to the general public.
Now they know
how little we know.
Further failures
will not be tolerated.
We plan to increase
personnel, focusing on
the cybercrime
department specifically.
We will then redouble our
efforts to capture the bombers.
To be frank, we have
no other options.
[KURAHASHI]
Thank you. You're all dismissed.
Go make me proud.
[INVESTIGATORS murmuring]
[NINE]
'Scuse us, coming through.
[TWELVE]
Just some routine maintenance.
Whoa!
[KURAHASHI]
Excuse me.
[CLARENCE]
Yeah. Yeah, we just got here.
Hang on a sec.
Nah, it's nothin'.
Don't worry about a thing.
Okay. Gotcha. I'll tell her.
[TWELVE]
What?
[NINE]
Something wrong?
Don't cha smell it?
There's a fire!
[NINE]
Hurry!
[TWELVE grunts]
Uh-- Welcome home!
[TWELVE coughing]
[LISA] There was no recipe,
so I just kinda free-wheeled it.
Dig in!
Think I'll pass.
What?
Yeah it's inedible.
Hey! You don't have
to be so rude about it!
[TWELVE]
Why don't you have a bite, then?
[LISA gags]
Terrible.
[TWELVE]
Told ya.
[NINE]
Doesn't really matter.
We never asked you to play
house-mom for us, did we?
If this was an attempt to
show us how useful you are,
then that plan backfired.
Aren't cha still
runnin' a fever?
You should probably
be back in bed.
[LISA groans]
[TWELVE]
It's fine. Just go lie down.
[LISA grunting]
[TWELVE] You know.
Even the crummiest food
is worth somethin'.
[NINE]
Huh?
Think about it. The food
we ate at the institution.
Do you remember?
[TWELVE]
So many meals.
I don't remember
enjoying any of them.
There was no taste. Just a task.
Another job to be completed.
[NINE]
It's almost time.
[MALE DETECTIVE 5A]
Hey, it's here! Come on!
[NINE] Greetings!
I'm Sphinx Number One.
[TWELVE] I'm lookin' for
a girlfriend to cook up
some bombs and tasty snacks.
I'm Sphinx Two!
[NINE] Now then, everyone,
you've seen our videos before.
You know what happens next!
[TWELVE]
That's right! It's riddle time!
Today's mega-mystery question:
Where do you go when
you connect the dots
between the punishment of F-E-Z
58-89 and the angel
who planted a grapevine?
[NINE] You have until, oh,
eight o'clock this evening.
[TWELVE]
Fail to solve it in time,
and you're gonna have another
big boom on your hands!
[NINE] Well then.
Happy hunting, officers!
[HAMURA]
God, I hate them.
Kato, grab some analysts
and get to work on this.
Yes, sir!
F-E-Z 58-89.
What does that mean?
License plate or--?
[KINOSHITA]
Hey!
[HAMURA]
Shibazaki, wait!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Mukasa.
Hm? Shibazaki?
F-E-Z-5-8-8-9.
Does that sequence
mean anything to you?
Huh? Yes, well?
Come on. How many years
you worked archives?
[HAMURA] What're you
doing in the file room?
Find something that'll
help solve the riddle?
[HAMURA] Document numbers.
An old case file?
[SHIBAZAKI] The bombers
must've seen our departmental
filing system after
they hacked us.
They only leaked files from
the current investigation
to the public. But it's
a reasonable assumption
they also got ahold of
some older documents.
So long story short,
they intentionally made a riddle
only the police
would understand?
Guess these terrorists
have taken a shine to us.
5-8-8-9. Found it!
[MUKASA] Let's see...
Corporal punishment case
from the public high
school in Tochigi?
[SHIBAZAKI] After showing
up late to their club's
morning practice, four
students got heat stroke
after being forced to run
in over 100 degree weather.
All charges against the
offender were dropped. Odd.
So what's this got
to do with the bombings?
[SHIBAZAKI] There's a passage
in the Apocalypse of Baruch.
The story of an angel
who angered God.
His offense was planting a
grapevine in the Garden of Eden.
The Kabbalah identifies
him as Samael,
but he's also known
as the Red Serpent.
Hell of a nickname.
So, tie it with the
information from the file.
High school kids punished
by being forced to run.
A red serpent forced to run.
What does that sound
like to you, Mukasa?
Running red serpent? No clue.
What could be stretched out like
a snake that runs? In a city?
[HAMURA gasps]
A train.
Right.
And a red train in the middle
of the city would be?
The Shuto Shinjuku!
Time to move!
We gotta tell somebody!
[SHIBAZAKI] The bomb's probably
in one of the train cars.
[HAMURA] Then we'll have
to check them all!
Subway, huh?
These targets are all
inter-connected somehow.
[MUKASA gasps]
[SHIBAZAKI] I'm saying these
aren't random acts of terrorism.
[TWELVE] Hey so, Nine.
That last riddle we gave.
Do you think it was
a bit too simple?
[NINE] It would be problematic
if it was too hard
for them to solve.
[TWELVE] I knew you
made it easy on purpose!
[NINE] Yes. This Detective
Shibazaki should have
figured out the
connection between
all of the bombing
locations by now.
Since we never
make any demands,
he's the kind who would
look for a connection
to figure out what we're after.
You sure have put a lot of trust
into a government official.
What?
Heh! Nothin'. It was a joke.
[SHIBAZAKI] Governor Aohara,
office in the Tokyo Metro
Government Building,
site of the first bombing.
Chief of Police
at Roppongi Station,
location of the second bombing.
A former Chief Cabinet
Secretary and owner
of the building next
to Shirahige Shrine,
the failed third bombing.
And last, head of the
municipal organization
that manages the
Shuto Shinjuku Line.
There's a connection
between 'em.
They all took part
in a seminar run by
the Rising Peace Academy.
The Rising Peace Academy?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah.
'Promoting interaction between
the government and its people'.
Looks like a non-profit
on the surface.
But their seminars have
attracted a lot of big-wig types
over the last few years.
From politicians to
captains of industry.
Pretty weird.
No, not weird.
This connects the dots
between their targets.
[MUKASA]
You're probably overthinking it.
These kids just wanna
watch our reaction.
Not make a point.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Oh, you've got some insight
on terrorist psychology? Huh?
Uh... I wonder
if they're done.
Dealing with the bomb, that is.
[NINE]
Anything?
[TWELVE]
Whole lotta nada.
[NINE] That's strange.
There's been no report
about the bomb being removed.
[TWELVE] Maybe the riddle
was still too hard for them?
[NINE] I don't think so.
That detective's smart.
He should've figured it out.
[TWELVE]
So what do we do? At this rate,
in a little over an hour,
we'll be mass murderers.
Not to worry.
This will deactivate it.
[TWELVE]
Huh?
[NINE]
What's wrong?
That's crazy. No signal.
What the--? Oh, ya
gotta be kidding me!
[WOMAN 5A]
Wha--?
[WOMAN 5B]
No signal.
[MAN 5A]
Are you there?
Weird.
[NINE]
None on this one, either.
[TWELVE] Every carrier,
same issue, same time?
That's impossible!
[NINE]
No, it's possible.
Someone's creating this
interference on purpose.
Like who? Nine?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Have you lost your mind?
Why haven't your people
removed the bomb?
We were given orders.
Straight from the top.
[SHIBAZAKI]
What?
They said the
special assault team
would take care of it
and we should standby
for further instruction.
But sir!
So we just twiddle
our thumbs?
That's what you're saying?
I'm afraid so.
And this
electromagnetic jamming.
It's got something
to do with this?
Look. I am out of the loop.
Shibazaki! Don't do
anything stupid!
Has the past taught
you nothing at all?
[HAMURA]
Shibazaki!
Check in. Can you
hear me, Twelve?
[TWELVE]
Loud and clear.
Let's work fast.
I can calculate the general
location of the train car.
But I won't be able
to pinpoint it yet.
[NINE] For that, I'm gonna
need to access their system
via a backdoor.
I'll give you a more
precise location later.
The bomb is set to
blow at eight sharp.
We have to personally
retrieve it before then.
[TWELVE]
Remove and disarm the bomb
in 50 minutes, undetected?
[NINE]
Correct.
[TWELVE] What is this,
Mission: Impossible?
[NINE]
This is the only way.
We used five kilos of
gunpowder this time around.
That's more than enough to
destroy the entire train car.
[TWELVE]
Well, that's awesome.
They should've solved
the riddle by now.
So what are the police up to?
[NINE]
The electromagnetic interference
is blocking out cell service.
I don't think this
is a coincidence.
[TWELVE] Are you telling
me someone outside
the police department is
creating these problems
to try and screw things up?
And whoever that is,
doesn't want the bomb stopped.
They want the thing to go off?
[NINE]
It's the logical answer.
[TWELVE]
That person's nutso.
[NINE]
To say the least. Yes. I'm in.
[NINE gasps]
Wait. Whaddaya mean
by "multiple signals?"
[NINE] Damn it! There's
no way another train car
could have the same
signature. It's impossible.
[TWELVE]
Obviously not.
[NINE] We're being cornered
with fake operations data.
Someone's doing this.
[TWELVE gasps]
[NINE] There must have been
a trap in the backdoor I used
to infiltrate the train
company's security interface.
[TWELVE] So the person
behind all of this knew
we'd hack into the system.
They set up a fake
backdoor to trap us?
Looks that way. Wait, here.
I'll make another sweep
through the normal OS now.
Try to track the train down.
[NINE] In the meantime, hop onto
the train car closest to you.
But we only have 30 minutes.
[NINE]
We don't have a choice!
[TWELVE]
Gotcha! No rest for the wicked!
[NINE gasps]
What?
They cracked their way in?
Whoever this is
knows their stuff.
No way.
[high-pitched ringing]
[NINE groaning]
Ready or not!
[NINE gasps]
[YOUNG FIVE]
Here I come!
[NINE whimpering]
[YOUNG FIVE]
Ready or not!
Here I come!
[NINE yelps]
[NINE panting]
[NINE]
It's her. She's back.
[HAMURA] Shibazaki.
I've been looking for you.
Hamura. Any thoughts on this?
On?
[SHIBAZAKI] They dispatched
the Special Assault Team
without an official runner,
and Kurahashi said
the order came from top brass.
[HAMURA gasps]
Don't tell me--
[SHIBAZAKI]
Do I have to?
Y'know ferreting out rats
is a real pain in the ass.
[SHIBAZAKI] You just gonna
stand there, or are you comin'?
[HAMURA]
Coming!
[LISA grunting]
[TWELVE]
Come on, 9-18! Damn!
Uh, excuse me. I was--
[NINE gasps]
Son of a...
Anyway. Could you--
[NINE grunts]
[LISA yelps]
[LISA sighs]
[TWELVE]
What? It's close by?
[NINE] If I head there from
here, I might make it.
Sounds good. I can wipe
the camera feeds!
[NINE]
Thanks!
[NINE panting]
[CROWD screams]
[NINE]
It's a bomb! Run, hurry!
There's a bomb on the train!
[CROWD screaming]
[NINE grunting]
[NINE grunts]
[CROWD screaming]
You wanna explain
what the hell's goin' on?
[SHIMADA]
Shibazaki!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Where was Special Assault Team?
You pulled us off the bomb
so they could deal with it!
[KURAHASHI] I was given every
assurance they would.
Yeah, from who?
What bastard let this happen?
[MALE OFFICER 5A] Everyone
please, try to stay calm!
Exit the subway in
an orderly fashion.
[NINE grunts]
[NINE coughs]
Nine! Can you hear me?
[NINE]
Yeah.
[TWELVE]
Are you okay? Are you alive?
Of course I am.
[MALE OFFICER 5A] Please
calm down, help is on the way!
[phones ringing]
Hey, Nine. Is this?
[NINE]
Yeah. There's no doubt.
Five is back.
[FIVE] Such a spectacular
fireworks display.
Perfect for celebrating
our reunion.
Don't you think? Nine?