[NEWS ANCHOR 6A]
The serial bombers called Sphinx
have resurfaced, once again
antagonizing authorities
through riddles.
[TWELVE] Nice! Looks like
we've got an impostor.
Guess that's one way to know
we've hit the big time.
[SHIBAZAKI] We'll have to hope
the default does the job.
[TWELVE] Haneda Airport,
International Terminal.
I don't think this
is really from Sphinx.
It's just that,
I want to be one of you.
Let me help your cause!
[CLARENCE]
Everything's in place.
[FIVE] Pull up the
"Runpass" activity log.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Yes, ma'am.
[FIVE] Filter down to users
active in the last 15 minutes.
[OPERATOR 6B]
Yes, ma'am.
You're getting careless, Nine.
[TWELVE]
It's about time, isn't it?
[OPERATOR 6A]
Target confirmed.
A chessboard?
That's crazy.
You think she wants to continue
the game from before?
Uh-huh. She's planning to
use airport as the board,
and us as the pieces.
[TWELVE] And lemme guess.
If we win, the position
of the last piece will
match the bomb's location.
Yeah.
[NINE grunts]
King's Knight to F-6!
Good luck!
[FIVE] It's been far too long
since we last played.
Run, Nine.
[DETECTIVES panting]
The bomb should be
in here somewhere.
I think we'll have to split up.
[HAMURA]
Hang on, so,
we gotta figure out a way to
search this entire airport?
Just the five of us?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah, and keep in mind,
a message will appear soon.
It could show up anywhere.
Like there! D4?
Exactly.
[NINE panting]
[GIRL 7A]
I hate this airport.
What happened to the dang map?
Ok, here we go.
It's her next move.
All we have to do is
get to the checkmate.
[NINE] That's where we
should find the bomb.
[HAMURA] What? You got
orders from the police?
Yep. They didn't tell me why.
I was just told to make sure
these images got on the screens.
And you're positive
it was the police?
[EMPLOYEE 7A] How did
you guys not know about it?
You should've, unless
you're not really cops.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Target B Lost.
It's like he
knows exactly where
all of the security cameras are,
and he's hidin' in
their blind spots.
[OPERATOR 6A]
That ain't possible, is it?
Get the footage of
Target B to the airport police,
and have them start searching
for him, immediately.
Tell them this is
their top priority.
Yes, ma'am.
The next move is NC3.
Is she saying she's
seen through everything?
Damn it! Why would the police
order him to put up that image?
And what does it even mean?
It's some kinda message.
I'd guess the sender is
whoever set the bomb.
They're communicating with
someone trying to disarm it.
So, who's got the
authority pull this off?
Wait a minute.
You're sayin' cops did this?
Someone on the force
planted the bomb?
Then the riddle from
earlier was just a fake
prepared by the department
for the real Sphinx.
Which means they
must be here too.
Sounds right. But I think
we'll be better off
tracking the movements
of the police.
[TWELVE]
Other than the restrooms,
there are 12 blind
spots on the floor.
[TWELVE] Nice. There's the
welcoming committee.
[OFFICER 7A]
Target B has been located.
Then go pick him up.
[OFFICER 7A]
Roger.
[NINE pants]
Castling.
[phone ringing]
[VOICE 7A]
BD3.
Not a bad move.
[KINOSHITA]
As far as that code goes,
I think it means the
location of a chess piece.
A chess piece?
So whoever's behind this is
having a match with someone?
Damn it! This doesn't
make any sense.
What are they planning? Ideas?
[phone ringing]
How's it goin'?
[NINE]
Perfectly.
Good! Then, I guess
it's time for us
to introduce
Sphinx Number Three?
If you insist.
[phone rings]
[LISA]
Seriously?
[TWELVE]
Yep! What you're lookin' for
is in the locker
next to counter 12.
[LISA]
Okay. Wait a sec, first, um.
[TWELVE]
What, can't do it?
No, I'm fine. I'm totally in.
[TWELVE]
Let's see...
Bingo!
[door slams]
[LISA whimpering]
C'mon. Stop freaking out.
[TWELVE chuckles]
[OKANO] Hey, there's
a police truck here.
That's weird.
Wonder what it's doing.
Come with me!
Yessir!
[FIVE]
N capture, F4.
Impressive, Nine.
But...
A1 equals Q.
And that's checkmate.
[LISA panting]
[LISA yelping, panting]
[GIRL 7B gasps]
[GIRL 7C] Whoa.
[fire alarm ringing]
[FIVE]
What's that?
Smoke detected in the
building at Area 17B.
[FIVE] Tell airport police
to get over there now.
[OPERATOR 6A]
Yes, ma'am.
Bring up camera 15.
Give me a close-up.
Clarence, you there?
[SHIBAZAKI] All right,
let's find that truck.
Good call, but where
do we start looking?
Places where a large
truck wouldn't stand out.
Like right there!
[HAMURA]
Got it!
[NINE panting]
[FIVE]
Get off.
Tch.
[FIVE gasps]
The time!
[NINE]
Don't move.
[FIVE] We haven't seen
each other in so long,
Nine, and this is
how you greet me?
Are you trying to
hurt my feelings?
I can't believe I didn't
notice it sooner.
There you were
in all your glory,
but the whole thing
was just a recording.
You found your opportunity
and switched out
the live feed with recorded
surveillance footage
from five minutes earlier.
Clever trick.
Why are you trying
to get in our way?
[FIVE]
You ask like you don't know.
Surely you realize I'm
here to settle our score.
[NINE]
And the bomb? Gate 1O6.
It's where the
checkmate is. Am I wrong?
[FIVE laughs]
No, you're right.
After changing the
surveillance footage,
Twelve started heading
directly for the bomb.
But what about that
plus one of yours?
They helped camouflage
you both by causing
a commotion with
that little fire?
I can't tell you how
delighted I was to find out
you boys had made a friend,
but, you know what that means.
And oh, how I love
a good weakness.
[NINE gasps]
[LISA gasps]
Shut up and come with me.
[FIVE] I have extended her
a special invitation
to see the bomb in person.
I didn't want her
feeling left out.
[OFFICER 7B grunts]
Don't move!
[OFFICERS shouting]
[OPERATOR 6B] Get him!
[FIVE] No, you do what I say!
But--
I don't remember
asking your opinion
or giving you
permission to shoot.
Can somebody get me
the control room?
[HAMURA]
Those were gunshots. Now what?
[SHIBAZAKI]
What the hell.
Like we don't already
have enough on our plate.
[HAMURA, SHIBAZAKI panting]
[HAMURA]
Shibazaki! What's the hold up?
Nine! I don't think
the bomb is here!
What?
I don't get it.
This was supposed to be
the checkmate spot!
[phone ringing]
I can't get out!
Please, you have to help me!
[LISA] I'm on a plane
and it's moving.
[TWELVE]
What? Why are you on a plane?
[LISA] This guy just
showed up and grabbed me,
and then forced me to get on.
The bomb is in here, too.
Tell me what to do!
[AIRPORT WORKER 7A]
Hey. Wasn't that plane
headed for the hangar?
Jus' stay calm, 'kay?
First of all,
who's piloting that thing?
[LISA]
Um. There's no one in there.
It's moving by itself!
Of course.
[NINE] That's why you
couldn't find the bomb
at the gate we thought.
[TWELVE] Because they
put it on a plane instead.
[NINE] Yeah. Now, that bomb
is on the move,
and I bet it's headed
right this way.
[NINE]
Gate 1O6, where we're standing.
[TWELVE gasps]
Damn it. What is her problem?
She's settling old scores.
[NINE] Okay, it's clearly
being driven remotely.
Which means we should have a
pretty good idea where she is.
[TWELVE]
In the control tower!
Here we are, Nine:
the final stage.
[FIVE]
Can you clear it, though?
What do we do?
The tower is crawling with
armed special assault forces.
We can't get anywhere near it.
We have to create
some kind of commotion.
The general public
needs to be evacuated.
Wait, what're you saying?
You know what'll happen to Lisa.
She's trapped in there
with the bomb!
I know.
[NINE] There is one way,
but it's risky.
[phone ringing]
[NINE]
Detective Shibazaki?
Who's this?
[NINE]
Sphinx Number One.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
What the hell? How do
you have this number?
[NINE]
No time to explain.
The bomb you're looking
for's not one of ours.
I'm sure you already
have an idea
of who'd wanna frame us.
But right now I need your help.
You do?
[NINE] At the moment,
there's a passenger jet
with a bomb on it heading
toward Gate 1O6.
[NINE] I have every reason
to believe it's real.
There's only one way to stop it.
You have to get into
the control room
and take over the
autopilot system.
It has to be you because
the special assault team
is swarming that area.
No way we can get near it.
Seriously. You're asking
for help from the police?
[NINE] The way I see it,
if that bomb goes off,
it becomes a problem
for both of us.
[SHIBAZAKI] So you're saying
we have mutual interests.
Well yeah. Isn't that
kinda your job?
To protect and serve?
Ha. Funny guy.
Not a line I'd expect
to hear from a terrorist.
Five minutes left.
[LISA grunting]
[phone rings]
Lisa, can you hear me?
You were told not to let
anyone through, rookie!
Yeah, but these guys
say they're detectives.
This is an emergency.
Get out of our way!
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM 7A]
We have orders, sir!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hey, we're all cops here!
And we got business
in the control room!
Back off, man!
[HAMURA]
There's no time!
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM 7B]
Get back!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Will you just listen to me!
Ya just have to do
what I told you.
You'll be fine.
Stay calm and breathe.
I know you can do this.
Shibazaki, run!
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM 7A]
We're on the same team!
Hey, wait! Let go!
[LISA grunting]
Lisa!
Oh, thank God. Okay.
Damn it!
[LISA screams]
No!
[LISA screaming]
[SHIBAZAKI panting]
[FIVE gasps]
[SHIBAZAKI] Hold it.
[OPERATOR 7A gasps]
You'll be taking
orders from me, now.
Tch!
I'm stuck.
Outta time! Hurry!
[OPERATOR 7A panting]
You realize you're
just his pet dog.
I can't believe
you're trusting him!
[LISA grunts]
Here!
[LISA screams]
[TWELVE, LISA grunt]
[SHIBAZAKI]
C'mon! You're not done yet.
[FIVE]
I will make you regret this.
[CROWD screaming]
[OPERATOR 7A sobbing]
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[OPERATOR]
It's locked!
[SHIBAZAKI]
No, wait!
[OPERATORS clamoring]
Damn you, Sphinx.
Lisa, you won't get away again.