[FIVE]
Goodnight, Romeo.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
The school! The bomb's
in locker D-12!
[CLARENCE]
I've regained visual!
[FIVE]
No! Stop!
[CLARENCE]
Five, what--?
[NINE] Excuse me.
I'm here to turn myself in.
What?
[NINE]
I'm Sphinx Number One.
[RECEPTIONIST 10A gasps]
[RECEPTIONIST 10A screams]
[OFFICERS gasp]
[OFFICER 10A]
Freeze, buddy!
[OFFICER 10B]
Don't do anything stupid!
[OFFICER 10D]
Hands behind your head!
[OFFICER 10E]
You gotta be kiddin' me.
[SHIMADA] Yes, we're checking
to see if it's really him.
[SUBORDINATE 10A] Captain!
Sphinx just surrendered!
What? Is this a joke?
[CLARENCE] Got it. I'll take
care of it right away, sir.
Yeah. Things are still,
uh, up in the air.
[DETECTIVE 10A]
Sphinx kid's telling us to get
a detective named Shibazaki.
He won't say
anything until we do.
I'm Kurahashi,
First Investigation.
Shibazaki is
currently on leave.
I'll hear what you
have to say instead.
Why did you turn yourself in?
Why would you
commit these crimes?
You can start by
telling me who you are.
[KURAHASHI groans]
I've set a timer on the
nuclear device we stole.
Huh?
If you wanna stop the clock,
I suggest you agree
to my demands.
What demands?
Hm? What's wrong?
Huh? Oh. Nothing.
I went to see Haruka.
[SHIBAZAKI'S WIFE]
Really?
You could've at least
mentioned it first.
I wanted to give
her a few things.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Right. Jeez. She's so grown up.
It's funny how kids
turn into adults
in the blink of an eye, y'know?
Something happen?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hm? No.
Weirdo.
Hey. This guy down
there looks suspicious!
[SHIBAZAKI]
What?
[SHIBAZAKI] You're creepin'
my wife out, man.
Just keeping an eye on you
so I can come with
when you go see Mamiya.
And if anything happens?
Fine. I'm prepared
for the worst.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Then I have an important request
to make of you.
Sure!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Buy me some cigarettes.
[HAMURA]
What?
[SHIBAZAKI]
It's a superstition.
When I feel like I'm about
to hit on something big,
there's a brand I always smoke.
Right.
[INSPECTOR GENERAL]
A press conference?
[FUKUDA] What could
he wanna talk about?
[SHIMADA]
I don't know.
He just said that
it should be at 8 PM,
and requested that we gather
all the different news outlets.
If we don't hold this thing.
I'm afraid this kid will
actually set off an atomic bomb.
So you plan to negotiate
with a terrorist?
[KURAHASHI] I plan to think
of the safety of our citizens.
He said as long as
we give him this,
he'll turn the bomb
over to the police.
We can't trust 'im!
[KURAHASHI]
They have kept their promises
in every crime announcement
they've made so far.
But this is different.
It's the first time they're
making a demand.
[CHIEF CABINET SECRETARY]
And?
If he's lying and the
worst were to happen?
I doubt it will, but,
I'll be accountable.
[FIVE heavy breathing]
[doorbell rings]
[ASSISTANT 10A]
Yes?
[SHIBAZAKI] Detective
Shibazaki, Metropolitan PD.
I'd like to speak
with Shunzo Mamiya.
[ASSISTANT 10A] I'm sorry,
but he's not receiving
any visitors at this time.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Please tell him I'm here
on behalf of the children
that disappeared.
All 26 of them.
[ASSISTANT 10A]
One moment please.
[HAMURA] Yeah, a pack
of Shinsei, please.
Looks like we
don't have 'em.
This is the eighth
place I've tried.
[MAMIYA] You want the truth.
But are you prepared to hear it?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Damn right.
I imagine your resolve
must be strong
if it brought you
here to see me.
Yes, and after 15
long years, at that.
I'm sure you don't
remember me, but,
I have quite the personal
grudge to settle with you, too.
You may leave us.
[CLARENCE]
I don't know the details.
All the locals said
was that the suspect
had turned himself in.
[CLARENCE]
Five!
[CLARENCE] They've never seen
a case like yours before.
Ya need more tests,
so try to take it easy.
He's mine. I won't let
anyone else have him.
[MAMIYA]
You're just a youngster.
So, you probably
can't imagine it,
but Tokyo used to
be a burnt field.
It's been almost 70 years.
70 years since the end
of that damned war.
However, this country
remains a defeated one.
Even now our spirit
is that of a loser,
no shred of dignity left,
and no pride left
to stand up to anyone.
This country must become
truly independent once more.
[SHIBAZAKI] So that's why you
implemented the Athena Plan.
[MAMIYA]
Exactly.
To artificially create
humans whose intelligence
and sensitivity surpass
that of ordinary people.
To raise personnel more
useful than any weapon.
To win, again.
That was the goal.
The plan was
considered a failure.
But if you ask my opinion,
it became a fine foundation
for the country.
A fine foundation?
What are you talking about?
Most of those poor
orphans were killed.
And two who lived
are now terrorists.
[SHIBAZAKI] Sphinx came
back to commit patricide.
Their goal is to kill you all.
So they took the last
thing you expected,
and the last thing you want the
rest of the world to know about.
[CLARENCE] We need to prove
that when this country's
constitutional
interpretation changed,
they started secretly
producing atomic weapons.
It's imperative we
secure the target alive.
That's the only way
to get our evidence.
Please do not forget that.
[MAMIYA] Allow me to ask you,
since you know so much.
Do you plan to bring
this to the authorities?
You realize, no matter what
a single detective shouts,
it'll be no more than a tiny
voice in a storm of noise.
It will be swallowed up.
The voice will never
reach a single soul.
Even if you're right,
I'll continue to
shout the truth.
You won't get away with
this one. None of you will.
[knocking]
[ASSISTANT 10A]
Excuse me, sir.
[MAMIYA] My assistant here
tells me Sphinx has surrendered.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[NEWS ANCHOR 6A]
We have just received word
that someone identifying
himself as "Sphinx"
has turned himself in.
The suspect has demanded
a press conference tonight.
He said in a deposition
that he will explain
everything at 8 PM.
[LISA]
Twelve!
Sphinx surrendered!
Nine turned himself in.
[TWELVE gasps]
[LISA]
I don't get it.
Why would Nine go to the police?
Do you know? What should we do?
I dunno. You wanna
go over there?
Come on, let's ride that!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Kurahashi, please!
Do this for me.
All I need's a quick look!
It's impossible.
Even within the department,
only a select few
have access to the suspect.
Can't you do something?
I know him better
--than anyone else!
--[KURAHASHI] Shibazaki!
I'm taking care of this.
He specified the
conference's location.
Any idea what he
wants to talk about?
[SHIBAZAKI]
You'll likely have interference
from different quarters.
No matter what happens,
do not let anyone else have him.
Yeah.
What's that?
[KURAHASHI] The location
of the press conference.
You "found" that note.
Stumbled across it.
[HAMURA] It's a trap,
no matter how you look at it!
[OKANO] There's always
an ulterior motive
when they turn 'emselves in.
Besides, there are two perps.
Where's the other one?
Yeah, right?
Y'guys think he'll bomb
the press conference
or somethin'?
Hey, you smokin' now?
No, probably not.
I bet our guys
are ready for that.
[HAMURA] Come on, we should
at least mention it, though.
[OKANO] How? We're all
suspended, remember?
We walk in there and tell
them before it's too late!
[HAMURA]
Here, take 'em!
Why the hell didn't
you wait for me?
Because you were
takin' too damn long.
You met with Mamiya,
didn't you?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah.
I'm gonna follow this through
to the end, no matter the cost.
But there's something
I still need to see first.
Their future.
With my own eyes.
[INSPECTOR GENERAL]
I told you. Only the Japanese
police are being allowed
to escort him there.
That's the Sphinx boy's
demand, not mine.
[CLARENCE]
I see.
You comply with the
demands of a terrorist,
and yet refuse the
American government?
Do I understand correctly?
No. That's not what I'm saying.
I certainly hope you
won't disappoint us.
You wouldn't wanna
let my bosses down.
[FIVE]
You're wasting your time.
If you want something,
you should just take it.
[CLARENCE]
Ever since your airport stunt.
we've been on less
than good terms
with the Japanese government.
We can't afford to interv--
[FIVE] What about an attack
from an armed group
of unknown affiliation?
That wouldn't have anything
whatsoever to do with us.
[TWELVE]
Look. Isn't this cute? Here.
[LISA]
Thank you.
Nine's holding a press
conference tonight.
So, what do you think's
gonna happen to him?
Will we ever see him again?
Eh. Doesn't matter.
[LISA gasps]
Really. S'not my concern.
[LISA]
Twelve...
I mean it. I have no
right to face Nine.
I left. Betrayed him.
You're being so stupid!
When I saw you there.
When you came for me.
I was so relieved, and so happy!
I think he'll feel like...
he'll feel that way, too!
[CLERK 10A]
Only press designated
by the police allowed.
I am the police.
Hey! Did you take
my badge? Shibazaki!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Here.
[COMMANDER 10A] ETA is in
15 minutes, at 19:20 hours.
Stay alert.
[FIVE]
Trace all vehicles that've left
the police department
in the past three hours
and make it quick.
[OPERATOR 10A]
All of 'em?
Get to it!
[OPERATOR 10A]
Yes, ma'am.
Go, hit the gas!
Do not let them
stop us! Cut through!
Right!
[DRIVER 10A gasps]
The transport's a decoy!
Okay, remove D-6 and E-7.
Understood, ma'am.
[FIVE]
This one? Clarence.
[KURAHASHI] All right.
We'll attempt to detain it.
Slow down!
Oh just calm your tits.
[NINE]
She's here.
[KURAHASHI, DRIVER 10B scream]
[KURAHASHI]
Shit!
So be it.
[KURAHASHI screams]
[KURAHASHI groans]
[OFFICER 10F, NINE groan]
[FIVE gasps]
[TWELVE yelps]
[NINE grunts]
[TWELVE grunting]
You're relieved of your duties,
Five, effective immediately.
This your idea of a joke?
[CLARENCE] Multiple instances
of insubordination,
not to mention breakin' the law.
Your weakened physical
condition pretty much sealed it.
It's regrettable.
It really is, Five. I'm sorry.
It's me.
The situation's changed.
Have another vehicle
pursue the target.
[gun fires]
[CLARENCE grunts]
Idiot. What are you thinkin'?
You want to be our enemy, now?
[FIVE]
I was very clear.
I'm not going to let
anyone else have Nine.
[NINE panting]
[NINE grunting]
[FIVE] Nine. I always wanted
to beat you, but I never could.
Did you realize this was going
to be my last opportunity?
Here we are.
Time was always going
to catch up with us.
I finally get to
thank you, though.
The only reason I was
able to survive
until this point is
because of you.
Yes. All along, you are what
gave me a reason to live.
[NINE]
Five. I'm sorry.
[FIVE]
I know.
Now's as good a time as any
to part ways, don't you think?
So. Let me help you
live this time, Nine.
[FIVE] Good luck, Nine.
Goodbye. I'm going on ahead.
[NINE]
Five!
[SHIBAZAKI] What the hell?
Why aren't they here?
[phone rings]
[NINE] Good evening.
This is Sphinx Number One.
Because of your interference,
today's press conference
has been cancelled.
Oh god.
Isn't this the press conference?
[WOMAN IN CROWD 10A]
It's cancelled?
[NINE]
This is an automatic broadcast
set to air if the press
conference fell through.
It will be the last message.
That being understood,
all negotiations
are off the table, and the
final bomb is in place.
It is an atomic bomb and will
detonate without fail at 10 PM.
Unfortunately,
no one can stop it now.
So I guess that's it.
People of Japan, sayonara.