[TWELVE humming]
[GUARD 1A]
Hm. It's the police. Hey.
Do you know why they're here?
No clue.
[phone rings]
Guardroom. What do you need?
[WORKER 1A]
All right. That's good.
[TWELVE humming]
[WORKER 1A]
Huh?
[alarm blaring]
[WORKER 1B] What's that about?
[WORKER 1C] Think it's a drill?
[WORKER 1B] I dunno.
[WORKER 1D]
Hey, what's going on?
[WORKER 1E grunts]
[GUARD 1F]
Watch out!
[GUARDS grunting, gasping]
[WORKER 1F grunts]
--I dont' know, sir!
--He's getting away! Gate Three!
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM 1B]
Stop! Hold fire!
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM groaning]
[SPECIAL ASSAULT TEAM grunting]
[TWELVE]
Woo-ho-hoo!
Man, it's stupid hot.
That makes sense.
I mean, it is summer.
[TWELVE]
Come on, Nine.
Don't tell me you're
not dyin' out here.
[NINE] Speaking of don'ts.
Don't do anything to stand out.
Try to act like
a normal student.
[TWELVE]
Look! Kururin!
It's so cute how his bangs
look like ant antennae.
I love that guy.
[NINE] I know. Did you
listen to me at all?
[TWELVE sniffing]
Ooh, I can smell chlorine!
[BULLY GIRL 1A]
Do it already. Jump.
Don't be lame, Lame Lisa.
[WAJIMA]
Yeah! Dive!
[WAKAMOTO]
Fly away, Lisa! Forever!
[GIRLS laughing]
[TWELVE]
Hey ladies, whatcha up to?
[LISA gasps]
[WADA]
What?
[WAJIMA]
Um. Do we know this creeper?
Oh! I get it! This is
what they call "bullying"!
[LISA gasps]
No, it's not. She told us
she wanted to swim.
[WAKAMOTO]
We're basically in a resort.
Might as well take advantage.
[WAKAMOTO] Right?
[GIRLS cackling]
Are you serious?
You're gonna swim
with your clothes on?
Yeah. I guess so.
'Cause I'm really hot.
Cool, me, too!
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE]
Woo-hoo!
[LISA gasps]
[GIRLS shriek]
[TWELVE laughs]
[LISA] That smile...
It reminds me of something.
The sun on a hot summer day.
[LISA]
But those eyes are like ice.
[MALE INSTRUCTOR 1A] This is
our new transfer student,
Arata Kokonoe.
It's nice to meet all of you.
Right. Okay, let's see.
Looks like you can take a
seat by the window over there.
--I call dibs.
--Hooker!
You already have a boyfriend!
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR 1A]
Wow...
This is, um, wow, uh,
Toji Hisami. Yeah.
Jambo!
We-hell!
[WADA giggles]
How sweet. Your boyfriend's
in our class, Lame Lisa!
[MUKASA laughs] And a cat won
the internet, Shibazaki.
That sucker is owning
the moonwalk!
[SHIBAZAKI]
I bet.
[MUKASA]
I'm sure your shogi game's
so much more
interesting, though.
[MUKASA] Huh? What is that?
You have to check this out.
Look!
Tch.
[NINE] A'ight, people!
[TWELVE] Let's do this!
[NINE] What's up?
I'm Sphinx Number One.
[TWELVE]
Mm-hmm!
I'm lucky Spinx Number Two,
and I heart curry!
So here's the thing,
we've got tomorrow's
weather forecast for you all!
[NINE] After three PM, Tokyo
will be enveloped in darkness.
[TWELVE]
Ooh!
Large sparks will fly, scattered
around the Shinjuku area!
[NINE] I'd be careful
out there if I were you.
We wouldn't want anyone to die.
[TWELVE] Well then, folks,
have a nice day!
[MUKASA] Really, this crap
is already showing up?
These kids aren't even out
for summer break, yet.
[MALE CHIEF 1A] Hey!
[SHIBAZAKI grunts]
Try to remember you both
are still on the clock.
Stop screwing around.
[MUKASA]
Oh, sorry, I, uh.
[MALE CHIEF 1A]
Shibazaki.
You're not still acting like
a detective, are you?
Because you're not one.
Yeah, I know. I am well aware.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1A]
Hello? We're talking to you!
[FEMALE STUDENT 1B]
Can you hear us? Hey, Arata!
[FEMALE STUDENT 1C]
Seriously!
[FEMALE STUDENTS]
So, can I have your number?
--Yeah, I want it too!
--Me three!
--Let me send you my--
[NINE] No. I don't have
a cell phone or anything.
[FEMALE STUDENTS] --Huh?
--What?
[pinging]
Idiot.
Oh, hey! How's it goin'?
I've already heard people
talking about you, so guess.
Not what we need right now.
It's not a big deal, people
are talking about you, too.
[NINE]
No, they're not.
[TWELVE]
Yes, they are.
Shiori Nonami and Haruka Asami
had a lot to say about you.
Apparently, they think
you're, like, "so hot."
[NINE] Why are you taking
the time to remember
names of students
from other classes?
It's just not necessary.
[TWELVE]
Yeah, yeah.
Look, it's Lisa.
Poor girl's takin'
her lunch with her.
Bet she eats in the bathroom.
Do not get involved.
I won't.
[phone vibrating]
[LISA]
More texts from Mom.
[LISA gagging]
[LISA panting]
[NINE gasps]
Nine?
Oh. Same nightmare again?
To be honest, I had a
feeling that would happen.
Well because of Lisa.
Her eyes look exactly like those
kids' eyes from the institution.
You know it's true.
All of those
children were weak.
That's why they died.
[NINE] We were weak, too. That's
why we couldn't save them.
And now?
Now, things are different.
We're strong.
Alright.
[WAJIMA] Right?
[WAKAMOTO] I mean, yeah.
[GIRLS giggle]
[camera clicks]
So adorable.
[NINE]
Three more minutes.
26 until the power
generators kick in
and electricity is restored.
[TWELVE]
Roger!
[NINE]
Are we straight on the plan?
Who do you think I am?
[NINE]
It's almost time.
[LISA panting]
[phone chimes]
[phone chiming]
I wish they'd all disappear.
[MALE SALES CLERK 1A]
Plus wi-fi-- Uh?
The lights?
Huh? Is it a blackout?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Hm? Ah, it'll switch
to the backup
generators eventually.
[MUKASA]
Yeah, I guess.
[SHIBAZAKI] "After three PM,
Tokyo will be
enveloped in darkness."
Mukasa can you find that video
from yesterday on your phone?
Huh?
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 1A]
Your attention, please.
You'll need to use the stairs
to exit the building.
[CHILD 1A sobbing]
I'm scared, mommy. I'm scared.
Mommy! Mom!
[NINE panting]
[LISA gasps]
It's you. Hey.
You really shouldn't
be in here, you know.
Eh?
So what -- are you
playing hide and seek?
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE]
You can borrow that.
It sucks hiding all by yourself.
Now you won't get lonely.
Oh, I, uh!
[TWELVE]
Promise me something.
Don't let go of him.
Not until I say it's okay.
[LISA] Hold up. What is this?
Where are you going?
[NINE] After three PM, Tokyo
will be enveloped by darkness.
[TWELVE]
Ooh!
Large sparks will fly, scattered
around the Shinjuku area!
[MUKASA] Nah. This has
to be a coincidence.
[NINE]
Wouldn't want anyone to die.
[TWELVE]
Well then, folks--
[phones ringing]
Did all go according to plan?
Mostly. There's just
one little hitch.
It's Lisa. She saw me inside.
[phone rings]
[LISA panting]
[fire alarm ringing]
[LISA grunts]
[TWELVE]
I left her in there.
If we don't do anything,
she'll most likely get killed,
but I did give her a Kururin.
[TWELVE]
This way,
we can either put her
out of her misery,
or we can go in and save her.
I figured you'd like to have
a choice in how we proceed.
What is this?
Are you trying to make me
relive that moment?
[NINE]
You know she's not one of us.
[TWELVE]
I'm aware. It's just...
I dunno.
I thought maybe this could help
you stop having that dream.
[NINE grunts]
[phone rings]
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE] Hello.
[LISA] Huh?
[TWELVE] Did you keep your
promise and hang onto him?
Give it. Listen up,
you have two options here.
[LISA gasps]
Choice one, you can
die where you stand.
Or choice two: you can
become an accomplice.
[LISA gasps]
Accomplice?
[NINE]
It's up to you. What'll it be?
I, uh, I don't know.
[banging]
I don't...
...wanna die.
[TWELVE]
Alright!
[NINE] From the resonance
I'm getting on my end,
you must be in the
stairwell. What floor?
Uh, the sixteenth?
[NINE]
Got it.
Take the stairs all the way
down to the fourth floor.
[LISA whimpers]
[LISA panting]
[NINE] When you get to Four,
take 15 steps forward.
Then move 23
steps to the right.
Take 12 steps forward.
When you're there...
[LISA sighs]
[NINE] ...leave the
plushie at your feet.
[CROWD screaming]
[alarms blaring]
[phone ringing]
[NINE] Go back the way you came
and hide in the hallway.
Keep to the shadows.
Do it now!
[LISA panting]
[LISA gasps]
[heart beating]
[BULLY GIRL 1A]
Do it already.
[WAKAMOTO]
Fly away, Lisa! Forever!
[NINE]
It's up to you. What'll it be?
[TWELVE]
So, what? Playing hide and seek?
[CROWD screaming]
[NINE] Remember, you chose
this path. Not us.
Do you understand what
you've agreed to?
I--
Lisa, there's no going back.
[LISA gasps]
[LISA] That smile...
It reminds me of something.
The sun on a hot summer day.
But those eyes are like ice.