[MALE SALES CLERK 1A]
Plus wi-fi--
[LISA gasps]
[NINE] Choice one, you can
die where you stand.
Or choice two: you can
become an accomplice.
[LISA gasps]
[LISA panting]
Lisa, there's no going back.
[LISA gasps]
[NEWS ANCHOR 2A] We're here
at the scene of the bombing.
The police have concluded
this was not an accident.
What we experienced
was an act of terror.
In their official statement,
the police promised to
take down these terrorists.
[LISA'S MOTHER]
Lisa!
Do you know how many
times I texted you?
Why would you wanna
make me worry like that?
I'm sorry, Mom.
[LISA'S MOTHER]
No, you're not.
This is all a part of your plan!
Wha--?
[LISA'S MOTHER] Don't lie to me!
Please tell me the truth.
What are you trying to do to me?
[LISA]
Please stop.
Are you planning to run away
just like your father?
You're going to leave me, too.
I won't allow it! Lisa! No!
[LISA grunting]
[LISA'S MOTHER]
Come back here! Lisa!
[LISA panting]
[LISA]
In that moment, I was terrified.
It wasn't my mother, though.
I was afraid of something else.
[NINE]
Lisa, there's no going back.
[LISA]
The words he said,
and how cold they made me feel.
[KURAHASHI] Can those in
the back hear all right?
[MALE INVESTIGATOR 2A]
Yes sir, we can hear.
[MALE INVESTIGATOR 2B]
Sounds fine to me.
[KURAHASHI]
Welcome. I'm Kurahashi.
The First Investigation
Division Chief. To start with,
we'll hear updates from
the different departments.
All right. Director Shimada
will share casualties.
[SHIMADA]
Thank you.
Before the Government
Offices collapse,
the building's fire alarm
was triggered
allowing a full evacuation.
As far as we know,
there were no fatalities.
There were 27 injuries reported,
but they were all
relatively minor.
We got lucky on this one, guys.
Considering the scale
of the damage,
these numbers are extremely low.
[KURAHASHI]
Thank you, and now
to Division Chief Kinoshita
from Cybercrime.
[KINOSHITA]
Thanks.
Regarding the video the
alleged suspects uploaded
on the day the
incident occurred,
there's not much to report yet.
We know they used
anonymity software
called Tor when
accessing the Internet.
So, basically, it's impossible
to determine their IP address.
[HAMURA] Excuse me!
I'm Hamura from First Division.
From watching the video,
it seems like the suspects
are a couple of kids.
Is there any way to find out if
their threat was the real deal?
It's possible. We are
analyzing the video again.
[KURAHASHI] Next up. Okano,
head of Special Investigations.
He'll be reporting on
the surveillance video
from the crime scene.
[OKANO]
Yes, at this point in time,
we have not found anyone
that looks like the suspects.
Thanks to the
large-scale blackout
right before the incident,
the cameras stopped
for a period of time,
and it is believed they
placed the bombs
in the 25 minutes it took
for the backup generators
to kick in.
[HAMURA]
Sorry, but,
are we also looking into the
possibility these suspects
might have been
behind the blackout?
[INVESTIGATORS murmur]
[KURAHASHI]
The Special Investigation team
is following up on that, now.
That's correct.
We're in the process
of interviewing the
construction workers
involved with the crane accident
that caused the outage.
[KURAHASHI] Finally, Section
Chief Hamada from Forensics.
Please give us your professional
opinion about the bomb.
Yes, sir. But, before
that, I'd like to talk about
the structure of
the government office.
The pillars that support
the frame of the building are,
in fact, four times
thicker than usual,
and due to that
particular strength,
they are commonly
referred to as "super pillars."
They were created
with attacks in mind,
so they can't be destroyed
by standard bombs.
To be clear.
You're telling us these were
not run-of-the-mill devices?
Thermite reaction
tells you they weren't.
Um, an on-site
investigation detected
the chemical reaction
was present.
A thermite reaction?
Is that unusual in
your experience, Chief?
[HAMADA]
No, on the contrary,
this reaction's extremely
common. As a matter of fact,
it's an everyday practice
for welding metal.
To put it very simply,
if a mixture of iron oxide
and aluminum powder is ignited,
it produces a large
amount of heat.
[HAMADA]
Up to 3,000 degrees Celsius.
Such a high temperature
is greater than
the melting point of
both iron and concrete,
which means the reaction has
the ability to melt either one.
The ingredients required
to create such a reaction
are also quite a bit easier
to obtain than gunpowder.
Are you're saying
this is what was used
to melt the pillars?
[HAMADA]
It more than likely was, yes.
The purpose of the mixture
was to set off the fire alarms.
Then, once the water from the
sprinklers combined with it,
a phreatic explosion
was created.
At that point, the pillars,
unable to withstand
the weight of the
building, collapsed
along with the structure.
There have not been
many terrorist attacks
that have used this
method in the past.
However, these bombers
didn't just use the reaction,
they planned for the
phreatic explosion as well.
Whoever is behind this assault
is without a doubt
extremely intelligent.
[HAMADA]
That being said,
there's still one thing
I can't figure out.
[SHIMADA]
And that would be?
[HAMADA] Strangely enough,
there was a single
TNT bomb used in the attack.
In no way could that have
been necessary to cause
the collapse of the building,
so I decided to reconstruct
the TNT bomb myself
to see if I could find out
why it was there.
What?
I didn't know you could
reconstruct a bomb.
Oh, it's not all that difficult
when TNT is being used.
Anyway, on the TNT, I found
letters that looked like
they had been written
by the bombers.
And?
[HAMADA]
This is what I discovered.
You can see them very clearly.
Three letters. V-O-N.
[KURAHASHI] Can you believe
Public Safety is letting
First Division lead a
terrorist investigation?
[SHIMADA]
Of course.
If this thing turns into
a worst-case scenario,
both the media and
the police department
want to be certain they
can still cover it up.
V-O-N.
[SHIMADA]
Yeah.
Guess we know it's connected
to that recent theft.
[SHIMADA] If the public
finds out, they'll panic.
[KURAHASHI]
Indeed, they will.
We need to consider the
likelihood that these attackers
are not with an
existing terrorist cell.
[SHIMADA]
I agree.
But the Public
Safety Bureau does not,
and we're supposed to be
cooperating with them--
indirectly, of course.
No surprise there.
If things don't go well, they
want the freedom to blame us.
Huh?
[TWELVE] Hey Nine, did you
catch that news report?
[NINE] Assume you mean
the one comparing us
to the Unabomber.
[TWELVE]
That's the one!
I was hoping to remind them
of Kenji Sawada, though.
[NINE]
Hear from that girl?
[TWELVE]
Lisa Mishima?
[NINE]
Yeah.
[TWELVE]
You worried?
Nah. I can't imagine she
has the guts to report us.
[TWELVE] Let me ask you
something. Why "accomplice"?
Why use that word when you
were talking to her?
Just trying to scare her.
That's all, huh?
[NINE]
Whose turn?
[TWELVE]
Hmm. One, two,
[NINE, TWELVE]
Three!
[NINE] Hello. Delivery
from Choujyuan Noodles.
Oh. Yeah, just bring it on in.
[NINE]
Cool. Thank you.
Yeah, tried that new
ramen place last night.
You gotta go.
[MUKASA]
I don't get you, man.
How can you work
on a crossword puzzle?
First Division looks like
they're in serious
trouble, you know.
But I guess that doesn't affect
us down here in archives.
[SHIBAZAKI] Which is why you're
just screwing around online.
Hey, help me out.
Do you know what the
"instant pork ramen from 1987
that was recently reissued" is?
Oh, come on!
Maybe you could help
me out and not assume
all fat people are
experts on carbs, yeah?
Oh. Try Toppa Chikara
Kusa Yantsuki.
Ah. T.O.P.
[MUKASA] And I'm not screwing
around, by the way.
I'm secretly and covertly
trying to figure out
what Sphinx's next
move could be.
[MUKASA gasps] Too late!
They released a new video!
[NINE]
I'm Sphinx Number One.
[TWELVE] I'm Sphinx Two,
and I heart explosions!
Did you enjoy the fireworks at
the Tokyo Government Office?
All that excitement came from
our very own handmade bombs.
He worked pretty
hard on it, too!
[NINE] This is only the
beginning of the party, though!
In the very near future, we'll
be setting off a second bomb!
[NINE]
We have a riddle for everyone.
Specifically those of you
from law enforcement.
What?
[TWELVE hums]
[NINE] What first walks on
two legs, then on four legs,
and finally on three legs?
[TWELVE]
If you solve the riddle,
then the next bomb
can be yours!
[NINE, TWELVE]
Good luck!
Aw, poor First Division.
Those guys sure as hell won't
be goin' home for a while.
[HAMURA] The hell's
the point of a riddle?
Damn snots need
to learn some respect!
How dare they?
They could just be mouthpieces
for the real guys.
In the long run though,
I guess it doesn't matter.
[door opens]
The last thing
we need right now
is children using bombs as toys.
[HAMURA]
Director Kurahashi.
[KURAHASHI]
The suspects refer to themselves
as "Sphinx," pronouncing it with
a "P" instead of the usual "F".
This isn't from the Egyptian.
It's actually a
Greek pronunciation.
[KURAHASHI]
Sphinx.
Commonly known as one
of the many creatures
from Greek mythology.
It appears in Oedipus Rex.
Laius, Oedipus's father,
after being told by an Oracle
that his son would kill him,
abandoned Oedipus
in the forest when he
was still just a child.
However, Oedipus survived
and grew into an adult.
The Oracle was right,
and one day,
Oedipus did end up
killing Laius.
Of course, at the time, he did
not know Laius was his father.
[LISA] Afterwards, Oedipus
married the king's wife.
But Queen Jocasta
was his mother.
[LISA] When Oedipus
discovered the truth,
that he had murdered
his own father,
that he had married
his own mother.
He could not bear the guilt,
and in order to punish himself,
he gouged out his eyes,
making himself blind.
[TWELVE]
Whatcha readin'?
[LISA gasps]
Oh, I-- n-nothing.
Hm.
[LISA] Um, if you don't mind
me asking, why are you here?
I understand if
you're keeping tabs.
It makes perfect sense.
--You wanna learn a fun trick?
--[LISA] Huh?
I'll just take that as a yes.
[TWELVE] First, make a blend of
half cola and half green tea.
Here you go. Then,
put this in and laugh.
[LISA yelping]
[TWELVE laughing]
[TWELVE]
It's the fresh maker cola!
[LISA]
Hey! Hold on a sec!
[LISA panting]
[KURAHASHI] Oedipus went to
visit the country of his father,
whom he had killed.
He was confronted there.
A monster appeared
and blocked his way.
[KURAHASHI]
The Sphinx asked riddles
of the people it encountered.
If they didn't give the correct
answer, they would be devoured.
Sounds fun. What kind of
riddles are we talkin'?
"What walks on four
legs in the morning,
on two legs in the afternoon,
and on three legs
in the evening?"
[OKANO, KINOSHITA gasp]
[KURAHASHI] That's right.
[KURAHASHI] It's very similar
to the riddle in the video.
We need to take
these guys seriously.
Okay, if that's the question,
what's the answer?
[KURAHASHI]
The answer is "man."
How come?
I get it.
As an infant, man is forced
to crawl on four legs.
Then as adults, we walk on two.
Elderly people use canes,
which makes three.
Correct. And the times of day?
[KURAHASHI] They represent
the different stages
in a man's life.
[HAMURA]
So how does that relate
to the next bomb
they've set "Man?"
Yeah, or people?
[OKANO] So, a busy shopping area
with a lot of foot traffic?
What if those numbers
match up to an address?
Like Fourth Street, Building
Two-Three or something?
Checking on corresponding
addresses, now.
[KINOSHITA gasps] There's a DNA
research facility in Minato!
[HAMURA] DNA, riddle of man.
That has to be it!
Good enough for me,
let's get a search warrant.
I'm coming, too.
[police sirens blaring]
[OFFICERS] --Come on!
--Let's go!
[CAPTAIN 2A] Move now, people!
[OFFICERS] Yes, sir!
[NEWS ANCHOR 2B]
As of right now.
Police on the scene,
are not giving us
an awful lot of information.
So, we're left to wonder
if the next bomb
is at this DNA
research facility.
It doesn't seem they're any
closer in finding out who--
[phone rings]
Ah, Shibazaki.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Oh good.
You haven't changed
your number on me, yet.
[KURAHASHI]
Not yet.
I've been thinkin'
about that riddle
those self-proclaimed
bombers left you.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Care to hear my thoughts?
Of course I do. N'you haven't
changed a bit, my friend.
Nope. They're referring to
the mythology of Oedipus.
[KURAHASHI]
Yeah. The answer is "man".
Wrong.
Although "Man" was the
answer to other riddle
the Sphinx was known to ask.
You mean it asked
more than one?
[SHIBAZAKI] Yeah, there's
another lesser-known version
of the story. Two legs in the
morning, four in the afternoon,
and three legs in the evening.
In other words, a
two-four-three progression.
Two-four...?
Meaning the answer
can't be "man" anymore.
[KURAHASHI] So do you
know what the answer is?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yes, it's Oedipus himself.
Gonna have to
explain that one.
[SHIBAZAKI] He started off
as a man with two legs,
however, after killing his
father and having intercourse
with his mother, he fell to the
level of a beast, so to speak.
That makes four.
In the end, he gouged
out his own eyes,
blinding himself.
He needed a cane to walk.
So, three legs.
[LISA panting]
[YOUNG MAN 2A]
Ah! Watch it!
[LISA]
I'm sorry!
[LISA panting]
It's true you may
be an accomplice.
[TWELVE]
You're not one of us, though.
[SHIBAZAKI]
So, we know it's Oedipus.
And what did they say?
"The riddle was for
everyone, but specifically
for the police?"
[SHIBAZAKI] In my opinion,
they're insinuating the bomb
has been planted
somewhere the police are.
The police?
[SHIBAZAKI] If that number
sequence is an address.
It corresponds with a
local police station.
Roppongi Station!
[phone ringing]
[TWELVE]
Nothing personal.
But one false move,
and I'll have to kill ya.
[LISA gasps]
[phone rings]
[CROWD screaming]
[DETECTIVE 2A] There's been
an explosion in Roppongi?
[OFFICERS clamoring]
Shibazaki! Roppongi's been hit!
Damn it. I was too late.
Huh?
[HAMURA]
Director!
There was an explosion
at Roppongi Station!
We should take this as a direct
challenge to the police force!
[OKANO]
Hamura!
Head to Roppongi immediately!
[HAMURA]
Yes, sir!
Shibazaki, understand
what I am about
to tell you is
highly confidential.
[KURAHASHI]
Six months ago, a nuclear fuel
reprocessing facility in
Aomori was broken into.
The two criminals
stole plutonium.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[KURAHASHI]
They vanished immediately,
and we have no leads.
However, they did leave
something at the
scene of the crime.
A message. The same
three letters
left on the TNT at
the government office.
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
Don't tell me.
[KURAHASHI]
That's right.
I think these guys
have every intention
of picking a fight with
this entire country.
We need you back. I'm sorry.
[SHIBAZAKI grunts]
Come on out.
I'm waiting for you.