[TWELVE] It's true you
may be an accomplice.
You're not one of us, though.
Nothing personal.
But one false move,
and I'll have to kill ya.
[LISA gasps]
[KURAHASHI] I think these
guys have every intention
of picking a fight with
this entire country.
We need you back. I'm sorry.
Come on out.
I'm waiting for you.
[HAMURA]
I can't believe this!
No! Some random, crusty
old dude from Archives
comin' up to be my boss?
It's a joke.
What. You haven't
heard of him before?
He's not random.
Shibazaki used to be
one of our best guys.
Huh?
[KINOSHITA] It's the truth.
He was incredible.
Everyone called him
"Razor Shibazaki".
Wish I had a nickname like that.
Wish I had a nickname, period.
An' how long's it been
since he was a detective?
This guy was basically
sent down to Archives
to rot until retirement.
And now he--
Morning.
[OKANO]
Hey, welcome back.
[MUKASA]
Come on, Shibazaki.
You realize I'm not helping you
move all this crap for free.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Anyone know where my desk is?
[OKANO] Yeah, it's right
over here. Scram.
Man, you should treat me to
lunch or something for this.
[SHIBAZAKI]
You like ramen, right?
Stop doing that!
[MUKASA] I mean, yeah, I do,
but quit assuming all fat people
worship at the carb altar!
[OKANO]
Hey, Hamura!
[TWELVE]
It's tough. I don't know, Nine.
What if the riddle
is too hard for them?
It's fine, Don't worry.
[TWELVE]
Yeah, so you say.
I'm just not sure
what we're gonna do
if no one can solve it again.
The other day, when they
were investigating
the Roppongi bomb.
[NINE] I saw vans from
the Nuclear, Biological,
and Chemical Terrorism
Special Forces.
Makes me think.
It's possible they've got
someone who's figured out
what we're up to.
[NINE] This ought to
help us know for sure.
[OKANO]
As you can see,
the culprit entered the
police station like this.
[OKANO]
Ignoring surveillance cameras,
he calmly planted a delivery box
containing the plastic bomb,
turned around, and
left. In my opinion,
we should consider this
act our confirmation.
They are directly challenging
the police force.
[SHIMADA]
Understanding this threat,
we have no choice but
to assume they're likely
working on their next
bomb as we speak.
[KURAHASHI] So, I've got more
on the stolen plutonium--
from the nuclear
facility in Aomori?
One of the fugitives
was an employee.
But he had only been working
there for a few months.
In the files he's
Yuzu Miyajima.
Apparently, though, that
person has never existed.
How's that happen?
Best guess?
He used the Basic Residents'
Registration Network
to get hired on. He infiltrated
the government office
and fabricated a new identity.
An identity with local ties,
since the facility
tends to hire from within their
community whenever possible.
[SHIBAZAKI]
And?
Look at his face. There's a
sketch of him in that file.
They didn't bother
takin' a photo?
No, they did. but it was
mysteriously deleted somehow.
At the time, we sent out
an emergency deployment.
But Miyajima and his accomplice
have seemingly vanished.
No trail, no trace, no
evidence they even existed.
Looks like he's only a kid.
[KURAHASHI]
Yeah.
I've told you about
what it was like
where I grew up, haven't I?
About being surrounded
by old people.
Oh yeah. You're from Hiroshima.
[SHIBAZAKI]
I'll never forget those summers.
Man, I hated them.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Once it started to get warm,
the city became a ghost town.
The elderly stayed in, almost
never leaving their houses.
They'd say they didn't feel
well because of the heat.
I spent a lot of time
with my grandmother.
I always felt
as though the summer
would steal her from me.
She'd turn into someone else.
Yeah. I hated summer.
I resented it.
That's why you took this case.
Second-generation
victim of The Bomb?
[KURAHASHI] Must be hard
to watch a couple of kids
playing around
with nuclear weapons.
Yeah. They bother me.
Somethin' about this, though.
I dunno. Just doesn't add up.
[HAMURA]
Mister Kawai.
You've been doing
this a while, right?
How could you make
such a simple mistake
while working the crane?
I told you. I was tired
from tons of overtime, okay?
I've said it for years, man.
That company's a sweatshop.
So uh, why don't you
investigate that?
You listen!
[door clicks]
[OKANO]
Shibazaki.
S'cuse me. Mind if I have
a chair? I have a bad back.
[OKANO]
Oh, sure.
So, Mister Kawai.
You're a big fan of gambling.
[KAWAI]
Yeah? What's your point?
[SHIBAZAKI] Horses or fights?
I'm guessing fights.
[KAWAI]
Huh?
What kinda bet did
you lose, guy?
I hear someone's hired gun's
been payin' you visits.
No, uh, not recently.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Why's that?
Why would a man whose job
is to get money from you
stop showing up?
Uh...
[banging]
What's this?
Maybe it's the debt collector in
question comin' to answer that.
[KAWAI gasps]
[door creaks]
[KINOSHITA]
I got something, Shibazaki.
[SHIBAZAKI] All the proof we
needed was just sittin' there
on your computer.
Surprising, since you handed
it over to us voluntarily.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Kawai confessed to everything.
He got an email saying
if he cut the power line
and made it look
like an accident,
he'd receive two million
yen for the effort.
And the money?
Did they ever actually
deliver any of it to him?
Yes.
Apparently, Kawai replied
saying he could do it.
And even though he never told
anyone his account number,
he had one million
transferred to him.
Have we looked into the sending
account and time of transfer?
Nothing there, either.
The transfer came from
a dummy account.
There's a bigger issue, though.
These guys knew
what would happen
if that power line was cut.
They planned this "accident" so
there'd be a citywide blackout,
cutting off power to the
government building.
[SHIBAZAKI]
But we're talking about
well-prepared criminals here.
Why would they choose
to leave behind an email
that could be traced?
Not to mention the footage
from Roppongi Station.
It's as if they're intentionally
leaving behind evidence
for us to find.
[KATO] Uh.
[OKANO] What's the problem?
[KATO]
We got another one! It's Sphinx!
[NINE]
Sorry to keep you waiting, fans!
It's time for "Can you
solve Sphinx's riddle?"
I'm Sphinx Number One.
[TWELVE]
And I'm Sphinx Two.
[NINE]
Now, for today's riddle.
What is the building next
to the house of the god
who solved the riddle?
[TWELVE] Remember,
there will be another "boom"
if you don't solve it in time!
[NINE]
You have until 10 AM tomorrow.
[TWELVE]
Good luck, everyone!
Keep walkin' until you have
to drag your foot behind you
like a good,
old-fashioned cripple!
[SHIMADA]
Right.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Can you replay the video?
[KINOSHITA]
Sure.
[SHIBAZAKI]
That's good.
[NINE] ...10 AM tomorrow.
[TWELVE] Good luck--
Sphinx Two is clapping his
hands like he's praying.
I'd say "house of the god" has
to refer to a shrine somewhere.
Okay, then what god
are they talking about?
Which one solved the
Sphinx's riddle correctly?
That was Oedipus!
Oedipus is from Greek myth.
You think maybe he's got
some kind of analog
in Japanese tradition?
[SHIBAZAKI] Yeah. I like
how you're thinkin'.
What do you think that
"drag your foot behind you"
comment was about?
Best guess, it has to do
with the name Oedipus.
It means "swollen foot".
[HAMURA]
Why name him that?
Because after abandoning
Oedipus in the forest,
Laius didn't want
him to run away,
so dear ol' dad put a nail
through his son's heel.
Well, that's brutal.
[SHIBAZAKI] He wound up
being saved by a shepherd
and then adopted by
the king of Corinth.
When the king saw
the child's injured leg,
he named him "swollen foot",
or Oedipus.
[HAMURA]
How literal.
According to one theory.
Oedipus remained disabled
to some extent his whole life.
"Crippled".
[KINOSHITA]
We need to move fast.
They gave us an
exact time of day,
which they haven't done before.
Check out all the
shrines in the city
'til we get somewhere with this.
Yes, sir!
[LISA'S MOTHER] Lisa, please!
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
[LISA sighs]
[game beeping]
[MUKASA grunting]
[MUKASA groans]
Shibazaki. I wanted to lie down
there and play. Will you move?
No dice. I need it more. I do my
best thinking on this couch.
[MUKASA]
Come on!
[SHIBAZAKI] You just wanna
play a video game.
Why don't you go home for that?
[MUKASA] Because I'm
keeping you company, bro.
I don't want you
to get lonely here.
You're welcome, by the way.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Yeah, thanks a bunch.
Hey. That's prob'ly
Sphinx's problem, you know?
They're just lonely and
want some attention.
Couple of brats.
Blowing things up 'cause
they're desperate for attention?
I can't accept that.
[MUKASA]
No! Aw, man.
Is that an online game?
[MUKASA] Yeah, you work
with other players
to defeat monsters.
It's pretty addictive.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Really?
I usually assume kids these
days play this stuff to avoid
dealing with people, but it
looks like making connections
might still be a thing.
That's not good. You just made
a "kids these days" comment.
Proof you're officially old.
I did it! Look! I finally
beat the green dragon!
I swear, I've been stuck
on this jerk for days!
[SHIBAZAKI]
A dragon.
That's right. He was an
ancestor of Oedipus's mother.
[SHIBAZAKI] Of course!
Mukasa, you're a genius!
[MUKASA]
Huh?
[phone ringing]
[door creaks]
[LISA gasps]
[LISA'S MOTHER]
Who's there?
[LISA gasps]
[LISA'S MOTHER]
Lisa? Lisa, is that you?
Yeah, I dunno.
You think that'll work?
Yes.
I don't understand. Are you
trying to provoke them?
Not at all, but I'll
take the heat if I do.
If that's what you want.
What are you talking about?
You won't take the heat!
If something goes wrong,
the Director's up
the creek, not you!
Well, in that case, I apologize
ahead of time if that happens.
Huh?
[OKANO grumbles]
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 3A]
A name is a gift of love.
But you have been abandoned.
Love does not
exist in your world.
Your old names are
signs of pretense;
which is unacceptable.
Pretense must be eliminated.
Therefore, you will be given
new, practical designations.
[NINE groans]
You okay? Are your
ears ringing again?
No. My ears are fine.
We swore not to lie.
Don't forget.
[NINE] I won't. But you're not
supposed to lie, either.
You met up with Lisa.
[TWELVE laughs]
That obvious?
Don't worry, I won't
get too involved.
Because, I know if I do,
it'll be much
more painful later.
[KINOSHITA]
Okay, any time.
[SHIBAZAKI] Hello. This is
for Sphinx One and Two.
I'm Detective Shibazaki.
[TWELVE gasps]
Nice!
You'll be happy to know I have
an answer for your riddle.
[SHIBAZAKI] You asked us
"What's the building
next to the house of the god
who solved the riddle?"
We know the one who solved the
Sphinx's riddle was Oedipus.
He wasn't the child of
a god, but the ancestor
of his mother and wife was
a dragon in human form.
One theory states that
Oedipus was crippled,
as you so eloquently put it,
for his entire life.
A dragon who drags
his feet? Arahabaki.
Oh, ho!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Arahabaki is a mysterious god
found in the Kanto
and Tohoku regions.
The god of fighting
and iron-making.
He's also known as
"god of feet".
At one point, he had to
wander different areas
after losing his home.
He became so exhausted
that he dragged his feet.
Please, excuse me.
We have breaking news.
We're being told the
Metropolitan Police Department
is using the internet to
answer the bombers' riddle.
[SHIBAZAKI] Also. The "habaki"
part of "Arahabaki?"
It's derived from "dragon tree".
Connecting it to
the dragon god.
The most famous Arahabaki
shrine is in Miyaki Prefecture.
However, he's still worshipped
within Tokyo proper, as well.
Right here.
[SHIBAZAKI]
Shirahige Shrine in Katsushika.
[NINE gasps]
[SHIBAZAKI]
This is the building next to it.
[KATO] We've just finished
disarming the bomb, sir.
Thanks. Good work.
There you have it.
The answer to your riddle.
Not bad.
Yes, that's right.
We've just been told
the bomb has been disarmed.
[TWELVE yawns]
[SHIBAZAKI] Well that's what
you wanted to hear, right?
How's it make you feel?
I'm betting it doesn't make
you feel anything at all.
I don't know if this is
a game to you or what.
But don't get carried away.
I hope you boys
realize the joker
you're wavin' around
is not a toy.
--And if you play that card.
--Cut the feed.
Right.
I will take you both out myself!
[NINE chuckles]
Shibazaki! What the
hell was that?
Were you just antagonizing
them on purpose?
Don't worry. I've asked
Director Kurahashi
to follow-up if
necessary, right?
Oh yeah, right.
Did you notice?
Yes, I did.
[NINE] Hazmat suits mixed
in with their bomb suits
and other gear.
[TWELVE]
Can only mean one thing.
[NINE] Yeah. The cops
have connected it.
They definitely know we were the
ones who stole the plutonium.
[FEMALE NEWS ANCHOR 3B]
A bomb was removed
from the building next to
Shirahige Shrine in Katsushika.
The Metropolitan Police
Department solved
the bombers' riddle from
a video streaming site,
and the bomb was
found succes--
[HAMURA] Um, excuse me,
Director Kurahashi?
Hm? What is it?
It's about Shibazaki.
What is his deal? I heard
he used to be an ace.
But then what? I'm just
curious what happened.
[KURAHASHI sighs] It goes back
15 years, when a Diet secretary
from the ruling party fell to
his death from a hotel room.
Okay?
[KURAHASHI] It was initially
ruled to be an accident
or a suicide, but Shibazaki
refused to accept that.
He insisted on the possibility
that the dead man
had been involved
in some kind of conspiracy,
and even went so far
as to investigate the leader of
the victim's political faction.
[KINOSHITA]
That couldn't have ended well.
The faction leader?
Originally from the
Police Department.
[HAMURA, KINOSHITA gasp]
[HAMURA] Totally get why he
was demoted to archives, now.
[KURAHASHI]
Shibazaki had a family.
He had his life.
The only thing he could do
at that point was
accept the transfer.
However, he has never forgotten.
And he hasn't given up.
That was a long summer.
[SHIBAZAKI
'Nother hot one again today.