[door creaks]
[LISA'S MOTHER] Who's there?
[LISA gasps]
[LISA'S MOTHER]
Lisa?
Lisa, is that you?
There you have it.
The answer to your riddle.
Oh, ho!
I hope you boys
realize the joker
you're wavin' around
is not a toy.
[NINE]
The cops have connected it.
They definitely know
we were the ones
who stole the plutonium.
I will take you both out myself!
[GIRL 4A]
Hey. I got stuck in Shibuya.
It totally started
raining cats and dogs.
Yeah, like out of nowhere.
And of course,
I just got my hair done.
Uh-oh. The cops just
stopped two guys.
They look like high schoolers.
[LISA gasps]
[GIRL 4A] That sucks.
They're both kinda cute.
[GIRL 4A] What can I say?
I like bad boys.
[HAMADA] The expert analysis
of the bomb we recovered
from the building next to the
Shirahige Shrine in Katsushika
has produced some
interesting results.
This device was an
"ammonium nitrate
fuel oil type" commonly used
as an industrial explosive.
From the model number left
on the electric detonator.
We've been able to
trace its purchase back
to a demolitions manufacturer
called Showa Gunpowder.
[FUKUDA] Wait a minute.
[HAMADA] Therefore--
These parts commonly used
by terrorists to make
bombs are just available
to the public?
As long as their application
form has been approved,
yes, someone could gain
access to these items.
[INVESTIGATORS murmuring]
[KURAHASHI]
Please continue.
Yes sir.
[OKANO] The suspect posed as
an employee of Hanabayashi,
a building contractor.
They forged the application
and illegally obtained
someone else's credit card info
to purchase the gunpowder.
How were they able to
use some else's credit card?
Probably through an illegal
website from Russia or China.
A clean card's info can be
bought for next to nothing.
[INVESTIGATORS murmuring]
[KINOSHITA] Because they used
a form of virtual currency
to buy the card, the transaction
is impossible to trace.
[HAMURA grunts]
[OKANO] My subordinates
are currently combing
through surveillance footage
from Showa Gunpowder.
We hope to find an image of the
suspect picking up his order.
In addition, we have
the relevant usage history
of the credit card.
They bought electrical tape
and a delivery box. As well as
a soba shop worker's outfit
all on the same day.
[KURAHASHI]
Where were they purchased?
[SHIMADA]
Entirely online, from Amazon.
Each time, the packages were
picked up at the supermarket,
but any surveillance footage
has been deleted.
So you're telling me we
don't have a single clue
that'd lead us to the culprits?
Is that the long
and short of it?
Get back to me when
you know something.
[LISA grunting]
It sorta feels like we're
just treadin' water here.
The more we chase,
the more they leave us behind.
[OKANO] Yeah. Wonder if
these leads could've been
planted as disinformation.
[HAMURA]
Like counter-intelligence?
You really think a couple
kids could pull off
such a complicated stunt?
Shibazaki seems to
believe these two
are capable of a lot.
Yeah. Speaking of Shibazaki.
Where did he go?
[OKANO] He said something
about heading to Aomori.
[SHIBAZAKI] Excuse me.
You're Yoshiharu Ebisuno.
Is that right?
[EBISUNO]
Yeah?
[SHIBAZAKI] I'm Detective
Shibazaki, Metro P.D.
[EBISUNO] So what.
This fella do somethin'?
Nah he's just a witness
for a minor incident.
I've been asking around all day.
But no one seems to remember
anything about the guy.
Well, he weren't
one to fraternize
with his coworkers much.
[EBISUNO] Even durin' lunch,
he'd always have
them earphones in his head.
So I said "you always
got them earphones in.
What're ya listenin' to?" Then,
he just looked at me and says
"Music from a cold land."
"A cold land?"
Anything else stand out
in your memory as odd?
Even the most trivial detail?
Uh-huh.
I asked him what his old man
did for a livin' once.
The kid just
clammed up real fast.
It seemed like maybe
I'd hit a nerve
or somethin' like that.
[SHIBAZAKI] Father.
Oedipus killed his father.
Riddles.
Bombings.
Missing plutonium.
They're all
interconnected. But how?
[TWELVE] What were you
expecting? A welcome mat?
[NINE] No. But this is
a Dual EC encryption.
There has to be a backdoor.
Hm. That one looked weird.
Hello!
It was a web shell.
Jackpot!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 4A]
So, like, I messaged him back,
and it said he read it.
But then, like,
that was it, no response.
I mean. What's with that?
Boys are so weird, right?
[KURAHASHI]
How was Aomori?
It's cooler up there, isn't it?
[SHIBAZAKI] It was
pretty much the same as here.
Can I bum one of those?
What? I thought
you quit smoking.
[SHIBAZAKI sighs]
One. Just having one.
[KURAHASHI] So you learn
anything about our culprit?
[SHIBAZAKI]
He wasn't much of a social type.
Very few of his fellow employees
even remembered him
working there, much less
anything noteworthy.
It's almost as if this guy never
existed in the first place.
Then this kid is
practically a ghost?
They've been careful to cover
their tracks up to this point.
[SHIBAZAKI] They sure didn't
leave any clues in Aomori.
Yeah? Then why'd you bother
to go all the way up there?
No matter how cleverly you erase
records and cover tracks,
you can't erase a
person's memory. Besides...
What's that?
I needed to be there in person.
To see the view they saw.
To hear the same sounds.
To breathe the same air.
To feel the same things.
[TWELVE] Hey. I'm headin'
out to run a few errands.
[NINE] Sounds good.
I'll finish up the next present.
[TWELVE]
A summer gift, eh?
Just in time for
the Obon Festival.
[TWELVE] This year, we have
a reason to celebrate.
[MUKASA]
Look, Shibazaki,
I hate to say this since
you're paying and all,
but I wouldn't mind
something other than ramen
once in a while.
Hey. The phrase
"music from a cold land".
What does that
make you think of?
"A cold land"? Hm.
Every single Christmas song?
Or maybe like the
Russian anthem?
Huh.
[chiming]
We interrupt this program
to bring you this breaking news.
[MALE NEW ANCHOR 4A]
We have just received updated
information regarding the recent
spate of terrorist bombings.
A new video has now
been made public
on a media sharing website
announcing the next attack.
Yeah. I'm watching it now.
[NINE] Good evening.
This is Sphinx Number One.
[TWELVE]
Ladies, I like moonlit strolls,
romantic dinners and explosives!
I'm Sphinx Number Two.
When exactly was
the video posted?
[NINE] ...are you ready
to play Time Shock Bomb?
[TWELVE sings]
[NINE] At the place where
the king who solved the riddle
received a frightening prophecy,
whose appellation
would you carve on its entrance?
[TWELVE] Solve the riddle
to stop our biggest bomb yet.
Buzzers ready?
It's time to play!
[NINE] And I sincerely hope
you'll play with boys like us
without resorting to cheating.
[TWELVE] Until then, we'll be
wishing you good luck
at the king's final destination!
Oh! And when you come,
make sure to use letters,
not bronze, okay?
[GIRL ON TRAIN 4A gasps]
Crazy, right?
[MALE NEWS ANCHOR 4A]
The footage you just saw
was made public
mere moments ago.
[MUKASA] Wait! Shibazaki!
You didn't pay!
[SHIBAZAKI] The king who
solved the riddle.
Oedipus' final destination
was the underworld.
After gouging out his own eyes,
his two daughters acted as
his guides leading him down
the great bronze stairway to the
very gates of the underworld.
Bronze stairs. But in
the video they said
to use letters instead.
A letter staircase?
[SHIBAZAKI] Right. Let the
letters lead you down
to the gateway?
[SHIBAZAKI]
That's it.
C'mon.
[HAMURA]
That's not good.
So the Internet
is the underworld?
[KATO]
Delphi?
The Oracle of Delphi
gave him the prophecy.
There are three maxims inscribed
on the entrance to the temple.
[KATO] "Know thyself."
"Nothing in excess."
And, "Make a pledge
and mischief is nigh."
It was in a shrine last time.
Could be in a temple?
[SHIBAZAKI]
Forget it.
If we enter the name of
the person the maxims
are referring to
as the password,
the bomb will
probably deactivate.
[KATO]
Can't be that easy.
I bet it's just something they
put in to make us waste time.
He's right! This could
just be a decoy.
No.
[KATO] That's the police
station they attacked
over in Roppongi!
[HAMURA, KATO grunt]
[KINOSHITA growls]
[OKANO]
So we have until midnight?
Well, I'm not gonna
sit around on my thumbs!
We need to coordinate a search
of all temples and shrines!
We're on it, sir.
Hey wait. What're you up to?
[VOICE 4A laughing]
[HAMURA growls]
Would you quit messin' with it?
[SHIBAZAKI] This is the first
time those two have made
any kind of request.
It could be their version
of a response to what I said
the other day on the news.
They want us to play.
[CREEPER MAN 4A]
Hey baby. Whatcha doin'?
[CREEPER MAN 4B] You alone?
Maybe you want a little company?
I know a real nice place.
[LISA]
No!
[TWELVE]
Hm.
[MALE ANALYST 4A yawns]
[NINE] "I won't get too
involved." That's what you said.
[TWELVE]
Yes, I know.
And I won't get
too involved. But uh...
But what?
Well, she's...
It looks like she ran away.
If she gets taken into custody.
She may end up saying
something about us.
That would be bad.
[NINE]
Your point?
[TWELVE]
I'm just saying.
I think it'd be better if we
kept a close eye on her.
Trapped your Queen.
You should have sacrificed her.
Here, guys. Take a look.
[MALE ANALYST 4B]
This is footage of the suspect
picking up their order
from Showa Gunpowder.
A few minutes later,
he shows up again.
This is surveillance footage
from a nearby
apartment building.
Last stop.
He gets off on the sixth floor.
Nice work, son.
We'd better move.
There isn't much time.
Full emergency deployment.
[HAMURA, OKANO]
Yes, sir!
[VOICE 4A laughing]
Hey! We got a lead on
where they're hiding out!
Huh?
[HAMURA] Little twerps have
finally screwed up!
C'mon, let's roll!
I'll leave that to you.
Huh? There's no need to solve
their stupid riddle anymore.
That's where you're wrong.
The video said to stop the bomb.
Last time they said "search
for", this time it's "stop."
Are you serious?
[SHIBAZAKI]
I am.
They gave us a puzzle,
and said not to cheat. Meaning.
[HAMURA growls]
[MUKASA whimpers]
Do you wanna play
their twisted game?
Or do you wanna help us
put an end to it?
Shibazaki? You gonna
be all right?
[TWELVE]
Whatcha doin'?
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE]
You should go home.
Places like this aren't
very safe at night.
[LISA]
Leave me alone.
I can't have you
wandering around,
it could cause problems.
Just shut up!
Hm?
[LISA] I don't really have
a home I can go to anymore.
[LISA] I'm so stupid.
I thought that somehow.
Somehow I could escape
from it all. Like...
Like someone would come
and lift me out
of my miserable, boring life.
Like it was all a bad dream.
But that's impossible, right?
I'm here. I'm awake.
This isn't some weird dream.
And things don't just
work themselves out.
So stupid.
[LISA sobbing]
[MALE OFFICER 4A]
Good evening, miss.
Is there any reason
you're out so late?
Ah! Hey, what do you think
you're doing, Shibazaki?
You can't smoke in here!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Window.
Ah. Is your head
screwed on straight?
[MUKASA]
Aw, jeez.
It was hard enough for you
to quit the first time around!
I'm serious!
I know you better than
you know yourself!
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[MALE OFFICERS grunt]
[LISA gasps]
[MALE OFFICER 4B gasps]
[TWELVE giggles]
[LISA gasps]
[LISA panting]
[MALE OFFICER 4A] Hey!
"Know thyself" was
carved at the gate.
Don't tell me!
Well done!
[SHIBAZAKI]
Wait. Why won't it stop?
[VOICE 4A] Even though you
answered correctly.
These friends of yours
decided to cheat.
Which means. Uh-oh!
The hidden bomb
cannot be stopped!
[SHIBAZAKI gasps]
[VOICE 4A]
So, ka-boom!
The hell?
[HAMURA]
Wait a second. Are those?
Yeah. They're sending out all
of our investigation reports.
[KINOSHITA] Yes sir.
The files are authentic.
It's unclear how they broke in.
[KINOSHITA grunting]
Hey. Do you wanna destroy it?
[TWELVE]
Huh?
The entire planet? Do you,
like, want to blow it all up?
[TWELVE chuckles]
[TWELVE laughing]
[LISA giggling]
It's been so long.
I haven't laughed
like that in forever.
I forgot how nice it felt.
Ah. So, uh--
Yeah, no.
[LISA gasps]
[TWELVE] Wait! Uh--
Having someone the cops
aren't looking for
would be kinda nice--
[NINE] She can't be trusted.
Don't you understand?
We're running out of time, here!
[TWELVE] But that doesn't
mean that Lisa would--
[TWELVE gasps]
[TWELVE, NINE]
Huh?