[alarm rings]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
Oh, my head...
Hangovers suck...
[KOBAYASHI]
Ooh, cold!
Come check out Maid Café: Cozy.
Stop by and say hi!
Hope to see you
at Maid Café: Cozy!
[KOBAYASH gulps, sighs]
Man. My lower back hurts, too...
[KOBAYASHI] Running that
new integration test
should be a straight-up
blast today.
[DRAGON growls]
[roars]
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Dragons.
The most powerful of all beings.
An imaginary creature
that has giant wings
for flight, possesses magical
powers, and breathes fire.
Ah! Ta-dah!
[giggles]
[KOBAYASHI]
Although, what do I know?
Having a good morning,
Miss Kobayashi?
I don't know yet.
Do you mind allowing
me in to your lovely home?
Oh. Sure, why the heck not?
[door bell rings]
So, you say we met yesterday,
and I offered to
let you stay here.
With me. And you're for sure
positive that's what I said?
Indeed!
[KOBAYASHI]
This is weird.
Why am I not waking up
from this dream?
Unless it's not a dream.
There's no way.
So, um...
Remind me where we met?
The mountains!
We met in the mountains!
Mountains...
[KOBAYASHI laughs]
[KOBAYASHI]
I remember mountains.
Okay, it's coming back.
[KOBAYASHI]
A dragon?
Apparently, a hilarious dragon.
Oh, God...
So, wanna stay
with me, "dragon"?
[echoes] So, wanna
stay with me, "dragon"?
[gasps]
I'll never forget
those wondrous words!
I can begin working
as your personal maid
immediately if you want!
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, that's a big negative.
Huh?
[KOBAYASHI] I'm not like
a dragon racist or anything.
I'm just not in the market
right now to hire a maid.
[TOHRU gasps] But!
You wouldn't have to pay me!
Yeah, no, that's not really--
Listen, I can be super helpful!
I can turn this
area into a sea of fire,
or curse people to death!
[KOBAYASHI]
No, no, no!
But, why maid instead of that?
Because you said a maid
would work better for you!
I did, huh?
Yeah, does make sense...
I'm sorry, Tohru.
I shouldn't have
made that promise.
No one can change
the impossible.
It's not, like, personal.
[TOHRU gasps]
Are you certain...?
It's impossible?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm... Sorry.
I understand.
My apologies as well,
for dropping in so suddenly.
[gasps]
Wanna stay with me, "dragon"?
[KOBAYASHI] Why won't this
stupid guilt go away?
[KOBAYASHI] Maybe this dream...
is really not a dream.
And if it's not, then...
I'm late?! Tohru!
[TOHRU]
Ah?
[pants]
Can you fly?!
[gasps]
Ah!
[KOBAYASHI screams]
Dragons are so fast!
[TOHRU]
Sorry, what did you say?
You're hella fast!
I could keep her.
[TOHRU]
Are you serious?!
So, now you can hear me?
[KOBAYASHI] I guess it wouldn't
be the end of the world
to have someone
around the house.
And if she's there--
[yelps]
This is murdering my lower back!
[KOBAYASHI] Okay.
First, let's take a look at
what you've decided is
the proper outfit for a maid
and why that's totally wrong.
Great idea!
Here you go.
--Huh...?
--It's says Maid Café Cozy, see?
What is this?
I discovered some real life
maids while on my way here.
Meaning we'll have
to start from scratch.
First thing, as
a housemaid--you clean.
Oh, I'm good at cleaning!
--How's that?
--No! It's all gone!
[TOHRU]
One moment!
[KOBAYASHI]
You can bring it back?
Next! Laundry maid!
Do laundry.
I can handle that, too!
[muffled]
I can produce a saliva
that specifically
removes stains.
[KOBAYASHI]
Gross! No one wants to see that!
Next! Parlor maid!
Greet people.
Easy thing for me!
[doorbell]
Hi, I just need
a signature for this delivery.
The foolish, inferior human
is not welcome at this home!
--Hey.
--Oh, you're an exception
of course, Miss Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI]
Last one! Kitchen maid.
--You cook.
--Cooking is my specialty!
Try my very own roasted tail!
[KOBAYASHI]
No, thanks.
--[TOHRU] Huh?
--[KOBAYASHI] No way.
Wha--?!
Would you prefer it
well-done instead?
[KOBAYASHI]
That's not the problem.
Then I'm confident
you'll enjoy it immensely!
I'm ethically
against dragon tail.
Ah-hah! Seems you're
a picky eater, Miss Kobayashi!
Dragon logic.
[TOHRU growling]
[gulps]
[KOBAYASHI]
It grows back?!
Took a bit longer
than usual because
I had to remove all the poison.
[KOBAYASHI]
And it's poisonous?!
Hate to break it to you,
but you don't know how to maid.
[gasps] Then, I'll learn
from the ground up!
Shall we start my education with
you telling me what you dislike?
What I dislike?
I can't do hijiki or eggplant.
Interesting.
I'll remember that.
Personally, I dislike
eggs when the yolks
have been removed.
A while back, I had
a friend named Herensuge
who was hit with one and killed.
[KOBAYASHI]
That's a powerful egg.
Hold up. Why are you
asking about dislikes?
Shouldn't you ask what I like?
No, that's bad luck.
Unfortunately, I've had
far too many friends slain
by the very things
they love most.
You know--liquor and women
and jewels and such.
Sounds a lot like humans.
However, I can certainly
let you know one thing I like!
It's you! I love you,
Miss Kobayashi!
You gonna eat me?
[TOHRU] No, not like that!
Like sexually!
I'm not into women or dragons.
Yes, but I can't put a label
on what I feel for you!
You saved me, and I'll use my
whole body to repay the favor!
Please use me to commute
to work again tomorrow!
Thanks, but I got enough of
that earlier. You're hard.
Gimme a chance, Miss Kobayashi!
I was raised to pay back all
favors, even if they were only
owed to a foolish,
inferior human being!
Call me crazy, but I sense bias.
Tohru, there is another
reason I'd rather not
let you fly me to work.
[TOHRU]
Your back?
Well, that's half of it.
The other half is--
[KOBAYASHI]
You're too loud and too fast!
I think a dragon's place is in
the home holding down the fort!
Fort? What?
You're one of the
stronger dragons, aren't you?
If you consider
"starting Armageddon" strong.
I do, and please don't.
The world's dangerous enough
without your help.
I'm just saying it would
be a relief to know
you're here keeping
the house safe for me.
[gasps]
Yes, I understand!
So consider it done!
So pretty.
Well, I'm off to the office.
If anybody calls,
you can answer
and take a message, yeah?
[TOHRU]
What's a "calls"?
Right, you're a dragon.
This is a phone.
When it goes "ring-ring,"
you pick it up like so.
[TOHRU]
Okay, got it.
They talk, then you talk.
[TOHRU]
They talk, then I talk!
--[KOBAYASHI] Okay, take care.
--[TOHRU] Save travels!
[giggles]
Hold the fort?
[TOHRU snarls]
Oh, is that what
those people were doing?
I'll just ask Fafnir for help!
[FAFNIR]
Kill them.
Kill all who try to
steal your treasure.
Kill all who are suspect.
Curse them with death.
Curse their generations to come.
He's always so helpful!
All right!
Time to do my best to earn Miss
Kobayashi's love and praise!
[lock rattling]
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
The lady who lives here
should be gone all day,
but let's make this fast.
We'll be in there
before you can say "open."
[TOHRU growls]
--[THIEF A] Uh.
--[TOHRU growls]
[BOTH whimper]
[screaming]
[DOG barking]
[THIEF A]
Save us!
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--[THIEF A] There's a monster!
--[POLICE A] A monster?
--[THIEF B] We saw it, I swear!
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm home.
[TOHRU]
Welcome back!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hold the fort down all right?
[TOHRU]
I suppose, but it was lonely.
--[KOBAYASHI] Ahh.
--[TOHRU] And I didn't even
--get to kill them.
--[KOBAYASHI] Ahh.
Wait, what?
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[TAKIYA]
Hey, Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
What is it, Takiya?
Want to grab some
drinks tonight?
Sure, but, like, only one round.
[KOBAYASHI]
So why me?
There are plenty of
other girls you could ask.
I don't want to go on a date.
I asked you 'cause
you're like one of the guys.
Wow, how sweet.
[TOHRU growls]
[TAKIYA] What's with
that girl staring us down?
--Do you know her?
--Uh...
Greetings, I'm Tohru Kobayashi.
Miss Kobayashi's new maid.
Her new live-in maid.
New violent live-in maid.
--[TAKIYA] Hmm.
--Yeah, it's my turn to
take care of the
"special" cousin.
I'm Makoto Takiya.
Kobayashi and I work together.
It's nice to meet you, Tohru.
And also you, Mister Takiya.
[TOHRU]
This man is clearly attempting
--to seduce Miss Kobayashi.
--[TAKIYA] Wait, are you even
--I shall not allow it!
--old enough to drink?
Of course I can drink.
You stultus.
Stultus?
[KOBAYASHI gulping]
Ah!
I love a good drink after work.
it's the best!
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi's the cutest!
I take it you won't
be joining us in
our fight against sobriety?
I won't.
--[TAKIYA] Got it.
--[TOHRU] I do not intend
to share drinks with him.
What do I do
about this silly man?
The laws are too strict in this
world to do what I want.
I know!
--I can flaunt how wonderfully
--Man!
--close Miss Kobayashi
--Today was tough!
--and I have become!
--I don't care what you say.
We're only secondary
or tertiary subcontractors,
so why bother complaining?
Because I don't like how
following their directions
consistently means we fail.
And the developers don't even
notice unless we point it out.
But making sure
they don't have to notice
their faults is part of our job,
so again, why complain?
[TAKIYA] I just think foisting
their problems on us
is a pretty sucky thing to do.
[TOHRU] I can't follow
what they're saying at all.
Speak, Dragon, please.
[TAKIYA]
Ah, I'm so sorry, Tohru.
We're not exactly including
you in this discussion.
[TOHRU growls]
No, it's fine.
The topic's just so trite,
I don't feel like joining in.
[TAKIYA]
Okay...
We should be discussing
the ramifications
of Ragnarok and Armageddon!
[TAKIYA gasps]
It doesn't matter,
I've had enough!
Time to use force!
Let the jackals feed off you
when you're dead!
[gasps]
Miss Kobayashi...?
[sighs]
Tohru...
Good maids don't talk that way!
No threatening murder!
She's gone drunk!
On top of that, what's with
your so-called maid uniform?
It's pretty disrespectful to
maid-dom, if you ask me.
I mean, have a
little self-respect.
You look like you're about
to lose a cosplay contest.
[screams]
Um, Mister Takiya?
Kobayashi! You're right, she's
just your basic cosplay maid!
It's cultural appropriation
but without any culture!
Agreed! I can acknowledge
the cuteness of Gothic Lolita,
but that's a specific
fashion trend,
not cosplay! Why does
it get so twisted?!
That's what I'm screaming!
Sure, Lolita and the maid
fashion do acknowledge
each other, and rightfully so,
but they should be careful
not to blend into boring!
[TOHRU] I think we're
well beyond me just being
a part of this
conversation, now.
Hey, Tohru!
We're giving
you some high-level
maid conversation,
so you better get in on this!
Maid talk!
Yes... I'm very sorry...
You know, Tohru,
those horns are a nice,
if not confusing,
touch to the cosplay.
Dragons have horns, and
that is all I know about that.
Take it off.
--[TAKIYA] Huh?
--[TOHRU] Huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Take it off!
--Huh...?
--Come on!
Gird your loins, sister!
Cosplay me crazy!
Where's the shame
in your role, maid?
[TOHRU]
I'm ashamed! [gasps]
Give me more! [snarls]
Show us what your
"moe" is made of!
--[TOHRU] This is insane.
--[KOBAYASHI] Bring more liquor
--Humans are terrifying!
--and maids! Victorian maids!
And don't forget a good butler!
[TAKIYA]
Sorry about that, Tohru.
Kobayashi and I go drinking
because we like to talk
about all things maid.
As an undercover otaku,
being able to share my passions
with someone else is
kind of precious to me.
I understand that perfectly.
And I'm assuming this means you
won't mind a little surprise.
[gasps]
Heh.
We can just say
I drank too much, too.
You really like
Kobayashi, don't you?
[TOHRU]
Yes.
[TOHRU] Since we're
being so honest,
you should know I hate you.
[TOHRU] Okay, so humans beings
all soil their clothing
with waste products?
[giggles]
Inferior species!
Miss Kobayashi's waste.
[moans]
Oh, there's no more left...
[KOBAYASHI groans]
I've said this before,
so don't make me say it again--
Please stop licking my laundry.
'Kay. Then, I'll take care of
it by licking you directly.
[KOBAYASHI] No licking me!
Can we discuss the laundry?
[TOHRU]
Am I doing it wrong?
[KOBAYASHI]
That's putting it mildly.
Tell me what you do
beginning to end.
Well, first, I use
my clairvoyance to make
certain your pockets are empty.
[KOBAYASHI]
Good.
[TOHRU] Then I separate
them into piles by color,
and wash them in
appropriate detergents.
[KOBAYASHI]
Good.
[TOHRU] Then I wash the
delicates in my mouth.
[KOBAYASHI]
No!
I told you I produce saliva
--that removes stains, yeah?
--So gross!
I told you nobody
wants to see that!
Oh. Would licking
make it better?
It's spit, not style!
Another thing. You can't wear
the same thing every day
like you're in some anime.
You're going to have
to change clothes, too.
But, these are my scales.
]
For real?
Yes. They're a part of me,
so I'd rather not take them off.
Oh. Makes sense.
[TOHRU]
Uh.
What's the matter?
[sighs]
It's just, uh...
I bought you some
personal clothes.
[gasps]
Thank you very, very much!
Well, you're doing
a lot for me, so I wanted,
um, to show appreciation.
[gasps]
Miss Kobayashi, would you like
to have a sacrifice later?
How fun. Care for
my fresh blood?
[KOBAYASHI]
What am I, a demon?!
Heavens no!
You're practically an angel!
But whatever you do,
please do not start serving God.
Look, just try it on.
[TOHRU]
Ah! [gasps]
--Well?
--[TOHRU] It's tight.
[KOBAYASHI growls]
What size bra do you wear?
A "D!" It
stands for "dragon!"
At least you bothered to
learn something. Gah.
Oh, crap, I gotta go.
All right, Tohru, use
the Internet to study up
appropriate hygienic
practices until I get home.
[TOHRU]
The inter-what?
Right. Dragon.
[TOHRU]
Oh!
[KOBAYASHI]
You look it up like this.
I understand!
I'll see you later, then.
[TOHRU]
Safe travels!
[TOHRU giggles]
The Internet!
[TOHRU] Hmm, I still
don't quite follow this.
I can just ask Fafnir
to help me out again.
--[FAFNIR] Kill them a--
--Or maybe not Fafnir.
Quetzalcoatl is knowledgeable,
so I'll try asking her.
Lucoa! Hey!
[LUCOA]
Tohru? It's been, like, forever.
[TOHRU] So blah-blah-blah
and yadda-yadda?
[LUCOA]
Mm-hmm...
Yeah...
This doesn't sound like a
problem of clean or dirty.
Huh?
[LUCOA] Well, you remember
Nidhogg, don't you?
[TOHRU] The one who gnawed
on that tree's roots?
[LUCOA]
The world's tree, yes.
No matter how much
Nidhogg's poisonous fangs
pollute Yggdrasill,
the goddesses purify it,
so the tree stays clean.
However...
[TOHRU]
Yes?
[LUCOA] What do you figure
happens to the spots he gnaws?
[TOHRU]
Ah...
As I recall,
he leaves energy behind.
Something like a curse?
[LUCOA]
Yep, that's it.
This Miss Kobayashi you speak
of is worried about that.
Of course!
Thank you very much!
[LUCOA]
Tohru.
Are you enjoying living
amongst the humans?
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU]
I am!
[TOHRU] At this rate,
Miss Kobayashi's laundry
is never going to get dry.
I know!
[roars]
[growls]
Great work, Tohru.
Really starting to doubt
my maid teaching skills.
--[CROWD murmuring]
--[MAN A] What just happened?
I know that breath.
I know it well.
[TOHRU giggles]
[TOHRU sniffs]
[sighs]
--[KOBAYASHI whimpers]
--[TOHRU] Surely there's nothing
wrong with
inhaling the scent?
I don't imagine
you need sleep?
Nope. But I wanna
sleep with you,
so I think I'm gonna
go to bed anyway!
Whatever, do what you want.
I have a feeling you
don't mean that!
Well, nighty-night.
[TOHRU]
Yes, good night.
[giggles]
[TOHRU giggles softly]
[KOBAYASHI]
It's cramped.
[TOHRU gasps]
Do you want me to go?
[KOBAYASHI]
Nah, it's fine.
[gasps]
[TOHRU roars]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[TOHRU growls]
[TOHRU gasps]
[pants]
You okay?
[gasps]
It was a fight.
In another world.
I was run through by a sword.
I bet that hurt.
[TOHRU]
Yes, quite a lot.
And does it still hurt?
[TOHRU]
No. It doesn't hurt now.
[KOBAYASHI]
That's good, then.
[TOHRU]
Ah.
[KOBAYASHI]
Sweet dreams.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU]
Sweet dreams.
Welcome back home,
Miss Kobayashi!
I said welcome home.
Welcome back, girl!
So, what are you
working on, Tohru?
[TOHRU] Miss Kobayashi!
Tell me what you like this time!
--[KOBAYASHI] Maids.
--[TOHRU] You mean me, then?
[KOBAYASHI]
No, not you.
[TOHRU]
What else?
[KOBAYASHI]
I dunno, peace.
[TOHRU] So you're saying
I'm enough for you?
[KOBAYASHI]
Nope. I never said that.