[KOBAYASHI]
I gotta pee.
[TOHRU groans]
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh?
Too close!
--[KOBAYASHI] Someone's here!
--Sorry, Kobayashi.
No, it's fine,
don't worry about it.
Hey, it's beer time!
[TOHRU]
Whoops, excuse me a second!
[KANNA]
Is there any juice?
--I'm officially over this.
--[KANNA, TOHRU talking]
You called looking for
a three-bedroom apartment?
Yes. I'd like one as close
to this area as possible.
[REALTOR]
How's this?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm.
[REALTOR]
How's this?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm.
[REALTOR]
How's this?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm.
[KOBAYASHI] They all
kinda look the same to me.
[REALTOR]
This one has a bonus feature:
The rooftop is actually
a common area shared by tenants.
Really.
[BOTH gasp]
[TOHRU]
The sky's so vast!
[KANNA]
It feels amazing!
What do you think?
Well...
[BOTH laugh]
[KOBAYASHI]
I guess we'll take it.
We've gotta get this
place ready for the move.
First, we clean.
Yeah!
[TOHRU] ♪ Cleaning,
cleaning, la la la. ♪
♪ Beat the dust
and de-de-destroy it!
[KOBAYASHI]
What is she singing?
[TOHRU] ♪ No dust
will be left behind! ♪
♪ New clean, clean everything. ♪
♪ If not, then death,
death, death to the world! ♪
[KOBAYASHI]
Are you trying to freak me out?!
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
So as a dragon,
do you like being clean?
I suppose so.
I like to take baths a lot
as well as brush my teeth.
You brush your teeth?
Do you have like a dragon-sized
toothbrush or something?
[TOHRU] No, I use my claws
to pick out the bugs.
[KOBAYASHI] Bugs?
But what about the bacteria?
Yeah. They're so small,
I don't really notice them.
Bet it's not easy to
have such a huge body.
[TOHRU] True. Finding somewhere
to live was horrible.
[KOBAYASHI] That figures.
What did you finally go with?
[TOHRU]
Sometimes caves.
Sometimes ruins.
Sometimes mountains.
I've even slept
in the sky a few times.
Seems dangerous!
Although, that would make living
anywhere a breeze. [chuckles]
--Whoa.
--[TOHRU] Actually, no.
Why is that funny?
Anyway, if I stayed in one place
too long, humans showed up.
They're the worst.
You were, like, a rare monster.
[TOHRU] The point is,
my body kept getting dirty.
But I barely got the
opportunity to bathe at all.
Ew.
When worse came to
worst, we would have to
--lick each other clean.
--[KOBAYASHI] Huh?!
Kanna and I've done that before.
[KOBAYASHI] Ugh!
That is inappropriate
behavior for humans!
[TOHRU]
Maybe so.
But most dragons
couldn't care less
about all the silly human rules.
We don't get sick
or unhealthy either way.
Wow. Okay, I'm jealous of that.
You know what?
You're a very sloppy person.
You leave beer cans
scattered all over,
and your clothes stay right
where you took them off.
What does it matter what I do?
That's what I liked so much
about living alone.
[TOHRU] Also, your books are not
in any order that I know about.
Now that's just being too picky!
[TOHRU]
Ahem.
Fine, I can overlook the
catastrophe of books.
However, you can at least clean
up your trash and clothes.
Don't forget this is my home.
You don't want Kanna to pick up
those nasty habits, do you?
No...
[KOBAYASHI] My father must
have felt exactly like this
when my mother yelled at him.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmph. You know, Tohru.
I keep leaving crap around
because I'm happy
you're here, okay?
I like that you clean up.
[gasps]
I mean, that stuff's
basically a cakewalk
for a mighty and powerful
dragon like you, right?
Uh-huh. It is!
Tohru, I'd love it if
you kept helping out...
...if you want.
[squeals]
I do want! I do! Yes!
So pretty.
Scoundrel Kobayashi.
All right, next up is packing.
Right!
[KOBAYASHI] I know almost all
of these things belong to me.
Sorry for asking
you to help out.
Never fear. You can ask
anything at all of me!
[KANNA]
I'll do my best, too!
[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
[KANNA]
Hmm?
[gasps]
Focus, Kanna.
Stop fooling around--
[gasps]
Chibi Kobayashi! Aah!
[gasps] Those dead-fish eyes
are killing me--they're so cute!
There's something
wrong with you.
[KOBAYASHI] Can you focus
for five seconds, please?
[BOTH gasp]
What? I had no clue
I still had this.
Focus.
Me?! I'm all focus!
[gasps]
Miss Kobayashi!
[KANNA, KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[TOHRU] Tell me this
maid outfit is yours!
--[KANNA gasps]
--Yeah, that's mine.
Will you please, oh, please
try it on for me?!
I want to see if you're
as adorable in it
as I know you'll be!
No.
Why? You bought it so
you could wear it, didn't you?
Yeah, but as soon
as I saw my reflection,
I realized I looked idiotic.
I'll never wear that again.
[TOHRU groans]
Then would you mind
if I wore it?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm? Not at all.
Hooray! Thank you!
So, how do I look?
[BOTH gasp]
Lovely, lady Tohru!
[KOBAYASHI] Mm-hmm!
I think it looks great, too.
[laughs]
I can't say I disagree! Thanks!
[sighs]
Although, your clothes
seem to always be a bit
too tight in the chest for me.
[growls]
Speaking of...
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
There's no way in hell
you're really just a D.
I'm a D for a dragon
if that helps.
[KOBAYASHI gulping]
Ah! Beer, win!
Great work today, you guys!
Yes. You two are so awesome!
Finally, time for a bath.
What happened to the
towels and clean clothes
I laid out in the bathroom?
I packed all of it up
in a box for you!
Huh?
Huh...?
You know which box
that is, by chance?
[doorbell rings]
[MOVER A]
Good morning!
Sansan Moving Service
at your service!
Great. Go to town, boys.
[gasps]
So this is a car, huh?
[KOBAYASHI] Let's figure out
how we're gonna use this space.
Living room, obviously.
Office in here? Sound good?
I think I'll take
this one as my bedroom.
Last, but not least...
You two will get to
share this room!
Huh?
Wait this is our room?
[KOBAYASHI] Yep. You can do
whatever you want with it.
[BOTH gasp]
Yay!
--[laughs]
--[sighs]
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
[KOBAYASHI]
A whole new life.
--[door clicks]
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
Shall I wash your back for you?
[KOBAYASHI]
What? No, I'm fine.
You said you liked it
when I made things clean.
That is what you said, right?
Ugh, that's your angle?
Okay, fine, come on in.
Okay.
[KOBAYASHI]
I have a question.
[TOHRU]
Yes?
[KOBAYASHI]
Wouldn't it be easier for you
to wash your body
in your human form?
[TOHRU] Technically, yes.
But I can't be as thorough.
All of the confusing
and finicky rules
in this world don't
help, either.
I find the whole thing
a little stifling.
You don't like your
human form, do you?
[gasps]
Yes!
[grunts]
And no, it's complicated.
Sure.
[KANNA]
Knock, knock. I'm coming in!
Lady Tohru, wash me, too?
[TOHRU]
Of course I will!
[KOBAYASHI]
Ugh, too close!
[TOHRU giggles]
Here I go!
[KOBAYASHI]
Morning, Tohru.
Hey, Miss Kobayashi!
Hope you slept well!
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru.
Uh, yes?
[KOBAYASHI] Want me to wash you
as a thanks for yesterday?
Do I?
Well, hurry up.
[TOHRU]
What? Okay!
[TOHRU sighs]
Thank you...
This is incredible...
[KOBAYASHI]
Feels like I'm washing a car.
[TOHRU]
Oh, thank you.
Miss Kobayashi,
you're the best.
[KOBAYASHI]
You're welcome, Tohru.
[gasps]
This is the old apartment!
[groans]
Damn it, why am I so stupid...?
[sirens blare]
[barking]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
--[pans rattling]
--[gasps]
--[loud music]
--[screeching]
--[squeals]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
Tohru, that's way too loud!
Huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Or not.
[KOBAYASHI groans]
Do you believe me
to be a loud person?
[KOBAYASHI]
No, I'm sorry.
[KANNA] Kobayashi, is your
hangover making your head hurt?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah...
I can't believe I feel
like this on my day off.
The noises sound
like they're coming from
both neighbors and above.
Would you like me to
speak with them about it?
[KOBAYASHI] Actually, if you
would, that would be great.
Make sure your horns
don't stick out, though.
Sure, no problem!
And if they refuse
to listen to me,
I'll just murder, dismember,
and pulverize them!
Seems excessive.
[TOHRU] I'll start with
Miss Sasakibe on our right.
[doorbell rings]
[SASAKIBE]
Coming.
Hello. Oh.
You're from next door.
[TOHRU]
I'm Tohru. How are you?
I'm good, thanks.
Did you need something?
Well... we've been hearing
some really loud noises,
so I decided to
come check it out.
I didn't realize
I was that loud.
What are you doing? Pillaging?
Just cooking.
[TOHRU]
Huh...?
Stay here a quick minute.
[TOHRU yelps]
Here, allow me to share some.
Stewed rapeseed blossoms.
Wow, thank you so much!
And if it wouldn't be
too much trouble,
would you try keeping
the noise down?
Sure.
[TOHRU] How could this
make such a racket?
[TOHRU] Now for Mister
Yana on the left side.
What? I'm playing music.
Playing music?
Yeah, want to listen?
--[screams]
--[heavy metal music]
[screaming continues]
Are you the god of
the underworld because
you sound like Hades
crushing Hercules.
Best compliment ever. Rock on.
[TOHRU] Anyways, please try
to keep the volume down.
[YANA]
Mm-hmm.
[TOHRU] Last is Mister Sone
on the floor above.
I'm sorry, but I have
to use a drill for work.
A drill?
Yes, I make hand-carved
wooden figurines.
Ooh, a gorilla!
That's really well done!
Anyway, one of the girls
I live with is suffering
from a hangover.
So please try to keep it down?
Yeah. I'll try.
[SASAKIBE]
You're the loud one!
[YANA]
No, I'm pretty sure that's you!
[SONE]
Or it's you both!
[SASAKIBE] This from the guy
who has to be the loudest
--in the room?
--[growling]
[TOHRU]
What's going on out here?
His drilling is way too loud!
The death metal's too loud!
That creepy noise is too loud!
All I'm doing is cooking!
[SONE, YANA]
Huh?
At the moment, all three
of you are too loud.
[GROUP]
We're sorry, Tohru.
[TOHRU]
Why do humans always make
the same mistakes over and over?
They're beyond help.
I'll kill them.
Excuse me. If I could
have a word, please?
[ALL]
Hmm?
The problem we're all
having is that everyone else
manages to be loud
precisely when
we'd rather things to be quiet.
So why don't we
organize all the times
we don't want to have a bunch
of noise driving us insane,
and plan around it?
We'll make a schedule out
of our noise preferences.
[gasping]
If some times don't work out,
then we can use the
power of the earplug.
[TOHRU] And you're certain
this plan is acceptable?
These are creatures that
haven't learned anything
since evolving from apes.
You know I'm one of
those creatures, right?
--[TOHRU] Mm.
--It's not a big deal.
I wouldn't mind so much if I
wasn't dying in hangover hell.
Besides, it's only
natural for people
who are going about their lives
to annoy other people
who are simply
going about theirs.
That's the definition
of neighbors.
[sighs] You might be
too good for your own good.
No, I'm not.
[KOBAYASHI]
I wouldn't like things if they
were too quiet either.
[TOHRU gasps]
[KOBAYASHI yawns]
I'm gonna take a nap real quick.
[TOHRU]
Of course.
Do you consider me
to be too loud?
[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
There are times when I feel
like you are, yeah.
Does it, um, annoy...?
[KOBAYASHI] Hmm. Kinda difficult
to give a precise answer
to that question.
[TOHRU sighs]
[KOBAYASHI]
However...
For what it's worth, this life's
fine. Good enough for me.
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm gonna sleep now.
Right. Then I will, too.
--[screeching]
--[KOBAYASHI screams]
[KOBAYASHI]
You're being too loud!
[TOHRU hums]
[KANNA sighs]
[KOBAYASHI]
What should I do about this?
I don't like slowing down
so I can be considerate
of management's
inability to drink like me.
Straight to the point as always.
Hmm... You should create
an excuse not to go.
An excuse?
[TOHRU]
We're having a party?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah.
I was talking to Takiya about
doing something here.
I need an excuse to get out of
my job's flower viewing thing.
You invited that man
to our home?
Oh, stop making that face.
He's a nice guy.
Give him a chance. Please?
[TOHRU growls]
I suppose so,
but I'm only putting up
with him for you.
--[KOBAYASHI] How mature.
--In return, can I invite
some of my friends, too?
Friends like who? People
from the shopping district?
[TOHRU]
No, like dragons.
Huh?
[TOHRU]
Don't worry.
They're all extraordinarily
well-behaved dragons.
[KOBAYASHI]
Ugh. Why isn't that comforting?
I'm here.
Welcome back home!
Surprise. I'm here, too!
Oh, hi. Welcome. Come in.
[TAKIYA] Funny how
I don't feel very welcome.
Now, you must be Kanna.
Nice to meet you.
[TAKIYA]
I like your goth-loli thing.
[KANNA]
Hmm.
[KOBAYASHI]
Where are your friends, Tohru?
[TOHRU]
They should be here soon.
--[doorbell rings]
--[gasps] Coming!
If you'll give me
one moment, please.
Fafnir, no!
Make yourself look like
the picture I sent to you!
[FAFNIR]
Good grief.
I hate this and everything
it stands for. Kill me.
[FAFNIR]
I'm already dead inside.
[BOTH gasp]
Miss Kobayashi,
I'd like you to meet Fafnir.
[KOBAYASHI] Hello, Fafnir,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
[TAKIYA] That is what's known
as a polite social greeting.
[KANNA]
Polite social greeting?
It's a magical set of
words that helps even
the shyest of people introduce
themselves with confidence.
[KOBAYASHI] Tohru, I have
a feeling your friend
might be hostile towards me.
That makes sense. He does have
a slight dislike for humans.
We're talking about an ancient
cursed dragon who's been
guarding his treasure in
a cave for, like, ever.
[KOBAYASHI]
You mean Hobbit style?
--[doorbell rings]
--[KOBAYASHI] Hm? There're more?
[TOHRU]
This one's the last.
[LUCOA]
Hey, Tohru.
Hi, there!
It's been way too long!
Miss Kobayashi,
this is Quetzalcoatl.
So cool to meet you.
Please, call me Lucoa.
I'm gonna assume all
dragons look this unrealistic.
--Huh?
--Oh, never mind.
It's cool or whatever
to meet you, too.
[LUCOA]
Hmm? Everything chill?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah, but...
Did you walk here
wearing that "ensemble"?
[LUCOA]
Of course I did.
[KOBAYASHI]
Doesn't really leave a whole lot
to the imagination, does it?
[gasps]
[VG MONSTER growls]
You wanna give it a try?
Now, when you get a hit,
be sure to move back a little.
Just like that.
Oh, you can't attack
when he's doing that move.
[VG KNIGHT grunts]
--[FAFNIR growls]
--Almost there.
Nice work.
Hey, you killed him!
Ignore that treasure chest if
you know what's good for ya.
--[VG MONSTER B roars]
--[VG KNIGHT grunts]
Those things are called mimics.
Sucks. You died.
[FAFNIR growls]
[KOBAYASHI]
He's completely hooked, now.
[LUCOA giggles]
[TOHRU hums]
It's great to see Tohru smiling;
she's not normally the type.
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--I assume that's thanks to you.
Doubtful. I'm just
a normal human being.
Could be what she needed since
she's never had anything
normal before.
Her friends are the same way.
You know, Lucoa. To be honest,
I'm grateful to Tohru, as well.
Truth is... I didn't use
to smile very much myself.
I'd never admit that
to her, though.
[LUCOA giggles]
The food's ready, everyone!
Yay!
Watch out for her tail.
Can I get you anything to drink?
[LUCOA]
Drink? Yes, thank you.
But, no offense, I'll need
to check it for curses.
[KOBAYASHI]
Curses?
Oh, yeah, forever ago, Lucoa,
who was still a goddess
at the time, had some
major drama go down
thanks to being forced
to drink some alcohol
an ally of hers cursed,
which made her get all sloppy
with her sister.
[LUCOA whines]
Will you please stop talking?
I'm starting to get that
a dragon's past is never good.
[slurred]
For the last time!
When it comes to
fancy butler men,
I say give me middle-aged
or give me death!
The young, handsome,
and devilish butler has been
taking the world by storm,
and say what you will,
--but he's here to stay, sister!
--Stop messing me up.
She's entirely different
when she's drunk.
Yeah.
Hey, you! You totally
wanna be a maid, don't you?
[LUCOA]
Uhhhh...
You do, too!
[TOHRU]
I thought I already was one.
I've told you before,
that's basic cosplay!
If you don't like the truth,
then take it off!
--[gasps] Fafnir!
--[TOHRU] Why?!
--[KOBAYASHI] And confess!
--We must avert our eyes to
preserve Tohru's dignity!
--Please, don't look!
--[FAFNIR growls] Stop it!
Let go! Grr! I can't see!
[KOBAYASHi]
Take it off!
I love how no one can not
move their body to that.
[TAKIYA] Fafnir, remember
to ignore that treasure chest.
[FAFNIR growls]
[TAKIYA]
Aw. It's a mimic.
No, don't go to that one either.
[FAFNIR snarls]
[TAKIYA]
That was a mimic, too.
Why do you instinctively go
after all the treasure?
[FAFNIR sighs]
It's my nature.