The sports festival
is coming up soon.
Be sure you give that
information I just handed out
to your parents, okay, kids?
--Hey, Saikawa?
--[SAIKAWA] Hmm?
What's this sports
festival thing?
Hold up.
Are you telling me you didn't
have them where you're from?
Oh, my gosh, a sports
festival is, like, one of
the most fun things ever.
There's running.
Running?
Ball-tossing.
Ball-tossing?
Tug-of-War.
Tug-of-War?
[SAIKAWA] Yeah, and lots
of other events where
the whole class
teams up together!
Whoa!
Our parents
get to come and watch
for the whole day, too!
Like, you get to eat lunch
with them and everything!
Whoa!
And you're, like,
the best at sports,
so I bet you'll win it all
and be the hero of the day!
I mean, your mom's gonna be
beyond proud of you after this!
Whoa!
[KOBAYASHI]
Gotta work that day. Can't.
[KANNA] Kobayashi...
Take the day off for me...
--Please...?
--Sorry, I can't do that.
Kanna, Miss Kobayashi's
in the middle of her death march
and on the verge of facing
Hades. Give it up already.
--No!
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
Also, what's a sports festival?
[KANNA] It's when you train
alongside your peers
to defeat strong opponents.
No, I think that's
a bit exaggerated.
[KANNA]
Defeat Hades fast, Kobayashi!
Then you can come watch me.
Don't be so selfish.
Besides, I'll come with you
to watch the sports.
[KANNA]
No...
Why's it gotta be
Miss Kobayashi, anyway?
What am I, chopped liver?
No, it's not you,
it's just that Saikawa said
our parents could come
with us for the day.
You're like my big sister.
Kobayashi's like a mom.
Reminder: I'm not
old enough to be Kanna's mom.
Although...
Some of my classmates
do have kids already.
Miss Kobayashi,
you hang in there!
[KOBAYASHI]
At any rate, I can't go.
Sorry, but you'll have to
make do with Tohru.
Great. "Make do."
Forget it!
Ah, Kanna!
I never thought
a parent showing up or not
was that big of a deal.
To start off with, it's not
like I'm Kanna's mother.
I'm just a random human she met.
I don't think that matters
to her much because
she's been treating you
like a mom-type figure for
a while now.
[sighs]
But why?
I can barely be around people.
How could I be a good mother?
This is stupid.
I never had both my parents
make it to sports festivals.
They were always
too busy working.
I never got upset, either.
I knew they had to support us.
Well, Kanna's parents
basically gave her free rein.
They felt a dragon would grow up
strong all on its own.
Since she bears
the name Kanna Kamui,
I'm sure they told her
she had to make sure
to be super strong.
But what she wanted
was her parents' attention,
which is why she pulled
all those silly pranks.
It just got her
banished to this world.
Makes sense she'd want you
to spoil her and give her
that attention, now.
I get what you're
saying, but I still just--
[sighs]
Hey, good morning, Kanna.
Something wrong?
Kobayashi won't come
to the sports festival.
Really? Wow. It's okay.
There's way more to
the day than just parents!
We get to work together
with the whole class to win,
and that's super fun.
It does sound fun.
Except your version
of "work together"
and ours is totally different.
You shut up! No one asked you!
[FUKUSHIMA] No one has
to ask me for my opinion
for me to give it.
[SAIKAWA]
Why are you still talking?!
Oh, my god, shut up!
[TAKIYA]
Sports festival?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
Bad luck that
it falls directly on
our delivery deadline day, huh?
Yeah, but I'm kinda
not sure if there's really
any need for me to
go in the first place.
Do you not wanna go?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm... No, it's not that.
But I think it would be
nice if I could go.
[TAKIYA]
Hmph.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm? What is it?
Oh, you know,
just my first time seeing you
worry about something like this.
Seriously?
Hmm. Oh. I guess so.
Well, I think it's more
a question of do you want to go,
rather than can you go.
[sighs]
So do I want to go?
[TOHRU] ♪ La, la, la,
I'm the cutest, ♪
♪ most adorable maid
forever and ever! ♪
[giggles]
Hey, I'm home.
[TOHRU]
Oh, I didn't hear you come in.
[TOHRU] Kanna, are you
still in a bad mood?
You should let it go.
Lady Tohru. Perception block me.
--Huh?
--Use perception block on me.
Uh...
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm back, guys.
[TOHRU]
Welcome home.
[sighs]
[TOHRU]
I'll get your dinner ready.
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm...
Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Don't worry about it.
Coming to the
sports festival, I mean.
Huh?
It'll still be fun
to be able to work together
with everyone in my class.
It's fine. And I hope
you make your deadline okay.
Oh. Thanks.
[KANNA]
Good night.
So, um...
Kanna might have used
my perception blocking
to go secretly observe
you at your work today.
[sighs]
[KOBAYASHI] I know
I've felt like this before.
[KOBAYASHI]
Right. It's guilt.
Just like with Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru.
That's me.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll be getting home even later.
Do you mean...?
Okay!
[STUDENTS]
35! 36! 37!
38! 39! 40-- [cheering]
'Kay! Great work, kids,
but that's enough for today.
You should all be
so proud of yourselves!
Look at how long
you can jump, now!
All we have to do
is keep this up,
and we'll win the sports
festival, easy!
[STUDENTS, KANNA]
Yeah!
Kanna, we're not gonna
let 'em down, are we?
[KANNA]
No way.
[TAKIYA groans]
You're tearing it up.
[KOBAYASHI]
Trying.
Going to the
sports festival, then?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
Decide that you want to go?
[KOBAYASHI] Nope.
Decided that I ought to go.
Lemme help.
Tell me whatcha need.
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh? Oh.
Thanks. You're awesome.
[TAKIYA]
I know.
And, next
drinking night is on you.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yes, it is.
I'll be there tomorrow.
[gasps]
Really?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm. Yep, really.
You beat Hades already?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm. I sure did.
[gasps]
I love you, Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI]
Whoa.
That's so cute.
I forget she's
still just a child.
[ELMA]
What do they expect me to do?
What do I do...?
I could go for both!
No, that would
go over my daily limit!
I can't!
But, still...
Oh, god...
Look, ma'am. We really need you
--to make a decision.
--Yes, I know that!
I'm trying to!
[TEACHER A]
Welcome to the 43rd annual
Oborozuka Elementary
Sports Festival!
The events will begin now!
First up on the program
is the opening parade!
Oh, look! There's Kanna!
Where? I don't see her.
She's looking our way.
Hey!
Yeah, I bet she wants to
make sure that I showed up.
[SAIKAWA'S MOM]
Riko!
[GEORGIE]
Little Miss!
[BOTH]
You're gonna do great!
[LUCOA]
Shouta, baby!
--Oh, Miss Lucoa's here, too.
--I'll be right here
cheering for you!
Hooray, Shouta!
[SHOUTA whines]
[BOYS] The pledge: We
athletes hereby pledge to honor
the spirit of good sportsmanship
and compete fair and square
with all participants until the
very end of the competition!
[TEACHER A] Fifth on today's
program is the three-legged race
by the third graders.
You can do it, Kanna!
No pressure, though!
Riko! You've got this!
Do your best!
[TEACHER A]
Ready...
Um, okay, let's
tie our legs together, now.
[KANNA]
Mm!
[shrieks]
[KANNA]
Done.
Yeah, thank you, Kanna.
You're the best.
Still have to hold on to
each other's shoulders.
[KANNA]
Mm.
[shrieks]
[TEACHER A]
Okay, next pair.
Come on, Saikawa.
It's our turn to go.
[SAIKAWA shrieks]
I-I'm so sorry, Kanna.
I was just way too happy.
That's all right, Saikawa.
We're gonna get 'em next time.
Jeez, Riko, what are
you doing out there?
[yells]
[TEACHER A] Seventh on
our program today is
the fifth graders'
treasure hunt.
[cheering]
[SHOUTA pants]
[groans]
[cheering]
What? You want me?
[TEACHER A]
Yep. Perfect.
--[BOYS cheer]
--[LUCOA] Hmm...?
Shouta, your older
sister's incredible!
[SHOUTA]
Mm... Yeah...
[TEACHER A] We'll now be
taking a break for lunch.
Students and parents, please
enjoy your time together!
Everyone make sure you're
careful of heat stroke
and drinking lots
and lots of water.
We'll see you back in a bit!
[KANNA]
Oh, my gosh! This looks yummy!
Yeah, it does.
[TOHRU chuckles] I'm not just
your everyday dragon maid!
Thank you.
Lady Tohru, it's good.
Thank you for saying so.
Miss Kobayashi?
Say, "ah."
Tohru... What kind
of meat is that?
--Tch.
--[KOBAYASHI] Knew it.
Ah.
Yeah, this lunch
really is especially tasty.
I'm glad you like it.
Eat enough to make sure
you have lots of energy!
[KANNA] Mm. We'll turn
things around after this.
[ELMA]
What do they expect me to do?
What do I do?
How am I supposed
to choose just one from
over ten different combinations?
I could go for
variations of 'em all!
No, then I wouldn't last.
But, still...
Oh, god!
[ELMA] There's the pumpkin
and sweet potato.
--But chestnut's hard to pass.
--Please, anytime.
The surprising
pairing of grape and pear
would be good, wouldn't it?
No, wait. Chestnut.
[TEACHER A] It's now time to
start today's afternoon segment.
Coming up 15th
in our program,
we have the third
graders' jump rope.
Everyone ready?
And... go!
[STUDENTS]
1!
2!
3!
4!
--5!
--Go, Kanna!
Jump, Kanna, jump!
Riko, keep those feet up!
Do your best, Little Miss!
[STUDENTS]
22!
23!
[TEACHER A] Classes 1 and 4
have tripped on their ropes!
[STUDENTS]
42.
43.
Uh-oh, Class 3 has
tripped on their rope, now!
But watch Class 2!
They're still going strong!
[STUDENTS]
55.
56.
57.
58.
[BOTH]
Keep on jumping!
Don't stop, now!
--[TEACHER A] Finished!
--[STUDENTS cheering]
Class 3-2 wins!
Did you see that? We just won!
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm! Talk about impressive.
[TEACHER A] Nineteenth
on today's program,
the fifth grade boys'
calvalry battle.
[LUCOA]
Shouta, baby! You can do it!
Kick their tushies!
[TEACHER A]
Begin!
[BOYS yelling]
Hooray! Go, Shouta!
[BOYS sighing]
[SHOUTA yells]
Get 'em, baby!
Take 'em down!
[SHOUTA yells]
[TEACHER A]
Finished!
Class 3 with an
overwhelming victory!
[cheering]
Shouta, you're so lucky!
Your sister's awesome!
[SHOUTA]
Mm. Yeah.
[TEACHER A]
Now for our 20th event,
the third graders' tug of war!
[TEACHER B]
Class 1 and 2. Ready?
Go!
[STUDENTS]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Come on, Kanna!
Win the tug of war!
Focus, sweetie!
Do your best!
[STUDENTS chanting]
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
[gasps]
[SAIKAWA shrieks]
The winner is...
...Class Two! Congrats!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Saikawa, can you believe?
We won it!
Hooray!
Yeah! She's doing amazing!
Keep up that
winning pace, kiddos!
[whistle blows]
[TOHRU] Kanna's class
has made it all the way
up to second place.
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm. First after this game.
Ooh! It's about to start!
[TEACHER A] Thirty-second
in today's program,
the third graders' relay!
Hey, Kanna.
If we take first place here,
we'll win!
[KANNA]
Mm!
[TEACHER A]
This will be the final event
for the third graders.
Family and friends, they're
going to need your support
now more than ever!
[TEACHER B]
First female runners.
Take position!
[TEACHER B]
Ready...
[gunshot]
Go, Iida! Get it!
You can do it, Iida!
[TEACHER A] All the classes
have started strong.
Right now, Class 1
holds the lead.
Behind them are Class 2, 4,
and 3 bringing up the rear.
[TEACHER A] The baton's
passed to the second runner.
Makishima, keep up the pace!
Saikawa, you're gonna do great!
Well, yeah.
I'll be passing you the
baton from first place!
What a race!
Class 1 and 2 are currently
neck and neck!
Good job, ladies! Keep it up!
[SAIKAWA]
Hmm!
Here, I, go!
[TEACHER A] Wow,
Class 2 is closing in fast.
And now they've
passed Class 1!
[SAIKAWA panting]
[SAIKAWA gasps]
Ah!
[TEACHER A]
Oh, no! What a disappointment.
Class 2 dropped the baton!
[SAIKAWA whimpers]
[SAIKAWA pants]
[TEACHER A]
Class 1 is back in the lead.
Behind them are Class 4,
then 3, and last place is 2.
[SAIKAWA whimpers]
I'm sorry!
I got this!
[pants]
[TEACHER A] The anchors are
all fighting for the win,
but look at Class 2 go!
She's passing the others
with no problem.
[SAIKAWA gasps]
She's so fast.
[BOTH]
Just one more!
You can do it!
[STUDENTS]
Kanna!
[gasps]
[TEACHER A]
Finish!
The winner: Class 2!
[cheering]
[GIRLS giggle]
[BOYS chuckling]
[BOTH]
You're the best, Kanna!
[gasps]
[IIDA] I'm not kidding.
That was incredible!
[MAKISHIMA]
You were so cool!
[SAIKAWA gasps]
Kanna!
You licked me!
But, um... I'm sorry.
I messed up real bad...
No, you kept running.
If you'd given up,
there's no way
I could've passed all of them.
[SAIKAWA]
Huh...?
Thanks for being
such a good teammate.
[SAIKAWA squeals]
[SAIKAWA]
Oh, Kanna!
[SAIKAWA'S DAD sobs]
[KOBAYASHI]
Here you go. You were so good.
Thanks. I had a lot of fun.
You worked hard out there, too.
I know. Everyone
in our class worked hard,
that's why we were able to win.
I imagine it's less than
satisfying not being able
to go full out like
you normally do.
No, it was fine.
I like being with
the other kids.
Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Thank you so much for
coming today, really.
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
You are very welcome.
[KANNA] And thank you
for lunch, Lady Tohru.
No problem! Heh!
It was hardly anything.
[KOBAYASHI] Participating in a
sports festival as a guardian?
What in the world have I become?
[KOBAYASHI] And when did
this change even happen?
Although, I suppose
it would be rather nice
to let loose a little
bit more today.
I agree.
I'm so down. It's been too long.
Let's get to it, then.
Hey, I wanna play, too!
Oh, how fun!
All three of us together!
That okay, Miss Kobayashi?
[sighs] Yeah, sure,
as long as you go where
you don't bother anyone.
[KANNA]
Lady Tohru, where should we go?
[TOHRU] Let's use the same place
we did last time.
--[LUCOA laughs]
--Oh, dragons.
[ELMA]
Which should I choose...?
Which should I choose?
Which should I choose?!
Which?!
[ELMA]
Why?!
Why must the stupid products
of man trouble me so?!
Humans are just...
...terrifying.
[GEORGIE] I'm the maid Georgie,
servant of the Saikawa family.
[LUCOA]
I'm Shouta's familiar.
You can just call me Lucoa.
--[GEORGIE] Familiar?
--[LUCOA] Yeah.
[GEORGIE] It seems we both have
somewhat unique hobbies, huh?
[LUCOA]
Yeah.