[STUDENTS talking]
[KOBAYASHI] She's been watching
school kids a lot lately.
You think she might
be wanting to go?
Who, Kanna?
Yes, I would assume so.
It's only natural, after all.
Eventually, every dragon
wrestles with ideas like death.
Oh, youth!
Uh. What are you talking about?
Kanna's journey to
eliminate humanity?
[KOBAYASHI]
No, jeez.
I meant "think she might
be wanting to go to school"?
[TOHRU]
Oh, right.
I see stuff about school
on the Internet all the time.
The Internet?
Sure got a hold of you fast.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm.
Hey, Kanna?
[KANNA]
Hmm?
Hey, Kobayashi.
Did you need something?
No, I was just wondering...
Do you want to go to school?
[gasps]
[KANNA]
Kobayashi! Hurry up! Come on!
Kanna, stop!
You should treat Miss Kobayashi
with more respect!
I don't understand why you need
all this just to go to school.
[TOHRU] There's nothing to
understand once you recognize
the obvious conspiracy
between the schools
and the manufacturer.
Total conspiracy.
That's doubtful
on many levels, Tohru.
Not according to the Internet!
[KOBAYASHI] So dragons
fall for online BS, too.
[KOBAYASHI] How about
we pick up the basics first?
[TOHRU, KANNA]
Okay!
Hello, welcome!
[KOBAYASHI]
Yep. This is it.
How funny, these school
supplies haven't changed,
like, even a little
since I was a kid.
--[KANNA] No.
--What, why no?
They're not very cute.
They're wha...?
Wow, Miss Kobayashi.
You're so clueless.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Don't worry 'bout it, though.
I've got this!
[KOBAYASHI]
Why are we here?
Because feathers that
have been plucked from
living birds during this time of
year produce the best pens!
That's creepy.
No...
[KOBAYASHI]
Looks like you're clueless, too.
This doesn't make sense.
Back in our world, practically
everybody uses quill pens.
I want a cute one, though.
A cute one!
Uhh. I think she
wants a cute one.
[TOHRU] Hmm... I heard about
a new store that just opened
outside the shopping district.
It should have cute stuff!
[gasps]
Hello, glitter.
I'm blinded with sparkling.
[KANNA]
Kobayashi, look!
What's this?
How am I supposta use it?
[KOBAYASHI]
You write with it like this.
[KANNA gasps]
You'll be using
a pencil, though, Kanna.
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi! How'd I do?!
[KOBAYASHI]
Uh.
[KANNA]
Kobayashi, look.
What's this thing? It looks
like a dragons mouth to me.
[KOBAYASHI]
It's a stapler.
--[TOHRU screams]
--[KANNA gasps]
Or it's a torture device...
How'd you jump to that?
[KANNA]
And what about this?
C'mon, it's obvious. That is
a tool for slave branding.
You use it to
mark your property.
[gasps]
Oh, Miss Kobayashi!
Will you please
brand me as yours?
No way.
[TOHRU whines]
[KANNA]
Ah. Look, Lady Tohru. A unicorn.
--Mine!
--[giggles]
[TOHRU] If that
unicorn knew about this,
I think it would be very happy.
[KOBAYASHI]
Part of me wants to ask,
but the other part knows better.
[CLERK A]
Thanks so much!
[KANNA sighs]
Not much left to get, now.
Onward, ho!
[KANNA]
Ho!
[TOHRU grunts]
Do we really have to
go here, of all places?
[KOBAYASHI] Sorry,
there's nowhere else close
to us that sells backpacks.
I can appreciate our situation,
but I don't like it.
I can't help but
remember back when--
[KOBAYASHI] Whatever.
We can go by ourselves.
I didn't say I wouldn't go!
[TOHRU growls]
[KANNA gasps]
Well, Kanna? You decide yet?
Uh-huh.
[KOBAYASHI] Surprisingly
normal, considering.
[TOHRU]
Great choice, Kanna.
I had a feeling you'd
go with a cursed backpack
soaked in the blood of humans.
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm.
[KOBAYASHI]
That was her reason?!
[gasps]
[sighs]
[CLERK B]
That'll be 38,000 yen.
[gasps] It's not
made out of gold, is it?
[TOHRU]
Is that too much?
[KOBAYASHI]
No, it's fine...
I'm gonna use my card
to pay for this.
[CLERK A] Of course.
We take all forms of payment.
[gasps]
Hi, how're you?
Miss Kobayashi,
Kanna's gonna pout again
if we go in another
store like this.
[KOBAYASHI]
We don't have a choice.
This is where the school
said we have to go.
[TOHRU]
Conspiracy.
[KOBAYASHI]
Let it go.
[KOBAYASHI] I think these
are the ones on our list.
[TOHRU]
They all seem the same to me.
That's the point.
They want the kids to
all wear the same thing
so they'll all look the same.
Why would they want that?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm. So no one feels different.
Boys, girls, new students.
Everyone is supposed
to be exactly the same
as everyone else.
It's a big deal.
[TOHRU] And what happens
when you're different
from everyone else?
They eliminate you. It sucks.
I know it might be
different for dragons,
but humans aren't that
accepting of people
who are different from them.
That's ludicrous.
Yeah. I completely
agree with you.
The truth is, people
are just terrified.
They fear anything different.
[TOHRU sighs]
I kind of understand.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm. I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to
bring the room down.
You're sweet to worry about me.
Well, Kanna.
Looking forward to school?
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm.
[KOBAYASHI]
All right, once we get home,
we prepare for tomorrow!
[KANNA]
Yay!
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi, that's not fair!
You should be holding
my hand, too!
[KOBAYASHI]
Fine, whatever.
[TOHRU laughs]
[KANNA]
Kobayashi!
Look at me!
[KOBAYASHI]
Whoa! You look amazing!
Super-cute deluxe.
[TOHRU gasps]
[KANNA]
Lady Tohru.
Look! What do you think?
[TOHRU] Kanna. Hey, can I
borrow that for just a second?
[KANNA]
Hmm?
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi!
Check it out!
What do you think of me?
I think jealousy is
not your best look.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU] I can't believe
she wore that backpack
for the rest of the day.
She must be really excited.
I get that she's excited,
but this seems a bit excessive.
[KOBAYASHI] She may be a dragon,
but she's also still a child.
Any idea what Kanna's doing?
She's practicing her writing.
Oh!
So... how's it going?
[KANNA]
Huh...?
[chuckles] Maybe it's time
to stop practicing.
[STUDENTS]
Good morning!
[TEACHER A] Yes, yes,
good morning, children.
Today, I have a brand-new
student and friend
to introduce to you.
This is Kanna Kobayashi.
I'm Kanna, and it's
a pleasure to meet you.
She's adorable!
Where are you from, Kanna?
Ushishir Island.
[DAITANI]
Overseas?
[STUDENTS gasping]
No surprise that
Kanna's classroom introduction
is going over so well.
[KOBAYASHI] Make sure you watch
over Kanna today, okay?
[TOHRU giggles] Don't worry.
Tohru is on the job!
[TEACHER A]
Good. Let's try this one, now.
Kanna? Do you think
you can solve it?
That problem is so lame.
I don't get what she finds
so fascinating about school.
Correct. Very good, Kanna.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KANNA whimpers]
[TOHRU] Such an
inefficient way to learn.
Putting those kids in different
classes based on their abilities
would help all of
them develop faster.
[TOHRU sighs]
Their game seems to be simply
hitting each other with a ball.
Fitting pastime for barbarians.
Kya!
--[grunts]
--[gasps]
[grunts]
Yes! Very good, Kanna!
She's showing them no mercy.
[TA]
Kanna, you're incredible!
You can do anything, huh?
Kanna, do you think
we could be friends?
[KANNA]
Mm.
[MUROI]
Oh, can I be your friend, too?
[KANNA]
Hmm.
The truth is people
are just terrified.
They fear anything different.
[TOHRU] Maybe so,
but they clearly try
to ally themselves
with the strong.
They may be young,
but they're still only human.
[STUDENTS]
Goodbye, have a good evening!
[TEACHER A]
Thank you, kids. You, too!
[SAIKAWA]
Yo, Kanna. Kanna Kobayashi.
[KANNA]
Hmm?
You are getting
way too much attention!
Ugh. Saikawa's acting
like a queen again.
Great, thank you for
making things so clear!
Now, shut up, no one
asked your opinion!
You were saying?
You bet I was!
You really piss me off!
You're so cute I just
want to hug you forever!
I challenge you,
Kanna Kobayashi!
I'll prove to the class that
I'm better than you'll ever be!
[MOTO]
Don't fall for it, Kanna!
Saikawa plays dirty and
she's a big ol' cheater!
Not to mention she's
a sad meanie who'll never
admit she lost anyway.
You shut your
stupid, lying mouth!
You wanna try arm-wrestling me?!
I look weak, but I've won karate
tournaments, so I-- Oh, uh...
I just... I just
wanted to be friends...
Oh, gahwd! I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to make you sad!
The truth is, I just wanna
be friends with you, too!
I swear it! Oh, shoot,
Saikawa, look what you did!
[KIDS]
She is so messed up...
Please don't cry! I have candy!
Want some candy?
Uh-oh! We're not allowed to
bring candy to school, Saikawa!
I said, shut up!
[TOHRU]
Fake crying, huh?
Seems kind of a devious way
to settle things, doncha think?
I would've obliterated them
and been done with it.
[KANNA]
Hmm.
[TOHRU] Why did you decide you
wanted to go to school?
[KANNA] I thought it would be
fun to watch the kids.
Was it fun, though?
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm.
Keep in mind some aspects
might not be too fun.
[KANNA]
Hmm.
[TOHRU] There's no reason
for us to try and be
exactly like the humans.
Living among them doesn't mean
we have to live as them.
You know what I mean?
[KANNA]
I do.
But they're so close by, and we
share our lives with the humans.
[KANNA] Embracing them
just feels a lot better
than hating them.
Embracing them...
I've seen comrades
destroy themselves,
all because acceptance
was too foreign,
so they thought hate
was their only option.
But there's a choice.
And I think, for now, I'm gonna
go with embracing, too.
[KOBAYASHI gulping]
Ah! So how was your first day?
It was really fun.
That's good to hear.
Miss Kobayashi, I fulfilled
my given mission, too!
Please praise me!
You are now praised.
Oh, I almost forgot.
[KOBAYASHI]
For you, Kanna.
[KANNA]
Hmm?
[gasps]
But how...?
It's a congratulations.
You should be able to
hang it on your backpack.
[KANNA whimpers]
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi!
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--What'd you get me?!
What about me,
Miss Kobayashi?! Me?
♪ Ta-dah. ♪
Oh, yay!
[KOBAYASHI]
So pretty...
What are you doing
to your stuff?
I'm labeling it.
They said I was supposed to
put nametags on all my things.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TV GIRL] Call now for
today's special product!
That wasn't too hard.
Huh...?
[hearbeating]
[KOBAYASHI]
Why?
How?
[KOBAYASHI] Why and how
did things get like this?
[KOBAYASHI]
The story starts one day ago.
[LUCOA sips]
This is real good!
You're the best.
[TOHRU]
No, you are.
Sorry I keep dropping by
all the time.
You're checking up
on Tohru, aren't you?
Yeah. How'd you know?
Well. You're not alone.
Uh. I'm bored with this game.
I would like to play something
else, if you don't mind.
Come on, be honest. You're here
to check up on Tohru, too.
[KANNA]
I'm home.
Ooh, you survived another day!
--Oh, no...
--[SAIKAWA sobs]
What happened?
A duel.
[KOBAYASHI]
A duel?
--[gasps]
--I shall assist you.
I shall kill.
[KOBAYASHI]
Calm down, ya delinquents!
It happened earlier
on the way home.
[SAIKAWA]
Kanna.
I decided that, today,
I'll go home with you,
so consider yourself
honored with my presence.
[KANNA] Hmm. You are
very kind, Saikawa.
I like you.
--[SAIKAWA squeals]
--[echoing] I like you.
--[shrieks]
--[KANNA] Hmm?
Today, I'm gonna show you
the best place to play!
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm.
[TEENS yelling]
Well? This place is huge,
but it's kind of a hidden spot,
so no one ever comes here.
[KANNA gasps]
That's the thing you fly with!
[SAIKAWA]
What? Fly?
Yeah. in the clouds.
[SAIKAWA]
Hmm? Sure, sounds fun.
Let's play on the seesaw.
[gasps, screams]
[TEEN B]
Sorry about that, girls.
Be more careful, you idiots!
What's wong? Widdle baby
fwightened by a widdle ball?
Don't be a jerk. We're sorry.
Sometimes, dodgeball gets crazy.
And? Little kids come
here to play, too,
so you should leave if you
can't handle your dumb game.
Nowhere else to go.
[We wouldn't leave if
there was somewhere else.
It's time for the
babies to go home.
[SAIKAWA growls]
For real, dude, who hurt you?
You'll pay.
[TEEN B]
What?
I challenge you to
a dodgeball game tomorrow!
If you lose,
you can't play here!
[TEENS]
Uh...
--[laughing]
--You hear that?!
The infant thinks
she's gonna defeat us!
Yeah, we're not gonna
play with you,
but thanks for the offer--
we appreciate it.
Why, what's wrong? You scared?
Maybe you're afraid you're
gonna get embarrassed
in front of all your nerdy,
loser friends?
Try not being so chicken!
What did you say?
Don't listen to her, man.
[SAIKAWA] Or don't listen
to that mama's boy!
Huh?
Wanna call your mom
to see if she thinks
you can win against us,
mama's boy?
Is that what you need?
"Help me, Mama, help me!"
You are such a brat.
What's wong?
Are the big, bad boys fwightened
by a widdle, baby girl?
Hmph. Pathetic, much?
--[growling]
--Fine, snot nose, bring it on!
Don't throw a fit when you lose!
[SAIKAWA whimpers]
What do I do...?
[KOBAYASHI]
So you picked a fight
and they took you up on it?
[SAIKAWA whines]
How many kids have
agreed to help you out?
About zero.
Saikawa's not very popular.
I know! I'm the worst!
What to do about it...?
I bet you could still
negotiate with them.
No way! I assure you,
they must fight!
Under no circumstances shall
the noble and proud dragon
be taken lightly!
Do you know how to play?
Yes!
I know, as well. I've played
a lot of Explosive Dodgeball.
[KOBAYASHI]
This isn't that kind of game.
Come on, we can do this!
Yeah!
Don't stress.
I'm sure it'll work out.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm...
What's this, squirt?!
Had to call in friends?!
We're not gonna go
easy on ya, now!
[laughs]
[yells]
[SAIKAWA gasps]
Tohru.
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
No killing.
'Kay!
[KOBAYASHI] I knew how
it would end at the start.
From the onset, their
abilities-- Well, their species.
They were on different levels.
This game was above
and beyond one-sided.
[whimpers]
[KOBAYASHI]
It wasn't a win.
It was a massacre.
--[TEEN B] Damn it!
--[TEEN A] That's not fair!
You set us up!
You're gonna regret this!
[KOBAYASHI]
Oof, "beat up" is not his color.
Kanna, your friends
are incredible!
[KANNA] Hmm. You're right,
they're the worst scum ever.
Not untrue, but you
could be more delicate.
[sighs] I could play
this game all day long.
Well, what a coincidence.
Same here.
Yeah, me three.
[TOHRU] I just remembered...
Now, I might be wrong,
but have I yet to win
against the two of you?
Think today's the day?
Probably... no.
Huh, this could be real bad.
I wanna play!
[SAIKAWA]
Huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
From that moment forward...
...the playground
became a battlefield.
[TOHRU]
Rah!
[FAFNIR growls]
[TOHRU growls]
--[SAIKAWA whimpers]
--So many dragons.
Excellent.
[KOBAYASHI] Where did
my peaceful, boring, little life
run off to? Meh, whatever.
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
And that brings us to now.
[sighs]
Don't stress. I'll restore
the playground to normal.
And I'll tweak the memories
of anyone who saw us.
[KOBAYASHI] You're more and
more useful to have around.
[KOBAYASHI] After that,
they took to playing dodgeball
on the regular.
[TOHRU] Pay more attention
to your lower back!
[FAFNIR]
Oh. is this better?
Think "old lady about
to be deserted"!
[KOBAYASHI]
Nailed it again.
[SHIMA]
Look, Kanna!
Isn't it super cute?
Oh... Yeah, that's wicked.
Kanna, over here.
These are so cool!
Oh... Yeah, that's wicked.
Kanna, hey!
Hello, Saikawa, you're wicked.
Okay! Time to start class, kids.
[STUDENTS]
Oh, yeah, that's wicked.
--[whimpers]
--[TEACHER A] What's wicked?
What are they talking about?
[SAIKAWA] Kanna, aren't you glad
we won the dodgeball game?
[KANNA]
Yes.
[SAIKAWA] We almost lost our
right to play at the playground!
--[KANNA] That's okay.
--[SAIKAWA gasps]
[KANNA] I'll be happy anywhere
if I'm with you, Saikawa.
[SAIKAWA squeals]