[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm.
[KANNA]
Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[KANNA]
Here.
A bento lunch?
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm. It's for next week.
I've got a field trip.
Oh!
Make one!
Okay. What kind of
food do you prefer?
[KANNA]
Hmm...
[TOHRU] Don't worry about
that, Miss Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
I can take care of it. Domestic
creativity is kinda my thing!
[KOBAYASHI growls]
Oh? Is that so?
Um, yeah. I'm only
the best there ever was!
[KOBAYASHI]
That's funny,
because I'm even
better than the best.
Well, I'm better than
"even better than the best."
[KOBAYASHI]
Sure.
According to... you.
Care to prove your
so-called betterness,
or are you scared?
Careful there, Tohru.
You're good, but
you're not that good.
Uh-oh. An inciting incident.
[TOHRU, KOBAYASHI]
It's on!
Ready to lose?
[TOHRU, KOBAYASHI]
Three rounds!
Bento Lunch Competition!
Of course you guys would make
a game show set for this.
[FAFNIR]
You'll each make three dishes:
a salad, a main course,
and a dessert.
Use all your skills.
Entertain me!
[KOBAYASHI]
What is your character
even supposed to be anymore?
Ingredients are up to you.
But remember to stay within the
budget as you compete.
We don't wanna strain
Miss Kobayashi's wallet, do we?
[giggles]
--[KOBAYASHI] Hey!
--[LUCOA] Ready?
[squeals]
Begin!
They both really
want to win this.
Who knew Kobayashi cared?
[LUCOA]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm...
[TOHRU, KOBAYASHI]
Finished!
[LUCOA]
First dish: complete!
Let's see.
Contestant Kobayashi appears
to be serving cherry tomatoes.
Did you just throw the match?
You can't possibly
expect to beat a seafood
and paprika Caesar.
I mean, there's no comparison.
[FAFNIR] Agreed.
There's no need to compare.
The winner of
the salad round is...
...Kobayashi.
What?! How'd I lose?!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmph.
[TOHRU]
I can't accept this!
How could my salad extravaganza
lose to two tomatoes?
Calm down. Allow me to explain
your first round failure.
Now, then.
The problem, Contestant Tohru,
is that you were not prepared
because you didn't bother
to find out the definition
of a bento lunch.
There was limited space.
And you made too much!
[TOHRU growls]
Heh.
[squeals]
That's all right.
I'll win next!
--[FAFNIR] Tohru wins.
--[KANNA] Lady Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI]
Bacon and eggs can't lose!
Hamburger's better, though.
But bacon and eggs
are a delicious staple!
[KANNA]
Hamburger's better.
[KOBAYASHI]
No, it's not...
Although, when I was a kid...
...I always asked my
parents to make burgers...
[FAFNIR]
Last round is dessert.
Something in a cup,
or a fruit would work.
You are to bring one item
that has not been cooked.
'Kay.
--[LUCOA] Tohru.
--[gasps]
[LUCOA]
This is rather unusual.
You and Kobayashi
don't normally fight.
No, we don't.
Not ever.
So why...?
[TOHRU]
I'm heading off.
[LUCOA]
Be careful.
[FAFNIR]
This is deplorable.
What do you mean?
I love seeing Tohru like this.
It's refreshing!
It's the final round,
oh, what am I going to get?
Hold on. I know!
Of course. It's perfect!
[TOHRU giggles]
[LUCOA] You realize
this fight only happened
because you've grown
so close to each other.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[LUCOA] I mean,
you're fighting but you're not,
like, fighting-fighting.
Either way, it's not a big deal.
She may be a dragon maid.
but she can be my friend, too.
Excuse me.
You cannot honestly believe that
you and a dragon are equals...
...human?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
Huh?
That's at least how
Tohru and I both feel about it.
Probably why we
fought today, too.
Good grief.
Why is Tohru not back yet?
Close enough to fight. Huh.
This is disgusting.
Huh...? [giggles]
[TOHRU]
I'm back!
Oh! Hi, Miss Kobayashi.
--You're late.
--I'm sorry.
I'm so not gonna lose, now!
[KOBAYASHI]
Really?
Because I'm not
gonna lose either.
[gasps]
Wait. My shoes...
[LUCOA]
Third round complete!
[GROUP gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm? What's that thing?
Why? Would you like to try some?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
Wow!
That's so good!
What is it?
Where do they sell it?
[TOHRU] Um... The shopping
district, I guess?
Did she just do
what I think she did?
[FAFNIR]
Yep.
It's a fruit?
No way. I've never
seen this before.
[TOHRU giggles]
It's official!
You can tell her
that I won now!
[PINK FRUIT growls]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[barking]
[KOBAYASHI screams]
[FAFNIR] Items from the other
world are against the rules.
[giggles]
Oopsie...
[KOBAYASHI yells]
Ugh! Tohru!
[PINK FRUIT howls]
[KOBAYASHI]
Whew, that was awesome. Thanks.
[TOHRU]
Sure!
Just to be clear,
your food's always
been delicious, Tohru.
Jeez, are you
trying to flatter me?
Oh, yeah.
We've got dessert!
[gasps]
What's wrong, Tohru?
Uh...
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Who would've thought
I'd find you hiding out
here of all places...
...Tohru!
Our home...
[ELMA] Have you forgotten
all of our laws?!
Dragons disrupt the order of
this world and are forbidden!
You are to return with me!
[TOHRU] Hmph, I see you're as
boring and persistent as ever.
Surprise. I'm not going back.
[KANNA] Lady Tohru and Lady Elma
are on very bad terms.
Yeah?
They're like cats and dogs.
Oh! Did you learn
that idiom at school?
Good girl.
[KANNA squeals]
[KOBAYASHI]
If you asked me,
they look like they're about
to explode any second.
You think they'll be okay?
[KANNA]
I can't say.
Last time they fought,
three islands disappeared.
[KOBAYASHI]
That's awful!
[ELMA] Hmph. Our power may be
considered equal by some...
...but this time,
I plan on settling the score!
[stomach growls]
Her stomach just
growled like no big whoop.
I'd be mortified, but dragons
don't care about that stuff.
--After all-- [gasps]
--[ELMA whimpers]
[KOBAYASHI] Or maybe not.
She looks embarrassed.
Shut up, human!
You are being very
distracting right now!
[KOBAYASHI] Hmm? Well, you've
got quite the attitude on ya
considering you just
destroyed my home.
[ELMA gasps]
[KOBAYASHI] Maybe you should
follow the laws in this world
before you try protecting it.
Even Tohru wouldn't do
something like this.
[ELMA]
Uh... Sorry...
[KOBAYASHI]
Prob'ly.
[ELMA]
I'm sorry!
Wait. Why do I always
wind up doing the apologizing?!
[KOBAYASHI]
That says a lot.
Hey. She doesn't seem
like a bad person,
so why don't you all get along?
Because we're from
different factions.
Not all dragons are
united in thought.
There's the harmony faction
that values law and order,
the chaos faction that yearns
for chaos and destruction,
and the spectating faction
that doesn't work
with either group
or even each other.
[KOBAYASHI]
Wow.
[TOHRU] Elma belongs to
the harmony faction.
I'm with chaos, obviously.
So we oppose each other.
[KOBAYASHI] Hold up:
you're one of the villains?
[TOHRU]
No, no, that is not true.
I am a good dragon, and I'm
on my very best behavior
in this world.
That sounded a bit forced.
Sorry to interrupt!
But I'm taking you home, Tohru!
By force, if I must.
Yeah? Try it!
I'll eliminate you from this
world and leave no trace
of your filth behind!
Take it somewhere else!
I've prepared another dimension.
We can finish this there.
What's wrong?
[ELMA]
Nothing.
[ELMA] I'm just surprised
to see the fiendish Tohru
listening to a human.
What in this world happened?
[ELMA]
Hurry up!
[TOHRU growls]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hey! You cheated!
Who, me? No, I simply respected
order like she wanted.
It was a peaceful resolution.
Now then,
would you like me to fix
what she so
carelessly destroyed?
[KOBAYASHI] By the way,
where'd you send her?
[TOHRU] The field Kanna and I
played in that one time.
[ELMA]
U-Uh... Uh... Oh, man...
Where am I?
[doorbell rings]
How dare you trick me?!
You actually came back here?
[ELMA] I can't believe you
sent me to another continent!
Can we stop this?
I'm not gonna do anything.
I'll be happy as long as I can
quietly be a maid in this world.
Hey, Tohru?
What's going on?
The freak decided to come back.
[ELMA]
Oh, yeah, I'm the freak?!
You're planning to take over
this world, just admit it!
[TOHRU]
Hmph. You're wrong.
[ELMA] Shut your mouth!
No more excuses!
[stomach growls]
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, you poor thing...
[ELMA groans]
You haven't had any food
to eat since yesterday,
have you?
[ELMA]
I can't...
I'm not from this world...
so I'm not allowed to interfere.
Oh.
Here, something like this
should be all right, yeah?
Come on. Try some.
It's cream bread.
Thank you...
I'll kindly take you
up on the offer.
If only to restore my strength.
[ELMA gasps]
What's this?
It's melting in my mouth!
I think I just ate heaven!
[TOHRU growls]
[ELMA]
All right. I'm energized now!
Time for us to have
that rematch, Tohru!
Or you could go away.
If you do, I'll let you
have all of these.
[ELMA]
Sorry for the intrusion!
[SHOUTA groans]
[SHOUTA]
Too big, way too big...
I'm being crushed...
[PINK FRUIT howls]
Who's this?
[ELMA] I'll be working
with you starting today.
My name is Elma Joui.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
No way!
What the heck is going on?
Why are you here?
I could ask you the same
question, human.
This is my work,
so I get to ask stuff.
This cannot be just a
coincidence, can it?
[ELMA] I'm investigating...
It's cultural standard research.
I wanna see if beings from
other worlds can really
integrate successfully.
That makes sense.
She did say you were with
the harmony faction.
Wait, can you even do this job?
You know you can't use magic.
[ELMA]
Hmph. Don't be silly!
Trust me. I can do human
labor better than any human.
You just watch and learn!
[ELMA]
What the heck is this...?
I don't understand any of it.
What are these bizarre boxes?
And what is everyone
doing with them?
Ooh! I think I did something!
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah. Try this.
[ELMA]
Whoa!
Yep. Then, you push this.
[ELMA]
Apologies, human.
You do some pretty
difficult work.
But I've taken the time to
memorize Romanized character
input and that kind of nonsense,
so I won't fall behind anymore!
Hope not.
I do have a question.
when will I receive compensation
for today's labor?
Oh. That's, uh,
about a month from now.
Do you mean to tell me
I won't receive my pay tomorrow?
No. We total out at
the end of the month,
and today's the first,
so it'll be a while yet.
[ELMA gasps]
Then what do I do for
rent and food in the meantime?
Well, if you commute
from the other world,
I-- [gasps]
Let me guess,
you can't go back.
[ELMA gulps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Right...
I don't possess enough
power to open the gate
between worlds at
will like Tohru can.
[KOBAYASHI] I thought your power
was equal to Tohru's.
It is. I'm just as strong as
her, but in a different way.
Oh. [gasps] Wait here.
I know you've
got a lot on your plate,
but hang in there.
If you're gonna be
working with me,
I'll teach you as much as I can.
Don't want ya making
my life harder.
You have my gratitude.
That's pretty hot,
so be careful.
Later!
[ELMA sighs]
[gasps]
Yummy!
[KOBAYASHI] I probably
should keep quiet
about meeting Elma today.
Hey, guys. I'm home!
[TOHRU]
Welcome back!
Guess what we're
having for dinner--
[sniffs]
[gasps]
What're you doing?
[TOHRU]
There's a strange smell on you.
Is it a dog?
[TOHRU]
No, it's a dragon!
Are you secretly cheating on me?
[KOBAYASHI] Whatever.
Look, so, today at work--
[TOHRU]
Wait, is it an office romance?!
Congrats. You've picked up
another weird phrase.
[TOHRU sobs]
[BEAR growls]
[SHOUTA groans]
Can't breathe...
I can't breathe...
[PINK FRUIT howls]
[ELMA]
Miss Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh?
[ELMA]
Thanks for your help today!
[KOBAYASHI]
You're doing great.
You've learned a lot
about PC operation, huh?
Impressive.
I'm all over this!
Yep. I'm gonna prove
myself to you.
[KOBAYASHI] Good, because you've
still got a ways to go.
[ELMA] Oh, Miss Kobayashi,
let's grab some sweet chestnuts
on the way home!
They're so yummy!
[KOBAYASHI]
Sure, whatever.
Why, you...
[KOBAYASHI] It's been a while
since my last day off.
Ugh, I wanna do nothing.
--Morning! Please excuse me!
--[KOBAYASHI screams]
I'll clean everything
so you can enjoy your day off
in a clean room, Miss Kobayashi!
Does that sound good to you?
Yeah, I mean, I guess.
It's not that I'm
not grateful, but--
Hey! What are you doing?!
[KANNA]
Hmm?
[TOHRU giggles]
What do you think?
When I get serious,
I can make a room spotless!
Except for the sparkling,
of course.
This room's never been so clean!
[TOHRU] It's brand new,
as if Shiva passed through!
[KOBAYASHI]
What about my furniture?
[TOHRU] A space for
relaxation doesn't need
any of that nonsense!
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[TOHRU] Please enjoy sleeping
to your heart's content
in this spacious
and relaxing room!
[KOBAYASHI]
As if I could!
Put it back the way it was!
I swear...
[KANNA]
Kobayashi.
I'm really hungry.
Yeah, I could eat, too.
Let's have breakfast, okay?
Hold it right there!
I'm in charge of breakfast,
be it a full course meal
or an imperial feast!
Oh! Would you like
me to slaughter a cow?
I think I'd prefer
to have something light.
[TOHRU]
Yes! I understand!
Ta-dah! Sandwiches!
[KANNA, KOBAYASHI]
Oh!
They look good.
Wait. This meat...
[TOHRU whimpers]
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru.
Show me your butt, now!
You mean you want me
to satisfy your lust,
and not your appetite?
--[KOBAYASHI] Are you dumb?
--Yes...
[KOBAYASHI]
I knew it!
The tail again?
[KOBAYASHI]
What's going on?
What do you mean?
You're just unusually gung-ho.
You really can't tell
what's wrong?
[KOBAYASHI] I can't. You're
spinning your wheels, though.
It's like you reverted
to how you were
when you first came to me.
--[doorbell rings]
--Oh. Coming!
[KOBAYASHI]
No, it's fine. I'll get it.
Hello?
Good morning, Miss Kobayashi!
How are you?
[KOBAYASHI]
Elma?
What are you here for?
Well. You know I appreciate how
you're always helping me out,
so I decided to bring you
something to say thanks.
What's this?
[ELMA]
A protective charm.
It turned out well, too.
Whaaat? You made this?
So cool. Thanks!
--[TOHRU growls]
--Oh. I get it, now.
[gasps]
Tohru!
Today, I'm taking you back!
Be gone, Elma!
--[KOBAYASHI yelps]
--[gasps]
[screams]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi.
I know that I can
be really selfish.
So, I try to control
myself and put up with it.
But...
I feel like you're being mean.
I work hard, too...
All I want is a lot of praise.
And maybe to have you
pet my head a little bit...
Look, Tohru.
I'm not used to being wanted or
even thought that much about.
[KOBAYASHI] This has never
happened to me before.
I don't have a clue
what to do about it.
[KOBAYASHI]
Human relationships...
I dunno. I've always found
them to be super confusing.
I have a tendency
to put distance
between me and other people.
I've had friends before.
But I never let them
get too close.
[TOHRU sighs]
[KOBAYASHI]
So here.
I mean, um...
I can't make it any
clearer than this, okay?
Take the hint, please.
[TOHRU whimpers]
[TOHRU]
Yes, I'll take the hint...
[ELMA groans]
Oh, right. I can make
you a protective charm, too.
Then, you'll also gain the
protection of evil gods!
It'll be great!
No, thanks.
[SHOUTA grunting]
Huh...?
[gasps]
Why're you so handsy,
Shouta, baby?
[SHOUTA]
Bad demon!
[ELMA]
Tohru! You're too dangerous!
You know that yourself!
[TOHRU]
Elma, you're too-- Uh...
[ELMA]
What?
[TOHRU] For now, please put down
the cream bread you're holding.
[ELMA]
How come? They're so yummy!
[TOHRU]
I don't care.