Good morning!
Your coffee's ready,
Miss Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
Just what I needed. Thanks.
Kanna, you'll have to eat
faster than that
if you wanna be on time.
'Kay.
[TOHRU]
I made you some hot milk.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm?
I'm sure you have
something particular
you want for dinner, yeah?
Hmm... Not really.
Anything works for me!
Except for that.
[gasps]
Still no tail?
Tohru, what about you?
What would you like to eat?
What would I like?
Uh... Omurice , I guess.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yummy!
For real?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yes, let's do that!
It's gonna be delicious, right?
You betcha!
Tohru's on it!
So, what time do you
expect to be
getting home this evening?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hopefully not too late.
[sighs]
I hope that, too.
[KANNA]
See you later, Lady Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm heading out, too.
[TOHRU]
See ya! Have a good day!
All right! Here I go!
Time to get my maid on!
[TOHRU]
Cleaning, cleaning, la la la.
♪ Beat the dust
and de-de-destroy it! ♪
♪ No trash or fleck of dust
will be left behind! ♪
♪ Now clean, now clean
clean everything. ♪
Ugh! What?
Oh, no, you did not.
Death, death,
death to the world!
Oh! Um...
Bathroom, check!
Bedrooms, check!
Entrance, check!
Rooster, check!
Living room, check!
--[sighs]
--[machine chimes]
Classic Tohru! Perfect
timing on the laundry, too!
I bet these
will dry fairly quickly
with all this sunshine today.
[doorbell rings]
Coming!
Just need your stamp, please.
Thank you for
all your hard work.
[DELIVERY A]
You're welcome. Thank you!
Must be that cushion
to help with
Miss Kobayashi's
lower back pain.
Good.
I finished everything
I needed to.
All that's left now is to
make the omurice for dinner.
Mm. Mmm!
This is all for Miss Kobayashi.
It's gonna be delicious, right?
Tonight's dinner will be
the best omurice ever!
I need to do a trial run.
--[water running]
--[chop, chop]
[sizzling]
[TOHRU]
Not too bad!
[giggles]
Good work, me.
Fluffy, juicy eggs,
hot rice with ketchup,
and all at restaurant quality.
As for the taste?
[TOHRU]
Average?!
It's not that it tastes bad,
it's just that...
Hmm...
It's gonna be delicious, right?
[gasps]
It's just that I want it to be
more special than average.
And she made it clear
she didn't want any of my tail.
[doorbell rings]
[TOHRU]
Coming!
Hey.
Oh, hi! What are you
doing here, Lucoa?
[LUCOA]
To see you and bring these.
Want some snacks?
[TOHRU]
Duh. Thank you!
[giggles]
[TOHRU]
What are you wearing that for?
Oh, those pesky patriarchal
societal demands
were getting on my nerves,
so I changed clothes.
[TOHRU] Give it a week, they'll
be begging you to change back.
[LUCOA]
Huh?
[TOHRU]
You can come on in if you want.
[LUCOA]
Okay, I think I will. Thank you!
[sighs]
No wonder that little shop
had such awesome reviews.
Would you like me
to make you some more tea?
Oh. No, I gotta go,
thanks, though.
Sure! I was just...
I was in the middle of making
trial batches of omurice
for Miss Kobayashi
for dinner, and...
Well, do you know
any cooking techniques
that might make it
taste a bit better?
Huh. Making omurice better?
Mmm...
The simplest thing
I can think of to do
is to use the best
ingredients you can find.
Yes, that's brilliant!
See ya later!
Thanks for the tea,
it was heavenly.
I'm sure you meant that
as a compliment.
The best ingredients.
[TOHRU groans]
[TOHRU]
It's so expensive.
Let's see. That plus...
...the best rice,
vegetables, and eggs.
Uh! Wait. I'm over budget?!
Are you shopping for
dinner tonight, Tohru?
Oh. Mister Tatsuta.
Yes, but this chicken is
expensive, don't you think?
[laughing]
Well, that's because it's
locally raised,
free-range, and organic.
[TOHRU] I don't suppose
you could give me a discount?
[BUTCHER A] Sorry, it's already
priced as low as I can go.
[TOHRU]
Not even a little discount?
[BUTCHER A] I can't.
If I go any lower than this,
I'll be losing money.
[TOHRU]
I understand.
[BUTCHER A]
But I do want to thank you
for doing the Christmas show.
So I could give you
some off on these cuts.
[TOHRU]
Average?!
Average cuts
would defeat the point.
The point of what?
It's gonna be delicious, right?
I have no other options.
[TOHRU]
Hereabouts should be good.
I'm back from school!
[TOHRU]
Welcome home, Kanna!
Lady Tohru. What'd you do?
I picked up ingredients
for omurice .
And you had to
go back to do that?
Just for a second.
Goodness.
So, whose eggs are these?
Oh, those? I got them
from Gullinkambi's nest.
Really? The rooster who is
Valhalla's alarm clock?
--Yep.
--Doo-a-doodle-cock!
[EINHERJAR]
They're unbelievably good!
[TOHRU]
They are?
An Einhairjar told me they were
the best quality eggs
in anywhere ever.
And this?
[TOHRU]
That's uh.
That's fresh spring water
from an elven village.
I plan to use it
to boil the rice.
It's pure!
Only problem is I've fought
with the elves before.
So I kinda snuck in and took it.
[KANNA] Wow. They have every
right to kill you over that.
I also grabbed some meat
from bull demons.
As well as fruits that are
in season over there.
Where did you get
the rice and vegetables?
I thought it would be best
to just use the ones
they already have here.
Good call.
The rice in this world
is out of this world.
Yeah, because
they're using magic.
Apparently, it's what's known as
"selective breeding."
I should see if I could
get someone to teach me
that incantation sometime.
Now, then.
Time to get this
cooking party started!
Will you help me
get this perfect, Kanna?
[KANNA]
Yeah!
[LUCOA]
Growl!
--[LUCOA] Roar! Growl, growl!
--Out with bad demon,
--and in with good blessings!
[LUCOA]
Roar!
--[LUCOA] Roar!
--[SHOUTA] Out with bad demon,
--[LUCOA] Growl, growl, roar!
--and in with good blessings!
[LUCOA]
Growl, growl, roar!
[sighs]
--Lucoa!
--Huh?
--[CAT A meows]
--What's wrong?
Was Shouta-baby
worried about me?
No, he wasn't!
Shut up!
[LUCOA]
Awwwww.
[KOBAYASHI]
Ugh, I'm so exhausted.
Oh. That's right.
Tonight's dinner is omurice .
That was the first normal
meal Tohru cooked me,
now that I think about it.
Dinner's ready, Miss Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI] She presented it
to me with such confidence.
And it was pretty good, too.
Before that, everything
she made was so weird.
Either way, it's been nice.
I honestly can't remember the
last time someone was willing
to cook for me at all, much less
with that level of excitement.
I remember telling her
the omurice was just okay.
Today, I won't.
I'll tell her...
that it's good.
[WORKER A]
Hey, hurry up and get it to me!
[WORKER B] Forget about that,
you need to fix this error!
Kobayashi!
It's almost deadline time!
[KOBAYASHI]
I know!
Kobayashi! Error alert!
[KOBAYASHI]
Fixing them now, sir.
Kobayashi! Help over here.
[KOBAYASHI]
On my way, sir!
Kobayashi! Kobayashi! Kobayashi!
Shut up!
Gimme another one!
Coming up.
[laughing]
There goes my stop!
I don't know where I'm going to!
[laughing]
The mountain sounds good.
Air's clear here.
[KOBAYASHI shouting]
What? Bears! Bring it on!
Tasty beary bears!
[laughing]
Oh man! It's pitch dark
black! Can't see!
[KOBAYASHI]
Ow.
[TOHRU growls]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
You shall not pass!
[hiccups]
Huh?
[TOHRU] Human. Out of
what hole dids't thou crawl?
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh...?
Whoa! A dragon, ooh, hug me!
Ow!
[TOHRU]
Depart, insolent human!
Otherwise, I shall eat you!
[TOHRU] Alas. I am
going to die, as well.
How tragic it is
the last being I meet
is a pathetic human.
Hey, do you ever get bored
listening to yourself talk?
Is froufrou lingo
like, your thing?
[TOHRU]
How dare you?
You want me to pull that out?
[TOHRU]
Huh? Well...
[KOBAYASHI hiccups]
[TOHRU]
No! You fool!
If a mere human touches God's
sword, their mind shall be torn.
[KOBAYASHI]
I dunno about all that.
But if God exists, then...
...he should exteeeend...
--[TOHRU] No. No, no, no.
--...my stupid deadline...
--...right now!
[KOBAYASHI]
Aaah!
I know this is
just my dream, but...
...why does a dragon gotta be
such a big, jerk-baby?!
[TOHRU] Apologies.
You saved me regardless,
and it is appreciated.
I was defeated in battle
with the gods,
and barely escaped
to this world.
I imagine you only managed
to remove that sword
because you lack faith.
I am truly grateful.
Don't judge
on prejudices- yours!
Boop, boop, boop.
Wanna drink?
Sure you do!
Drink with me, dragon!
Drink with me,
and listen to my story!
[sobbing]
Why won't you drink?
[TOHRU groans]
[KOBAYASHI]
Uh.
[hiccups]
[KOBAYASHI]
So you're a lady dragon, then?
Yes. I am female.
To be honest, I detest
using this spell, but...
[KOBAYASHI]
Ooh! You're down to drank!
Yay! Just us girls, let's go!
[TOHRU]
You're a girl?
Yes, Rude Dragon!
[TOHRU]
I'm sorry.
[KOBAYASHI] You're gonna have
to let me fondle your tits.
It's okay to be curious
even though society
pressures me to say I'm not!
--[TOHRU] Okay.
--[KOBAYASHI] I can?
For real!
I work hard and for what?
I'm telling ya, this whole
world is unfair, man!
Yeah, keep preaching sister!
Let me bring an end
to this place for you!
And what the hell?
Your subordinate, your problem!
[screams]
Do not assume all dragons
are really lolicons
who randomly demand
villages' virgin daughters!
Gaahhh!
[BOTH laughing]
[burps]
Nights like this are when
I wonder why I'm all alone.
[hiccups]
Me, too.
But I truly am alone here.
There's no one.
Just me.
[KOBAYASHI]
Do you have anywhere to go?
[TOHRU]
No.
But to be fair, I have been
alone from the start.
Huh. So, wanna stay
with me, dragon?
[TOHRU sobbing]
Yes, I do!
You can be my maid!
Your what?
Listen! We're not talking about
just a simple servant here!
Seriously, you can have
house maids, laundry maids,
all kinds of maids.
And it takes major training--
it's not all those posers
at maid cafés!
--[KOBAYASHI] Oh.
--[TOHRU] Eh?
My name's Kobayashi.
My name's Tohru.
Hello, Tohru!
Look, I don't mean
to shade maid cafés,
they're fine for what they are,
but they help contribute
to the maid profession
being taken lightly.
[VOICE A]
Oborozuka. Oborozuka.
[KOBAYASHI]
Crazy.
I feel like I dreamt about
something important.
--[KOBAYASHI] I'm home.
--[KANNA] Kobayashi!
[TOHRU]
Yay! Welcome back home!
We just finished the omurice !
[KANNA]
I helped make it!
Oh!
It's gonna be great!
[KOBAYASHI]
The omurice was delicious.
But I was so busy pointing out
all the obvious issues.
I sorta forgot to tell her
how good it was.
[keyboard keys clicking]
Thanks for coming
out of nowhere, rain!
I'm back!
Remember this morning when
they said, "No chance of rain."
[FAFNIR]
Takiya, help me.
It's guerrilla warfare.
Time to ambush.
[TAKIYA]
Yeah, sure.
[TOHRU]
Hmm.
I guess we'll be having this
for lunch for a while.
[VOICE B] He's so cute!
Is it okay if I pet him?
[VOICE C]
Of course!
[DOG panting]
Good grief, that's ridiculous.
Come on. You're squishing us!
What simple pets, giving such
affection to their humans.
Yeah, you're one to talk.
--Kanna.
--No.
[TOHRU]
Groans.
Speaking of the
nearness of me,
were there any humans
in your old world
you were particularly close to?
Humans in my world?
I guess so, kinda.
There is one human
I can think of.
You could say
I associated with them,
if only for a little while.
Really? What were they like?
[TOHRU]
Heh. If you'll excuse me.
I'm going to have to talk
a lot about myself now.
[TOHRU] I first met that
human in a deserted village
that was in ruins.
[TOHRU] This should work
as my home for a while.
[TOHRU]
Uh!
It's rare to encounter
a dragon in a place like this!
I'm actually only here
to hide out, myself.
Do you mind if I
stay a short time?
[TOHRU]
You're a bandit?
Yes, that's right.
I mistook a noble
for a merchant
and attacked their party.
Now, I'm on the run!
My comrades have been captured,
leaving me alone.
So I'm currently
debating my options
on where I should go next.
[TOHRU]
Do you believe I care?
I could save you time
and kill you.
[HUMAN A laughing]
[TOHRU]
How dare you laugh at me!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I mean no offense, Dragon,
but you're not very used to
threatening people, are you?
[TOHRU]
Excuse me?
It's just not
very convincing, sorry!
[TOHRU]
'Tis not just a threat, human!
See what I mean?
[TOHRU growls]
[HUMAN A]
So. It's okay, then?
You'll let me stay for a while?
Eeeh!
--[TOHRU] Do as you please.
--[HUMAN A] Thank you!
[TOHRU]
Thinking back on it now,
I could've just left
and found somewhere else.
But in that moment...
I guess...
I couldn't allow myself
to yield to a human.
[HUMAN A] Hey, so...
you're a dragon, right?
What's that kind of life like?
[TOHRU]
What do you mean?
You know, like how you can fly.
And you possess so much power
you'll pretty much
never lose a fight.
I wish I knew what it
was like to live so freely.
Must be wondrous.
Uh! Hey! I'm talking!
[TOHRU] At the time,
I found myself thinking.
What was my freedom like?
I had never thought of myself
as "free" before then.
I was born with
the chaos faction.
I lived with chaos,
and I fought the divine.
If that all ended,
would I be free?
Would it ever end?
Even if it did end, and I was
free, what would I do?
[TOHRU] What would you do
if you had my freedom?
[HUMAN A]
Hmm? I'd be a maid!
--[TOHRU] A maid?
--Yes! A maid.
I'd wear the cutest maid outfit.
I'd greet every single guest
with my very best smile,
and I would totally
fall in love with my master.
[TOHRU] You would willingly
enslave yourself?
[HUMAN A] Yep! But
that's kinda the point!
I'd get to have a choice!
Mine!
Had I chosen it, my life would
be so different, y'know?
Even now, if I could
make my own decision
between the two options.
At least I could
choose to stay a bandit
or choose to be a slave.
[TOHRU]
I see.
[HUMAN A]
Right?
[TOHRU]
I realized that I had never made
my own choice, either.
But I hadn't been as
bothered by it as she was.
[TOHRU] Since there wasn't
anyone else I wanted to see,
I allowed the girl to stay and
chatted with her for a while.
[HUMAN A]
I'm probably good to go.
[TOHRU]
You are leaving?
[HUMAN A] Mhmm. I think
I'll cross over the mountains
and see if I can get into
a nation bordering this one.
I'm sure something'll
work out for me.
Oh, do you mind?
Can I ride you real quick?
[TOHRU]
Of course not!
I shall never let
a human ride me!
Selfish! Selfish!
[TOHRU] Say what you will.
I would die first!
[laughing]
I hope to see you again.
Goodbye, Dragon!
And thank you.
[TOHRU]
For what?
[HUMAN A]
For spending time with me.
[TOHRU]
She left after that.
The annoying human
was finally gone.
At least, that's how
I should have felt.
But instead,
I felt a little sad.
I'm sure.
Do you think that person
might have something to do with
why you decided
to become my maid?
[TOHRU]
Probably.
I don't say this sort
of thing often, but
I don't think I'd mind
seeing that human again.
[KOBAYASHI]
I get that.
[TOHRU]
Yeah?
Oh, by the way, Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI] The way you used to
talk sounds like an old man.
Huh? Well, I think it's fancy!
[KOBAYASHI]
Whatever.
[HUMAN A]
How nice.
The weather's perfect.
[ELMA]
Oooh. I think I get that.
[sighs]
I've thoroughly
blended in to this world.
Meh. Is what it is.
[KOBAYASHI] Tohru, do you think
that bandit girl is still alive?
[TOHRU]
Who knows? But if she is,
I bet she's
serving as a maid.
[KOBAYASHI]
Same as you, then.
[TOHRU]
Exactly.
[KOBAYASHI]
Either way, I hope she's well.
[TOHRU]
I hope so, too.