Wow!
The beaches in
this world are pretty.
Real pretty!
With so many people, don't you
wanna just mow 'em all down
at once, Miss Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Can't say I do.
The ocean here's salty?
Yep, sure is.
That's the same, then.
[LUCOA] My favorite thing about
swimsuits is that you can
show off as much
flesh as you want!
[KOBAYASHI]
Not accurate or appropriate.
For real?
Shouta, baby, what do you think?
--[screams]
--[SHOUTA] So aggressive!
[sighs]
Way less scary.
Not a compliment,
but thanks for the effort, kid.
[STAFFER A]
Excuse me, ma'am.
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--Yeah?
I need you to come with me--
your swimsuit is way too skimpy.
Hey! Hold on!
[KOBAYASHI] Well, that
was entirely expected.
[sighs]
They finally let me back out!
Why did you think
to bring an extra suit?
I didn't. These're scales.
You guys wearing
scale suits, too?
They're cute.
I'll give you that.
[TOHRU] Thanks! We looked
up designs on the Internet.
Aren't you jealous?
[KOBAYASHI]
Of the suit? No.
Of what's filling it out? Yes.
I wanna go play, please.
Looks like we're
gonna go play for a little bit.
What'll you do here
without us, though?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm... Probably nothing.
What's the matter,
Miss Kobayashi?
You haven't seemed
excited all day.
There's a good reason for that.
To be honest, I'm not
a huge fan of the beach.
Huh?!
I think you might've
been too honest.
Whatever. It's hot, I burn,
and sand gets everywhere.
I couldn't agree more.
I prefer to be indoors, myself.
If that's true,
then why agree to come out
to a beach with us?
I have my reasons!
Primarily, I don't have a whole
lot going on this summer.
On top of that, my manager asked
me if I would look after Shouta.
I figured going along with
you guys was the path
of least resistance.
Wait, I get it. This is
a tsundere thing, am I right?
Not even a little.
I wanna go play now, please.
Oh, right, gotcha. Just a sec.
Uhh...
[screams]
Sunscreen! First things first!
"I'm an inferior human
'cause my skin gets damaged
by the sun without this stuff!"
Okay, let me start with you,
Miss Kobayashi!
Get weird and get fired.
[gasps]
Here you go, Shouta, baby.
You don't mind, do you?
Perfect. Have at it!
[whimpers]
C'mon.
[SHOUTA]
No, I can't!
Boo. Then let's switch!
[laughs]
[SHOUTA gasps]
All right. Is that good?
What? Is what good?! [whimpers]
[LUCOA]
Am I coating you good?
[SHOUTA growls]
I knew it. You are a demon!
Why...?
[SHOUTA] Bad demon, bad!
Stop trying to seduce me!
Lucoa, um...
At this point, you might
as well start acting like
you're a demon.
I want to play now, please.
How about watermelon splitting?
[KANNA]
I'm in.
[TOHRU]
Go a little farther right!
[LUCOA] No, too far,
too far. Go back left.
[TOHRU] Go straight.
That's right. Okay, stop.
[KANNA grunts]
[GROUP yells]
--Yay.
--Good job, Kanna!
You obliterated
every last trace of it.
Well. Whaddaya gonna do?
[KANNA]
I wanna swim, now!
Heck yeah. I wanna swim, too!
Hey, be sure
that you don't go too far out.
What? How come?
[KOBAYASHI]
It's dangerous.
Yeah. I guess you're
right about that, so okay.
Not too far.
I still remember that time
Leviathan almost killed me,
and I don't want that.
What did you do?
I was too far away
to see him clearly,
so I accidentally
called him Rahab.
[LEVIATHAN]
Why, you...!
My point was less
dragon rage and more,
"don't drown."
Oh, yeah, I totally
forgot humans don't have
the ability to
breathe under water.
Stupid and inferior.
[KOBAYASHI]
You can breathe under water?
Well, of course!
There's nothing like swimming to
your heart's content, you know?
[KOBAYASHI]
What, does she have gills now?
Lady Tohru,
let's race to the area there.
Sure, I think that's reasonable.
Do you mind giving us the
signal, Miss Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Okay. On your marks, get set.
Go!
[gasps] I forgot to remind
them to hold back.
[TOHRU]
Not too bad, Kanna.
[KANNA]
Impressive, Lady Tohru.
[TOHRU]
I win!
That was too far!
[BOTH]
We know. We're sorry.
[sighs] Well, it's whatever.
Are you ready for lunch?
[BOTH gasp]
Yeah!
[GROUP]
Thank you. It was delicious!
[KANNA]
What's next, Lady Tohru?
[TOHRU]
I dunno.
Miss Kobayashi,
what do you--
What's wrong, Miss Kobayashi?
Oh. Nothing.
Just realized that old man
hasn't changed much
since the last time I saw him.
[TOHRU]
When was that?
[KOBAYASHI]
Back when I was a little kid.
I used to come to this beach
with my family a lot.
[TOHRU]
Family...
[TOHRU'S FATHER]
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
[KOBAYASHI]
You okay?
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[TOHRU]
I'm fine.
Miss Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Could you please tell me
more about your family?
I mean, that is if you
don't mind telling me.
Huh?
I'd appreciate it.
Yeah, okay, sure.
I think we were
a normal family.
Y'know, for the most part.
I felt like I was raised
normally, at least.
They got me through
college, so I can't complain.
After that, though,
I left home to go to work.
I call my parents every now
and then to catch up.
Tell 'em how I'm doing,
stuff like that.
I, uh, I haven't seen
them in a while now, though.
And is that
considered normal for
a human family in this world?
I guess.
[TOHRU]
Normal, huh?
Then, why would she welcome
a dragon into her home?
And if she's from
a normal family,
why aren't most humans as
accepting as Miss Kobayashi?
I don't get it.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe humans of this world
actually could accept dragons.
[TOHRU'S FATHER]
Kill them! Humans are evil!
Kill them all!
[KOBAYASHI]
You sure you're okay?
[TOHRU gasps]
Yeah. Don't worry.
I'm fine!
I just, I feel listless today.
I'm not used
to having low energy.
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru.
[TOHRU]
Uh?
Can I ride you?
[TOHRU gasps]
[GROUP yells]
[gasping, yelling]
[KOBAYASHI]
This is incredible!
[TOHRU] I'm glad you're
having fun! I am, too!
[KOBAYASHI]
All right.
Tohru.
Do you think you're
starting to get homesick?
[TOHRU]
No, not particularly.
Well, that makes
one of us, then.
Thanks to our discussion,
I feel like I need to
go visit my parents.
[TOHRU] I'd like to see my
parents every now and then.
But it's no big deal.
No? Then what's
really bugging you?
[TOHRU] I thought for a
second about introducing you
to my parents.
You can do that if you want.
[TOHRU]
No, I can't.
Why not?
[TOHRU] Because I'm
pretty sure they'd kill you.
Does seem excessive,
but, that's most likely
just common sense in
your world, huh?
[TOHRU]
For sure.
From my parents' point of view,
I'm about as far from normal
as you can get.
They don't think I have any
common sense to speak of.
It's makes me sad.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm...
[KOBAYASHI] Talking to Tohru
about this kind of stuff
is intense. And yeah.
That makes me sad, too.
[KOBAYASHI] Certainly drives
home the difference between
understanding words and
understanding each other.
I've never really considered
how completely different
our worlds are.
Although, I bet that's
why I always feel like
I need to cherish the time we
get to spend together so much.
You know what?
That sounds an awful lot like
independence to me.
[TOHRU]
Independence?
Yep. You've developed your own
unique set of values, Tohru.
[TOHRU] So then, you mean
I've become an adult?
[KOBAYASHI] Who knows?
I'm not even sure about me.
Most people don't try to become
adults, they just reach a point
where they realize they can't
stay children any longer.
[TOHRU] Ooh, that's deep,
Miss Kobayashi!
Got one!
[KOBAYASHI]
Tiny...
[TOHRU chuckles]
[KOBAYASHI]
Ready to head back?
[TOHRU]
Sure!
[TOHRU, KANNA]
Dragon fireworks?
That's right.
Won 'em in a lottery at
the shopping district.
[BOTH gasp]
[KANNA]
That's it?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yep.
[TOHRU gasps] A real dragon is
way cooler than that crap!
[inhales]
[KANNA gasps]
Very impressive, Lady Tohru.
[TOHRU (muffled)]
See! See!
How's that, Miss Kobayashi,
how's that?!
What?
I can't understand anything
you're saying right now.
[gasps]
What on Earth is that?
[KOBAYASHI]
The admission line for Comiket.
And the reason we're
around all these people
is to provide cover
for Mister Takiya?
Not cover. We just came to help.
Apparently, his other
two assistants collapsed.
Ooh, I'm all over this!
With my power, I'll be able to
exterminate them in no time!
Do not.
[TOHRU] By the way, was leaving
Kanna behind a good idea?
[KOBAYASHI]
There's a lot of stuff here
children shouldn't see.
Thanks, guys! You're saving me!
I'm screwed without help.
It's cool. I kinda
owe you a few anyway.
I would have thought
you'd ask Fafnir
to help you out with this.
Uh, he's
participating as a circle.
Huh?!
What? He's a circle?
Sorta?
A circle's a group
of people like us.
We sell the art we
make to other fans.
It's way fun.
That makes sense.
But why would Fafnir ever
do anything like that?
[TAKIYA] I recommended all kinds
of anime and games to him.
At some point he
started drawing his own.
[TOHRU] He really seems
to be getting into this world.
Kobayashi, you can handle sales.
Tohru, I'd really appreciate it
if you could deal with the line.
Sure thing.
[TOHRU]
Hmph. All right. Fine.
[VOICE A] Attention, Ladies and
Gentlemen, as of this moment,
the third day of Comic Market
has officially begun!
Guys? What's going on?
[STAFFER B]
No running in the hall, please.
[gasps]
[STAFFER B]
Please do not run.
[TOHRU]
This is bizarre.
It's like they can all barely
contain themselves!
Something powerful is holding
back their selfish desires.
What in the world?
[GUY A]
The new one, please.
[KOBAYASHI]
Cash or charge?
Cash! Thank you very much.
[GUY B] The new and
the previous one, please.
[TOHRU] The end of the line
for Water Dragon Shrine
starts right here!
Up there, could you guys
group closer together, please?
[sighs]
[TOHRU] Hard to believe tens
of thousands of individuals
are able to take such
unified actions without
any prior exercises or training.
An extremely powerful
energy must be at work.
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
Uh, excuse me.
Who, me?
Yeah, are you,
by chance, a cosplayer?
No, by choice, I'm not.
Right, gotcha. I'm sorry.
Well, you look awesome.
I figured you were from
abroad or something.
I happen to be a
real maid wearing a uniform.
Uh. Oh, I get it now.
You're just in character.
How fun!
You're wrong. I'm the real deal.
Hey, I understand. It's policy.
If you don't mind,
I promise to come by
and take your
picture later, okay?
No, wait! I told you
that I'm real!
The end of the line for
Water Dragon Shrine starts here!
[whines]
[TOHRU]
These people are passionate.
Meanwhile, I'm over
here feeling like
I'm in a firedrake's stomach.
Thank you, sir. Have a good one!
[TOHRU] I can't believe
it's this insane.
Comiket is not
to be underestimated.
Still, though...
What in the world could be
attracting this many people
and keeping them all in check?
It's beyond me...
and kinda terrifying.
--[TAKIYA] Tohru!
--Oh?
Thank you so much for your help!
--Need a drink?
--[gasps]
I've been waiting for this!
[gulping]
[KANNA]
Bug collecting.
[cicada chirping]
Cicada...
...is...
...very...
...crunchy.
[TOHRU]
Let's see...
We should be getting close.
What are you looking for?
Trying to find Fafnir.
I figured I should stop by and
say hi while I'm on my break.
If you say anything,
I'll kill you.
Don't be fussy. Besides,
you're the one who looks dead.
It's no fun, but this is what
it's like for first-timers.
Mind if I, um,
look at your book?
[FAFNIR]
Heh. Help yourself.
[TOHRU]
"Curse Anthology."
[gasps]
You-- Fafnir!
You've printed real,
effective curses!
You even tell how
to inflict them!
You could curse someone
to death if you read this aloud!
You what?
[TOHRU]
That's all you're charging?!
Wow, talk about a bargain.
So, uh, maybe...
you shouldn't be
selling that to people.
There are so many
cosplayers here.
I think that's my favorite part.
It's fun to watch.
You'd be surprised
how many races from my world
are represented by these humans.
[KOBAYASHI] For them,
it's more about pretending to be
characters from anime and manga.
If you wanted to,
you could totally do that.
I am a proper maid, thank you!
No matter how you dress me up,
I will always be
your loyal sex slave.
Uh... That's not proper or maid.
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
What's up?
There's a goblin, a witch,
and a sahuagin over there.
[KOBAYASHI]
Wonder what they're from.
Nothing. They're real.
Huh?
They're not dressed up in
costumes, and they're not human.
Huh?!
Excuse me? Yes, hello.
I just had a real quick question
for the three of you.
Oh, hi. Can I assume
you're like us?
Yes. I was wondering
what you're doing here?
I like to come to these
to spread my wings.
[GOBLIN]
Same here.
I normally live my life
disguised as a human.
But being able to come
to events like this gives me
a chance to enjoy
my real form.
I see that.
Why not take a chance
and join us, dear?
You can let your real form be
seen while also being safe!
No. That'd be impossible.
I mean, I'm a dragon.
[GROUP gasps]
Dragon?!
Yes?
You're a real damn monster?
I guess?
And you... You could eat
us all if you wanted?
Huh?
--[MONSTERS] Run!
--[STAFFER B] No running!
[KOBAYASHI] Dragons must
do some crazy stuff.
[TOHRU]
Don't believe them...
Huh?
When dragons get hungry,
we only eat as much as
necessary to survive.
And this world is survival of
the fittest anyway!
So you're not denying anything,
just explaining it?
[STAFFER A] Hey, you!
Could you come with me, please?
You're costume's too skimpy.
Did you not read the
participant's guide?
[TOHRU] I didn't expect
Lucoa to show up.
[LUCOA]
Hey...
[KOBAYASHI]
Skimpy is as skimpy does.
Now that I look closer,
there's more than
I first thought.
Beings in their
true form, I mean.
Are there a lot?
Yes.
Those that've had a greater
presence while they were here
have left records of
their stays in this world
on several different
levels for tourists.
Like Fafnir and Lucoa.
I'm sure you've heard of some.
I, umm... I think--
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
I think, that...
I wanna be in my real form.
At least partly, just for a bit.
Please...?
As long as you can
do it and stay out of trouble.
It's fine with me.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Sorry that took so long!
[gasps] Can I take your
picture like that?
[TOHRU giggles]
Yes!
Excuse me!
Can I take one, too?
[PHOTOGRAPHER C]
Hey, me, too!
[TOHRU]
Uh?
[PHOTOGRAPHER D] Over here!
Can you look this way please?
[PHOTOGRAPHER E]
Look over here, next, please!
[KOBAYASHI]
Crap, our break's almost over.
[PHOTOGRAPHER F] Stay there and
just move your head this way!
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, well.
[sighs]
See? Told ya! I came for
your pic like I promised!
Right. Hello. How's it going?
Uh, to be honest,
it's been going
pretty rough for me.
But I'm hanging in there!
Hey, so.
From my perspective, it seems
like everyone in this place
has been drawn here by
something with a lot of power.
Do you have any idea
what that something might be?
Uh...
I'm not sure, but uh...
Well, it's for sure special.
And it's only right here
in this moment.
Might as well make
the most of it.
[gasps]
Whatever this is, it's making
a lot of people happy.
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
Yes, you're right.
Might as well
make the most of it.
[PHOTOGRAPHER G]
Hey, buddy.
Will you take
the picture already?
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Uh-oh! Geh!
Don't tell me there's
another line forming?
[VOICE A]
As of right now,
Comic Market 90
is officially over.
Thank you everyone
for your participation.
We hope to see you
all again in the winter
for the next epic Comiket!
Thank you again!
[TOHRU pants]
I'm back. [sighs]
You survived!
And don't worry, we managed
fine without you after lunch.
I'm so sorry.
I honestly never
intended to ditch you.
I know, it's fine.
Oh, hey, Fafnir,
how'd your book sell?
[FAFNIR growls]
Apparently, not all that well.
All right, so what did you think
of your first ever Comiket?
[TOHRU]
Hmm? Well, let's see...
Mainly, it just reconfirmed
my love for you,
Miss Kobayashi.
Huh?
[TOHRU giggles]
Thank you, ladies!
You were a huge help today.
Like, the best assistants ever!
And if it's no trouble,
I'd love your help
again this winter!
[screams]
Hell no, I'm done with this!
[TAKIYA]
Huh...?
[laughs]
What do you think we should
print for our next thin book?
[GOBLIN]
How about a dragon maid girl?
That sounds great!
So they gave you "free studies"?
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm. It's my summer homework.
What do you think I should do?
Well, if I were you.
I would probably choose
something mysterious.
Something that I'd like
to know more about
so I didn't get bored with it.
[KANNA]
Okay. That makes sense.
Whatcha doing, Kanna?
Studying you. Act natural.
Huh? [groans]
[TAKIYA] You know, Kobayashi,
there's a lot of talk
about Tohru on the Internet.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah, I bet.
[TAKIYA]
They mentioned you, too.
They said there was a sales lady
with dead-fish eyes.
[KOBAYASHI]
Sorry 'bout that.
[TAKIYA] And they got
turned on by those eyes.
[KOBAYASHI]
And now I'm creeped out.