--[CROWS caw]
--[CATS meow]
[KOBAYASHI slurps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm?
I promised Saikawa
that I would
play with her in the park today.
Oh, fun. Have a good time.
Do you have any big plans
for the day, Miss Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI] Hmm. I guess I'd
like to spend my day off
relaxing at home.
I knew you'd say that!
So I am prepared
to give my utmost
to ensure said relaxation.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmmm.
Cool. Leaving me alone
is enough, though.
[TOHRU]
Kanna!
Be careful!
'Kay!
[TOHRU]
I hope the sun comes out today.
So pretty.
Shepherd's purse?
[KANNA]
Flower language?
It's a book about
what flowers mean.
Georgie is letting me borrow it.
I think it's way neat.
[gasps, screams]
You all right?
Let's look up
shepherd's purse.
Oh, there it is!
Apparently, it means
I'll offer everything to you.
[SAIKAWA]
Here you go, Kanna.
My everything!
You mean me or the flower?
[TOHRU]
Here you go, Miss Kobayashi.
Thank you, Tohru.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm.
Do you love it?
Yeah, it's really tasty.
I was hoping so!
I've been working on adjusting
the temperature and intensity
to compliment how you're
feeling at the moment!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmmm.
You dragons
are an amazing bunch.
[TOHRU] Oh, it's not
because I'm a dragon.
It's because I'm me.
I suppose it's about time
for me to go shopping.
Any thoughts on
what I should make
for tonight's dinner?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm.
Omurice .
I was just thinking
the same thing!
[KOBAYASHI] But this time,
please make it normal.
Normal, it is!
I'll be back in a bit.
'Kay.
[TOHRU]
Omurice tonight.
Omurice tonight!
Their lifespan is just so short.
True, but take the house mouse.
For example, it only
lives for maybe a year
to a year and a half.
Oh! So sad!
[MALE TV A] Not at all.
Every living creature
has its own perception of time.
Applying human standards
to them is a mistake.
[TOHRU'S DOUBT] How long are
you planning to continue this?
[TOHRU gasps]
Who are you? Are you me?
[TOHRU'S DOUBT] Indeed.
I am the doubt within you.
[TOHRU'S DOUBT] Do not avert
your eyes and deceive yourself.
Be honest.
I repeat: How long are you
planning to continue this?
The time I have now.
I simply want to enjoy it.
I want to spend time with
Miss Kobayashi, that's all.
[TOHRU'S DOUBT]
How long will it last?
You understand, do you not?
One day you will have to return.
[TOHRU]
You're wrong.
I'm not going back.
Because, I am
Miss Kobayashi's maid.
[TOHRU'S DOUBT]
You are not. You are a dragon.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU'S DOUBT] What will you
do if a need to return rises?
If the war back there worsens?
If you long for battle?
What if...
Miss Kobayashi were to...
[TOHRU yells]
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi.
This is where I belong.
She is where I belong.
[TOHRU]
Father?
You understand why I've come.
Return home with me.
Now, Tohru.
This world is not
where you belong.
[gasps]
Lady Tohru!
[door knob clicks]
[KOBAYASHI]
Welcome home, Kanna!
Tohru's still not back
from shopping.
Omurice takes
more effort than I thought.
[KANNA]
Lady Tohru went home.
No, she's out. She's not here.
She went home.
Huh?
[KANNA]
To the other world.
Her father came to take her.
He's the Emperor of Demise.
So you mean she went home.
Yes, and I don't think
she'll come back
to this world ever again.
She can't refuse
the Emperor of Demise.
[KOBAYASHI]
No.
Tohru's gone.
[alarm clock ringing]
Crap, crap, crap!
Kanna, wake up! It's time to go.
[KOBAYASHI]
Shoot, shoot. I totally forgot!
--[KOBAYASHI] Huh?
--[ding]
--Hot!
--[clang]
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, man.
Whoa.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm sorry, Kanna.
It's okay.
[YAMASHITA]
Kobayashi.
Kobayashi?