[TOHRU]
[KOBAYASHI]
Seriously, Tohru.
What made you think a kitchen
fire was a good plan?
It was more of
an instinct than a plan.
[KOBAYASHI] You know the
stove makes fire, right?
[TOHRU] Yes, but I didn't think
it would be strong enough!
[KOBAYASHI]
Strong enough to what?
Incinerate the kitchen?
I worry you may
have brain damage.
[KOBAYASHI]
Which reminds me.
Why've I been letting her
go shopping on her own
this whole time?
Probably not the best idea.
But maybe she's not
a disaster there.
--[TOHRU] Wait!
--[KOBAYASHI] Huh?
Aren't we going to
the shopping district?
You mean you don't go to
the big supermarket over there?
Oh, no.
That place feels like a castle
and completely freaks me out.
Castle?
Yes, and the whole
thing's white, too.
Gives me flashbacks to run-ins
with crusader's bases.
That's unfortunate.
[TOHRU] The shopping district's
more like the guild's bazaars.
It's a little better.
[KOBAYASHI] So you shop
based on Dragon PTSD.
Good to know.
You wanna start by
picking up some fish?
[TOHRU]
Sure!
Tohru! What's up?
--[gasps]
--Good afternoon, Mister Toda.
You're normally out here
alone, aren't you?
Is she a new friend?
No, she's my Master.
--Huh?
--Uh... Hello.
Tohru's a pretty
funny lady, huh?
We've got some good mackerel
in today. Sound good?
[TOHRU]
Hmm... Sounds great!
Let me have two of those
and two dried jack mackerel.
[FISHMONGER A]
Coming up.
[KOBAYASHI] He gave us
an extra fillet of mackerel.
Wasn't that sweet of him?
Why and how are you friends
with the fishmonger?
Huh? We're not friends, though.
I was just nice to him at first,
so he's been nice to me and
gives me free stuff in return.
--That's all.
--The more I get to know you,
the more I get you don't
know how humans operate,
like, at all.
Oh! Now, don't worry.
Things are different with us!
We share mutual love!
Like "at all"
at all don't get it.
[BUTCHER A]
Hey there, Tohru!
So what can I get you today?
A little extra included.
[giggles]
That's so sweet!
[KOBAYASHI]
Here, too? This is weird.
Hey, long time no see.
[TOHRU]
Hello.
[BOY A]
It's the cosplay lady!
That's me!
Have a good one!
[KOBAYASHI] This dragon's better
at being social than me!
So Miss Condescending
calls us foolish,
inferior humans and what not,
but she's working this crowd
like a champ and
seems to enjoy it.
Maybe she doesn't
hate us, after all.
Didn't mean to keep
you waiting. I'm sorry.
Oh. it's fine.
[KOBAYASHI]
Now that I think about it,
I kinda hardly know
anything about Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI] I think I'd
like to know more. I think.
[KOBAYASHI] Probably best
not to bring up that whole
injury thing, though.
It's clearly a touchy
topic for her.
Wanna grab some dessert, too?
What? You mean it, really?
Sure, what d'ya want?
I would like to have
an éclair, please!
Did you know that the word
"éclair" translates to
"flash of lightning"?
[KOBAYASHI]
I did not.
Speaking of lightning,
talk to me about Thor.
Is your name related to his?
Absolutely not! It comes from
an author in this world.
At least that's what my
parents have always told me.
Right. Of course
you have parents.
--[WOMAN A shrieks]
--[gasping]
Someone, help!
He's got my purse!
Do you mind? May I get him?
[KOBAYASHI]
What? I dunno.
Can you do it without people
knowing you're a dragon?
Yes!
Here I go!
[THIEF A]
Too far away to catch, now!
[gasps, grunts]
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Hmm?
--[CROWD gasping]
--[KOBAYASHI] Oh, crap.
This could be bad.
[TOHRU gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru!
[CROWD cheering]
--[gasps]
--Huh?
That was so amazing!
I can't believe
how strong you are!
[BOY A]
That was awesome!
[sighs]
That coulda been way worse.
[FISHMONGER A]
She's keeping us safe! [laughs]
[TOHRU giggles]
[TOHRU]
So, um... That was scary.
[KOBAYASHI]
I was stressing a bit, myself.
Sorry. I should have
told you to hold back more.
It's fine.
[TOHRU]
Um, your hand...
[TOHRU gasps]
[KOBAYASHI] You wanna hold on
a little longer?
[TOHRU]
Yes...
[TOHRU] I won't be washing
that hand for a while...
[TOHRU hums]
[KOBAYASHI]
What's your tail like?
[TOHRU]
Uh. Oh, it's sweet and creamy!
[KOBAYASHI]
Astounding humility.
[doorbell rings]
Must be my delivery.
Hello?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[KOBAYASHI] So this is
what I let into my house.
This girl-thing has
to be Tohru's friend.
She's got horns and a tail, too.
Tohru would be out
shopping right now.
What do I do about this for now?
[KOBAYASHI]
What's your name, sweetie?
[grunts]
You break up with Lady Tohru.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm? Lady?
Sorry, what'd you just say?
I know the truth. You seduced
her with your... Your body!
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--You cuckold.
--You slut in glasses!
Okay, pretty sure
you're making a mistake.
Don't slut-shame me--
--Break up with her, slut!
--Whoa-kay!
--Give her back!
--[grunts] Okay! Ow!
--I'll kill you!
--Miss Kobayashi, I'm home--
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
[TOHRU snarls]
Miss Kobayashi,
are you cheating on me?!
This is already weird,
don't make it worse.
Lady Tohru.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
This girl is Kanna Kamui.
She's an acquaintance of mine.
Figured as much.
Lady Tohru
completely disappeared,
so I came to find her.
Completely disappeared?
Tohru, you should
communicate with your friends
better than that.
I know.
I'm surprised you found
this place, Kanna.
I saw you breathe fire
on those clouds the other day.
--And I sensed your magic.
--[TOHRU] Right...
[KOBAYASHI] It's almost like you
shouldn't have done that.
Lady Tohru, why are you
dressed in such an odd outfit?
Will you please
come back home with me?
I need you, Lady Tohru.
[TOHRU sighs]
[TOHRU]
I'm not going home.
[gasps]
But why not?
Why?
Because I'm in love
with Miss Kobayashi!
Be serious.
--I knew it!
--[KOBAYASHI] What?!
I saw you on your
little date at the bazaar!
Holding each other's hands
in public. You perverts!
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm sorry, what?
[TOHRU chuckles]
[KOBAYASHI]
Why are you blushing?!
You should know,
if I must, I will kill you.
[gasps]
Now, die!
[grunting]
[pants]
[grunts]
Kanna. What happened to you?
You're practically powerless.
Your power's special
here, Lady Tohru!
The mana purity
is too low for me!
[KOBAYASHI] Kanna, does that
mean... you can't get home?
[KANNA gasps]
No. That's not true, shut up.
All right. Well, can I ask,
do you have anywhere to stay?
[KANNA gasps]
[KOBAYASHI] Tohru, look me in
the eye and answer for her.
[TOHRU] I can't.
Your dead-fish eyes scare me,
Miss Kobayashi.
Kanna, please tell us
honestly what you're planning.
It's okay.
But if you're after
Miss Kobayashi for yourself,
--you need to give that up--
--Tohru, shut up for a second.
[KANNA whines]
Actually...
You were exiled
for a stupid prank?
[TOHRU] Kanna always has
loved practical jokes.
[KOBAYASHI]
Okay, so long story short...
--It's like this?
--[BOY B] I'll be good!
--Yes, it's like that.
--Mommy, open up!
I'm sure they want her to
reflect on her actions.
It would be useless for me
to send her back.
[KOBAYASHI] So right now,
she's all on her own.
[TOHRU]
Yes...
[KOBAYASHI]
Kanna?
Do you wanna stay here
with the two of us?
[gasps]
Hold on.
Why'd it take you so much longer
to decide to let me stay, huh?
Once you're stuck with one,
you might as well have two.
Tch! I don't trust
you humans, though!
You must be plotting something!
You just wanna use me!
[gasps]
You can't trust anyone
in an unknown world?
Hey, that makes sense to me.
I wouldn't trust anyone, either.
I think a person
has to earn trust.
And that can only happen
after you become friends
or get, like,
"romantically" involved.
[KANNA whines]
Listen, Kanna. I'm not asking
for your trust or friendship.
You can live here. That's all.
[KANNA whimpers]
Okay...
--[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
--[KANNA sobs quietly]
[TOHRU]
She's so good.
I'm so glad I fell in love
with Miss Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
There!
There! There!
Here!
[KOBAYASHI]
How to tame your dragon.
[KANNA]
Shoop!
I want to play!
But the game?
[KANNA]
Yeah, I'm bored with that.
Remember, Kanna's still a child.
She craves physical
exercise to the fullest!
[KOBAYASHI]
What's wrong with video games?
When I was a kid, that's how
I spent all of my time.
Kanna, would you like to go
play outside with me today?
[KANNA]
Mm! Yeah!
Care to join, Miss Kobayashi?
Yes! Please join us!
I don't exercise.
[screams]
And we're... where?
I dunno.
I landed in the first big field
I saw that looked pleasant.
Well, whatever works.
I'll be here sleeping off
the fatigue from my deathma.
Wake me up when
we're finished playing.
Then, figure out
how to get us home.
All right, if that's
what you want.
You ready to play even
if it's just the two of us?
[KANNA]
Mm!
[KOBAYASHI yelps, gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Tch!
[KANNA gasps]
Wait! Wait, wait!
Oh, hey. I thought
you were gonna take a nap?
[KOBAYASHI] How can I sleep
when you two are trying
to kill each other?!
Don't be silly-- we were only
roughhousing a teeny-tiny bit.
You over-exaggerate.
[KOBAYASHI] Shoot,
I'm at the disadvantage now.
Oh! I bet you wanted to join in,
too, right, Miss Kobayashi?
Shame! You should
be more honest!
[KOBAYASHI]
You'd kill me!
[KANNA groans] It's fun to
move around in a human body.
What happened with you, Kanna?
I thought your strength
had been depleted somehow.
It had been, but the source
of my power is electricity.
It returned after I recharged.
So what, you're made of lithium?
If you're playing,
keep it to human standards.
What? We were at
human standards.
--Huh?
In our world there are
plenty of humans capable
of doing this kind of thing.
[KOBAYASHI] There's very few
who can do it here, like, none.
[TOHRU] That's not true, I saw
some on TV the other day.
[KOBAYASHI] What you saw
was fiction, not reality.
--[BOTH gasp]
--[KOBAYASHI] Oh.
Sorry, for crushing your dreams.
Whatever. I'll be
sleeping in this spot.
Try to keep your playing
around my level.
Sure! Well, there
you have it, Kanna.
Let's start by recalling exactly
how Miss Kobayashi usually acts.
[KANNA]
Okay!
[KOBAYASHI]
The power of dragons.
I've seen it a few times now,
but it's still terrifying.
If they wanted to,
this world would be gone.
[TOHRU]
My lower back! It's killing me!
[KANNA]
I'm tired... I'm gonna die...
[KOBAYASHI] Yeah, never mind.
They'd never destroy our world.
And, for the record,
they've both totally nailed me.
[TOHRU]
Ah, that was super fun.
Was it?
I suppose you really didn't want
to play, Miss Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmph.
I don't mind playing Word Chain.
Indigo.
Gorilla.
Lambskin.
Intercom.
[KANNA]
Compadre.
[TOHRU]
Dre... Dre...
Oh, dragon!
[KOBAYASHI]
Ha, ha, you lose.
[TOHRU]
Agh! [laughs]
[KOBAYASHI grunts]
[TOHRU]
Ah! You're being rude.
you only left my
tail-meat behind again!
I said I was ethically opposed.
Although, if you turned
it into ground meat,
I probably wouldn't notice.
But then you would
have no way of knowing
it was specifically my meat.
Why is that so important to you?
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--Miss Kobayashi...
Please don't enter or
even peek into the kitchen
until I call for you, okay?
Thank you...
Hey!
[KOBAYASHI]
I will never want your tail!
[screams]
[KANNA]
Where are you going, Kobayashi?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm? To work.
I wanna go with you.
Kanna, you have things to do
with me today, remember?
[KOBAYASHI]
Things like what?
[TOHRU] Kanna hasn't been in
this world for very long.
I thought it would be good for
me to teach her some basics.
Yeah? You thought that?
No way! I want Kobayashi!
This came out of nowhere.
If you keep being selfish,
I'll break you.
--[KOBAYASHI] I'm off!
--[TOHRU] Safe travels!
Now then. It's time
for you to learn
common sense for this world.
[KANNA]
What kind of common sense?
[TOHRU] To start with, you need
to learn what you must not do.
Oh!
[TOHRU] Honor traffic
lights at all times!
Otherwise, you'll be
squashed by a "car."
[KANNA] That's what those
iron boxes are called?
Lady Tohru, you're smart!
[TOHRU chuckles]
[KANNA]
How do they move around?
[TOHRU]
Probably with magic.
Apparently, you need a device
called a "license" for them.
Does Kobayashi have that?
A license?
I'd love to ride in a car!
[TOHRU] From what I understand,
she possesses a license,
but she does not have a car.
Cars impose strains
called "inspections,"
"loans," and "tires."
[KANNA] It seems power comes
at a price in every world.
But... wouldn't it be easier
if she just had you carry her?
Why doesn't Kobayashi do that?
Great question.
[TAKIYA] Wow, you've got
another relative with you?
This one a maid, too?
Gothic Lolita. A Gothic Lolita
with a tribal theme.
Huh, interesting twist.
[KOBAYASHI] Tohru said she was
gonna teach her some things,
so I'm a little worried.
[TAKIYA] Why? Tohru seems
to have her act together.
You think so?
Well, at the very least,
I'm confident she has
compassion for her friends.
For real? That is hilarious.
Are you serious?
[KANNA]
What's he saying?
[TOHRU]
Magic words.
You can get through
most conversations using
those phrases,
so try to remember them.
[BOYS AND GIRLS
laughing, chatting]
What's that thing?
[TOHRU]
I don't know.
A tool children play with?
How do they play?
It looks like it uses
the principle of levers, but...
[gasps] That's a training
device for catapults!
[KANNA]
Oh!
[TOHRU] This is how human
children learn the means
of combating monsters
in the sky!
[KANNA]
Ooh!
[DRAGON A roars]
What's that?
That's called a crepe stand.
It's sweet, like the
eggs of a yatagarasu.
What's that?
Oh, that's an ice cream stand!
It's cold. But yummy!
[KANNA]
This world is peaceful.
[TOHRU]
It is, isn't it?
Are there dragons here?
Other than visitors.
[TOHRU]
No, it seems there aren't.
I don't know if they went
extinct or if they moved away.
[KANNA] Is it bad to
revert to my original form?
[TOHRU] No, not as long
as you don't allow
that form to be seen.
Have you learned how to use
perception blocking yet, Kanna?
Not yet.
That's okay. Besides,
it's not like there's ever
any real need for it anyways.
Uh. Um, Lady Tohru?
Yes, ma'am?
[KANNA] Why did you decide
to come to this world?
[TOHRU sighs]
All the rumors I heard
said that you died.
I was happy to find out
they were wrong.
Well, to be honest,
I came to this world
just to escape.
I was on the verge
of death when I got here,
but Miss Kobayashi saved me.
Kobayashi?
I decided to repay her by being
her personal, live-in maid.
Meanwhile, I let people
think I was dead.
I've only told a handful
of dragons about my survival.
Like Miss Lucoah
and Mister Fafnir.
That's neat, you kinda
sound like a retiree.
[chuckles]
I guess I kinda am.
You know what's funny, Kanna?
[TOHRU] I'm very happy.
Right in this moment.
[KANNA]
Hmm.
[TOHRU]
Come on, Kanna!
There's gotta be more stuff
you want to know about!
[KANNA]
Hmm.
I'd like to see
Kobayashi's work.
Uh. She might get mad at you.
[KANNA]
So what? I wanna see.
[TOHRU]
Hmm. Well, all right.
Let's go say hello to her, then.
[TOHRU] Feel free to change.
I blocked perception of us.
[KANNA]
Mm.
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[gasps]
What's wrong with you?
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh? Oh, nothing's wrong.
Whatever.
It's not practice for catapults?
It's not. Just a
toy kids play on.
How about that.
[giggles]
[KANNA]
Whoa.
Whoa, this is fun!
Yeah.
[TOHRU]
This toy is great!
Glad it makes you happy.
[TOHRU] Kanna, supposedly
there are myriads of gods
living in this world.
[KANNA] Lady Tohru,
what does "myriads" mean?
[TOHRU] Basically, gods reside
in all kinds of things here.
[KANNA]
Whoa, that's scary.
[TOHRU]
Don't let your guard down.
[KANNA]
Right.