Oh...
[TOHRU]
Christmas, huh?
I do hate the idea of
celebrating the birth
of You-Know-Who's son,
but I gotta say,
it sounds like a good time.
Tohru, hey!
[TOHRU]
Hey back!
Oh, no!
What happened to you?
[BUTCHER A] Unfortunately,
I was practicing for
the local retirement home's
annual Christmas Eve show,
but I ended up injuring myself.
Ah...
You must feel so
weak and flimsy.
Oh, hey!
Tohru, do you think you
might be willing to put on
the show in my stead?
Uh?
The residents in the home
were looking forward
to the event, so I feel like
I'm letting them down.
Put on a show?
Are you serious?
Yes, of course.
No one could represent
our shopping district
better than you!
Okay, we'll do it!
And don't worry, it'll be super!
[TOHRU giggles]
[TOHRU]
And so I'm totally gonna do it!
Are you sure?
Sure, I'm sure!
I'd like to help out,
too, but I can't.
I have stupid work.
That's all right,
Miss Kobayashi.
You just stay
focused on your job,
and I'll take care
of everything.
Whatever. If you say so.
[TOHRU laughs]
It'll be easy.
All I gotta do is ask my
reliable and free friends
to help me out!
Ready, everyone?
Let's put on a show!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
Um. Yeah.
Wait a second!
Jeez, what is it?
Have I been lied to?
Because I was told I could
eat as much candy as
I wanted if I came here.
I even made room in my
schedule even though
it's one of the busiest
times of the year!
Miss Kobayashi told me
the truth about you, Elma.
You're completely
useless at work.
Uh--
So much so that they've
even announced they didn't
need you to be in
their way right now.
Ah... It doesn't make any sense!
Now I can actually
type with my fingers!
What else can I do when
I can't afford to interfere
with this world?
Believe me, you're already
interfering plenty.
[ELMA groans]
Question.
Why isn't Kanna's
mom doing this?
Unlike Elma, Miss Kobayashi
is busy with her work, so,
it's up to us to take
care of this on our own!
What do ya say?
Boring.
I heard something
important was happening.
Turns out it was just
something pathetic instead.
Oh, come on, Fafnir!
Let's keep an eye
on how it goes.
[ELMA]
Well, then.
What exactly do you want
us to do for this show?
I think, to start off with,
it should probably be
something the elderly
would enjoy watching.
That works for me.
Any other ideas?
I know!
An eating contest!
No.
You just wanna stuff your face.
How 'bout a race?
[LUCOA]
That might kill them.
We should play a VR FPS,
FFA, AKA frag fest.
[LUCOA]
I'm sorry, could you use words?
But all of these ideas require
the audience to participate.
You can't judge us
when you haven't
actually proposed anything!
Do the two of you
have any suggestions?
I'm okay with whatever.
Okay, so, what if
we put on a play?
Wait, a play?
Is that where humans pretend
to be different humans
on a globe stage
that's not a globe?
Globe stage that's what?
[TOHRU]
A play, huh?
That's perfect!
Let's put on a play!
Fine.
We will put on a play, but what
do you think we should put on?
Since it's Christmas time,
why not The Little Match Girl ?
Ooh, that sounds funny.
Is it funny?
[SAIKAWA]
Um, no.
It's about this poor little
girl selling matchsticks
on a very cold winter's night.
Sadly, no one will buy
any matches from her.
So, in order to warm
her chilled body,
she lights one of the matches.
Then, in the flame,
she sees a warm stove
and lots of delicious food.
She lights match after
match, and eventually,
her beloved and yet
very much dead grandmother
appears to her.
The little girl continues
lighting her matches
to keep her grandmother
from disappearing,
until finally, the grandmother
gently hugs the little girl.
Then the little girl
ascends to Heaven,
embraced in her grandmother's
warmth and love.
It's kind of a
sad story, and gosh,
it gets me every time.
Yeah, it's pretty famous.
Oh.
So, what happens after the
girl ascends to Heaven?
Does she sell her matchsticks?
Idiot.
The girl ascends to Heaven
because she's dead.
Wow.
That woman strangled
her own granddaughter.
Die!
[ELMA]
No, that's not it either.
You know a lot,
Saikawa. It's so cool.
Uh-- Yeah, I guess.
It's no big deal.
I'm good with putting on
The Little Match Girl
if you guys are!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
Sure hope we don't blow it.
Fafnir will obviously
be directing.
Keep in mind,
Fafnir will not stand for
any sophomoric performances.
Fafnir is the
absolute authority.
Challenge him and
you will suffer.
[BOTH gasp]
Also, keep in mind
Fafnir's only the director
because he can't act.
Now, come on nepotism!
Before anything,
Fafnir needs to cast
the lead of this play.
He wants each of you
to audition for the role
of Little Match Girl.
Yay! I can go first!
Tohru, auditioning for
Little Match Girl.
[FAFNIR]
Just get started.
Do not disappoint Fafnir.
Matchstick.
Oh, please, won't
anyone buy a match?
Boring. Next.
What? Already?
[FAFNIR]
I'll give you one more shot.
This time, see those
heartless humans ignoring you
like the trash you are.
[gasps]
[FAFNIR]
Feel it.
Then, allow the lines
to flow naturally.
[TOHRU]
Feel it, huh?
Why, you foolish,
inferior humans!
How dare you ignore me
to suffer like this?
--I'll make you pay for--
--[FAFNIR] Fail. Next.
Hello, my name is Elma,
and I'm unrepresented.
Matches?
Do you need any matches?
I don't.
[ELMA]
Please, sir!
Please at least hear me out!
I can't go back to the office
until I've sold them all.
[FAFNIR]
What are you doing?
The salesmen that come
to our company always
put on a performance like that.
[FAFNIR]
Sucks for them.
Next.
Good afternoon!
I'm Riko Saikawa.
Thank you for your time.
Ah!
I... Uh...
[SAIKAWA whimpers]
Oh, god, why?
I'm so sorry!
[FAFNIR] To be honest,
none of you are any good.
[TOHRU]
To be extra honest,
your directing style is
way too sadistic for us.
Ooh, me!
[TOHRU]
Yeah, you what?
[LUCOA]
Let me direct.
I can be nice and firm!
And I'll make Shouta the lead.
Uh--
What are you even talking about?
Shouta's a boy,
not a little girl.
Well, you just leave that to me.
Shouta, baby, come here.
[ALL]
Ooh...
[ELMA]
He looks just like a girl!
[KANNA]
So cute.
[TOHRU]
Yeah, I'll buy it.
[SAIKAWA]
I dunno.
He's not as cute as Kanna.
Wha...
[ALL]
"Wha"?
What are you all
planning to achieve
--by embarrassing meee?
--[LUCOA] Shouta, baby,
--come back!
Well, that was to be expected.
C'mon, cheer up, sweetie.
[TOHRU]
What should we do, now?
[ELMA]
I can be the director.
I'll at least be better
than those two.
[TOHRU]
That's true.
Any thoughts on who we
should make our lead?
Matches.
Please buy some matches.
[yelps]
[squeals]
[ELMA, TOHRU]
Mm-hm! Perfect!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hey, guys, I'm home.
[KANNA]
Matches.
Do you wanna buy
any matches, please?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mind filling me in?
We decided to perform
The Little Match Girl
for our show at the
retirement home.
Kanna has been cast
as the title character.
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, I see.
Congratulations, Kanna!
[KANNA]
Mm-hm. I'm excited.
I promise to come see you.
You sure you'll be okay?
Of course we will!
There's no way a play
can take down a dragon.
Right.
Do you want to buy
any matches, please?
[KOBAYASHI] She's at
her most dangerous
when she gets like this.
[KOBAYASHI]
If you say so.
--[KANNA] Match?
--I'm gonna go take a bath.
--[TOHRU] 'Kay!
--Matches?
[phone ringing]
Coming, phone.
Hello, Kobayashi residence.
[FAFNIR]
It's me.
I thought about the
script some on my own.
You're still not gonna
be the director,
so if it's that, let it go.
Otherwise, what did
you come up with?
[FAFNIR] If we stick
to the original play,
it won't match the current era.
So, I decided to make the little
match girl into a magical--
[TOHRU] All right then, time to
prepare Miss Kobayashi's dinner.
Do you want to buy
any matches, please?
Lady Tohru, is there a
chimney in this house at all?
Is there a chimney?
No, why do you ask?
[KANNA] Because Saikawa told me
that Santa visits your house
by coming down the chimney.
Oh, yeah, you mean that old man
who's covered in blood?
Ho!
[KANNA] Do you think Santa will
still try to visit us?
[TOHRU]
Hm...
Yes!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm?
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
What the crap?
[ELMA]
What are you doing?!
No, no!
How many times do I
have to tell you?
No, where do you
think you're going?
Tohru! Why would a rando use
Kobayashi as reason to refuse
to buy matches?
Yeah, well, why would
I be in a hurry if
I wasn't doing
something for her?
[ELMA]
Not my problem!
Lucoa! The grandmother would
not try to warm the girl up
while practically nude.
[LUCOA]
Why not?
It's much warmer this way.
[ELMA] Fafnir, you're
completely out of line.
A human father would never call
his daughter a "mere human."
Focus!
[ELMA] Why is accepting this
script such an ordeal?
[TOHRU] Well, I don't think
it translates that well,
culturally speaking.
Not to mention it's
slow and repetitive
and might bore the audience.
[ELMA] True, and we don't
want that to happen.
Then why don't we try
changing things up just a bit?
What are you suggesting we do?
Nothing too extreme.
I mean, I think
at the very least,
we should make it more fun.
That sounds good to me!
[TOHRU] Why don't we mix
other myths in with it,
like the Kasa Jizou story!
Like we have the old man
selling hats next to the girl.
[ELMA]
Or we could follow the script.
[LUCOA]
I like it.
[FAFNIR] The main character
should be a magical girl.
She can obtain power
to burn this corrupt world,
burn it to ash.
[ELMA] Now there's nothing
from the original left.
[LUCOA]
You know, I've heard 47 Ronin
is popular with the elderly.
[FAFNIR]
Oh, yes, the one about humans
and their quest for revenge.
I can appreciate that.
[KANNA]
Are there any dragons?
[LUCOA] We might as well have
some while we're at it, right?
[ELMA]
Hey, Grandma!
Stop making it sexy!
Narrator, stop grinning
like an idiot!
[TOHRU]
Kanna.
From what I've heard, this
Santa guy won't be coming by
for a little while longer.
[KANNA]
Does Santa know where we are?
Will he really come?
[TOHRU] I guess we'll
have to wait and see.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm exhausted.
What the crap?
--Merry Christmas!
--Still have some cake left!
[KOBAYASHI, TAKIYA panting]
[OLD FOLK murmuring]
Are we too late?
--[TAKIYA] No, we're good.
--It's just about to start.
All right, now the performance
of The Little Match Girl
brought to you by
the wonderful Oborozuka
Shopping District.
Please enjoy the show.
[applause]
The City.
It was terribly cold that night.
A light shone upon
the street corner.
Standing in that light
was a girl selling matches.
Matches.
Do you want to buy any matches?
[SAIKAWA] Unfortunately, no one
wanted to buy her matches.
[KANNA]
I can't sell any.
[SHOUTA]
Umm.
Excuse me, young girl.
would you like to buy some hats?
Huh?
[SAIKAWA] Before her
appeared an old man selling
very strong hats.
I'm an old man,
and my old wife made
these hats for me to sell.
Oh, they're very strong.
I do not have any money.
Are you all right?
I'm cold.
That must be difficult.
Here, you can burn one
of these to get warm!
Burn the hat?
Odd choice since
his wife made it!
They're actually
setting it on fire!
[SAIKAWA] Then something
unexpected happened.
A strange smoke appeared,
and with it, a suspicious man.
Look, pathetic humans.
Who are you, sir?
What do you want?
You have been chosen.
You will be a magical girl
with a duty to bear.
I did not see that one coming.
I grant unto you the power
to correct and punish
this corrupt world!
Okay!
That was quick!
Very good.
--Let us go.
--Wait! Me, too!
I want to be...
...a magical girl!
[FAFNIR] Why do you wish
to be a magical girl?
So I can use my power to
commit many nefarious deeds.
I need the money, you see.
My wife is very poor and dying
from a terrible sickness!
Why wouldn't he just heal her
with his magical power?
You would dare voice
your desires like that
without any shame, old man?
Acceptable.
You shall be a
magical girl, too.
[SHOUTA]
Oh. This is embarrassing.
But, unfortunately,
I only have one staff that will
allow you to use your powers.
You will fight, and the
survivor shall have the staff.
Now!
[LUCOA]
No, you must not fight!
I am a magic fairy.
Do not let yourselves be fooled
by that suspicious man's offer.
Hmph!
[OLD FOLK]
Ooh...
I shall not allow you to toy
with the hearts of others.
Leave this to me and go,
little girl and old man girl!
No, magic fairy, we cannot
just leave you here.
That's right!
You are so kind.
Our time together
was very enjoyable.
I shall never forget you two!
It was seconds.
No way.
Do you know what
we should do now?
A magical girl's role
is to cleanse corruption
from this world, right?
I'm on it!
Where are all the bad
and rotten people?
[SAIKAWA] Incredibly, the spell
cast by the young girl
struck a devastating blow
to a nearby mansion.
Let's go look over there.
[BOTH] Run, run, run,
run, run, run, run.
Are you the two responsible for
setting this place on fire?
No, what? Who would
do such a mean thing?
[BOTH]
So guilty.
I'm very sorry.
I meant nothing ill by it.
It's cool. Don't worry.
I am Kuranosuke Oishi.
Thanks to this fire,
I can easily sneak into
the Kira mansion, so you
have my utmost gratitude.
What are you doing here?
I've come to finally
avenge my lord and claim
the head of Kira Kouzuke
No Suke Yoshinaka!
Now it's the 47 Ronin ?
[TOHRU screams]
Avenging your lord?
Hilarious!
Prepare yourself, Kira!
If you'd forfeit
your life, come!
She did not just do that!
That's the source
of the corruption.
And the enemy of
all magical girls!
[yelps] No!
[TOHRU laughs]
No one can beat me in this:
my final and ultimate form.
I'll turn you into dust!
They have to stop
before they lose control!
That's amazing.
This must be that CGI!
Ya darn right I'm spry!
--[OLD MAN B] No, CGI.
--[ELMA] All right.
[ELMA] Then, I'll have
to get serious, too!
[TOHRU]
I dare you!
[applause]
[giggles]
What an incredible show!
[KANNA]
Kobayashi!
So, what did you think?
We were amazing, right?
Uhh.
Yes, you were.
I'm proud that you did it
all on your own, too.
Good job, Tohru.
Thank you!
Does anybody wanna join
me for an after party?
Let's do it!
We can take this appreciation
cake they gave us!
Elma.
You just wanna stuff
your face again.
What? That is not at all true.
[stomach growls]
[ALL laugh]
[ALL]
Cheers!
[KOBAYASHI]
Ouchie.
Where is everyone?
They just left to
head to their homes.
Apparently, they're each
having their own,
individual parties, too.
What about Kanna?
[TOHRU]
She escorted Miss Saikawa home.
Would you like a bath?
Or are you too tired
to mess with that tonight?
Well.
Since it's Christmas,
I have an idea.
[yelling, laughing]
[KOBAYASHI]
It's beautiful!
[TOHRU]
You sure you're not cold?
No, I'm great!
[TOHRU]
This is unusual.
You've never asked me
to see the view at night.
That's weird.
[TOHRU]
Oh.
I almost forgot!
Here!
What?
Is this Christmas gift for me?
[TOHRU]
Yes!
I got you some medicine that
works well for lower back pain.
For real? That's so sweet!
[TOHRU] It's a valuable item
in the other world!
You grind it down and apply
it to your achy areas.
It works exquisitely!
Yeah.
Right.
Ya know, I was worried
about you all day today.
[TOHRU]
What for?
What do you mean?
[KOBAYASHI] To be honest,
I was super anxious
while watching your play.
Kept worrying if and when I
should jump in to stop you.
But then, I realized
everyone loved it.
[KOBAYASHI]
You really did a nice job.
[TOHRU]
Thanks!
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
It's a White Christmas.
Here, I sorta got a Christmas
present for you, too!
[TOHRU]
Uh? What is it?
Merry Christmas, Tohru.
Enjoy!
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi!
[yelps]
Tohru, slow down! I'll fall!
[TOHRU]
I can't!
[TOHRU giggles]
[floor creaks]
[KOBAYASHI]
I suck at this!
[TOHRU] Fafnir, that was quite
the excellent performance!
[FAFNIR]
Hmph.
[TOHRU immitating FAFNIR]
"Look, pathetic humans."
[FAFNIR]
Stop it.
[TOHRU] "Huh? Why do you wish
to be a magical girl?"
[FAFNIR]
Don't mock me.
[TOHRU]
"Acceptable.
You shall be a
magical girl, too."
[FAFNIR]
I'll kill you all!