[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi! Kanna!
Breakfast is ready!
[KOBAYASHI slurps]
Your miso soup is killer today.
[TOHRU]
Thank you, I'm glad you like it!
I decided to try
something different
and only use ingredients
from this world.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmph.
[BOTH]
We'll see you later.
[TOHRU]
Okay.
Be sure to watch out
for those cars!
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
Remember, Kanna, if a car hits
you, you'll smash it to bits.
[KANNA]
I know.
Perfect! Miss Kobayashi didn't
get angry or chastise me
about anything
I did this morning!
Success, Tohru! Success!
[laughs] I feel like my maid
skills are definitely improving!
Hey, that could mean
I'm finally getting used
to this world. Yay!
[CROWS squawking]
[TOHRU growls]
[FEMALE WORKER A] I don't know
what's going on with you,
but you've been
a lot happier lately.
What? I have?
Yeah, it's not like
you were sad,
but you were a bit more stoic.
Well, a lot more stoic.
I dunno, you just seem a lot
more open, if that makes sense.
[BOTH laugh]
[FEMALE WORKER A]
See you later!
[KOBAYASHI] It's been, what? Two
months now since she showed up?
[KOBAYASHI]
Two months, and I have no idea
what I was like before then.
[TOHRU yells]
[CHEF A] The secret to this dish
is to marinate it in honey.
[TOHRU]
I should try that.
Yeah, maybe then, Miss Kobayashi
will give my tail meat a shot.
[HOST A] Our poll reveals
how women really want
to be treated by their
significant other!
Being knocked back
on a wall is number one?!
--[CONTESTANT gasps]
--[CROWD laughing]
Okay. So they're like birds.
They pursue love with sound.
[CONTESTANT A]
Totally right, ladies
Pursue... Love...
Miss Kobayashi...
Tohru.
[REPORTER A]
And now for the evening news.
Early this morning, a fire broke
out in Tatsumicho Nishiku.
[TAKIYA]
Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Y'know, I hate asking,
but would you mind
helping me out with this?
Sure, whatcha got?
[KOBAYASHI] Whoa.
Looks like I'm not the only one
who takes on too much.
[TOHRU chuckles]
I've been wanting to see
what Miss Kobayashi
is like at work
since I first found out
she had a job!
[giggles]
[TOHRU] One of my 48 maid
skills: perception blocking.
Now I can walk around
without anyone noticing.
Ah! There she is!
Well, looks like I don't
have any other choice.
Yeah, thanks. You, too.
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
[TAKIYA] Uh-oh, that
didn't look very good.
[TOHRU growls]
Takiya?
Yeah, no. Remember that project
Yamashita was working on?
Well, there's a
big problem with it.
And if it's not fixed today,
he'll basically be screwed.
Ah...
Sorry.
So, as of now,
I've gotta prioritize that.
Meaning I can't help you.
At least, not at until
that's fixed. I'm sorry.
Why're you apologizing?
I totally get it. No worries.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmph.
[TAKIYA] Hey. We need
to go drinking again.
[TOHRU growls]
[MALE WORKER A]
Hey, can you help me here?
[MALE WORKER B] Sure thing.
Gimme a minute though.
This schedule sucks.
I mean it's just impossible.
There's gotta be a way
to push it back.
Gotcha. But this still
needs to be reevaluated.
[TOHRU] Humans may gather
together, help each other,
and accomplish a lot of things,
but their civilization could
easily be destroyed by dragons.
Bottom line, I still think
dragons are way better.
[BOSS A]
Kobayashi!
Come on, you've gotta
be done by now.
[KOBAYASHI]
No. Not yet.
Y-- What are you doing?!
Are you completely useless?!
Did you forget that
part when I told you
to finish it "immediately"?!
[TOHRU snarls]
[TOHRU]
Who's this jerk?!
Big shock. The Chief is yet
again pushing his work off
onto Kobayashi.
[MALE WORKER C]
It's nuts because his project
isn't even that crucial.
[BOSS A]
Listen, honey--
You better quit screwing around
and finish this thing fast,
--got me?!
--Understood, sir.
Grr! Christ...
[BOSS A chuckles]
[yelps, grunts]
--Pfft!
--Cheese it, guys!
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Hmph! Serves him right.
That oughta cheer up
Miss Kobayashi.
[gasps]
[TOHRU] Uh! I thought I
was blocking perception.
No, there's no way
anyone knows I'm here.
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi sure works hard.
And that's on top of everyone
asking for her help
all the time.
[TOHRU giggles]
[TOHRU] Miss Kobayashi is
just-- She's just the best!
[BOSS A]
Kobayashi!
--[KOBAYASHI] Hmm?
--[TOHRU growls]