This place is
completely packed today.
Leaving the house
between Christmas
and New Year's is a nightmare.
[KANA]
What's that?
It's a lottery.
I wanna do lottery.
We'd need to have tickets.
[TOHRU]
You mean like these?
How'd you get those?
With magic?
Magic?
No, I got them during
my daily trips here
to the shopping district.
They just gave them to me.
Assimilated much?
[LOTTERY STAFF A] Okay, with
these, you'll get three turns.
[TOHRU] Ooh, the grand prize
is a hot springs vacation!
Oh, yeah.
Hot springs would be nice.
I'm getting that prize!
As long as you don't use magic.
Duh! I know!
[LOTTERY STAFF A]
Here's your consolation prize:
pocket tissues.
[LOTTERY STAFF A]
Pocket tissues.
Last chance, but this time
I'm gonna win or else!
[KANNA, TOHRU]
Huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
Congratulations!
I won!
Third prize!
You'll be set for
the winter, now!
Enjoy your new warm kotatsu .
[KOBAYASHI, KANNA]
Oh!
Ko-what?
[WORKER A] You traveling
anywhere, Yamashita?
[YAMASHITA] Yeah, going
to Hokkaido to see family.
If you want I'll pick up
some nama chocolates
for you as a souvenir.
Nama chocolates.
So, what about you?
You gonna go visit family?
Nope.
You got plans?
Well, winter Comiket, obviously.
Did you forget?
Ah.
[ringing]
[WOMAN A]
The train's leaving now.
[WOMAN B]
Oh, you're right!
Happy New Year!
[KOBAYASHI] I can't believe how
much has happened this year.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm here.
Hey, welcome home.
Glad you're back.
[sighs] Done with work
this year, finally.
Congrats, Miss Kobayashi.
Quick question.
That means you don't have
to go to the office anymore?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yep.
I'm off through the third.
[KANNA]
Oh!
[TOHRU]
You're always so busy.
I hope you'll try
to take it easy
over the rest of the holidays.
[KOBAYASHI]
That is my plan.
[sighs] This is heaven.
I'm glad you won
the kotatsu for us.
Yeah, me, too.
I need to move soon
so I can start preparing
the New Year's dishes.
I even borrowed the tools I
need to pound mochi and soba!
You realize you don't have to go
all-out like that, don't you?
It's a maid's responsibility
to make sure any and all
seasonal events are carried out!
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm...
Uh-oh. Do you need
to use the restroom?
Don't wanna get up.
Tohru, will you go?
You can do it for me.
Ew.
Okay, fine.
I'll go take care of it.
Hey, uh, since you're up,
you mind hitting
the switch on the rice cooker?
[KANNA]
Hey, grab me the remote, too.
What are you doing?
Ahh.
This is New Year's curry.
Is it--
Don't worry, it's mild.
[TV VOICE A] The New Year's
parlor trick tournament
will be on January third.
You can look forward to
several outstanding guests
performing in our comp...
[TV VOICE A] Ready for
our huge New Year's sale?
Doors open at 6:30 AM
on the first!
[yells]
According to what I've heard.
I can just pound the soba
tomorrow before we eat it.
Tohru, this isn't
too much for you?
No way.
I'm simply fulfilling
my specific maid duties.
I do feel like we're forgetting
something important, though.
[doorbell rings]
Oh, someone's at the door.
Wonder who it could be.
Looks like we'll never find out.
[SASAKIBE]
Tohru! Hello, anyone home?
[ALL gasp]
You better get up.
They're calling for you.
Of all the freezing
stupid luck. Coming.
Yes, hello?
Oh, Miss Sasakibe.
Afternoon!
Hungry?
I've got extra candied sweet
potatoes with chestnuts!
They're yours if you want 'em.
Ooh, I didn't make any
of those, they look tasty.
Thank you very much!
Ah! Can you stay there
just a moment, please.
Here, have some
mochi we pounded.
It'll stay good for at least
a month if you freeze it.
Thanks! I adore mochi!
Good work, neighbor.
[TOHRU]
I know, right?
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
[TOHRU]
Yes, hello?
Good afternoon, Mister Yana.
I brought back way too many
mandarin oranges from home.
You want these? They're sweet.
This is a lot!
Thank you for thinking of us.
If you don't mind holding
on just a second,
I'll grab you some of our mochi!
Good work, again.
[TOHRU]
I guess so.
What's wrong?
It's just, as soon as
I get back under there,
I know someone will come.
[TOHRU]
Maybe not.
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
[TOHRU]
Mister Sone.
Is that a rooster?
That's right.
New year, new animal.
Wow, thanks so much.
He's really well made!
And I've got the perfect
place to put him!
Here.
We pounded some extra mochi.
Have some!
You're the best neighbor ever.
This time, it was Mister Sone
with a rooster for us!
[KANNA]
Rooster!
From the zodiac?
[KANNA]
What do those words mean?
[KOBAYASHI] There are twelve
animals in the Chinese zodiac.
Rat, Ox, Tiger...
Let's see, what else?
[TOHRU]
Rabbit, Dragon, Snake, Horse,
Ram, Monkey, Rooster,
Dog, and Pig.
Was that a spell?
I'm surprised you know.
It's because I stumbled
across horoscopes online
while I was searching
for all things New Year.
I refuse to accept it, though.
Why's that?
[TOHRU] Because their big
origin story is that the order
of all the animals was
decided by which ones
reached God the fastest on
the morning of the New Year.
[KOBAYASHI] Oh, right.
I totally forgot about that.
The Rat stole first place
by sneaking a ride on the Ox.
[KOBAYASHI] So, what's the part
about it you "refuse to accept"?
[TOHRU]
Pause the story right there!
No way a dragon was slower
than an ox and a tiger,
let alone a freakin'
bunny rabbit!
That is utterly ridiculous.
Right. Well, it's only a story.
Whoa.
This mandarin orange
thing is sweet!
[KOBAYASHI]
Tohru.
Yes?
I just wanna say,
y'know, for getting along
with the neighbors
and the other stuff.
Thank you.
You're welcome,
and thank you, too!
[TOHRU]
Yummy, it tastes like you.
[KOBAYASHI]
No, it doesn't.
[TOHRU]
Oh, wait a second!
I knew there was something
I was forgetting.
Here.
[KOBAYASHI]
New Year's cards?
[TOHRU]
Yes. I bought them for you.
[KOBAYASHI] I haven't written
one of these in years.
[ELMA pants]
[ELMA grunts]
Huh?
[KIDS cheer]
[TV VOICE B] Are you confident
about your first performance?
[IDOL A]
No. I wrote the lyrics down...
The noodle shop owner in the
shopping district taught me
how to do that neat-o trick!
Wow.
[KANNA]
Kobayashi.
Please put my kimono on.
[KOBAYASHI]
Kimono?
[TOHRU] She promised
to join Miss Saikawa
on her first shrine visit.
She lent me a kimono so we
could wear them together.
That should be fun.
It's not too tight?
[KANNA]
No.
[KOBAYASHI] All right,
you have been kimono-ed.
[KANNA]
Whoa!
Incredible, Miss Kobayashi,
it was like magic!
I was a kid when my mom
taught me how to do that trick.
Your mom, really?
It's adorable!
Would you like to
wear one, too, Tohru?
Uh?
[TOHRU humming]
Glad you like it.
What a relief mine fit you!
It's a good thing
kimonos give room
to adjust for chest size.
Whatever.
[TOHRU] These past few days,
we've been losing big time
against the temptation
of the kotatsu ,
but going outside for
a change is nice, huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Sure is.
Fresh air can be nice.
It's a little cold.
[SAIKAWA]
Hi, Kanna!
[KANNA]
Saikawa.
You look so cute!
Your face is warm.
[gasps]
[squeals]
Hey!
You came, too?
Duh! But why is she here?
[ELMA]
Should I not be?
[LUCOA]
I ran into Elma not far away.
[ELMA] I only came because
I've heard there's
a lot of unusual
foods for me to try.
[KOBAYASHI] Lucoa, so,
what's with your kimono?
[LUCOA]
Well, it is New Year's.
I decided to go traditional.
Why not, right?
If that's traditional,
what's your idea of risqué?
Hey! What's up, guys?
Ooh!
Do you realize how good
that looks on you, Fafnir?
Yes, he does.
[FAFNIR]
Hmph.
Can we go now?
They'll run out of amazake .
Welp. Shall we?
We shall!
[giggles]
[gong]
[ELMA gasps]
So sweet.
It's a nostalgic flavor.
What? Really?
[LUCOA] Mmhm. I used to
drink something like this
all the time.
It takes me back, you know?
Oh, when you got drunk,
and you and your sister--
[yells]
[KANNA]
Ah...
It's a pretty charm, huh?
[KANNA]
Mm-hm.
[SAIKAWA]
Whaddaya think, Kanna?
Wanna buy matching ones?
[KANNA]
Matching?
[SAIKAWA]
Yes.
It's a relationship charm.
Look at the pretty charms!
You want one?
[SAIKAWA]
An academics charm.
I could make you
one if you wanted
something that worked.
What do you think, Shouta?
Do you need any charms?
I'm from a family of mages.
I can achieve my desires myself!
[LUCOA laughs]
You're my charm, Shouta, baby!
[SHOUTA]
Let me go! Stop!
An evil-banishing arrow?
Purchased because
it might be useful
for researching new, fun curses.
[KOBAYASHI]
How'd Comiket go?
Aw, thanks for asking.
We sold out again.
You're as popular as ever, huh?
[TAKIYA]
Fafnir's Curse Anthology Two
didn't even sell one, though.
He made a second volume
after nobody bought the first?
[ELMA]
Kobayashi!
They give fortunes over there?
That's a great
blessing, Georgie!
Alas, it is too great
a blessing for a maid.
You should have it
instead, little miss.
No, Sis. I mean, um.
No, Georgie, it's your luck!
[TOHRU]
Miss Kobayashi, look!
It's my fortune.
Nice. What is it?
The great curse.
I've never seen this one.
Got any clue what it means?
[KOBAYASHI] Your wishes
will prove difficult.
The one you wait for will come.
That which you've lost
won't be found.
I don't exactly get it.
Sounds like a
great curse, though.
But uh, silver lining,
seems like things
can only get better!
Yay!
[WOMAN C]
I think it's almost time!
It's time, for serious?
Seriously time.
I wonder what's going on?
[KOBAYASHI]
Oh, the year is almost over.
The time sure flew by.
Guess that means we had fun.
[CROWD]
13, 12,
11, 10, 9,
8...
[ALL]
...7...
...6...
[CROWD]
...5, 4, 3, 2...
...1!
[CROWD]
Happy New Year!
So, Tohru.
Happy New Year.
And a Happy New Year
to you, as well!
Ah-choo!
Little miss, are you
feeling all right?
[SAIKAWA]
I'm just kinda cold.
[KANNA] Kobayashi, may I
invite Saikawa over?
It'll be warm
under the kotatsu .
Hey, why don't we
take this opportunity
to invite everybody over?
We have plenty of
food to snack on!
Sounds good, but we need to ask
people's parents
if it's okay, first.
[TOHRU]
All right!
Let's talk and walk!
The Ozoni soup's
ready if you are!
[ELMA]
What is this?
Don't tell me you made it.
Shut up, you don't have to
eat it if you don't want to!
Tohru and Kanna made
the mochi from scratch.
You went all out.
I'll go ahead because it's
a new year, and I'm nice.
Thanks, Tohru!
[ELMA gasps]
Yum!
I learned how to make
the right seasoning
from Miss Kobayashi's family.
It is not mild, though.
[TOHRU] Don't worry. I'll make
some sweet red bean soup later.
Tohru.
What meat is this?
[TOHRU] It's a special
treat, just for you!
[KOBAYASHI] How many times
do I have to tell you
I don't want your tail?
[TOHRU] You'll never know
unless you try.
Could you, would you
for the new year?
I could not, would not,
now let it go.
Aw!
Just get in here already.
'Kay!
Kotatsus are the best.
[TAKIYA]
Yeah, this is pretty great.
Maybe we should get one?
[FAFNIR]
Hmph. Do what you want.
[gasps]
Ah...
I got to see the first sunrise
of the year with Kanna,
so this year is bound
to be a magical one!
What's so special about sunrise?
This sunrise is the
first light of the year.
[BOTH yawn]
It's officially here.
[TOHRU]
Yeah.
[TV VOICE B] As is true
every year on January second...
Put on anime.
There're only reruns
until the holiday's over.
[sighs]
I totally get how you feel.
You wanna pick that up, Tohru?
Negative. I can't
step away right now.
What do you mean?
It's closer to you anyway,
so can't you do it?
[KOBAYASHI grunting]
Ugh. Okay, fine,
whatever, gah.
[TV VOICE B] As is true
every year on January third,
it's day two of...
What is happening?
Are those people running the
same race as yesterday?
Yesterday, they ran to Nagaura,
today they're running back.
It's boring.
You wanna play a game, instead?
[KANNA]
Uh-uh.
I have to do my homework.
[BOTH]
You have homework?
[KOBAYASHI]
First script of the year?
[KANNA]
Mm-hm.
What do you plan on writing?
Anything'll do.
[KOBAYASHI]
Ko ...
... ta ...
... tsu .
Kotatsu !
Wow, that looks super pretty.
You could do it.
You really think so?
[KANNA]
Mm-hm.
[TOHRU]
Okay!
[phone vibrates]
What kind of thing
should I write down?
I think a thing you like.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yes, hello?
Lady Tohru?
Oh, on it!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hey, Mom.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM]
Happy New Year, hon.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah, Happy New Year.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM] I got the
greeting card you sent.
Oh, I was hoping it would
get there by the first.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM] You've never
sent us a card before.
[KOBAYASHI]
I know.
Everyone doin' all right?
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM]
Yes, we're all well.
[TOHRU]
Oh, no! It went out of bounds!
Don't be sad. It looks good.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM]
Sounds lively.
[KOBAYASHI]
I have some friends over.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM laughs]
So you're having fun, then?
[KOBAYASHI]
I am.
I'll call you sometime soon.
Give everyone my love.
[KOBAYASHI'S MOM]
I will. Good to hear you.
[KOBAYASHI]
Thanks. You, too.
Look at you go!
Yep!
So, um.
Who was on the phone?
That was my mom.
Huh?
She said, "everybody's
doing all right."
[TOHRU]
That's good.
[groans] My vacation
is almost over.
Miss Kobayashi, you
weren't going to see
your family, not even
for New Year's?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm. Well, normally every year,
I spend the holidays sleeping
off all my built up fatigue.
It's not like I'm on
bad terms or anything
like that with my family.
I mean, we occasionally
talk on the phone.
That's how it is?
You know, how human
families work.
[KOBAYASHI] I think it's
probably different for everyone.
In my case, I moved away
from home and just got used
to having a life without
any family nearby
to visit or hang out with.
Yeah, that kinda makes sense.
What about you?
You could go back if you
wanted to, couldn't you?
You don't wanna go visit?
[KOBAYASHI]
No, I don't want to go,
because living here with you
is my life now, Miss Kobayashi.
[BOTH gasp]
See, we score if we
get enough chances!
Yeah, we do!
[KOBAYASHI]
Score.
[KANNA]
New Year's money?
I completely spaced about it.
[TOHRU]
New Year's money?
It's my first time
receiving any.
It's mine, too.
Well, it's my
first time giving any.
Okay, I'm off.
[TOHRU, KANNA]
Have a good day!
Come on, first sweet
dream of the year!
Fuji Lucoa!
Hawk Lucoa!
Eggplant Lucoa!
[SHOUTA]
Bad demon!
[KANNA] Lady Elma, Kobayashi
gave me some New Year's money!
[ELMA]
Oh, good for you, Kanna.
[KANNA] Kobayashi gave me
some New Year's money!
[ELMA]
Uh...
[KANNA]
New Year's money.
[ELMA] Oh, all right!
I'll give you some, too.
[KANNA]
Oh!