Hey, so, um, Kanna...
Do you wanna come play
with me at my house?
You want me to play
at your house?
[SAIKAWA]
Mm-hmm! Mm-hmm!
Will it be fun?
Are you kidding me?!
We have tons of games and
all the toys and snacks!
Oh, yeah! We have a maid, too!
A maid?
Yeah, you could bring your maid
with you if you wanted to!
You know, the one who
played dodge ball with us?
After I told my maid about it,
she said she would
really love to meet her.
She wants to talk maid shop
and that kinda stuff.
So does that sound okay to you?
Yeah, sure.
[shrieks]
This is it?
So the loser who dares to
challenge my maid-dom
lives in this house?
I'll crush her!
[KOBAYASHI]
Sorry, why am I here, too?
Because you're the one
who knows the most about maids.
Hello and welcome
to my lovely home!
I see you brought your
maid and your, uh...?
[KANNA] This is Kobayashi.
She's my guardian.
Oh, it's very nice to
meet you, Kanna's mother.
What? Do I look old
enough to be her mom?
Don't let that bug you,
Miss Kobayashi.
After all, if you were my age,
you'd be old enough
to be every human's mom.
[GEORGIE] Young Lady,
I believe introductions are due.
If you say so.
Introducing... our,
um, our family's maid.
[GEORGIE]
Pleasure to meet you.
My name is Georgie,
and I am proud to serve
this wonderful family.
What's that
outfit about, Georgie?
You don't look like
much of a maid to me.
Where's the basic
black and white?
No. There's actually not
a set uniform for the maids
in this world.
Unfortunately, as the role
of servant grew larger
and more formal over
long periods of history,
their outfits evolved into what
is commonly thought of today.
Thank you.
This maid outfit is a simple one
created with the wages of a girl
who's recently
entered the service.
I am humbled.
You have a discerning eye.
You mean...
That's right. We are...
[BOTH]
Allies!
[TOHRU wails]
Please, Miss Kobayashi,
you can't let yourself be
influenced by this maid
and her ugly outfit!
Oh, yes, you must be Tohru.
I've heard rumors about you
in the shopping district.
Honestly...
I've wanted to discuss maids
and, well, anything with you
for a while, now.
We're so ready!
[gasps]
Please, come this way!
[TOHRU whimpering]
[TOHRU]
Oh, god!
This is the first time
Miss Kobayashi's pulled me along
with such passion!
Okay, so, um...
You wanna go play
in my room, Kanna?
[KANNA]
Mm-hmm.
So, what should
we play? Any ideas?
What is that game?
[SAIKAWA]
Oh, yeah, this is Twister.
It's a kid's game.
I wanna try it.
Sounds good to me.
Let's give her a go.
[VOICE A]
Player one, left hand, yellow.
[SAIKAWA] You just gotta
follow the directions.
So I put my left hand on yellow.
[VOICE A]
Player two, right hand, blue.
You'll be player two, Kanna.
--[KANNA] Mm.
--[SAIKAWA gasps]
[VOICE A]
Player one, left foot, red.
Oh, red. Here I go.
[VOICE A]
Player two, right hand, blue.
[KANNA]
Blue.
[VOICE A]
Right foot, red.
Okay.
--[VOICE A] Left foot...
--[KANNA] ...green.
[SAIKAWA]
Ah, K-Kanna's so... So soft!
[SAIKAWA sighs]
I'd like to play a video game.
[gasps] Yeah, totally.
I have a ton of those!
A fun one, please.
Sure thing! A fun one!
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm! Smells so good.
Is it a first flush?
Impressive.
Interestingly,
I've recently acquired
some first flush Darjeeling.
Yes, I've heard about that!
It's a good, fresh tea, right?
You see... there are
a few things I know, too!
Wow. This is beautiful.
Must be antique.
From the
Victorian era, obviously.
Can you believe I picked it
up at a flea market?
Georgie, mind if I ask what
made you such a fan of maids?
It was a children's
book I read that told
the story of a young girl
becoming a maid.
I know that book!
I read it, too!
Really? You did, Kobayashi?
They were
professionals entrusted
with taking care of the home.
The pride they had along with
such dignified character
moved me on a different level!
What about all those
costume changes?
Loved them and loved how
they had to pay attention
to their appearance even
when they were working!
[KOBAYASHI] Oh, my god,
I died over their posture!
[SAIKAWA]
How about this game?
[KANNA]
Sure.
[SAIKAWA]
All right.
Here you go.
[KANNA]
You sit there.
What?
[SAIKAWA]
Right here?
Wait, um...
That's perfect.
You're comfortable. Thanks.
Yes! You're welcome!
Saikawa, I can't breathe.
[SAIKAWA]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I couldn't help myself.
[KANNA]
Hey, I have a question.
Okay?
Do you think
I'm getting along with
the kids in our class?
[SAIKAWA]
Well, of course you are!
You can do everything,
and everyone praises you
because of it.
[KANNA] I guess it just
feels different to me.
I can't explain this well,
but I want what Kobayashi
and Tohru have.
It's special, and I like that.
[gasps]
Listen, Kanna.
I think you know by now
that I like you a lot.
But I want to be even
closer to you than this.
Like married.
Oh, gosh. I said it.
--Fine.
--[SAIKAWA gasps]
I'm fine with that kind
of close. Ready?
Um... Yeah, but...
First... I need to
prepare my heart!
[KANNA]
Saikawa.
[SAIKAWA whimpers]
No! No more!
--Help!
--[KOBAYASHI] Don't run!
[GEORGIE] Join us in
our maid conversation!
Save me, Kanna!
[KOBAYASHI] So Georgie is
Saikawa's older sister, then?
Huh.
I wonder if Georgie is her real
name or just what she uses
when she's dressed
up like a maid.
[TOHRU] She wasn't actually
a maid, merely a maid fanatic.
I'm confused... So confused...
What was Kanna gonna
do to me earlier?
[inaudible]
...dragon style.
[KOBAYASHI]
Ugh. Will it ever stop raining?
Say no more!
Please don't do that.
Hold up, you mean
you also decided to move
from your world
to this one?
[LUCOA]
Mm-hmm!
[KOBAYASHI]
But why would you do that?
Well, lately I've been
hanging out with you guys
more regularly, and travel
can be such a beast, you know?
I dunno, I guess I just
like being closer.
What? Closer?
Yeah, I'm staying
at someone's house
not too far away, just like
Tohru's doing with you!
Hey, do you maybe
wanna swing by and see it?
As long as it's okay,
yes! Definitely.
Great, you can help with
the misunderstanding.
The what?
So funny.
But our silly little mix-up is
partly why I thought staying in
this world would
be a good idea.
It all started one day
while I was on my way home
from here, mostly
minding my own business.
Wait, it feels like someone is
performing a ritual nearby.
What? A kiddo?
Might as well.
[gasps]
[TOHRU] So you seriously
let yourself get summoned
by a ritual performed
by a curious child.
And then you said,
"Sure, I'll be
your servant, kid."
Don't be so judgy.
Besides, this family is
apparently part of a long line
of mages, so it could
all wind up for the best.
Mind clarifying
the misunderstanding
that needs clearing up?
Yeah, so he got it into
his head that I'm a demon.
I was hoping you might be
willing to talk some sense
into him and make
my life easier.
Yay! We're here, guys!
Welcome to Shouta's house!
Well, come on in.
[KOBAYASHI]
Uh, sure it's okay?
No one's at home, now.
I swear, you're so paranoid.
Just follow me.
I'm crashing in one
of the rooms upstairs,
so we can chill out in there.
You want some tea?
I'd offer something else,
but I don't have that.
--Hey.
--[LUCOA] Yeah?
I wanna ask something,
but I'm afraid it
might sound rude.
[LUCOA]
Hmm?
What the hell are you, Lucoa?
Yeah. Sounds rude.
[KOBAYASHI]
Sorry.
It's just I thought you
were a dragon like Tohru,
but now I'm thinking that
might not be the case.
My bad. Talk about rude!
I didn't tell you!
I don't have a category, per se,
but I guess you could call
me an ex-goddess.
Yeah, I like ex-goddess.
Why ex?
Because she was
served that cursed liquor,
and then while she
was drunk, she got all--
[LUCOA laughs]
Oh, yeah. You've
mentioned that before.
[TOHRU]
Long story short:
she was forced out of
being a goddess.
Then you might as
well be a demon.
[LUCOA] Well, I'm still
responsible for spreading
civilization far and wide,
so it's hard to call
myself a demon.
Plus, I'm like a
really good being, so...
I prefer, "ex-goddess,"
or "feathered serpent,"
or "Venusian," even!
Okay, ex-goddess
is gonna work for me, too.
Oh, sounds like
someone's home, now.
[LUCOA]
It's Shouta.
He's the one who summoned me.
[TOHRU]
Poor kid seems super fidgety.
[LUCOA] Right? He's always
like that when I'm home.
[KOBAYASHI] Well, when he's with
an older woman whose body
is an agitator of lust,
it's gotta be kinda unsettling.
I know, and that's why
I've tried to steady his nerves.
I've snuggled with him.
I've taken warm baths with him.
But none of it seems to work.
[groans]
[gasps]
She invited people!
Welcome home, Shouta, baby!
Bad demon, I know you know
a familiar can't
act on their own!
You're gathering allies!
Are you planning to take over
our home, because no, ma'am!
Fancy. He really wants
to be the strong guy, huh?
I know, he's adorable!
[SHOUTA whimpers]
Sorry. Can you forgive me?
Yes. As long as you behave.
Look, I get it's scary
to have people at your house
you don't know, but I invited
them here to help you
understand me better.
[gasps]
What do you mean?
I want you to know
I'm not a demon.
I'm a dragon, isn't that fun?
Stop lying! I used
a demon summoning circle.
Which I noticed
and thought it might be
a little dangerous
for someone your age,
so before a mean
ol' demon could show up,
I decided to answer
the call first!
What? No way.
I-I don't have enough magical
power to summon a dragon, yet.
[gasps] No, you're just
bluffing to make yourself
seem more powerful
and trustworthy!
Bad demon!
You won't fool me!
Literally does this
every time I try. It's so cute.
[KOBAYASHI]
Womb crippling.
--Hey, Shouta?
--[SHOUTA] Yes?
I've heard
about how you're from
a family of mages, so...
why perform a summoning ritual?
Um... It's 'cause...
I wanted to be accepted, now...
To be a full-grown mage.
Mages live pretty quietly here.
But we maintain our power for
when we return to our world.
My father's been in charge of
that all by himself.
He's working hard
to pass down his knowledge
and strength to me, but it
seems like it's taking forever.
I just want to be better faster.
Ah, so you summoned
Lucoa in order to prove
that you have your own power
because of daddy issues.
Wow, kinda makes me
feel bad for Lucoa.
[gasps] I never
thought about it like that.
[KOBAYASHI]
Let's say she was a demon,
sure would suck to be
summoned for no reason,
and what exactly were
you planning to do
after she materialized
in front of you?
Take her along
to elementary school?
Why would any demon
stay with you?
You're right! Everything
you say is the truth!
For real?
She's right, Lucoa,
and I'm sorry.
[LUCOA] Wait, does this mean
he's gonna want me to leave?
Please, don't send me away!
I don't want to go home!
You wanna stay?
But you can't just
live at someone's house
and do nothing in return, Lucoa.
I mean, take a look at me
and Miss Kobayashi.
I'm working as a
splendid maid to help her.
Uh, "splendid"?
Don't be mean!
My mom takes
care of all the housework
and stuff like that.
[LUCOA] Huh... In other words,
what you're saying is that
I need to do something
specific for Shouta
if I want to live in his house?
How would you feel
about me giving you more gold
than you could ever use!
I don't need it
because my dad is
really good at alchemy.
Does agricultural
technology sound like fun?
No way. I don't
wanna be a farmer.
Everyone could use
some crazy strong charisma,
am I right?
I think that would
just cause more problems
than it's worth.
How about vast magical
powers, then?
[SHOUTA] Hmm... Now
that one is kind of appealing.
Consider it settled.
[SHOUTA]
But no, thanks.
No? But why?
I don't believe there's
a point in having vast power
if you haven't worked hard
to earn it for yourself.
Wha...?
Gotta admire the integrity.
Lucoa, it doesn't look
like you're gonna be
any help to him.
There's one more thing.
And it's all I have left.
[yelps]
My body.
[gasps] I knew it!
You're a demonic succubus!
[LUCOA]
What? Oh, no...
Yeah, you basically tied
your own noose with that move.
[KOBAYASHI]
That was awesome.
It's nice to see Lucoa get
flustered every once in awhile.
[TOHRU] All that effort,
and she's just gonna be
treated like a succubus.
[KOBAYASHI]
By the way.
[TOHRU]
By the what?
[KOBAYASHI] I noticed
something that struck me
as unnerving about that house.
[TOHRU]
Oh. Really? Do tell!
From what I could see,
it was pretty ordinary.
[KOBAYASHI] It's about
who Shouta's father is.
[KOBAYASHI] I saw some pictures
of him around the house.
I think he's the director
of my company.
[TOHRU]
What? Small world, huh?
[gasps]
Hey, Shouta!
[screams]
Stay back!
Get out of here, demon!
[LUCOA] Come on.
I told you I'm not a demon.
--Look at me.
--[SHOUTA] Go away, succubus!
Bad girl!
--[LUCOA] Just look at me.
--[SHOUTA] Don't come near me!
[TOHRU]
It's still pouring.
This must be what
"rainy season" means.
Let's hang these up.
What is that? A ghost?
A teru teru bouzu .
Teru teru bouzu ?
Will something
that simple really make
the rain stop?
[KOBAYASHI]
Eventually, yeah.
I'm off, Kobayashi.
Have a good evening.
Yeah, same to you.
Guess I should head home, too.
I'm hungry, anyway.
[TOHRU] Looks like someone
didn't put in overtime today.
I gotta admit, I'm happy you
came home early!
[KOBAYASHI]
I come home when I can.
Takiya went home at
the regular time, too.
Stultus...
Y'know, I haven't
heard anything
from Takiya about Fafnir.
I hope they've been
getting along okay.
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen
Fafnir much lately.
I saw him today.
[KOBAYASHI]
What? Where?
On the way home from school.
He was in the park jumping in
circles over and over.
He was mumbling something, too.
That cursed dragon, what on
earth could he be up to? Jeez.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yeah, no way that's innocent.
--What do kings do?!
--They rule.
--Citizens!
--They suck.
--Nyami-nyami.
--Rules.
[BOTH]
Kaboom.
[TAKIYA] Nice! You're
really nailing this.
You've improved
so much, Faf- kun !
That's great,
but who's Faf- kun ?
Not you if you
don't want it to be.
My apologies, Fafnir.
[TAKIYA] How do you feel knowing
you're ready for the call
and respond part of
tomorrow's event?
[FAFNIR] I can now obtain
a limited-edition item
at said event, yes?
[TAKIYA]
Indeed!
We're having curry
for dinner tonight.
[FAFNIR]
Mild?
[TAKIYA]
As requested.
Thank you for everything.
Let's roll.
I will not lose.
Damn it, traps!
[TAKIYA]
What are you doing?
What'd you hide?
[FAFNIR] You idiot,
you can't go that way!
[TAKIYA]
Boom, got the weapon!
I fainted.
Victory is mine anew.
I know.
[FAFNIR]
I'll win next time.
[TAKIYA]
Bring it on anytime, man.
[sighs]
Hey, uh, Fafnir, I've got
this game I'd like you to try
playing for just a little bit.
The one you're selling
at Comiket again?
Yep, that's the one.
I'm about to the
80% mark, now.
Where is that?
About there, give or take. Yeah?
Can you not...
add something here?
Gotcha.
You know, I thought
this felt slow, too.
I've been wondering.
Do you know how many hours
a day you're logged in roughly?
[FAFNIR] Somehwere
around 21 hours.
And what level are you
at the moment?
[FAFNIR]
Level 280.
I've cleared all the limited
time events, so I'm free, now.
On the fast track to
game addiction, huh?
[FAFNIR]
Hmm.
[growls]
[TAKIYA] Oh, right,
I've got a surprise for ya.
What is it?
[TAKIYA] I grabbed some
shampoo-conditioner
on my way home
from work for you.
And that will help me
with my hair?
It should, yeah.
[sighs]
You shooting for
another all-nighter?
Wish I could, but I gotta sleep.
Good night, Fafnir.
Stay strong, man.
Morning, Fafnir...
I knew you could do it.
We're having natto
for breakfast, 'kay?
Is it mild?
Sure, why not?
[KANNA]
Rain, rain, rain.
Rain, rain, rain!
I can't not love
how happy Kanna is
about her new umbrella!
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm-hmm.
What are you doing?
You really don't know,
Miss Kobayashi?
This is called sharing
a lover's umbrella.
I know that's
what you think this is,
but you have your own umbrella.
[TOHRU giggles]
Yes, but I prefer yours!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm...
Hmm?
Good, it seems
they're getting along okay.
I shouldn't say this
after recommending him,
but Mister
Takiya's incredible.
Being able to live with
Fafnir is no easy feat.
[FAFNIR] Humans are
either hits or misses.
The misses make
themselves known quickly,
but it takes time to know
if you've found a hit.
Spending that
much time on every person
would be too aggravating.
As far as I'm concerned,
the misses that trespass
on my home to steal
my treasure are my
favorite humans.
Why did you wait outside?
[FAFNIR]
And yet...
I can't wait for
today's event, can you?
Faf- ku -- Oh...
I don't mind.
Huh?
You're a hit, Takiya.
I am?
Hurry up.
Oh! Right behind ya!
Our teru teru bouzu
ghosts aren't working at all.
Nope. Rain, rain, go away.
I love rain. I love it so much.
Yeah, you're right.
Rain's not all that bad.
[SHOUTA] Lucoa, you're forbidden
from approaching me
naked from now on!
That's an order!
[LUCOA] But my clothes are my
scales, so I'm always naked.
I'm naked right this minute!
[SHOUTA]
What? No! Bad demon!
[whines]