Gon: HE'S SO FAR BEYOND ME.
BUT HE'S NOT SO FAR OUT OF REACH
I CAN'T CATCH UP SOMEDAY.
I NEED MORE TRAINING IN NEN.
I'VE GOTTA FIND A POWER
THAT'S AS STRONG AS HISOKA'S.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( waves crashing )
( sea cranes calling )
Gon: AUNT MITO!
Mito: HUH?
♪
AUNT MITO, HEY!
Mito: HUH? GON.
( gasps )
GON!
Gon: AUNT MITO!
HA HA!
I'M FINALLY HOME.
Mito: WELCOME BACK.
HMM?
( chuckles )
AND YOU MUST BE KILLUA.
Killua: WHAT?
♪
Mito: MY GOODNESS.
I WISH YOU'D LET ME KNOW
YOU WERE COMING HOME.
I DIDN'T HAVE TIME TO PREPARE.
Gon: IT'S FINE. NO BIG DEAL.
Mito: MAYBE NOT TO YOU,
BUT YOUR FRIEND
JUST CAME ALL THIS WAY.
Killua: OH,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
Mito: HONESTLY, YOU SHOULD
HAVE CALLED AT LEAST.
I'VE BEEN WORRIED SICK.
( both chuckle )
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ Mito: ARE YOU LISTENING?!
( both chuckle )
Mito: OH, RIGHT.
YOU TWO GO AND TAKE YOUR BATHS
WHILE I FINISH SUPPER.
AND PUT OUT
ALL OF YOUR DIRTY CLOTHES.
‐ I'LL DO LAUNDRY.
‐ Gon: OKAY, LATER.
Mito: RIGHT NOW!
YOU'VE GOT 10 SECONDS!
1, 2, 3...
‐ Killua: SHE ALWAYS LIKE THIS?
‐ Mito: 4, 5...
‐ Gon: PRETTY MUCH.
‐ Mito: 6, 7...
‐ Gon: COME ON! HURRY UP!
‐ Mito: 8, 9, 10.
Gon: YEAH. NOW THIS IS
WHAT I CALL LIVING.
Mito: OKAY, LET'S EAT.
Killua: WOW! IT LOOKS DELICIOUS.
EH? HMM?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'RE OFFERING OUR GRATITUDE.
Killua: 'KAY.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Mito: WELL, LET'S DIG IN!
PLEASE, HELP YOURSELF
TO WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
Killua: THANKS.
♪
Gon: OH, YEAH. AUNT MITO...
Mito: HMM?
Gon: LOOK!
THIS IS A HUNTER LICENSE.
Mito: WOW.
IT LOOKS PRETTY ORDINARY.
THERE.
( Gon gasps ) COME ON!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
( Mito laughs ) I'M KIDDING!
YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
Gon: WELL, I JUST HOPE
IT STILL WORKS.
AUNT MITO, I'M GONNA SHOW
KILLUA AROUND THE ISLAND, KAY?
Mito: BUT WON'T THAT
TAKE A WHILE?
WANT ME TO PACK LUNCH?!
Gon: IT'S OKAY! WE'LL FIND
SOMETHING TO EAT IN THE FOREST!
( Mito chuckles )
Gon: WHOA!
( both laugh )
( splash )
( Killua gasps, laughs )
( Gon laughs )
( waves crashing )
( Great‐grandmother sighs )
WHERE ARE THEY?
IT'S GETTING LATE.
Mito: IT'S BEEN A LITTLE WHILE
SINCE HE WAS LAST HOME,
AND IT'S THE FIRST TIME
HE BROUGHT A FRIEND WITH HIM.
THEY'LL BE BACK PRETTY LATE.
I'M SURE THEY'RE FINE.
YES, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
( Mito thinking ) MAYBE I SHOULD
TAKE SOME FOOD OUT TO THEM.
( insects chirping )
( fire crackling )
Killua: HEY, GON.
Gon: HMM?
Killua: SO, UH,
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO NOW?
Gon: WELL, I THINK
I'M GONNA REST UP HERE
FOR A LITTLE BIT WHILE I GATHER
ALL THE INFORMATION
THAT I'M GONNA NEED
FOR WHEN I FINALLY GO
TO YORKNEW CITY TO FIND MY DAD.
Killua: OH. I GOTCHA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK I SHOULD DO?
Gon: YOU SHOULD STAY HERE, TOO,
THEN GO
TO YORKNEW CITY WITH ME.
Killua: I KNOW.
I AM COMING WITH YOU,
BUT THAT ISN'T WHAT I MEANT.
I WAS JUST THINKING
I ADMIRE YOU.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: THERE'S NOTHING
I WANNA DO.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR THING.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
♪
( chuckles )
THERE ARE PLENTY OF THINGS
I DON'T WANNA DO, THOUGH,
LIKE STAY IN THAT HOUSE
OR TAKE OVER
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
I GUESS I'M
A LITTLE BIT JEALOUS.
Gon: KILLUA.
Killua: HUH?
Gon: IT'S FUN,
HANGING OUT WITH YOU, I MEAN.
Killua: H‐HEY.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
Gon: WHALE ISLAND'S AN OUTPOST.
IT'S WHERE FISHERMEN STAY
WHEN THEY'RE AT SEA A LONG TIME.
NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO LIVE HERE ARE NATIVES.
THERE IS A GIRL AROUND MY AGE,
BUT I JUST NEVER
GOT TO KNOW HER VERY WELL,
SO YOU'RE KINDA MY FIRST FRIEND,
MY SAME AGE AND EVERYTHING.
Killua: YEAH,
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
BEING STUCK
IN THAT HOUSE ALL DAY
AND SPENDING ALL MY TIME
LEARNING HOW TO KILL PEOPLE.
YOU WERE MY FIRST REAL FRIEND.
Gon: WHEN WE'RE TOGETHER,
YOU HAVE FUN, RIGHT?
Killua: HUH?
UH, I GUESS SO. YEAH.
Gon: I DO, TOO, SO I THINK
WE SHOULD STICK TOGETHER.
LET'S TRAVEL AROUND
AND SEE THE WHOLE WORLD,
JUST YOU AND ME!
Killua: YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW EMBARRASSING
YOU'RE BEING RIGHT NOW, HUH?
( Gon laughs )
♪
I'LL GO LOOK FOR MY DAD...
AND YOU CAN LOOK FOR SOMETHING
YOU REALLY WANT TO DO.
IT'S GONNA BE SO FUN!
( Killua chuckles )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
DOESN'T SOUND HALF BAD.
FINE! I'LL LOOK
FOR SOMETHING TO DO.
BUT IN THE MEANTIME,
I'LL HELP YOU FIND YOUR DAD.
Gon: HMM.
‐ Killua: OH.
‐ Gon: HUH?
Killua: I FORGOT. YOU NEVER
TOLD ME WHAT YOUR MOM DOES.
( squirrel squeaks )
Gon: IT'S HARD
TO ASK ABOUT MY DAD,
BUT ASKING
ABOUT MY MOM'S EVEN HARDER.
IT'S JUST THAT SINCE AUNT MITO
RAISED ME ALL BY HERSELF,
IT FEELS WEIRD, YOU KNOW,
LIKE IT'S WRONG OR SOMETHING.
Killua: IS THAT HOW IT WORKS?
Gon: WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
AUNT MITO TOLD ME
THAT BOTH MY PARENTS DIED
IN A TRAFFIC ACCIDENT.
SHE THOUGHT IF I LEARNED MY DAD
WAS ALIVE AND A HUNTER,
THAT I MIGHT END UP
JUST LIKE HE DID, SO...
Killua: SHE DIDN'T KNOW
HOW RIGHT SHE WAS, HUH?
Gon: WHEN I FOUND OUT
ABOUT MY DAD‐‐
I DON'T KNOW‐‐
I GUESS I KIND OF DECIDED
THAT IF HE WAS
STILL ALIVE SOMEWHERE,
MY MOM MUST HAVE BEEN
THE ONE WHO DIED.
Killua: THAT'S PRETTY HARSH,
SERIOUSLY.
Gon: EVER SINCE THEN, I'VE
THOUGHT OF AUNT MITO AS MY MOM,
THE ONLY ONE I'VE GOT,
SO THERE'S
NOTHING FOR ME TO ASK,
AND I DON'T NEED TO.
Killua: I SEE.
AH, MAN. I WISH I HAD A MOM
THAT WAS
AS COOL AS YOUR AUNT MITO.
Gon: SHE'S AWESOME!
EVEN IF SHE DOES NAG A LOT.
Killua: THAT'S NOTHING. IF I
JUST SAY I WANT TO GO OUTSIDE,
MY MOM IMMEDIATELY
STARTS CRYING. NO KIDDING!
SHE GETS HYSTERICAL
AND EVERYTHING.
( Gon laughs )
Killua: JUST THE OTHER DAY...
♪
( Killua sighs )
‐ Mito: HEY, GON.
‐ Gon: YEAH?
Mito: HOW LONG WILL YOU TWO
BE STAYING HERE?
Gon: UH...
HMM.
MAYBE ABOUT A MONTH?
AND AFTER THAT...
I'M THINKING ABOUT
GOING TO LOOK FOR MY DAD.
WHAT'S THAT?
Mito: IT'S SOMETHING
GING LEFT WITH ME.
Gon: WHAT?
Mito: HE ASKED ME
TO GIVE THIS TO YOU
WHEN YOU BECAME A HUNTER.
Gon: SO DAD LEFT THIS FOR ME?
Mito: IF YOU WANT, I'LL TELL YOU
ALL I KNOW ABOUT GING.
WELL, GON, GING IS MY COUSIN.
MY FIRST MEMORY OF HIM
IS ACTUALLY OF HIS BACK.
I RAN AFTER HIM
EVERYWHERE HE WENT.
I THINK I WAS ABOUT THREE.
LOOKING BACK ON IT NOW,
IT FEELS LIKE ALL I EVER DID
WAS TRY TO KEEP UP WITH HIM.
WHEN HE WAS JUST 12 YEARS OLD,
GING LEFT THE ISLAND
AND TOOK THE HUNTER EXAM,
SAME AS YOU.
OUT OF NOWHERE,
HE JUST SAID HE WAS LEAVING,
BUT WHEN I ASKED HIM WHY,
ALL HE SAID WAS...
"THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT."
BUT THEN HE NEVER ACTUALLY
TOLD ME WHAT IT WAS HE WANTED,
SO WE ARGUED.
RATHER, I WAS THE ONLY ONE
DOING ALL THE ARGUING.
BUT I NEVER
GOT TO SEE GING AGAIN
BEFORE HE PACKED UP AND LEFT.
Great‐grandmother:
ORIGINALLY YOU WERE TOLD
YOUR PARENTS DIED
IN A TRAFFIC ACCIDENT, RIGHT?
THAT WAS ACTUALLY
WHAT HAPPENED TO MITO'S PARENTS.
Gon: OH.
Great‐grandmother: IT HAPPENED
NOT LONG AFTER GING
LEFT THE ISLAND.
Mito: AFTER THAT, GING'S DAD
WENT ON A FISHING TRIP
AND THEN
JUST MYSTERIOUSLY DISAPPEARED.
Great‐grandmother: IN THE END,
I LOST BOTH OF MY SONS
IN A VERY SHORT TIME.
Mito: YES. ALL THAT HAPPENED
AFTER HE WENT AWAY.
Great‐grandmother:
GING EVENTUALLY RETURNED
TO THE ISLAND
NEARLY 10 YEARS LATER.
Mito: WHEN HE DID,
HE WAS CARRYING YOU WITH HIM.
YOU WERE STILL
JUST A LITTLE BABY.
HE JUST SHOWED UP
COMPLETELY OUT OF THE BLUE
AND ASKED US
TO TAKE CARE OF YOU FOR A WHILE.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT YOUR MOTHER,
BUT ALL HE WOULD SAY
IS THEY WERE SEPARATED.
Great‐grandmother:
AND RIGHT WHEN I
WAS ABOUT TO AGREE TO TAKE YOU,
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
SHE STARTED YELLING,
"ARE YOU CRAZY?!"
JUST LIKE THAT,
AND I IMAGINE EVERYONE
ON THE ISLAND HEARD IT.
Mito: GRANDMA! YOU DON'T
NEED TO TELL HIM THAT!
NOW, AS I WAS SAYING,
I KNEW WE COULDN'T RELY ON GING
TO RAISE YOU BY HIMSELF.
( sighs )
ANYWAY, WE REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
Great‐grandmother:
MITO EVEN YELLED,
"DON'T YOU
EVER COME BACK HERE!"
AND SHE WAS CRYING
AND EVERYTHING.
‐ ( Gon laughs )
‐ Mito: PLEASE! GRANDMA!
WHERE WAS I? OH, YES.
THAT'S WHEN GING
LEFT THIS LITTLE BOX WITH US.
Great‐grandmother: THIS GIRL,
SHE TRIED TO THROW IT AWAY
SO MANY TIMES.
Mito: WELL,
I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO
IF SOMEONE
DIDN'T KEEP PUTTING IT BACK
RIGHT WHERE IT WAS EVERY TIME!
Great‐grandmother: IF YOU REALLY
WANTED TO GET RID OF IT,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TOSSED IT
IN A TRASH CAN.
YOU'D HAVE BURNED IT
OR BURIED IT AT LEAST.
Mito: HUMPH.
( sighs )
YOU UNDERSTAND?
Gon: UH...
Mito: AND THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
THAT'S EVERY LAST THING I KNOW
ABOUT GING FREECSS.
Gon: GING.
GING, HUH?
Mito: HUH?
Gon: I MEAN, IS THAT...
YEAH! YEAH, THAT SOUNDS BETTER!
GING.
AUNT MITO,
TELL ME MORE ABOUT HIM.
WHAT WAS GING LIKE
WHEN HE WAS LITTLE?
OH. SORRY. DOES IT SOUND WEIRD
FOR ME TO USE HIS NAME?
IT JUST FELT MORE NATURAL,
I GUESS.
( Mito chuckles )
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
YOU WANT TO HEAR
WHAT HE WAS LIKE AS A CHILD?
Gon: YES!
SO DID GING HAVE ANY OTHER
FRIENDS HERE, LIKE, HIS AGE?
Mito: NOT REALLY.
THE ONLY KIDS AROUND HERE
WERE MYSELF AND YOUR FATHER.
OF COURSE, I WAS ALWAYS
PRACTICALLY BEGGING HIM
TO GO AND PLAY WITH ME,
BUT WHEN I DID,
HE WOULD JUST RUN OFF.
Great‐grandmother:
YOU'D FOLLOW HIM,
AND YOU'D GET LOST EVERY TIME.
Gon: REALLY?
Mito: THANKS! WE CAN
ALWAYS COUNT ON YOU, GRANDMA!
Great‐grandmother:
YOU'D FOLLOW GING
WAY UP INTO THE MOUNTAINS,
BUT THEN YOU WOULDN'T RETURN.
THE WHOLE VILLAGE WOULD PANIC
WHEN GING CAME BACK BY HIMSELF,
AND IT HAPPENED MANY TIMES.
BUT WHEN WE WOULD ALL GO OFF
INTO THE MOUNTAINS TO SEARCH,
GING WOULD ALWAYS BE THE FIRST
TO FIND YOU, WITHOUT FAIL.
IT DIDN'T MATTER
WHERE YOU WERE HIDING.
IT HAPPENED SO OFTEN,
PEOPLE STARTED TO WONDER
IF IT WASN'T YOU AND GING'S IDEA
OF A LITTLE PRANK.
Mito: WHAT?! I WOULD NEVER
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
Great‐grandmother:
HO! WELL, MAYBE NOT,
BUT YOU WERE
ALWAYS HIDING IN PLACES
NONE OF US
WOULD EVER THINK TO LOOK.
IT WAS ALMOST LIKE
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO BE FOUND.
Mito: I DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
HUMPH.
♪
WAS THAT REALLY HOW IT WAS?
OH! THAT REMINDS ME OF
ANOTHER TIME THAT GING AND I...
( Killua snoring )
( birds chirping )
Killua: HMM.
OKAY. SO...
THIS IS THE BOX, HUH?
HMM. LET'S SEE.
UH...
HOW DO YOU OPEN THIS THING?
Gon: MM, I TRIED
A WHOLE BUNCH OF THINGS,
BUT IT WOULDN'T EVEN BUDGE.
Killua: MIND IF I USE
A BIT OF FORCE?
Gon: GO AHEAD.
Killua: ALL RIGHT.
( grunts )
( panting )
NO USE. THIS THING'S NOT NORMAL.
I COULD TWIST OPEN
A REGULAR STEEL BOX, NO PROBLEM.
Gon: MM.
Killua: AND SINCE
WE HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S INSIDE,
WE CAN'T EXACTLY
SMASH IT, CAN WE?
DOESN'T MAKE A SOUND.
Gon: HMM.
Killua: YOUR DAD TOLD AUNT MITO
SHE WAS ONLY
SUPPOSED TO GIVE YOU THIS
AFTER YOU BECAME
A HUNTER, RIGHT?
Gon: YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
Killua: NOT 'TIL YOU HAD
BECOME A HUNTER. HUH.
WHOA.
WAIT A SEC.
I GOT IT!
GON, THERE'S STILL ONE THING
WE HAVEN'T TRIED YET!
Gon: EH?
Killua: WHAT'S SOMETHING
YOU HAVE NOW
THAT YOU DIDN'T HAVE
BEFORE YOU WERE A HUNTER?
Gon: HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT!
MY HUNTER LICENSE!
EXCEPT THERE'S
NO OPENING FOR THE CARD,
SO THAT CAN'T BE IT.
Killua: NO, NOT THAT.
I MEANT NEN.
♪
( both gasp )
( metal clatters )
Gon: THAT'S WHAT'S INSIDE?
ANOTHER BOX?
Killua: MM‐HMM.
REGULAR STEEL PLATES.
NO TRACE OF ADHESIVES.
( gasps )
Gon: WHAT IS IT?
Killua: THAT DESIGN,
LOOK FAMILIAR?
Gon: WAIT. THIS IS‐‐
I KNOW!
THIS LOOKS JUST LIKE THE PATTERN
ON THE PROMISE THREAD
MR. WING GAVE ME.
Killua: MM.
THE PROMISE THREAD WAS DESIGNED
TO SNAP IF NEN WAS EVER USED,
WASN'T IT?
I'LL BET YOU THIS PATTERN
HOLDS A POWER SIMILAR TO NEN,
Gon: AND IT LOOKS LIKE...
MAYBE THE CARD GOES IN HERE.
HEY! IT WORKED!
Killua: BINGO!
Gon: A RING
AND A CASSETTE TAPE...
Killua: AND A MEMORY CARD?
LOOK. THAT PATTERN'S
ON THE BACK OF THE RING, TOO.
YOU SHOULD BE REAL CAREFUL
BEFORE YOU TRY PUTTING IT ON.
Gon: 'KAY.
YOU THINK GING WOULD...
TRY TO DO SOMETHING TO ME?
Killua: BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
Gon: WELL, WE CAN START
BY LISTENING
TO THE CASSETTE TAPE.
Killua: GUESS SO.
OH! CAN YOU COPY IT FIRST?
Gon: YEAH, SURE. BUT WHY?
Killua: BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
‐ ( tape crackles )
‐ Ging: HEY. GON.
( Gon gasps )
Ging: SO YOU BECAME
A HUNTER, TOO, HUH?
ANYWAY, I HAVE
A QUESTION FOR YOU.
DO YOU...
WANT TO SEE ME?
♪
Narrator: IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
GON HAD EVER HEARD
HIS FATHER'S VOICE,
AND IT FELT TO HIM
LIKE GING WAS READING HIS MIND
AND GETTING
RIGHT TO THE POINT.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY, WE'RE INTRODUCING
AUNT MITO. SHE RAISED ME,
SO SHE'LL ALWAYS BE MY MOM
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
Killua: I REALLY WISH
I HAD A MOM LIKE AUNT MITO.
Gon: SHE'S THE BEST,
BUT SHE DOES NAG A WHOLE LOT.
♪
NEXT TIME, "REPLY FROM DAD."
EARTHQUAKES, THUNDERSTORMS,
FIRES, OR DAD...
Killua: WHICH ONE OF THOSE
SCARES YOU MOST?
Gon: AUNT MITO.