Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS OFF
YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kastro: YOU SEE,
MY DOUBLE IS NO MERE ILLUSION.
IT'S REAL, JUST AS REAL
AS I AM UNTIL I MAKE IT VANISH.
YOU MUST KNOW THIS.
YOU FELT IT
STRIKE AGAINST YOU.
TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO FACE
TWO OF ME AT ONCE!
NOW BEHOLD THE CULMINATION
OF MY MASTERY OF NEN,
THE TRUE TIGER BITE FIST!
♪
( crowd cheering )
Narrator: KASTRO USED NEN
TO CREATE A DOUBLE OF HIMSELF,
AND HIS SPECIAL ATTACK,
THE TRUE TIGER BITE FIST,
HAS SEVERED
HISOKA'S RIGHT ARM.
WHICH OF THESE CONTENDERS
WILL EMERGE VICTORIOUS?
( Hisoka chuckles )
( crowd murmuring )
Cocco: NOW WHAT?!
HISOKA HAS COVERED
HIS RIGHT ARM WITH A SCARF?
Hisoka: SHALL I DEMONSTRATE
MY POWERS OF CLAIRVOYANCE?
( Kastro growls )
( Kastros gasp )
Cocco: WOW!
HIS RIGHT ARM DISAPPEARED,
AND NOW CARDS
ARE RAINING DOWN!
WHAT IS HE DOING?!
Hisoka: THE CARDS YOU SEE
GO FROM ONE TO 13.
I WANT YOU TO PICK A NUMBER
AND VISUALIZE THAT CARD
IN YOUR HEAD.
Man: HE'S DOING
A PICK‐A‐NUMBER TRICK?
Hisoka: READY?
ONCE YOU'VE SELECTED
YOUR NUMBER,
I WANT YOU TO ADD FOUR TO IT.
THEN DOUBLE THE RESULTING SUM.
AFTER THAT SUBTRACT SIX,
AND DIVIDE BY TWO.
LASTLY, SUBTRACT
YOUR ORIGINAL NUMBER.
NOW, WHAT DO YOU GET?
Woman: GIVE ME A SEC.
Woman #2: DID HE SAY
SUBTRACT SIX?
( woman #1 groans )
I FORGOT ALREADY!
Hisoka: I KNEW YOUR ANSWER
EVEN BEFORE YOU
ARRIVED AT IT YOURSELF.
( Kastro gasps )
( crowd gasping )
THE NUMBER YOU CHOSE
WAS ONE.
Man #2: HE'S TOTALLY RIGHT.
IT WAS.
Man #3: HOW DID HE KNOW?
Man #1: REALLY?
Cocco: WHAT?! HE'S INSANE!
THIS IS THE DEVIL'S MAGIC!
AND HE'S INCORPORATED
HIS OWN INJURY INTO THE TRICK!
Killua: I DON'T GET IT.
WHY IS HE SO CALM?
Cocco: THERE ARE
NO POINTS FOR TRICKS.
IT DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE MATCH,
BUT STILL HE'S PERFORMING MAGIC.
THAT'S THE BIZARRE BEHAVIOR
WE EXPECT FROM HISOKA.
Hisoka: WOULD YOU
LIKE A SOUVENIR?
( Kastro slaps card )
YOU FOOL!
I WILL SEVER YOUR LEFT ARM
SO THAT YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO MOCK ANYONE AGAIN.
♪
( grunts )
Hisoka: YOU MUST NOT
HAVE HEARD ME.
YOU CAN TAKE IT.
Kastro: I'LL BE MORE
THAN HAPPY TO OBLIGE!
Cocco: WHOA! ONE OF THE KASTROS
IS CHARGING FORWARD!
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
HISOKA HAS ACTUALLY SACRIFICED
HIS REMAINING ARM!
WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THIS GUY THINKING?!
Kastro: WAIT. WHAT?!
Hisoka: SO YOU DID ATTACK WITH
YOUR DOUBLE. HOW INTERESTING.
IF YOU HAD COME AT ME YOURSELF,
I WAS FULLY PREPARED
TO COUNTERATTACK...
BY USING THIS.
‐ ( crowd gasping )
‐ Cocco: WHAT?
HIS SEVERED RIGHT ARM
IS BACK TOGETHER AGAIN!
BUT HOW?
( Hisoka chuckles )
IT'S ANOTHER MAGIC TRICK.
CAN YOU GUESS THE SECRET
BEHIND THIS ONE?
Kastro: HE'S LYING.
IT'S OBVIOUS HE'S USING NEN
TO ACCOMPLISH THIS FEAT.
BUT WHAT KIND OF ABILITY
IS THIS?
( Hisoka laughs )
WHAT'S WRONG? ARE YOU SCARED?
YOU'RE SURPRISED, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T KNOW THE TRICK.
BUT THAT'S MAGIC.
SEE, YOUR POWER TO CREATE
A DOUBLE IS MAGNIFICENT,
BUT NOW I UNDERSTAND
HOW IT'S DONE.
I CAN ANTICIPATE
HOW YOU'LL ATTACK
WITH YOUR DOUBLE.
NOT TO MENTION,
I KNOW HOW I SHOULD RESPOND.
IT'S TOO BAD, REALLY.
YOU HAD THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME A SKILLED OPPONENT,
AND THAT'S WHY
I DECIDED TO LET YOU LIVE.
( Kastro growls )
Hisoka: I PREDICT...
YOU'RE GOING TO DANCE
YOURSELF TO DEATH.
( Kastro growls )
SHUT UP!
NO! HOW DID HE PICK ME OUT?
Hisoka: DOUBLES ARE MADE
FROM THE IMAGE
THE ORIGINAL HAS IN MIND,
WHICH IS WHY THEY TEND
TO BE PRISTINE.
BUT YOU CAN'T REPRODUCE
THE GRIME THAT BUILDS UP
DURING COMBAT.
( blows whooshing )
OH...
HAD YOU NOT REALIZED THAT YET?
♪
( Kastro yells )
( groans )
Cocco: WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?!
I'M SEEING IT,
BUT I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO UNDERSTAND IT!
IS THIS ANOTHER ONE
OF HISOKA'S MAGIC TRICKS?
Hisoka: DON'T BOTHER. I HIT YOU
SQUARE IN THE LOWER JAW,
SO YOU'LL BE STUNNED
FOR A MINUTE OR TWO,
AND THAT MEANS
YOU'LL BE HELPLESS
TO AVOID MY NEXT ATTACK.
Kastro: WHAT?!
WHERE DID THIS ATTACK COME FROM?
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
I HAVE TO PRODUCE
MY DOUBLE TO BLOCK THE CARDS.
Hisoka: YOU CAN'T MAKE
ANOTHER DOUBLE.
CREATING A NEW DOUBLE USING NEN
REQUIRES INTENSE FOCUS.
THE ONLY REASON
YOU WERE ABLE TO PRODUCE
AND RELEASE THEM FREELY
WAS THAT, UP UNTIL NOW,
YOU WERE
IN A NORMAL STATE OF MIND.
♪
Hisoka: USING NEN TO REPLICATE
AND MANIPULATE SOMETHING
THAT'S AS COMPLEX
AS THE HUMAN BODY
IS EXTREMELY DIFFICULT.
HOW DIFFICULT, YOU ASK?
BY THE TIME YOU'VE LEARNED
TO USE A DOUBLE,
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN HOW TO USE NEN
FOR ANYTHING ELSE.
SAD, REALLY.
IT'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
I LIKE TO CALL MEMORY OVERLOAD.
YOU ONLY LOST
BECAUSE YOU SQUANDERED
YOUR MEMORY CAPACITY.
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: KASTRO'S DOWN,
AND HE'S NOT GETTING UP!
HISOKA WINS BY KNOCKOUT!
( Gon gasps )
HISOKA.
( crowd cheering )
( Hisoka gasps )
Woman: NICE JOB.
( Hisoka chuckles )
Woman: WELL? HURRY UP,
AND SHOW ME YOUR INJURIES.
♪
I WAS NEVER QUITE SURE BEFORE,
BUT TODAY'S MATCH
PROVED IT TO ME.
Hisoka: HMM?
Woman: YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
( Hisoka chuckles )
THAT'S QUITE POSSIBLE.
Woman: WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO PUT
YOURSELF IN DANGER THIS WAY?
WHAT WAS THAT?
PERFORMANCE ART OR SOMETHING?
Hisoka: WELL...
Woman: OKAY. YOU'RE PAYING ME,
SO I GUESS I CAN'T COMPLAIN.
♪
FIRST, I'LL NEED
TO STOP THE BLEEDING.
Hisoka: HEY, BE GENTLE,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
Woman: YEAH, WHATEVER.
TURN OFF YOUR AURA.
( camera shutter clicks )
( Hisoka chuckles )
Woman: I'LL START
WITH YOUR LEFT ARM.
( chorus vocalizing )
HERE WE GO.
STARTING NEN STITCHES.
( Hisoka sighs )
Woman: THERE. ALL DONE.
BONES AND BLOOD VESSELS,
NERVES, AND MUSCLES,
THEY'RE BASICALLY
ALL CONNECTED NOW.
( Hisoka sighs )
THAT'S BRILLIANT.
Woman: NEXT I'LL DO
YOUR RIGHT ARM.
YOU CAN HOLD IT YOURSELF
THIS TIME.
( chorus continues )
Hisoka: HMM.
THIS IS ALWAYS
SO FASCINATING TO WATCH.
I SO ENJOY GETTING TO SEE
YOUR NEN STITCHES IN ACTION,
THAT MAYBE
I INJURED MYSELF ON PURPOSE.
Woman: FINE. WHATEVER.
TWENTY MIL FOR THE LEFT ONE.
FIFTY FOR THE RIGHT ONE.
ALL RIGHT? NOW FORK IT OVER.
Hisoka: I'LL TRANSFER IT
DIRECTLY INTO YOUR ACCOUNT.
Woman: ALL RIGHT.
AND YOU CAN TREAT THE REST
OF THE INJURIES YOURSELF.
Hisoka: YOUR BEDSIDE MANNER
COULD BE BETTER.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO MANAGE
WITH YOUR BUNGEE GUM
AND YOUR TEXTURE SURPRISE.
Hisoka: AH. I GUESS
I SHOULD CONCEAL THEM.
IF I DO, THEY'LL THINK MY ARMS
WERE HEALED MAGICALLY
DURING THE MATCH.
THIS IS NOTHING MORE
THAN AN ORDINARY SCARF.
I USE BUNGEE GUM
TO ATTACH IT TO MY ARM,
THEN TEXTURE SURPRISE
TO CREATE A LAYER OF SKIN.
Woman: HE'S SO FAST,
FAST ENOUGH TO FOOL A NEN MASTER
INTO BELIEVING THE ARM
HAD ACTUALLY HEALED
BEFORE HE THOUGHT
TO TAKE A SECOND LOOK.
Hisoka: NEXT I'LL DO THE LEFT.
( gum whooshes )
Woman: BUNGEE GUM.
HE MODIFIES HIS AURA,
MAKING IT
BOTH ELASTIC AND STICKY.
IT STRETCHES EXTREMELY WELL,
CONTRACTS SWIFTLY WHEN NEEDED,
ADHERES TO MOST SUBSTANCES,
AND IT CAN BE REMOVED
AT ANY TIME.
Hisoka: BY THE WAY,
I CALL THIS TRICK BUNGEE GUM,
BECAUSE THAT WAS THE NAME
OF MY FAVORITE CHEWING GUM
WHEN I WAS A CHILD.
Woman: YEAH, YOU REALLY
DIDN'T NEED TO TELL ME ALL THAT.
TEXTURE SURPRISE.
HE COMBINES HIS AURA
WITH IMAGERY
IN ORDER TO REPRODUCE
THE APPEARANCE OF SKIN.
IT'S ESSENTIALLY
A HIGH‐QUALITY COPY,
SO YOU CAN TELL IT'S FAKE
IF YOU ACTUALLY TOUCH IT,
BUT HISOKA PROBABLY FINDS
THAT DRAWBACK EXCITING.
Hisoka: I CALL THIS ONE
TEXTURE SURPRISE,
WHICH COMES
FROM THE GAG STICKERS
THAT WERE INCLUDED
WITH A POPULAR SNACK
NOT TOO LONG AGO.
Woman: LIKE I SAID,
I REALLY DIDN'T NEED
TO KNOW ALL THAT.
Hisoka: WEREN'T YOU
IMPRESSED BY MY APPLICATION
OF THESE ABILITIES
DURING THE MATCH?
I WAS ALMOST CERTAIN YOU WERE.
Woman: HUH?!
Hisoka: WELL, YOU DID
SEE EVERYTHING, DIDN'T YOU?
Woman: YEAH, I THINK I DID.
♪
YOU STARTED WITH A MISDIRECTION,
TOSSING 13 CARDS INTO THE AIR.
AT THE SAME TIME,
YOU THREW YOUR ARM,
ATTACHING IT TO THE ROOF
WITH BUNGEE GUM
AND THE SCARF TO THE GROUND
THE SAME WAY.
BUT YOU DIDN'T LET GO.
THE AURA FROM EACH WAS CONNECTED
TO THE STUMP OF YOUR RIGHT ARM.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL. THE CARDS
YOU THREW AS A DISTRACTION
WERE ALSO SECURED TO THE GROUND
WITH THE ENDS
OF THE 13 STRANDS OF AURA
CONNECTED TO YOUR LEFT HAND.
AND THEN...
WHEN YOU THREW
THE ACE OF SPADES AT KASTRO...
Hisoka: WOULD YOU
LIKE A SOUVENIR?
Woman: THE AURA
IN YOUR LEFT HAND WAS RELEASED.
( Kastro slaps card )
Woman: THEY CONNECTED.
ALL 13 OF THE AURA STRANDS
YOU HAD BEEN HOLDING
STUCK TO KASTRO'S BODY.
Hisoka: CORRECT. YOU'RE MUCH
MORE OBSERVANT THAN KASTRO WAS.
Woman: I ALSO NOTICED
THAT YOU EMPLOYED
ONE OF THE BASIC TECHNIQUES
OF NEN, ZETSU,
TO HELP MAKE YOUR AURA
ALMOST INVISIBLE.
Hisoka: YES. HOWEVER,
THERE WAS ONE WEAKNESS.
Woman: YEAH. PRETTY MUCH
ANYBODY WHO'S LEARNED REN,
ANOTHER BASIC NEN TECHNIQUE,
COULD HAVE DETECTED IT EASILY
BY FOCUSING THE AURA
IN THEIR EYES AND WATCHING.
♪
THAT'S WHY YOU USED
THAT CRAZY MAGIC TRICK OF YOURS
TO THROW HIM OFF GUARD
WHILE YOU JUST STOOD THERE
SMILING AND PRETENDING
TO BE NONCHALANT.
IT EVEN WORKED
AS A KIND OF CAMOUFLAGE.
YOU HAD HIM CONVINCED
THAT YOUR LACK OF AURA
WAS A SIGN OF CONFIDENCE.
ONCE YOU WERE SATISFIED
THAT EVERYTHING
WAS GOING ACCORDING TO PLAN,
YOU SURREPTITIOUSLY
EXTENDED A THREAD OF AURA
FROM YOUR LEFT HAND,
THE ONE HOLDING THE CARDS,
AND CONNECTED IT
DIRECTLY TO KASTRO'S CHIN.
EVERYTHING WAS READY.
YOU'D ALREADY
USED TEXTURE SURPRISE
TO ALTER THE SCARF ON THE FLOOR
TO RESEMBLE HUMAN SKIN...
AND SO WHEN KASTRO
ATTACKED YOUR LEFT ARM,
YOU ACTIVATED THE BUNGEE GUM
BETWEEN YOUR RIGHT ARM
AND THE SCARF ON THE FLOOR.
YOUR ARM WAS RESTORED,
AND THE SCARF
CONCEALED THE WOUND,
LEAVING EVERYONE CONVINCED
YOUR RIGHT ARM
WAS MAGICALLY BACK.
HOWEVER, THIS PERFORMANCE
HAD THE UNFORTUNATE EFFECT
OF BRINGING KASTRO
BACK TO HIS SENSES.
Hisoka: IT MADE NO SENSE
FOR A SEVERED ARM
TO SIMPLY REAPPEAR,
ESPECIALLY
IN PRISTINE CONDITION.
IT WAS THEN THAT KASTRO REALIZED
I WAS ACTUALLY USING NEN
TO ACCOMPLISH THESE FEATS
AND NOT MAGIC,
AS HE WAS LED TO BELIEVE.
Woman: THAT'S TRUE,
BUT YOU DIDN'T MISS
THE EVER‐SO‐SUBTLE CHANGE
IN HIS PSYCHOLOGICAL CONDITION.
Hisoka: SEE, YOUR POWER TO
CREATE A DOUBLE IS MAGNIFICENT,
BUT NOW I UNDERSTAND
HOW IT'S DONE.
I CAN ANTICIPATE
HOW YOU'LL ATTACK
WITH YOUR DOUBLE.
NOT TO MENTION,
I KNOW HOW I SHOULD RESPOND.
IT'S TOO BAD, REALLY.
YOU HAD THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME A SKILLED OPPONENT,
AND THAT'S WHY
I DECIDED TO LET YOU LIVE.
Woman: YOU SAW THAT KASTRO
WAS ABOUT TO RECOVER...
Hisoka: I PREDICT YOU'RE GOING
TO DANCE YOURSELF TO DEATH.
Woman: BUT THEN YOU
PUSHED HIM OVER THE EDGE.
Kastro: SHUT UP!
NO! HOW DID HE PICK ME OUT?
Hisoka: YOU CAN'T
REPRODUCE THE GRIME
THAT BUILDS UP DURING COMBAT.
♪
Woman: AND JUST LIKE THAT,
YOU WERE ABLE TO EXPOSE
THE WEAKNESS OF HIS DOUBLES.
Hisoka: BUT IF HE HAD
JUST STAYED CALM AND COMPOSED,
THEN HE ACTUALLY WOULD HAVE
HAD A FIGHTING CHANCE.
Woman: HOWEVER...
KASTRO COULDN'T BEAR
THE MENTAL STRAIN...
( Kastro yells )
Woman: AND SO HE LOST.
YOU DO REALIZE
JUST HOW PERFECT
BOTH OF THOSE ABILITIES ARE
FOR SOMEONE LIKE YOU,
DON'T YOU?
PRACTICALLY TAILOR‐MADE.
Hisoka: AS OPPOSED
TO KASTRO'S DOUBLE ABILITY,
MY TECHNIQUES ARE SO ADAPTABLE
THAT THEY DON'T LOSE
THEIR EFFECTIVENESS
IF MY OPPONENT KNOWS ABOUT THEM.
Woman: WELL,
I'M HEADING BACK NOW.
Hisoka: ALREADY?
Woman: YEAH. WHY STICK AROUND
AFTER THE JOB IS DONE?
THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
THAT NEN STITCHES CAN DO,
SO TRY NOT TO OVERDO IT UNTIL
YOUR ARM IS FIRMLY ATTACHED.
OH, RIGHT.
I CAME HERE FOR A REASON.
Hisoka: HMM?
Woman: THE MESSAGE
HAS BEEN CHANGED.
ALL TROUPE MEMBERS
ARE TO BE IN YORKNEW CITY
BY NOON, AUGUST 30th,
NOT JUST THOSE WHO DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING BETTER TO DO.
Hisoka: WILL THE BOSS BE COMING?
Woman: PROBABLY.
THIS COULD TURN OUT TO BE
OUR BIGGEST MISSION YET,
SO KNOW IF YOU BLOW IT OFF,
THE BOSS MIGHT
HUNT YOU DOWN HIMSELF.
Hisoka: NOW, THAT IS SCARY.
OH, BY THE WAY, CARE TO JOIN ME
FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
WHAT A PITY.
( door opens, closes )
Gon: KILLUA. SO HOW WAS
HISOKA'S FIGHT? TELL ME.
Killua: BORING.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU DIDN'T MISS MUCH.
Gon: BORING?
AND HISOKA, DID HE WIN?
Killua: OKAY, I WAS LYING.
Gon: EH?
Killua: IT WAS
AN INCREDIBLE FIGHT.
HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT I WATCHED HISOKA WIN,
AND I STILL DON'T KNOW HOW.
( Gon gasps ) YOU SERIOUSLY
COULDN'T TELL HOW HE DID IT?
Killua: GON, YOU AND ME,
WE'VE GOT TO LEARN
ALL THAT WE CAN ABOUT NEN.
( Gon laughs )
YEAH!
Woman: HE'S SUCH A MYSTERY.
( shower running )
HE NEVER TALKS ABOUT HIS PAST.
IT DOESN'T INTEREST HIM.
HE'LL PROBABLY FORGET WHAT
KASTRO LOOKS LIKE BY TOMORROW.
HE DOESN'T BELONG
TO ANYTHING OR ANYONE.
HE'S HIS OWN MAN,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE HE'S
ABSOLUTELY CONVINCED
THAT HE'S THE MOST POWERFUL.
( shower running )
Hisoka: HMM?
OH, I FORGOT TO TAKE THIS OFF.
A SPIDER.
I FOUND SOME NEW TOYS
TO PLAY WITH.
TIME TO START THE HUNT.
♪
Narrator: HISOKA HAS
BEEN MASQUERADING
AS A MEMBER
OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
BUT TO HIM, THE PHANTOM TROUPE
IS NOTHING MORE
THAN ANOTHER TARGET.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE MEET KASTRO,
WHO USES THE TIGER BITE FIST.
Killua: HE MAKES
A DOUBLE OF HIMSELF WITH NEN.
THOSE AREN'T EASY TO DEAL WITH.
Gon: WITH THIS DOUBLE, I CAN USE
THE TRUE TIGER BITE FIST.
Both: SCARY, ISN'T IT?!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"AN EMPTY THREAT."
AH‐‐ACHOO! DO I HAVE A COLD?
Killua: I BET SOMEONE'S TALKING
ABOUT YOU BEHIND YOUR BACK.
Gon: AUNT MITO?