( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kurapika: TAKE THIS TO HEART.
FIRST, A GENUINE
PHANTOM TROUPE TATTOO
HAS THE MEMBER'S NUMBER
INSCRIBED ON THE SPIDER'S BACK.
SECOND, THEY DON'T BOTHER
TALLYING THE PEOPLE
THEY'VE KILLED,
BECAUSE IT'S IRRELEVANT
TO THEM.
AND THIRD,
DON'T EVER MENTION
THE PHANTOM TROUPE TO ME AGAIN.
IF YOU DO,
I WILL KILL YOU
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
♪♪♪
Narrator: LEORIO HAS VOLUNTEERED
FOR THE FOURTH ROUND.
IF HE WINS, THE GROUP'S VICTORY
IS ASSURED.
BUT WILL HE BE ABLE TO DO IT?
Lippo: HMM.
Leorio: OKAY!
IT'S TIME TO END THIS!
DRAG HIM OFF,
AND SEND IN YOUR NEXT CONTENDER!
( woman giggles )
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
Leorio: WAIT. WHAT?
Woman: I SAID I'M AFRAID
WE CAN'T MOVE HIM.
HIS MATCH ISN'T OVER YET.
Leorio: I DON'T GET IT.
HOW IS THE MATCH NOT OVER?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
Woman: HE'S STILL ALIVE,
JUST UNCONSCIOUS.
OH, DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
THIS WAS A FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
ONE OF THEM HAD TO EITHER DIE
OR ADMIT DEFEAT.
HE'S STILL ALIVE,
AND HE HASN'T SURRENDERED.
( giggles )
( Leorio scoffs )
TALK ABOUT SPLITTING HAIRS.
Killua: MAYBE, BUT YOU'VE
GOTTA ADMIT SHE'S RIGHT.
Gon: I'M WITH KILLUA.
( Leorio growls )
THAT'S HOW IT IS?
ALL RIGHT, KURAPIKA.
GET OVER THERE, AND PUT
THAT LOSER OUT OF HIS MISERY.
Kurapika: I REFUSE.
Leorio: WH‐‐HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, REFUSE?!
Kurapika: THE FIGHT
WAS ALREADY OVER.
IT WAS CLEAR TO ME
THAT BY THE TIME I PUNCHED HIM,
HE HAD ALREADY LOST
THE WILL TO FIGHT.
I WILL NOT CONTINUE
FIGHTING A LOSER.
Leorio: SERIOUSLY?!
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?!
'CAUSE THOSE GUYS ARE CLAIMING
THE MATCH HASN'T EVEN ENDED YET!
Kurapika:
I WILL LEAVE THAT TO HIM.
Leorio: HUH?!
Kurapika: HE CAN DECIDE
HIS OWN FATE
JUST AS SOON AS HE REVIVES.
Leorio: COME ON.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH TIME,
AND IT'S RUNNING OUT FAST.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO JUST
SIT AROUND HERE AND WAIT.
Kurapika:
MY MIND'S MADE UP, LEORIO.
Leorio: AH, GIMME A BREAK!
Killua: HEY, I CAN KILL HIM
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
Gon: KILLUA?
Killua: NEVER KILLED ANYONE
BEFORE, HAVE YOU?
ARE YOU SCARED?
Kurapika: WHETHER OR NOT
MURDER IS FRIGHTENING
HAS NEVER ENTERED MY MIND.
REGARDLESS,
THIS IS A ONE‐ON‐ONE BATTLE.
YOU CAN'T INTERFERE.
Killua: FINE. I WON'T ARGUE.
EXCEPT IF YOU WERE
A TEAM PLAYER,
YOU WOULDN'T
BE ACTING SO SELFISH.
Leorio: HEY! YOU SAID
SOMETHING USEFUL FOR ONCE.
DO THAT MORE OFTEN.
DON'T YOU KNOW YOU'RE
SCREWIN' UP OUR CHANCES?
Kurapika: THAT'S TRUE, BUT IT
DOESN'T CHANGE MY POSITION.
Leorio: YOU STUBBORN
LITTLE IDIOT.
ALL RIGHT!
TIME FOR MAJORITY RULE!
PRESS "O" TO KILL THE BASTARD
OR "X" TO LET HIM LIVE.
‐ ( Tonpa chuckles )
‐ Leorio: READY, AND...
( wind blowing )
WHY IN THE HELL
ISN'T IT WORKING?!
Gon: I BET IT'S CAUSE WE'RE
THE ONES ASKING THE QUESTION.
Leorio: HUH?
Killua: IT LOOKS LIKE
THE TIMERS ONLY WORK
FOR QUESTIONS THE EXAMINERS ASK.
Leorio: I SHOULDA KNOWN.
IN THAT CASE, OKAY!
WE'LL DO IT
THE OLD‐FASHIONED WAY.
RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU
THINK WE SHOULD FINISH HIM!
ME!
HEH. ( gasps )
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
A MINUTE AGO,
YOU WERE TRYING TO GET HIM
TO DO IT JUST LIKE I WAS!
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER!
WHERE'S YOUR TEAM SPIRIT?
Killua: I JUST
DON'T SEE THE POINT.
NOT LIKE HE'S
GONNA CHANGE HIS MIND.
Leorio: HEY, GON, WHY DON'T YOU
THINK WE SHOULD KILL THE GUY?
Gon: I'M WITH KURAPIKA
ON THIS ONE.
HE WAS JUST ABOUT TO SURRENDER
WHEN HE KNOCKED HIM OUT.
WE SHOULD WAIT
FOR HIM TO WAKE UP.
Leorio: BUT THERE'S NO TELLING
HOW LONG THAT'LL TAKE.
I OUGHT TO JUST DO IT.
Tonpa: IT'S BETTER
IF YOU DON'T FORCE THE ISSUE.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT EVERYBODY
TO SHARE THE SAME OPINION.
Leorio: YEAH, WELL,
NOBODY ASKED FOR YOURS, OKAY?
Tonpa: HEY, COME ON. IF YOU
WANTED TO PUT IT TO A VOTE,
YOU KIND OF DID.
( Leorio growls )
FINE!
IF YOU WANNA WAIT, THEN WAIT.
JUST SEE IF I CARE!
Gon: LEORIO, WAIT!
( Leorio mutters )
WHAT IS WRONG WITH THESE PEOPLE?
Gon: AH, HE'S SULKING.
Leorio: NONE OF THIS MATTERS
IF WE GET STUCK HERE.
AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO GETS IT?
Killua: LET'S JUST
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
( Tonpa thinking )
FOOLS.
HE TOTALLY FALLING FOR IT,
THE TRAP OF MAJORITY RULE.
WHEN FIVE PEOPLE
WHO BARELY KNOW EACH OTHER
ARE TRYING
TO DECIDE ON SOMETHING,
YOU'D THINK VOTING
WOULD BE THE EASIEST
AND MOST EFFICIENT WAY TO DO IT.
PEOPLE TEND TO THINK THAT VOTING
EMPOWERS THE INDIVIDUAL,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
IT CAN JUST AS EASILY
TURN THE MAJORITY
AGAINST THE MINORITY.
WHEN SOMEONE KEEPS
FINDING HIMSELF IN THE MINORITY,
HIS OPINION IS ALWAYS REJECTED.
HIS ANGER, ALIENATION,
AND FRUSTRATION
MAKE HIM RESENT
AND ANTAGONIZE THE GROUP.
EVENTUALLY,
IT TEARS THE TEAM APART.
AFTER ALL, IT'S EVERYONE
FOR HIMSELF IN THE HUNTER EXAM.
THE FEELING YOU GET WHEN YOU'RE
FORCED TO FOLLOW A PATH
THAT OTHER PEOPLE SET
CAN BE A REAL PAIN.
IT'S ANNOYING
AND MAKES YOU FEEL FOOLISH.
BUT NOW HE'S ALL CAUGHT UP
IN THE WHOLE
MAJORITY‐RULE SCENARIO,
AND HE'S STARTING TO USE IT
EVEN WHEN HE DOESN'T HAVE TO.
AND THEN HE MADE THE MISTAKE
OF DISCUSSING THE OPTIONS
BEFORE HE CALLED FOR THE VOTE.
HE EVEN ASKED
FOR A SHOW OF HANDS,
MAJORITY RULE
IN ITS WORST FORM.
WHEN PEOPLE ARE JUST PRESSING
BUTTONS ON THEIR TIMERS,
THEY'VE GOT ANONYMITY.
BUT WHEN YOU RAISE YOUR HAND,
EVERYBODY KNOWS
EXACTLY WHAT SIDE YOU'RE ON
AND WHO'S STRAYING
FROM THE CROWD,
AND IF YOU'RE IN THE MINORITY,
THERE'S NO CHANCE
FOR A REBUTTAL.
WHEN SOMEONE'S OPINIONS
ARE CONSTANTLY REJECTED,
THEY FEEL LIKE THEIR VOICE
ISN'T BEING HEARD,
AND THE GROUP BREAKS DOWN.
AND IN OUR CASE, IT MEANS ALL
FIVE OF US WILL FAIL THE EXAM.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
( chuckles )
Sedokan: THE ATMOSPHERE ON
THE OTHER SIDE IS PRETTY GRIM.
( woman laughs )
Hunter:
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU...
HISOKA.
I'M NOT AN EXAMINER THIS YEAR.
I'M HERE FOR REVENGE.
EVER SINCE THE LAST EXAM,
ALL I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT
IS KILLING YOU.
AND TODAY I GET PAYBACK
FOR ALL THE SCARS YOU GAVE ME!
( Hisoka chuckles )
THOSE SCARS ARE BUT A SYMBOL
OF YOUR INCOMPETENCE
AS AN EXAMINER.
DON'T BLAME ME
FOR YOUR INADEQUACIES.
Hunter: SHUT UP!
( chuckles )
NOW PREPARE TO DIE.
Hisoka: TWO‐BLADE STYLE, EH?
( gasps )
♪♪♪
Hunter: ALL‐DIRECTION
FOUR‐BLADE STYLE!
TAKE THIS!
( roars )
I'M NOT DONE!
( laughs )
UP, DOWN, LEFT, RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT NOWHERE TO RUN.
YOU'RE GONNA BE CUT UP
FROM EVERY ANGLE
BY MY ENDLESS BARRAGE OF BLADES!
YOU CAN'T DODGE
MY ATTACKS FOREVER.
I'M GONNA HAVE YOU
WRITHING IN PAIN,
AND I'LL SAVOR EVERY SECOND!
‐ Hisoka: HM.
‐ Hunter: HAH!
AND THEN YOU'LL DIE, HISOKA!
( gasps )
♪♪♪
Hisoka: DODGING YOUR ATTACKS
WOULD HAVE BEEN DIFFICULT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
( slurps )
STOPPING YOUR BLADES, HOWEVER...
( Hunter thinking )
IMPOSSIBLE.
IT TOOK ME
MORE THAN SIX MONTHS OF TRAINING
TO MASTER CATCHING THOSE BLADES.
Hisoka: MY, MY.
THAT WAS EASIER THAN EXPECTED.
NICE TRY,
BUT IT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
( Hunter gasping )
DAMN IT!
( slice )
♪♪♪
Hisoka: HMM?
Announcer: FIRST TO PASS
THE THIRD PHASE,
HISOKA, NUMBER 44.
TIME ELAPSED,
6 HOURS, 17 MINUTES.
♪♪♪
( Leorio scoffs )
( Tonpa grunts )
( chuckles )
Killua: WHAT'S UP, GON?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
Gon: YEAH.
Killua: OH, I SEE.
‐ HEY.
‐ Leorio: HMM?
Killua: IT'S LOOKING MORE AND
MORE LIKE HE'S ALREADY DEAD.
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Gon: WELL, HE'S BEEN LYING THERE
FOR A LONG TIME NOW,
AND HE HASN'T MOVED
OR ANYTHING.
Leorio: DAMN IT. IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO TELL FROM THIS FAR AWAY.
HEY, YOU!
WE WANT TO GO OVER THERE
AND CHECK HIS BODY!
Woman: WHAT WAS THAT?
Leorio: HE MIGHT
BE DEAD ALREADY,
AND WE JUST WANNA SEE IT
FOR OURSELVES.
Woman: IT'S LIKE
I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
HE'S ONLY UNCONSCIOUS.
Leorio: YEAH, WELL,
HOW MANY HOURS
DO YOU THINK WE'VE BEEN HERE?
YOU THINK WE'RE JUST
GONNA TAKE YOUR WORD FOR IT?
Woman: CARE TO MAKE
A WAGER, THEN?
Leorio: WAGER?
A WAGER ON WHAT?
Woman: ON WHETHER
HE'S DEAD OR ALIVE.
Leorio: WHAT ARE THE STAKES?
WHAT ARE YOU PROPOSING?
( ticking )
Woman: TIME.
Leorio: TIME?
Woman: WE WILL SETTLE OUR MATCH
THROUGH GAMBLING,
BETTING TIME INSTEAD OF CHIPS.
( clink )
LOOK AT THE MONITOR
ON THE WALL.
WE'LL EACH HAVE 50 HOURS
WITH WHICH TO WAGER,
AND BETS CAN ONLY BE PLACED
IN 10‐HOUR INCREMENTS.
WE BET UNTIL ONE OF OUR CLOCKS
REACHES ZERO.
Leorio: GAMBLING WITH TIME, HUH?
( buzzer )
Woman: WE'LL TAKE TURNS
DECIDING WHAT TO BET ON.
IF YOUR CREDIT REACHES ZERO,
YOU WILL HAVE 50 FEWER HOURS
TO ESCAPE THE TOWER.
WHAT IF YOU HIT ZERO FIRST?
Woman: 50 YEARS
WILL BE ADDED TO OUR SENTENCES.
( Leorio gasps )
Woman: IF YOU
ACCEPT THESE TERMS,
I'LL CONFIRM
WHETHER HE'S ALIVE OR DEAD.
Lippo: LEROUTE,
SENTENCED TO 112 YEARS
FOR TRAFFICKING
ENDANGERED WILDLIFE
AND BREAKING GAMBLING LAWS.
THIS KIND OF MATCH
IS RIGHT UP HER ALLEY.
Leorio: MAN,
THAT WOMAN'S CRAZY...
BETTING WITH
HER OWN JAIL TIME LIKE THAT.
Kurapika: CONSIDER
YOUR ANSWER CAREFULLY.
IF YOU LOSE,
WE'LL ALL HAVE 50 FEWER HOURS
TO CLEAR THE TOWER.
Leorio: YEAH, WELL,
NOBODY'S ASKIN' YOU.
IN CASE YOU FORGOT,
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO GOT US INTO THIS STUPID
DAMN MESS IN THE FIRST PLACE!
Kurapika: VERY WELL.
YOU WON'T HEAR
ANOTHER WORD FROM ME.
( Leorio scoffs )
Gon: COME ON! WE SHOULDN'T
BE FIGHTING EACH OTHER.
( Killua sighs )
( Tonpa chuckles )
( thinking )
KEEP IT UP, BOYS. KEEP IT UP.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT!
I ACCEPT YOUR DAMN CHALLENGE!
Leroute: OKAY.
I CHOSE OUR FIRST BET,
SO YOU MAY SET THE ANTE.
DECIDE HOW MANY HOURS
WE'LL WAGER
ON WHETHER HE'S ALIVE OR DEAD.
Leorio:
I BET 10 HOURS HE'S ALIVE.
( Bendot chuckles )
WHAT THE HELL?
HE WAS JUST WHINING
ABOUT MAJITANI BEING DEAD.
( Leroute laughs )
ALL RIGHT, THEN. LET'S CONFIRM.
Kurapika: PLAYING IT SAFE,
AREN'T YOU?
Leorio: I THOUGHT YOU
WEREN'T GONNA SAY ANOTHER WORD.
( Kurapika grumbles )
( Tonpa thinking )
10 HOURS, HUH?
( Leorio thinking )
IT'S THE SMART MOVE.
EVEN IF I'M WRONG
AND HE IS DEAD,
THEN KURAPIKA
WILL HAVE WON HIS ROUND.
IT'S PROGRESS, AT LEAST.
IF I BET THAT HE'S DEAD
AND HE'S JUST OUT COLD,
IT'S ADDING INSULT TO INJURY.
♪♪♪
( pulse thumping )
Leroute: SEE?
HE'S ONLY UNCONSCIOUS.
Leorio: SO IT SEEMS.
Gon: YES!
LEORIO'S TAKEN AN EARLY LEAD!
‐ Killua: THIS IS BAD.
‐ Gon: HUH?
Killua: MAYBE HE WON'T WAKE UP,
NO MATTER HOW LONG WE WAIT.
Kurapika: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
Killua: DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHEN SHE WALKED BY
THE GUY ON THE FLOOR?
Kurapika: WHAT OF IT?
Killua: WELL, I WAS PRETTY SURE
HE WAS ALREADY DEAD BY THEN.
BUT WHEN I THOUGHT ABOUT IT,
I REALIZED HE'S MORE USEFUL
TO HIS TEAM ALIVE
AS LONG
AS HE STAYS UNCONSCIOUS.
SEE, IF HE DOESN'T WAKE UP
BEFORE THE TIME RUNS OUT,
THEIR SENTENCES
WILL BE SHORTENED BY 72 YEARS.
Gon: SO IF HE DOESN'T WAKE UP
AT ALL, THEN THAT MEANS WE‐‐
Killua: THAT'S MY POINT.
Kurapika: SO THAT'S BEEN
THEIR INTENTION ALL ALONG.
Leroute: OKAY, IT'S YOUR TURN.
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO BET ON NEXT?
Leorio: LET ME SEE.
I SAY WE BET ON WHETHER OR NOT
HE'S ACTUALLY UNCONSCIOUS.
Leroute: HUH?
Killua: OH, I GET IT.
Tonpa: HMM?
( Majitani thinking )
WAIT. WHAT?!
THIS WASN'T ON THE NOTE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
WHEN I WOKE UP, THERE WAS A NOTE
LYING ON THE GROUND NEXT TO ME.
IT SAID, "KEEP PRETENDING
YOU'RE OUT COLD.
HIDE THIS NOTE IN YOUR MOUTH."
I KNEW
WHAT I WAS SUPPOSED TO DO!
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS STAY DOWN
UNTIL THE CLOCK RAN OUT,
AND WE'D GET 72 YEARS
OFF OUR SENTENCES.
BUT NOW WHAT?
DO I STAY DOWN
AND KEEP PRETENDING?
Leroute: ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BET 20 HOURS
THAT HE REALLY IS OUT COLD.
( Majitani thinking )
OKAY, I GOT IT.
THAT'S THE PLAY, THEN.
I'LL JUST KEEP ACTING
LIKE I'M UNCONSCIOUS.
Leroute: THE QUESTION IS
HOW DO YOU PROPOSE
WE GO ABOUT CONFIRMING THIS?
Leorio: OH.
IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
( grunting )
HEAVY BASTARD.
I FIGURED I WOULD
JUST PUSH HIM OFF THE EDGE.
( Majitani thinking ) THAT'S
THE WORST IDEA I'VE EVER HEARD!
Leorio: IF HE
REALLY IS UNCONSCIOUS,
HE'LL FALL TO HIS DEATH,
AND THAT'S THE END OF IT.
Leroute: ARE YOU INSANE?
HIS MATCH
HASN'T BEEN DECIDED YET.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN ACCEPT THOSE TERMS.
Leorio: DON'T WORRY.
IF HE FALLS
AND KICKS THE BUCKET,
WE'LL FORFEIT THE MATCH,
GIVING YOU
A GRAND TOTAL OF TWO WINS.
THAT WORK FOR YOU?
Leroute: IT DOES.
VERY WELL, THEN.
( Majitani thinking )
WHAT WAS THAT?!
COME ON!
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT MY LIFE HERE!
Leroute: IN THAT CASE,
I'M CHANGING MY BET.
I BET 40 HOURS THAT HE
ISN'T UNCONSCIOUS AFTER ALL.
THAT'S EVERYTHING I HAVE LEFT.
( Leorio chuckles )
LITTLE SNEAK.
FINALLY SHOWING
YOUR TRUE COLORS.
( heartbeat racing )
GUESS I'LL LET GO, THEN.
Majitani: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA! HOLD ON!
DON'T LET GO!
I'M AWAKE! I'M AWAKE!
YAAH!
WAIT! WAIT!
I'M GONNA FALL!
Leorio: GOOD MORNING.
HEH.
( Majitani gasps )
YOU'RE BOTH COMPLETE LUNATICS!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
I LOST PLAIN AND SIMPLE, OKAY?
FORGET REDUCING MY SENTENCE!
I'M GOING BACK TO PRISON,
WHERE IT'S SAFE, DAMN IT!
Leroute: YOU KNEW HE WAS AWAKE,
DIDN'T YOU?
Leorio: BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
BUT I'M PRE‐MED.
THE WAY HIS EYES WERE MOVING
WAS A DEAD GIVEAWAY.
Leroute: EVEN SO, YOU HAVE
ONLY 20 HOURS REMAINING.
Leorio: I KNOW, BUT AT LEAST NOW
WE'RE IN A BETTER POSITION
WITH A TWO‐ONE LEAD.
NOW...
LET'S KEEP THIS BALL ROLLING.
THE CHOICE IS YOURS,
SO WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
♪♪♪
Narrator: MAJITANI
THROWS IN THE TOWEL,
GIVING GON AND HIS FRIENDS
A TWO‐TO‐ONE LEAD.
HOWEVER, IN THE MATCH
WHERE THEY GAMBLE FOR TIME,
THEY'RE DOWN 80 TO 20.
IT'S LEROUTE'S TURN
TO PICK THE NEXT BET,
BUT WHAT WILL SHE CHOOSE?
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"TROUBLE WITH THE GAMBLE."
BULL‐‐BULL‐‐BULLDOG!
( barks )
♪♪♪