( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Tonpa: I...
GIVE UP!
‐ Killua: HUH?
‐ Leorio: WHAT?
BASTARD!
I KNEW WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE TRUSTED YOU!
ALL YOU'RE GOOD FOR IS
SABOTAGING THE OTHER APPLICANTS.
YOU'RE JUST
A WORTHLESS PIECE OF GARBAGE!
Tonpa: IT TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
THAT'S WHAT I DO EVERY YEAR,
AND I'LL KEEP DOING IT
FOR AS LONG AS I CAN.
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT PASSING THE HUNTER EXAM.
I'M IN IT FOR THE THRILLS.
♪♪♪
Narrator: THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE EXAM
IS UNDER WAY AT TRICK TOWER,
WHERE LONG‐TERM PRISONERS
ARE HELD.
GON AND FRIENDS
HAVE CHOSEN TO PARTAKE
IN A FIVE‐ON‐FIVE BATTLE
WITH SOME OF THE INMATES.
THANKS TO TONPA, THEY'VE ALREADY
SUFFERED THEIR FIRST LOSS.
THE NEXT ROUND WILL PIT GON
AGAINST SEDOKAN.
WHO KNOWS WHAT
THE UPCOMING BATTLE WILL BRING?
Sedokan: NOW, THEN,
AS YOU'VE ALL PROBABLY NOTICED,
I'M NOT TERRIBLY STRONG.
I DON'T ENJOY FIGHTING
OR RUNNING, JUMPING,
ANYTHING PHYSICAL, REALLY.
Gon: I LIKE THAT STUFF
A LOT MORE THAN THINKING.
I GUESS I'VE NEVER REALLY BEEN
ALL THAT GREAT AT USING MY HEAD.
Sedokan: THOUGHT SO,
SO I CAME UP WITH A GAME,
ONE I THINK WE'LL BOTH ENJOY.
Gon: A GAME?
Sedokan: YES, A SIMPLE GAME
THAT DOESN'T RELY
ON MENTAL OR PHYSICAL ACTIVITY.
Gon: WHAT IS IT?
( Sedokan chuckles )
WE EACH LIGHT A CANDLE
AT THE SAME TIME,
AND WHOEVER'S CANDLE
GOES OUT FIRST IS THE LOSER.
ALL RIGHT?
Gon: YEP. MAKES SENSE TO ME.
I'M IN! LET'S DO IT!
Sedokan: OKAY. IN THAT CASE...
( chuckles )
( all gasp )
( Tonpa chuckles )
Sedokan: SO WHICH CANDLE
DO YOU WANT TO USE?
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
PRESS "O" FOR THE LONG CANDLE,
OR PRESS "X" IF YOU WOULD
RATHER HAVE THE SHORT ONE.
CHOOSE BY MAJORITY RULE.
Leorio: SO WE
HAVE TO CHOOSE ONE?
THIS IS A DAMN TRAP.
NORMALLY, YOU'D WANT
TO GO FOR THE LONG ONE,
WHICH MEANS THAT LOWLIFE MUST'VE
DONE SOMETHING TO SABOTAGE IT.
Kurapika: YES, THAT WOULD BE
THE SAFE ASSUMPTION.
HOWEVER, IT COULD BE A TRICK
AND HE'S ACTUALLY TAMPERED
WITH THE SHORT ONE.
Leorio: HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY...
Kurapika: CORRECT.
THERE IS NO END.
Tonpa: SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE
GOT YOURSELVES A REAL DILEMMA.
Leorio: YOU KEEP
YOUR BIG MOUTH SHUT!
Tonpa: YEAH, YEAH.
Kurapika: SOMETHING HAPPENS
WHEN YOU'RE PRESENTED
WITH AN OBVIOUSLY
BIASED CHOICE.
SUSPICION MOUNTS,
AND THE DECISION‐MAKING PROCESS
SEIZES UP.
YES, THIS TRULY IS A DILEMMA.
MOREOVER,
THE PSYCHOLOGICAL IMPACT
OF MAKING THE WRONG CHOICE
IS MUCH GREATER
THAN IF THE OPTION WAS BETWEEN
TWO EVENLY MATCHED OPTIONS.
( buzzer sounds )
( Leorio groans )
( Kurapika chuckles )
Sedokan: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
PLEASE, TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU NEED.
IT'S A MAJORITY DECISION,
BUT FEEL FREE
TO TALK ABOUT IT FIRST.
NO RUSH.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME,
BELIEVE ME.
Gon: HEY! WHAT SHOULD I PICK?
Leorio: DAMN IT.
GOOD QUESTION.
( Sedokan giggles )
Kurapika: GON,
THE CHOICE IS UP TO YOU!
PICK WHICHEVER CANDLE
YOU THINK IS THE BEST OPTION.
THAT'S HOW WE'LL ALL VOTE.
Killua: ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IT'S JUST THAT HE
DOESN'T THINK THINGS THROUGH.
Kurapika: INSTEAD OF FRETTING
OVER THE CHOICE,
LET'S JUST PUT OUR FAITH
IN GON'S INSTINCTS.
Killua:
TRUST HIS INSTINCTS, HUH?
Gon: OH, I GET TO CHOOSE?
IN THAT CASE, I'LL GO
WITH THE LONG CANDLE, OKAY?
( Sedokan chuckles )
YOU WANT THE LONG ONE?
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
Gon: OF COURSE!
THE LONGER THE CANDLE,
THE LONGER IT BURNS.
IT'S KIND OF A NO‐BRAINER.
Leorio: WELL,
THAT'S ONE WAY TO LOOK AT IT.
Killua: I TOLD YOU HE WASN'T
GONNA THINK IT THROUGH.
Kurapika: WELL, THAT SETTLES IT.
Leorio: YEAH,
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'D BE ABLE
TO FIGURE OUT
WHICH ONE'S THE TRAP, ANYWAY.
( Tonpa chuckles )
Sedokan: OKAY.
LOOKS LIKE
YOU GET THE LONG CANDLE,
AND I'LL TAKE THE SHORT ONE.
( gears grinding )
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S LIGHT 'EM TOGETHER.
( Lippo chuckles )
( munching )
( laughs )
Killua: SO, UH, NORMALLY
HOW LONG WOULD IT TAKE
THAT CANDLE TO BURN?
Kurapika: I WOULD ESTIMATE
FIVE TO SIX HOURS.
( wind gusting )
Gon: OH, WOW.
THAT SURE WAS A CLOSE ONE.
( wind continues )
Leorio: THERE'S A PRETTY STRONG
WIND COMING UP FROM BELOW.
THEY'LL HAVE TO STAY STILL,
KEEP AN EYE ON THOSE FLAMES.
THERE'S NO CHANCE
TO LET THEIR GUARDS DOWN.
♪♪♪
( Sedokan laughs )
IF YOU DON'T PAY ATTENTION,
YOUR CANDLE WILL BLOW OUT.
Gon: YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE PLANNING
TO DO SOMETHING BAD.
AREN'T YOU?
OTHERWISE, YOUR SHORT CANDLE
WOULD GO OUT FIRST.
I WON'T DO ANYTHING.
( laughs ) 'CAUSE, YOU SEE,
I CAME PREPARED.
( Gon gasps )
♪♪♪
( gasps )
( Sedokan chuckles )
THERE. SEE?
Leorio: HEY, TAKE A LOOK
AT GON'S CANDLE.
THE FLAME SUDDENLY
GOT A LOT STRONGER.
Kurapika: I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
HE SOMEHOW LACED GON'S CANDLE
WITH GUNPOWDER
OR SOME OTHER ACCELERANT.
THAT'S WHY IT'S
BURNING SO MUCH FASTER.
Gon: OW!
HOT! HOT, HOT, HOT!
Killua: AT THIS RATE,
HE'S ONLY GOT
ANOTHER TWO OR THREE MINUTES.
Leorio: DAMN!
HEY, THAT WAS A DIRTY TRICK!
I KNEW IT! YOU MESSED WITH
THE LONG ONE, DIDN'T YOU?
( Sedokan chuckles )
( thinking)
YOU'RE WRONG.
I HAD FOUR CANDLES
PREPPED AND READY.
THE DISPARATE CHOICE
I PRESENTED YOU WITH
WAS MERELY CAMOUFLAGE
FOR THE ACTUAL TRAP.
YOU ASSUMED THAT ONE OF THE TWO
WOULD BE A TRICK CANDLE.
THE CHOICES WERE SO UNEVEN,
YOU NEVER STOPPED
TO CONSIDER THE POSSIBILITY
THAT I'D RIGGED BOTH OF THEM.
IN THE END,
IT DIDN'T REALLY MATTER
WHICH OF THE CANDLES YOU PICKED.
LONG OR SHORT,
I'D HAVE HANDED YOU
AN OIL‐SOAKED CANDLE EITHER WAY.
‐ ( Gon laughs )
‐ Sedokan: MM?
Gon: I GUESS NOW THAT THE FLAME
IS BURNING SO MUCH STRONGER...
IT'LL TAKE A LOT MORE
THAN A LITTLE BREEZE
TO PUT IT OUT.
Sedokan: HUH?
HE'S FAST!
( Gon laughs )
I WIN!
Leorio: YES!
( Bendot growls )
Lippo: OOH.
THAT ONE'S GOT A REAL SPRING
IN HIS STEP, DOESN'T HE?
AND HE KNOWS HOW TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF A BAD SITUATION.
IMPRESSIVE. VERY IMPRESSIVE.
Gon: ALL RIGHT! I WON!
Leorio: YOU SURE AS HELL DID!
THAT'S ONE WIN FOR US!
ONCE KURAPIKA AND I WIN,
WE CAN ADVANCE.
Prisoner: HUMPH! IDIOT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR RELYING ON CHEAP TRICKS.
Sedokan: DAMN.
Prisoner: PROPER DECEPTION
CALLS FOR A LITTLE SACRIFICE.
WATCH AND LEARN.
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TAKE THE NEXT ONE.
♪♪♪
( Leorio gasps )
( prisoner yells )
♪♪♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
( Majitani laughs )
THE NEXT CONTENDER'S
GOTTA FACE ME!
( laughs )
Leorio: MAN, THAT IS
ONE FREAKY BODY.
Killua: YEAH, AND FACE.
Majitani: DO YOU SEE THIS, KID?
I'VE KILLED 19 PEOPLE SO FAR,
BUT IT'S SUCH AN UNEVEN NUMBER.
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
IT KINDA BUGS ME.
HEH HEH.
I'VE BEEN LOOKIN' FORWARD
TO MEETING NUMBER 20
FOR A WHILE.
( laughs )
Leorio: OH, GREAT. WE'RE DEALING
WITH A SERIAL KILLER?
Majitani: THE ONLY WAY
I'LL DO THIS
IS IF WE PUT
OUR LIVES ON THE LINE.
IT'S ALL OR NOTHIN'.
DO YOU HEAR ME, BRAT?
GIMME BLOOD,
SPILLING ENTRAILS,
AND SWEET AGONY!
( laughs )
( thinking )
OH, YEAH.
YOU MUST BE TERRIFIED RIGHT NOW.
‐ Kurapika: VERY WELL.
‐ Majitani: EH?
Kurapika: YOU CAN DECIDE
HOW WE SETTLE THIS,
AND I WILL ACCEPT IT.
( Majitani laughs )
YOU'VE GOT SOME BALLS, KID.
( thinking ) HEH. BUT I KNOW
YOU'RE QUAKING IN YOUR BOOTS.
HOW LONG CAN YOU KEEP UP
THE TOUGH GUY ACT?
THEN YOU'RE ACCEPTING
A DEATH MATCH.
WE GO UNTIL ONE OF US DIES
OR ADMITS DEFEAT
AND NOT A SECOND EARLIER,
UNDERSTAND?
HOWEVER...
DON'T THINK ADMITTING DEFEAT
OR SURRENDER WILL STOP ME.
NEVER HAS, AND,
IN FACT, IT NEVER WILL,
SO GET IT OUT
OF YOUR HEAD RIGHT NOW.
( laughs )
( thinking ) WELL,
SCARED STIFF NOW, AREN'T YA?
Kurapika: FINE. I ACCEPT.
Majitani: EH?
Kurapika: SHALL WE BEGIN?
( Majitani thinking )
WHAT IS HE, AN IDIOT?
DIDN'T HE HEAR WHAT I JUST SAID?
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
WE'RE FIGHTING TO THE DEATH.
WAIT. HE SHOULD BE TREMBLING
JUST AT THE SIGHT OF ME.
HOLD ON!
THERE'S SOMETHING
I FORGOT TO MENTION.
ABSOLUTELY NO WEAPONS
ARE ALLOWED,
SO THIS HAS TO BE
A SIMPLE FISTFIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH I'VE BEEN HIRED
AS AN EXAMINER,
I AM STILL A PRISONER,
AND THAT MEANS I'M
NOT ALLOWED TO CARRY WEAPONS.
Kurapika: THAT MAKES SENSE.
I UNDERSTAND.
IS THERE
ANYTHING ELSE YOU FORGOT?
IF NOT, I'D LIKE TO GET STARTED.
Majitani: EH. ( grumbles )
( thinking )
THAT LITTLE BASTARD.
HE HAD A CONCEALED WEAPON.
I'M GLAD I SAID SOMETHING
BEFORE IT WAS TOO LATE.
BUT FROM THE LOOK OF IT,
HE DOESN'T RELY ON IT MUCH.
IS HE REALLY THAT CONFIDENT
IN HIS COMBAT SKILLS?
NO. I DON'T THINK
IT'S THAT, EITHER.
HEH. I BET
HE'S DYING TO RUN AWAY,
BUT HE DOESN'T WANT
TO LOOK LIKE A COWARD
IN FRONT OF HIS FRIENDS.
OR MAYBE HE'S JUST SO STUPID
THAT HE DOESN'T COMPREHEND
HOW SCARY I AM.
HE CAN'T EVEN WRAP
HIS HEAD AROUND IT.
YEAH! YEAH, YEAH,
THAT'S GOTTA BE IT.
( chuckles )
WELL, IN THAT CASE, I'VE GOT
A FEW CARDS UP MY SLEEVE
FOR DEALING WITH FOOLS LIKE HIM.
( inhales )
( grunting )
Leorio: HEY, GUYS,
IS KURAPIKA GONNA BE OKAY?
'CAUSE IF YOU ASK ME,
THIS GUY LOOKS PRETTY DANGEROUS.
( Killua thinking ) WHAT LOOKS
SO DANGEROUS ABOUT HIM?
IT'S OBVIOUS‐‐
WELL, TO ME, ANYWAY‐‐
THAT THIS GUY'S A BIG TALKER.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE GUTS TO HIT
ANYBODY, LET ALONE KILL THEM.
Gon: I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT IT MUCH.
Killua: HUH?
Leorio: WHY NOT?
Gon: BECAUSE WHEN I'M
LOOKING AT HIM,
I DON'T GET CHILLS OR ANYTHING.
Leorio: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Majitani: I THINK IT'S TIME
TO SHOW YOU MY SECRET WEAPON!
RAAAH!
THE FIRST OF MANY!
Leorio: HERE HE COMES!
♪♪♪
( growls )
Tonpa: OH, MY GOD.
Leorio: HE JUST PUNCHED A HOLE
IN THE DAMN FLOOR.
( Majitani thinking )
THAT WAS PERFECT.
AND THAT'S NOT THE ONLY TRICK
UP MY SLEEVE.
( chuckles )
( Kurapika gasps )
♪♪♪
Leorio: LOOK AT HIS TATTOO.
IT'S A SPIDER WITH 12 LEGS,
AND THAT MEANS...
Tonpa: YEAH. I RECOGNIZE IT.
ANYBODY WHO WANTS TO BE A HUNTER
HAS HEARD ALL ABOUT TATTOOS
LIKE THAT ONE.
IT'S THE SYMBOL WORN BY MEMBERS
OF THAT NEFARIOUS BAND
OF VICIOUS THIEVES,
THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Gon: REALLY?
Leorio: YEAH. NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
ITS MEANING IS WIDELY KNOWN.
IN FACT, I‐‐I HEARD ABOUT THEM
STRAIGHT FROM KURAPIKA.
( Majitani thinking )
BETWEEN THE STEEL IMPLANTS
THAT GIVE ME THE STRENGTH TO
SHATTER ROCK WITH MY BARE HANDS
AND THE SYMBOL
OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE,
THEY MAKE ONE HELL OF A COMBO.
NOBODY WOULD WANT TO FIGHT ME
AFTER GETTING A PEEK AT THOSE.
( laughs )
AW, WHAT'S WRONG?
CAT GOT YOUR TONGUE?
NAME'S MAJITANI.
I'M ONE OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE'S
FOUR DEVAS.
THAT FIRST STRIKE
WAS JUST AN INTRODUCTION.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO GIVE UP.
IF YOU DO,
I'M STILL WILLING TO‐‐
EH?
( Kurapika panting )
Majitani: HEY,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU‐‐
( gasps )
( groaning )
WAIT!
WAIT! I GET IT!
HOLD ON! WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T!
YOU WIN, OKAY?
( all gasping )
( Killua whistles )
Kurapika: TAKE THIS TO HEART.
FIRST, A GENUINE
PHANTOM TROUPE TATTOO
HAS THE MEMBER'S NUMBER
INSCRIBED ON THE SPIDER'S BACK.
SECOND, THEY DON'T BOTHER
TALLYING THE PEOPLE
THEY'VE KILLED,
BECAUSE IT'S IRRELEVANT
TO THEM.
AND THIRD,
DON'T EVER MENTION
THE PHANTOM TROUPE TO ME AGAIN.
IF YOU DO,
I WILL KILL YOU
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
♪♪♪
Tonpa: OH, WOW.
Leorio: KURAPIKA.
Killua: YEAH, I SAW THAT ONE
COMING FROM A MILE AWAY.
Leorio: HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
Kurapika: YES. I'M NOT INJURED.
Leorio: NO, I MEAN IS IT SAFE
FOR US TO BE
AROUND YOU RIGHT NOW?
( Kurapika sighs )
FROM THE FIRST MOMENT I SAW HIM,
I KNEW HE WASN'T NEARLY
AS POWERFUL AS HE LOOKED,
AND IN MY MIND,
I KNEW RIGHT FROM THE START
THAT THE TATTOO WAS A FAKE,
BUT AS SOON
AS I SAW THAT SPIDER,
MY VISION WENT
ALMOST COMPLETELY RED.
Leorio: WELL, NOBODY'S
GONNA BLAME YOU FOR THAT.
Kurapika: TO BE
PERFECTLY HONEST,
WHENEVER I SEE A SPIDER,
ANY SPIDER,
ALL MY RATIONALE COLLAPSES,
AND I TURN PRIMAL.
( all gasp )
Leorio: YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD US,
LIKE, A LONG TIME AGO.
Kurapika: THAT CAN
ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
THE RAGE INSIDE ME
REMAINS AS STRONG AS EVER.
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD BE HAPPY.
Gon: I THINK
WE OUGHT TO KEEP KURAPIKA
AWAY FROM ANY SPIDERS
FROM NOW ON.
Leorio: OH, YEAH.
Bendot: DAMN YOU, MAJITANI.
YOU WERE COMPLETELY WORTHLESS
OUT THERE.
THOSE FACIAL SCARS ON HIM ARE
FROM A BOTCHED PLASTIC SURGERY.
THAT'S ONE HELL OF A FRAUD
HE PULLED OFF.
OKAY. YOU KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING, RIGHT?
AFTER TWO LOSSES,
IT'S DO OR DIE.
Woman: I'LL HANDLE IT.
IN FACT, I KNOW JUST THE THING.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT! TIME FOR ME
TO SECURE OUR VICTORY!
Narrator: WITH KURAPIKA'S
TRIUMPH OVER MAJITANI,
THEY ONLY NEED ONE MORE WIN
TO CLEAR THE TRIAL
AND REACH THE NEXT PHASE,
BUT THE QUESTION
ON ALL OF THEIR MINDS
IS HOW WILL LEORIO
HANDLE THE NEXT CHALLENGE?
♪♪♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"TRICK TO THE TRICK."
THE TRICK TO THE TRICK
IS TO TRICK‐‐I CAN'T SAY IT.
Killua: SAY IT PROPERLY.
♪♪♪