( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( seabirds calling )
♪♪♪
Mito: "DEAR AUNT MITO
AND GRANDMA,
"HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M DOING PRETTY OKAY MYSELF."
( laughs )
"I JUST PASSED THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
"ISN'T THAT GREAT?
BUT IT HAS BEEN PRETTY TOUGH
GETTING THIS FAR."
( Gon, fading in )
RIGHT AFTER I LEFT THE ISLAND,
THE BOAT I WAS TRAVELING ON
RAN INTO A REALLY BIG STORM.
( thunder crashing )
( Gon only )
IT WASN'T ALL BAD, THOUGH.
THAT'S WHERE I MET
LEORIO AND KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: IF ONLY YOU COULD
BUY CLASS AS WELL, LEORIO.
( Leorio groans )
THAT WAS STRIKE THREE.
STEP OUTSIDE.
TIME TO FINISH OFF
THE FILTHY KURTA BLOODLINE
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
Kurapika:
TAKE THAT BACK, LEORIO!
I SAID TAKE IT BACK.
Leorio: IT'S MR. LEORIO.
♪♪♪
Kurapika: TAKE BACK
WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT MY CLAN.
I WILL FORGIVE YOU
IF YOU REPENT, LEORIO.
Leorio: YOU OWE ME AN APOLOGY,
AND I'M NOT TELLING YOU AGAIN.
I'M NOT REPENTING FOR ANYTHING,
HEAR ME?
Kurapika: VERY WELL.
( crew yelling )
( Gon gasps )
( both gasp )
( together )
DAMN.
Katzo: THANKS, GON.
YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE BACK THERE.
Gon: YEAH, WELL,
I DIDN'T DO IT ALL ALONE.
THOSE TWO OVER THERE
HELPED RESCUE YOU, TOO.
( both gasp )
Katzo: HE'S RIGHT.
THANK YOU BOTH.
Kurapika: PLEASE,
NO THANKS NECESSARY.
Leorio: UH, YEAH, NO PROB.
WE'RE JUST GLAD TO SEE
YOU MADE IT OKAY.
Katzo: ME, TOO! IN FACT,
I OUGHT TO GET BACK
TO MY POST RIGHT AWAY.
( Leorio chuckles )
HMM?
( Kurapika chuckles )
Leorio: WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Kurapika: I'M EMBARRASSED
AT MY BEHAVIOR.
PARDON MY RUDENESS,
MR. LEORIO.
( Leorio gasps )
I WASN'T EXPECTING THAT.
JUST FORGET IT.
YOU CAN DROP THE "MR."
LEORIO'S FINE.
( Kurapika chuckles )
Leorio: I'M SORRY, TOO,
AND I TAKE BACK EVERYTHING
THAT I SAID TO YOU BEFORE.
THAT WAS WRONG OF ME.
Gon: THAT'S WHAT LED
TO THE THREE OF US
TRAVELING TOGETHER,
AND WE HEADED OFF
TO FIND THE SITE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
( birds squawk )
BUT THE JOURNEY
WASN'T EASY AT ALL.
( all gasp )
Woman: TIME FOR THE EXCITING
MULTIPLE‐CHOICE QUIZ!
‐ ( fanfare plays )
‐ ( bird caws )
‐ AND NOW HERE IS YOUR QUESTION.
‐ ( horn blows )
YOU LEARN
BOTH YOUR SON AND YOUR DAUGHTER
HAVE BEEN KIDNAPPED.
YOU WILL ONLY BE ABLE
TO RESCUE ONE OF THEM.
CHOOSE ONE FOR YOUR SON
AND TWO FOR YOUR DAUGHTER.
WHICH OF THESE TWO
WILL YOU RESCUE?
( Leorio thinking )
SHE'S MESSING WITH US.
( yells )
OUT OF THE WAY, KURAPIKA!
THIS OLD HAG
NEEDS TO BE TAUGHT A LESSON,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
SHE GETS IT!
Kurapika: WOULD YOU
PLEASE CALM DOWN?!
Leorio: HOW THE HELL DO YOU
EXPECT ME TO CALM DOWN?!
Kurapika: WE GOT IT RIGHT!
DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO JEOPARDIZE THAT?!
( Leorio gasps )
WE DID?
Kurapika: WE'VE ALREADY GIVEN
THE CORRECT RESPONSE, SILENCE.
ANY OTHER ANSWER
WOULD HAVE BEEN INCORRECT.
( glass shatters )
Kiriko son: PLEASE, SAVE HER!
YOU HAVE TO SAVE MY WIFE!
Kurapika: LEORIO,
SEE TO HIS INJURIES.
♪♪♪
Gon: KURAPIKA!
( Kurapika sighs )
Gon: SO WHO'RE YOU?
( Kiriko gasps )
HOLD ON. HOW CAN YOU TELL
THAT I'M NOT
THE SAME ONE FROM BEFORE?
Gon: HUH? OH, WELL,
YOU LOOK TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
YOUR VOICE IS DIFFERENT, TOO.
IT'S HIGHER AND KINDA THINNER.
( Kiriko laughs )
‐ Gon: HMM?
‐ ( Kiriko laughing )
Gon: WHAT'S UP?
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
IS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
Kiriko father: YOUR SUPERHUMAN
PHYSICAL ABILITY
AND YOUR POWERS OF OBSERVATION
DEFY LOGIC.
YOU, TOO, ARE WORTHY
TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM,
SO YOU PASS.
‐ ( Gon gasps )
‐ ( Leorio chuckles )
( Gon laughs )
THEN THE HUNTER EXAM
FINALLY BEGAN.
Satotz: I APOLOGIZE
FOR THE DELAY.
THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
THE ENTRY PERIOD FOR HUNTER
APPLICANTS IS OFFICIALLY CLOSED,
SO WITH NO FURTHER ADO,
THE HUNTER EXAM WILL NOW BEGIN.
♪♪♪
THE FIRST PHASE IS QUITE SIMPLE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
FOLLOW ME TO THE SECOND PHASE,
SO TRY TO KEEP UP.
Gon: THAT'S WHEN I MADE FRIENDS
WITH A BOY I MET.
HIS NAME'S KILLUA, AND HE'S
ABOUT THE SAME AGE AS ME.
( wheels rolling )
Killua: HEY, HOW OLD ARE YOU?
Gon: 12 YEARS OLD.
Killua: HUH.
( thinking )
SAME AS ME.
I THINK I'LL RUN
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Gon: WHOA! COOL! HA HA!
Killua: MY NAME'S KILLUA.
Gon: HI. I'M GON!
( applicants groaning )
Gon: HEY, WHY DO YOU WANT
TO BE A HUNTER, ANYWAY?
Killua: WHO, ME? I NEVER SAID
I WANTED TO BE A HUNTER.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: I JUST HEARD THE EXAM
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE REALLY HARD.
IT SOUNDED KINDA FUN,
SO HERE I AM,
BUT IT'S NOT AS FUN
AS I THOUGHT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
Gon: WELL, THE THING IS
MY DAD'S A HUNTER,
SO I DECIDED I WAS GONNA BE
A HUNTER JUST LIKE HIM,
NO MATTER WHAT!
Killua: HMM. SO WHAT KIND
OF HUNTER IS HE?
Gon: NO IDEA.
( Killua laughs )
IT'S THE WEIRDEST THING
‐ I'VE EVER HEARD.
‐ Gon: HUH?
Killua: YOU WANT TO BE THE SAME
KIND OF HUNTER AS YOUR DAD,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT HIM? THAT'S NUTS!
Gon: MITO'S THE ONE
WHO RAISED ME,
AND SHE TOLD ME A LITTLE,
BUT I'VE ONLY EVER SEEN HIM
IN PICTURES SHE SHOWED ME
FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
Killua: WAIT. SO WHO'S MITO?
Gon: SHE'S MY AUNT.
Killua: AH.
Gon: SHE SAID THAT MY DAD
TOOK THE HUNTER EXAM
WHEN HE WAS
ONLY 12 YEARS OLD, TOO.
HE PASSED HIS FIRST TRY
AND BECAME A HUNTER.
THAT'S WHEN HE DECIDED
TO LEAVE THE ISLAND.
SO I CAME HERE
IN ORDER TO FIND OUT
WHY HE CHOSE BEING A HUNTER
OVER STAYING AT HOME WITH ME.
♪♪♪
Applicant: THE EXIT!
Second applicant:
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
‐ Gon: GOAL!
‐ Killua: GOAL!
Gon: YEAH! I DID IT!
I FINISHED FIRST!
Killua: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT? I TOTALLY WON.
♪♪♪
Netero: NOW LET'S GO OVER
THE RULES OF THE GAME.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SIMPLY
TAKE THIS BALL AWAY FROM ME.
IF YOU CAN DO THAT BEFORE
THE AIRSHIP ARRIVES, YOU WIN.
( chuckles )
( Gon groans )
( Netero chuckles )
‐ Both: I'VE ALMOST GOT IT!
‐ ( Netero grunts )
♪♪♪
WELL, NOW...
( Gon gasps )
( Killua growls )
Netero: ...EXCELLENT TEAMWORK.
YOU GET AN "A" FOR EFFORT.
( Gon gasps )
THE HUNTER EXAM'S BEEN A LOT
OF FUN WITH KILLUA AROUND.
( Mito fading in )
"...WITH KILLUA AROUND."
WE'RE BEST FRIENDS NOW,
SO THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
( laughs )
♪♪♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
BESIDES KILLUA,
THERE ARE APPLICANTS
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD WHO
CAME TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM,
SO THERE ARE LOTS
OF AMAZING PEOPLE.
Hisoka: HMM.
NOT BAD, LITTLE BOY.
IS THAT A FISHING POLE?
HOW ORIGINAL.
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
DO YOU MIND?
Leorio: LEAVE HIM ALONE.
YOUR FIGHT'S WITH ME!
( Gon yells )
HUH?
Hisoka: DID YOU COME HERE
TO HELP YOUR FRIEND?
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: SUCH A GOOD BOY.
HMM. I ADORE THAT LOOK.
♪♪♪
WELL DONE.
I'M BEGINNING TO GET EXCITED.
( Gon yells )
( gagging )
Hisoka: IT'S SO DELIGHTFUL.
I LOVE THAT LOOK.
( Gon coughs )
Hisoka: DON'T WORRY.
I DIDN'T KILL YOUR FRIEND.
HE'S GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
AND THAT'S BECAUSE HE PASSED.
( laughs )
AND, YES, YOU PASS AS WELL.
NOW GO AND BECOME A GOOD HUNTER.
( Gon breathing heavily )
BUT I'VE GOTTA SAY
IT WAS ACTUALLY
PRETTY EXCITING BACK THERE.
I WAS SO SCARED THAT ALL
I WANTED TO DO WAS RUN AWAY,
BUT I COULDN'T,
'CAUSE I WAS EXCITED
AT THE SAME TIME.
ISN'T THAT WEIRD?
♪♪♪
THERE WERE 404 APPLICANTS
AT THE START OF THE HUNTER EXAM,
BUT BY THE TIME
WE REACHED THE THIRD PHASE,
THERE WERE ONLY 41 LEFT.
Beans: UH, AHEM!
EVERYONE, THIS IS THE SITE OF
THE HUNTER EXAM'S THIRD PHASE.
YOU'LL BE COMPETING HERE
AT THE TOP OF THE TRICK TOWER.
Applicant #107:
DID YOU SAY, "TRICK TOWER"?
Bean: IN ORDER
TO PASS THIS PHASE,
YOU MUST REACH
THE BASE OF THE TOWER ALIVE.
THE TIME LIMIT IS 72 HOURS.
Leorio: WHOA.
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE?
Killua: SEE THAT? OVER THERE.
♪♪♪
( Leorio gulps )
( Lippo over P. A. )
GENTLEMEN, LET ME EXPLAIN.
YOU'VE PROBABLY ALREADY NOTICED
THAT SOME OF THE PRISONERS
OF TRICK TOWER
ARE STANDING BEFORE YOU.
NOT JUST PRISONERS.
THE HUNTER EXAM COMMITTEE
HAS ALSO OFFICIALLY
HIRED THEM ON AS EXAMINERS.
IN THIS PHASE,
YOU'LL BE FIGHTING
AGAINST ALL FIVE OF THEM.
Kurapika: WITHOUT KNOWING
WHAT'S UP THEIR SLEEVES,
THERE'S FAR TOO MUCH AT STAKE.
GIVEN THAT, I'LL‐‐
Tonpa: NOPE. I'LL GO.
Gon: MR. TONPA?
( Tonpa growls )
Bendot: BEGIN! ( growls )
Tonpa: I...
GIVE UP!
Killua: HUH?
Leorio: WHAT?
Gon: DID HE JUST SAY
THAT HE GIVES UP?
Leorio: UH, MAYBE HE MEANT,
"GIVE ME A SEC."
( Sedokan laughs )
WE EACH LIGHT A CANDLE
AT THE SAME TIME,
AND WHOEVER'S CANDLE
GOES OUT FIRST IS THE LOSER.
( Gon gasps )
Leorio: HEY, TAKE A LOOK
AT GON'S CANDLE.
THE FLAME SUDDENLY GOT
A LOT STRONGER.
Kurapika: I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
HE SOMEHOW LACED GON'S CANDLE
WITH GUNPOWDER
OR SOME OTHER ACCELERANT.
THAT'S WHY IT'S BURNING
SO MUCH FASTER.
( Gon gasps, laughs )
I GUESS NOW THAT THE FLAME
IS BURNING SO MUCH STRONGER,
IT'LL TAKE A LOT MORE THAN
A LITTLE BREEZE TO PUT IT OUT.
Sedokan: HUH?
HE'S FAST!
( gasps )
( Gon laughs )
I WIN!
♪♪♪
Leorio: LOOK AT HIS TATTOO.
IT'S A SPIDER WITH 12 LEGS,
AND THAT MEANS...
Majitani: NAME'S MAJITANI.
I'M ONE OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE'S
FOUR DEVAS.
THAT FIRST STRIKE
WAS JUST AN INTRODUCTION.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO GIVE UP.
IF YOU DO,
I'M STILL WILLING TO‐‐
( gasps )
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU...
( gagging )
♪♪♪
Leorio: ALL RIGHT!
I KNOW WHAT WE'RE BETTING ON!
LET'S BET ON WHO'LL WIN
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS.
( Leroute laughs )
Leorio: HEY, WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Leroute: IT'S JUST I CAN ALREADY
TELL WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO USE.
I'M SOMETHING OF A MIND READER,
YOU SEE.
Leorio: THAT IS A LIE.
YOU CAN BLUFF ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IT'LL TAKE A LOT MORE
THAN THAT TO SCARE ME.
Leroute: YOU'LL BELIEVE IT SOON.
‐ YOU READY?
‐ ( Leorio gasps )
Leroute: AND ROCK, PAPER...
Both: SCISSORS!
♪♪♪
Leroute: WELL,
WHAT'LL YOU USE NEXT?
COME ON. THINK HARD.
( giggles )
Leorio: DAMN IT!
( screams )
WHAT IS HAPPENING?!
Leroute: HERE WE GO.
HERE COMES THE DRAW!
( beep )
( laughs )
I WIN! YAY!
Killua: HOW DO YOU
WANNA DO THIS?
Johness: DO THIS?
YOU HAVE THE WRONG IDEA.
SEE, YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE
ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF A ONE‐SIDED MASSACRE.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE EXAM
OR REDUCING MY SENTENCE.
ALL I WANT
IS TO HEAR YOU SCREAM.
Killua: REALLY? FINE.
WE'LL JUST KEEP FIGHTING
UNTIL ONE OF US DIES.
Johness: THAT'S RIGHT,
A BATTLE TO THE DEATH.
SOON I'LL TEAR YOUR BODY APART
WITH JUST MY BARE HANDS.
YOU GOT IT?
‐ ( heart beats )
‐ ( all gasp )
( heart beating )
Johness: THAT'S MINE.
IT BELONGS TO ME.
GIVE IT BACK.
GIVE IT TO ME.
( heartbeat stops )
♪♪♪
Announcer: PLEASE SELECT A PATH.
THERE ARE TWO AVAILABLE OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM,
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
WHICH THE ENTIRE GROUP CAN TAKE,
OR THE SHORT AND EASY PATH,
WHICH WILL BE LIMITED
TO ONLY THREE OF YOU.
( all gasp )
Gon: I'M GOING TO PRESS "O."
IT'S JUST WE ALL MADE IT
THIS FAR BY WORKING TOGETHER.
WE SHOULD FINISH TOGETHER.
Kurapika: GON.
Gon: IT'S A BIG RISK.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT STILL, WE'VE GOTTA TRY!
( all grunting )
Kurapika: WE ENTERED
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
BROKE DOWN THE WALL,
AND FROM THERE,
WE SNUCK
INTO THE SHORT AND EASY ONE.
Killua: BOY, MY BUTT HURTS!
Kurapika: I CERTAINLY
WASN'T EXPECTING
THE SHORT AND EASY PATH
TO BE A SLIDE.
Hisoka: THREE OF THEM, EH?
Announcer: 30 SECONDS REMAIN.
Gon: EVEN WITH THAT BIG SLIDE,
THAT WAS REALLY CLOSE!
Kurapika: HEH. MY HANDS
ARE COVERED IN BLISTERS.
Leorio: SAME HERE.
Announcer: LEORIO, NUMBER 403,
IS THE 23rd TO PASS.
Leorio: MY HANDS ARE WRECKED,
BUT ALL FIVE OF US CLEARED
THE TOWER TOGETHER, DIDN'T WE?
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO GON.
( Gon laughs )
( chime sounds )
Announcer: THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM IS OVER!
25 APPLICANTS HAVE PASSED,
INCLUDING ONE DECEASED.
♪♪♪
Gon: THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT,
AUNT MITO.
THAT'S HOW I COMPLETED
THE THIRD PHASE OF THE EXAM.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY PHASES ARE LEFT TO GO,
BUT I'M GONNA PASS
EVERY LAST ONE OF 'EM,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA BE
A HUNTER JUST LIKE DAD.
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
GON FREECSS.
( footsteps )
Mito: WELL,
DID YOU HEAR THAT, GING?
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR SON
IS FOLLOWING IN YOUR FOOTSTEPS.
SO...
ARE YOU HAPPY?
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"HIT THE TARGET."
A SNEAKY HIT.
Hisoka: HIT AND RUN.
♪♪♪