( bird shrieks )
Killua: THIS IS IT, GON.
MY BROTHER SENT THE U. R. L.
Gon: THAT'S AWESOME!
LET'S GET STARTED!
Killua: YEAH.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: AS KURAPIKA
SETS OUT ON THE PATH
TO FACE THE PHANTOM TROUPE
AND AVENGE THE KURTA,
GON AND KILLUA ARE ALSO BUSY
MAKING THEIR OWN PREPARATIONS
FOR THE AUCTION IN YORKNEW CITY.
Gon: IS THIS THE HUNTER WEBSITE?
Killua: YEAH. I'VE HEARD
THAT HUNTERS WORLDWIDE
POST LOTS OF INFORMATION HERE.
Gon: WORLDWIDE? REALLY?
THAT'S PRETTY AMAZING.
Computer: PLEASE SWIPE
YOUR HUNTER'S LICENSE,
AND ENTER YOUR LICENSE CODE.
( typing )
Killua: PUT THE CURSOR
ON THE BARTENDER.
Bartender: WHAT KIND
OF INFORMATION DO YOU WANT?
Gon: WOW! THAT'S A LOT OF INFO!
Killua: CLICK "GAME" CATEGORY.
THERE IT IS. "GREED ISLAND."
Bartender: PRICE IS
20 MILLION JENNY.
Gon: 20 MILLION?
I GUESS THEY WON'T GIVE OUT
INFORMATION FOR FREE.
ALL RIGHT. GUESS WE GOTTA.
Gon: OKAY, THEN.
I'M DEPOSITING 20 MILLION.
I CAN FEEL AURA
COMING FROM THE MONITOR!
Killua: THEN TO ENTER THE SITE,
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
ACTUALLY HAVE TO BE A NEN USER.
Bartender: OKAY.
NOW LISTEN VERY CAREFULLY.
YOU SEE, "GREED ISLAND"
IS A GAME CREATED BY NEN USERS.
‐ ( Gon gasps )
‐ Bartender: IT APPEARS
THAT THERE ARE MULTIPLE CREATORS
WHOSE MOTIVES ARE UNCLEAR.
THEY INFUSED NEN INTO
ALL HUNDRED COPIES OF THE GAME.
NEN ACTIVATES ON START‐UP,
PULLING THE PLAYER
INSIDE THE GAME ITSELF.
Gon: WAIT. INSIDE THE GAME?
Bartender: ONLY NEN USERS
CAN ACTUALLY PLAY IT.
AS LONG AS THE PLAYER
STAYS ALIVE WITHIN THE GAME,
THE CONSOLE
WILL CONTINUE TO RUN,
EVEN IF THE GAME IS UNPLUGGED.
IT WILL STOP IF THE PLAYER DIES.
THERE WAS ONE OWNER WHO HIRED
50 HUNTERS TO GIVE IT A SHOT,
AND OF THE 50,
NOT A SINGLE ONE EVER CAME BACK.
I HEARD YOU CAN RETURN
IF YOU CAN FIND A SAVE POINT.
Gon: IS THAT TRUE?
Killua: IT'S FROM
THE HUNTER WEBSITE.
IT'S GOTTA BE ACCURATE.
Bartender:
AT THE YORKNEW CITY AUCTION,
THERE ARE GOING TO BE
SEVEN UNITS OF "GREED ISLAND,"
AND EVERY ONE OF THEM
WILL BE AVAILABLE FOR PURCHASE.
OF COURSE,
THE LOWEST STARTING BID
IS 8.9 BILLION JENNY.
Gon: 8.9 BILLION?!
Killua: THE PRICE
HAS SKYROCKETED!
THAT'S THREE BILLION MORE
THAN WE'D PAY FOR RETAIL!
Bartender: GETTING ONE'S
RANKED LEVEL G.
Both: EH?
Bartender: THE GAME
IS CONSIDERED A LEGEND,
BUT THERE ARE STILL
PLENTY OF UNITS AROUND.
IF YOU HAVE ENOUGH MONEY,
IT SHOULD BE RELATIVELY EASY
TO PROCURE ONE.
Killua: HUH. A G‐RANK, HUH?
THAT'S LOWER THAN I THOUGHT.
Gon: YOU'RE TELLING ME
IF I CAN'T EVEN GET MY HANDS
ON A SIMPLE GAME,
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIND YOU, RIGHT, GING?
( ice clinks )
( buzzing )
Killua: STILL,
THE MONEY'S A BIG PROBLEM.
♪
Gon: HEY, THIS AUCTION,
DO YOU THINK THAT WE
CAN PARTICIPATE IN IT?
Killua: AT 8.9 BILLION?
COME ON.
THAT'S WAY OUT OF OUR LEAGUE.
Gon: MM‐MMM. NOT TO GO
BUY STUFF, BUT TO SELL.
Killua: SELLING, HUH? THAT'S IT!
Gon: WE CAN GO LOOK FOR TREASURE
AND THEN AUCTION OFF
WHATEVER WE MANAGE TO FIND.
Killua: YES! WE CAN START WITH
THE 800 MILLION THAT WE EARNED
FIGHTING AT HEAVENS ARENA
AND GO FROM THERE.
Gon: HMM.
Killua: FIRST OFF, WE'LL TRY
THE ONLINE FLEA MARKETS
AND AUCTION WEBSITES.
NOW, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE CAN DIG UP.
WE'LL INCREASE OUR FUNDS
AND THEN GET A COPY
OF "GREED ISLAND."
Gon: YEAH!
♪
‐ Killua: YEAH!
‐ Gon: ALL RIGHT!
( both laugh )
Gon: HOW MUCH IS LEFT?
Killua: BETWEEN THE TWO OF US,
WE'RE AT 10.84 MILLION.
( both sigh )
Killua: WHAT THE HELL?!
WHEN WE FIRST STARTED,
WE WERE MAKING A DECENT AMOUNT.
Gon: I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
THAT'S WHY I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD
STICK TO THE REPUTABLE SITES.
Killua: COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
THE RISKY SITES
ARE THE ONLY REAL WAY
TO MAKE A PROFIT.
( both sigh )
Gon: THIS ISN'T
WORKING OUT SO GOOD.
Employer: NOW THEN,
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'VE BROUGHT.
Kurapika: HAIR FROM
THE FAMOUS ACTRESS SARA,
DNA AUTHENTICATED.
Basho: TAKEN FROM
AN EGYPERSIAN PYRAMID,
IT'S A MUMMY'S RIGHT ARM.
Melody: THE SCALY SKIN
OF A DRACODERMA PATIENT.
Baise: THE SKULL
OF A UNICORN TRIBESMAN.
Employer: OKAY, THEN.
CONGRATULATIONS.
ALL FOUR OF YOU ARE HIRED.
MY NAME IS DALZOLLENE,
THE HEAD BODYGUARD.
YOU START NOW.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO WORKING WITH EACH OF YOU.
YOUR MISSION
IS TO SAFELY ESCORT THE BOSS
TO A YORKNEW CITY HOTEL ROOM.
A PRIVATE AIRSHIP
WILL TAKE YOU ALL TO LINGON,
AN AIRPORT OUTSIDE OF YORKNEW.
FROM THE AIRPORT,
IT'S 90 MINUTES
TO GET TO THE HOTEL.
A CAR WILL BE WAITING.
THE FOUR OF YOU WILL BE ASSIGNED
TO PROVIDE THE OUTER RING
OF SECURITY. ANY QUESTIONS?
Kurapika: DO YOU KNOW
WHO MIGHT BE TARGETING THE BOSS?
Dalzollene: THAT QUESTION'S
NOT DESERVING OF AN ANSWER.
Kurapika: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Dalzollene: THE BOSS IS A V.I.P.
IN THE UNDERWORLD.
THERE ARE PLENTY
WHO HOLD A GRUDGE.
Kurapika: SINCE YOU DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND, I'LL REPHRASE.
GRUDGES ASIDE,
CAN YOU THINK OF ANYONE
WHO MIGHT ACTUALLY COMMIT
TO AN ATTACK, ANYONE AT ALL?
IF WE CAN IDENTIFY
THE CANDIDATES,
THEIR STYLES AND MOTIVES,
WE CAN PREPARE,
HELPING US TO ENSURE
THE BOSS'S PROTECTION.
Dalzollene: KURAPIKA, IS IT?
YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO DOESN'T UNDERSTAND.
OUR JOB IS TO PROTECT THE BOSS,
NO MATTER WHO, WHEN,
WHERE, OR HOW THEY ATTACK.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
GOT IT?
SO DON'T BOTHER
BUILDING A MENTAL PROFILE.
EVERYONE WHO APPROACHES
IS AN ENEMY.
IT'S TIME TO MEET THE BOSS.
COME ON.
♪
( Baise gasps )
EXCUSE ME. WHAT'S THAT?
Basho: IT'S A LITTLE
TOO REALISTIC.
Dalzollene: THAT IS
AN ACTUAL HUMAN BEING.
( all gasp )
Dalzollene: HE USED TO BE
A FELLOW BODYGUARD,
BUT HE IGNORED MY ADVICE AND WAS
FOOLED BY FALSE INFORMATION,
PUTTING THE OTHER BODYGUARDS
AND THE BOSS AT RISK,
AND SO HE WAS PUNISHED
ACCORDINGLY.
YOU WERE ALL BROUGHT IN
TO BE HIS REPLACEMENTS.
LET'S GO.
BOSS, I'VE BROUGHT
THE NEW BODYGUARDS.
Woman: COME IN.
♪
Dalzollene: THE BOSS, MISS NEON.
( all gasp )
( Neon giggles ) NEW HIRES.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
♪
Basho: WELL, ANYWAY,
I WAS PRETTY SURPRISED
WHEN WE MET THE BOSS.
Baise: NO KIDDING.
THEY CALLED HER
AN IMPORTANT FIGURE
IN THE UNDERWORLD,
SO I THOUGHT IT'D BE
SOMEONE INTIMIDATING,
BUT SHE TURNED OUT
TO BE A CUTE LITTLE GIRL.
( somber chorus vocalizing )
( footsteps )
‐ ( gasps )
‐ ( grunts )
Man: PAKUNODA!
HEY, HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
Pakunoda: LONG TIME,
NO SEE, SHALNARK.
‐ YOU TOO, PHINKS.
‐ ( Phinks scoffs )
YOU SURE
TOOK YOUR TIME GETTING HERE.
Pakunoda: OH?
RIGHT ON TIME BY MY WATCH.
Phinks: YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO ARRIVE HERE 10 MINUTES EARLY.
SAME FOR YOU GUYS.
Shalnark: BONOLENOV! KORTOPI!
SO, YOU'RE GOING WITH US, TOO?
Man: HEY!
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN QUITE A WHILE.
I'M REPORTING FOR DUTY, BOSS.
WHAT'S OUR TARGET THIS TIME?
I'M ITCHIN' FOR OUR NEW ORDERS.
Shalnark: EASY NOW, UVO.
FEITAN'S GROUP
WON'T BE ARRIVING UNTIL EVENING.
WE'LL WAIT
UNTIL EVERYONE'S HERE.
Pakunoda: IMPATIENT AS USUAL.
Uvo: DAMN. THAT'S
AN ENTIRE HALF‐DAY OF WAITING.
HEY, IF IT ISN'T SHIZUKU.
Shizuku: HELLO.
Pakunoda: HAS THE OTHER
NEW ADDITION ARRIVED YET?
Shalnark: DON'T KNOW.
YOU SHOULD ASK MACHI.
( somber chorus vocalizing )
Dalzollene: THIS IS
FOR SEPTEMBER.
Neon: WHAT'S THIS?
SEEMS LIKE THERE'S A LOT.
Dalzollene: IT IS.
BOTH MR. TRINK AND MR. ROTTFELLI
WOULD LIKE THEIR FORTUNES TOLD.
Neon: AWW! THAT SUCKS.
I TOLD YOU I WAS GONNA QUIT
IF YOU ADDED ANY MORE.
Dalzollene: AND I DO APOLOGIZE.
YOUR FATHER COUNTS THEM BOTH
AMONG HIS CLOSEST ASSOCIATES.
Neon: WELL,
WHERE IS PAPA, ANYWAY?
Dalzollene: HE HAD A VERY
PRESSING MEETING TO ATTEND TO.
Neon: HE'S PROBABLY OFF HUNTING
OR PLAYING GOLF.
( phone line rings, clicks )
PAPA? THIS IS NEON.
WHAT?! NO WAY!
YOU CAN'T FOOL ME THAT EASILY!
NO. NO!
HMM? ( sighs )
FINE, IF YOU KEEP YOUR WORD,
BUT BREAK ONE MORE PROMISE,
AND I'LL QUIT FOR REAL.
( beep )
HOORAY!
I'M GETTING
ANOTHER PIECE OF TREASURE!
HEE HEE. SWEET DEAL, HUH?
Dalzollene:
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
Neon: 'KAY.
NOW THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
I'LL GET THIS OVER WITH.
( chorus vocalizing )
Dalzollene: HMM.
Basho: I HEARD SOMEWHERE
THAT SHE'S
AN INCREDIBLE FORTUNETELLER.
THANKS TO
HER FATHER'S CONNECTIONS,
SHE'S GOT SOME V. I. P. CLIENTS
IN THE UNDERWORLD.
Kurapika: YOU HAVE IT BACKWARDS.
Basho: THAT SO?
Kurapika: I'D SAY THAT
THE FATHER HAS USED HIS DAUGHTER
TO INCREASE HIS STANDING
AND MOVE UP IN THE UNDERWORLD,
AND THAT'S WHY
THE PROSPECT OF LOSING HER
IS SO FRIGHTENING TO HIM.
HE'S AFRAID HIS ENEMIES
MIGHT RETALIATE
BY TARGETING HIS DAUGHTER.
Neon: OKAY, ALL DONE.
HERE.
Dalzollene: EXCELLENT WORK.
Neon: TOMORROW'S AUCTION
STARTS AT NIGHT, DOESN'T IT?
I WANT TO GO SHOPPING
BEFOREHAND.
Dalzollene: IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANT, I SHALL ACCOMPANY YOU.
Man: HOW MANY YEARS
HAS IT BEEN, I WONDER,
SINCE ALL 13 OF
THE TROUPE MEMBERS GOT TOGETHER?
FEITAN?
Feitan: THREE YEARS, TWO MONTHS,
BUT TWO HAVE CHANGED SINCE THEN.
NUMBERS FOUR AND EIGHT
ARE DIFFERENT.
Man #2: MACHI,
DO YOU THINK NUMBER FOUR,
HISOKA, WILL ACTUALLY SHOW UP?
Machi: NO IDEA. DON'T ASK ME.
Man #2: WASN'T HE
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY?
Machi: I JUST TOLD HIM
TO BE HERE.
Feitan: I DON'T LIKE HISOKA.
WHY DOES THE BOSS
LET HIM DO AS HE PLEASES?
Man #1: FOR HIS SKILLS,
PROBABLY.
( Feitan scoffs ) SKILLS?
Man #1: WELL, HIS BUNGEE GUM
IS CERTAINLY VERY IMPRESSIVE.
IT WOULD BE DIFFICULT
FOR ANYONE TO COUNTER.
Feitan: ARE YOU SAYING THAT
THE BOSS IS AFRAID OF HISOKA?
WATCH YOURSELF.
Man #1: THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
Man #2: QUIT BEING GENEROUS.
YOU'RE GIVING THE GUY
WAY TOO MUCH CREDIT.
( man #1 scoffs )
TALK IS AS CHEAP
AS IT EVER WAS.
Man #2: SHUT UP, OR THIS IS
WHAT HAPPENS, NOBUNAGA.
Nobunaga: YOU WERE TALKING
JUST AS MUCH AS I WAS, FRANKLIN.
‐ Machi: HERE WE GO AGAIN.
‐ ( blows whooshing )
Feitan: IGNORE THEM.
THEY'RE JUST PLAYING AROUND.
Machi: SO, WHY IS THE CHIEF
CALLING EVERYONE TOGETHER,
ANYWAY?
Feitan: WE'RE THIEVES.
I ASSUME HE WANTS US
TO STEAL SOMETHING.
Machi: WELL, THAT MUCH, I KNOW.
Dalzollene: YES. WE'VE ARRIVED
SAFELY AT THE HOTEL,
BUT ONE OF THE YOUNG MISTRESS'S
FORTUNES CONCERNS ME.
"IN THE BASEMENT
WHERE PRICES RISE,
"YOUR BED SHALL BE MADE
WITH YOUR BROTHERS.
"DO NOT DESCEND STAIRS
YOU HAVE NEVER CLIMBED.
IN NUMBERS, DO NOT
COMPETE WITH OTHERS."
AND THERE ARE THREE OTHER POEMS
THAT BEGIN WITH THE SAME VERSE,
MEANING THAT ALL FOUR
OF THE CLIENTS
RECEIVED FORTUNES
THAT ARE NEARLY IDENTICAL.
IT SEEMS THE ONLY THING
THAT CONNECTS THEM
IS THAT AT THIS YEAR'S
UNDERGROUND AUCTION,
EACH ONE OF THEM
WILL BE ATTENDING.
Man: SO THE FORTUNE SAYS
THEIR LIVES ARE AT RISK
SHOULD THEY CHOOSE
TO PARTICIPATE?
Dalzollene: I THINK
THE SLEEP IMAGERY
IS A METAPHOR FOR ILLNESS
OR FOR DEATH.
Man: UNDERSTOOD.
I WILL PASS THE FORTUNES
ALONG TO THE CLIENTS.
Dalzollene:
THERE'S ONE MORE THING, SIR.
THE YOUNG MISTRESS
IS NEVER ABLE TO REMEMBER
THE FORTUNES SHE'S TOLD,
AND SHE CANNOT TELL HER OWN.
DOES IT MAKE SENSE TO LET HER
TAKE PART IN THE AUCTION?
Man: NO!
BRING HER BACK IMMEDIATELY!
Dalzollene: HOWEVER,
WITHOUT A PROPER EXPLANATION,
SHE WON'T LISTEN
TO A WORD I SAY,
AND IF SHE THROWS A TANTRUM,
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO STOP HER.
( Neon giggles )
Man: IN ANY CASE,
DO NOT TAKE HER TO THE AUCTION.
SEND SOME BODYGUARDS
TO PLACE THE BIDS INSTEAD.
Dalzollene: UNDERSTOOD.
( click )
( man sighs )
NEON.
( wind blowing )
( Phinks sighs )
HE ISN'T COMING.
Feitan: THE SUN IS ALMOST UP.
Uvo: DAMN IT, HISOKA.
NEXT TIME I SEE HIM,
I'LL TEAR HIM APART.
Hisoka: OH, DEAR.
THAT SOUNDS
QUITE GRUESOME, INDEED.
I'M SIMPLY TERRIFIED.
Uvo: HISOKA! YOU BASTARD!
Shalnark: GUESS YOU'RE
RUNNING A BIT LATE.
Machi: I WAS STARTING
TO THINK YOU WOULDN'T SHOW.
Hisoka: WHY WOULDN'T I?
YOU ASKED ME TO COME,
DIDN'T YOU?
HAD I BROKEN MY PROMISE,
I WOULD NEVER HAVE THE PLEASURE
OF SEEING
YOUR NEN STITCHES AGAIN.
( Machi scoffs )
Shalnark: OKAY, BOSS.
EVERYONE'S HERE!
♪
Uvo: WELL, BOSS,
WHAT ARE WE STEALING THIS TIME?
Boss: WE WILL TAKE THE TREASURES
OF THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
Shalnark: WHICH TREASURES
DO YOU WANT?
Machi: ANCIENT TEXTS, MAYBE?
THE BOSS DOES LIKE BOOKS.
Feitan: NO, BUT PERHAPS GAMES.
THERE WILL BE MANY COPIES
OF THE MOST EXPENSIVE GAME EVER.
Nobunaga: WOULDN'T IT
BE MORE LOGICAL
TO TAKE PRECIOUS METALS
AND GEMSTONES?
Boss: ALL OF IT.
WE'LL BE TAKING EVERYTHING
THAT'S UP FOR AUCTION.
Uvo: HOLD ON, BOSS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION
IS OPERATED
BY GANGS
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD!
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
IF WE DO THAT,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE ENEMIES
OUT OF EVERY LAST ONE OF 'EM.
Boss: ARE YOU SCARED, UVOGIN?
Uvogin: NO WAY. I'M ECSTATIC.
I CAN'T STOP SHAKING.
COME ON.
GIVE US THE ORDER, BOSS!
I WANT IT NOW!
( chorus vocalizing )
Boss: I GIVE YOU PERMISSION
TO KILL THEM ALL...
ANYONE WHO DARES
TO GET IN OUR WAY.
♪
( Uvogin roars )
Dalzollene: GOOD WORK.
I HAVE YOUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT.
YOU MUST WIN
THE THREE ITEMS ON THIS LIST
AT THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
MONEY IS NO OBJECT.
THE INTACT MUMMY
OF PRINCESS CORCO.
A TISSUE USED BY THE ACTOR
SONNE LIMARCH,
WITH A CERTIFICATE
OF DNA AUTHENTICITY.
( Kurapika gasps )
Dalzollene:
AND THE EYES OF A KURTA,
KNOWN AS THE SCARLET EYES.
( Kurapika shudders )
Dalzollene: ALSO WE'VE
RECEIVED INFORMATION
THAT THERE MIGHT BE
AN ATTACK ON THE AUCTION,
SO BE PREPARED
FOR ANY CONTINGENCY,
BUT KEEP YOUR FOCUS
ON THE PRIMARY OBJECTIVE
OF OBTAINING THESE ITEMS.
♪
Kurapika: THEY'RE COMING.
THEY'RE DEFINITELY COMING.
♪
Narrator: KURAPIKA
EAGERLY AWAITS HIS REVENGE
AGAINST THE PHANTOM TROUPE,
A BAND OF MURDERING THIEVES.
THE SUN HAS RISEN
ON THE FIRST DAY OF THE AUCTION,
WHERE ALL SIDES
WILL SOON COLLIDE.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING NEON,
THE DAUGHTER OF THE HEAD
OF THE NOSTRADE FAMILY.
Killua: SHE'S A FLESH COLLECTOR.
Gon: HER NEN ABILITY'S
THE LOVELY GHOSTWRITER.
Killua: I THINK I'D TRY
TO TELL MY OWN FORTUNE.
Gon: TURNS OUT
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
♪
NEXT TIME, "DEFEND AND ATTACK."
KILLUA, ARE YOU BETTER
AT DEFENDING OR ATTACKING?
Killua: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Gon: UM, ATTACKING?
Killua: BINGO.