( Noggin Lugging Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: OKAY, NOW!
♪♪♪
Menchi: THE JOY OF DISCOVERING
SOMETHING DELICIOUS.
AND NOW YOU KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
THAT FEELING IS WHAT
WE RISK OUR LIVES FOR.
( Gon laughs )
♪♪♪
Narrator: AFTER CLEARING
THE EXAM'S SECOND PHASE,
GON AND HIS FRIENDS
FLY THROUGH THE STARRY SKY
TOWARD THE SITE
OF THE THIRD PHASE.
Netero:
I WILL NOW TAKE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF PROPERLY
TO THE REMAINING 42 APPLICANTS.
I AM NETERO, THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE SELECTION COMMITTEE
FOR THIS YEAR'S HUNTER EXAM.
IT IS A PLEASURE
TO MEET ALL OF YOU.
Beans: AND I'M
HIS SECRETARY, BEANS.
Netero: I HAD ORIGINALLY PLANNED
TO MAKE MY APPEARANCE
DURING THE EXAM'S FINAL PHASE,
BUT, WELL, SEEING AS HOW
I'M ALREADY HERE...
I HAVE TO ADMIT
THERE'S NOTHING I LOVE MORE
THAN THIS FEELING
OF TENSION IN THE AIR,
SO I THINK I'LL STICK AROUND
FOR THE REMAINDER OF THE TRIP.
( laughs )
Beans: WE ARE SCHEDULED
TO ARRIVE AT OUR DESTINATION
TOMORROW MORNING
AT 8:00 A. M. EXACTLY.
YOU'LL FIND DINNER WAITING
FOR YOU IN THE DINING HALL.
YOU'RE ALSO WELCOME
TO GET SOME REST, OF COURSE.
YOU'RE FREE TO DO AS YOU PLEASE
UNTIL WE CONTACT YOU.
THE EVENING IS YOURS.
Killua: HEY, COME ON, GON.
LET'S GO
AND EXPLORE THE AIRSHIP.
Gon: YEAH. ( laughs )
Leorio: THEY'VE GOT
SO MUCH ENERGY!
NOT ME, THOUGH.
ALL I WANNA DO IS CRASH.
Kurapika: AS DO I.
HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE THING
THAT STILL CONCERNS ME.
Leorio: HUH? WHAT'S UP?
Kurapika: HOW MANY MORE PHASES
ARE THERE IN THE EXAM?
Leorio: HUH. YEAH,
THEY HAVEN'T SAID, HAVE THEY?
Tonpa: AS LONG
AS I'VE BEEN DOING THIS,
IT'S AVERAGED FIVE OR SIX.
Leorio: WHICH MEANS
THAT WE'VE STILL GOT
ANOTHER THREE OR FOUR
LEFT TO GO.
Kurapika: WELL, IN THAT CASE,
WE SHOULD GET SOME REST NOW
WHILE WE CAN.
Tonpa: OKAY, BUT I'D BE CAREFUL
IF I WERE YOU.
Leorio: HUH?
Tonpa: YOU HEARD
THE SECRETARY, RIGHT?
HE ONLY TOLD US
WHEN WE'RE ARRIVING.
HE DIDN'T SAY THAT
THE THIRD PHASE OF THE EXAM
WASN'T GOING TO HAPPEN
RIGHT HERE
ON THE AIRSHIP ITSELF.
AND WE'LL BE NOTIFIED,
BUT WHO KNOWS IF THAT'LL BE
AT 8 A. M. OR NOT?
Leorio: HOLD ON.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Kurapika: I SUPPOSE
THAT MAKES SENSE.
Tonpa: YOU MIGHT WAKE UP
AND FIND OUT
THE EXAM ALREADY TOOK PLACE
AND YOU SLEPT RIGHT THROUGH IT.
IF YOU WANT TO GET
TO THE NEXT PHASE,
THEN YOU BETTER
NOT LET YOUR GUARD DOWN,
EVEN UP HERE, UNDERSTAND?
( Leorio scoffs )
COME ON. GIVE ME A BREAK.
WELL, THANKS FOR THE ADVICE.
SEE YOU LATER.
Kurapika: WE'LL BE SURE
TO KEEP IT IN MIND.
Tonpa: GOOD LUCK
TO ALL OF US, HUH?
( thinking )
PSYCHED 'EM.
I BET THEY'RE BOTH SO NERVOUS,
THEY WON'T SLEEP A WINK.
THEY'LL BE WORTHLESS BY MORNING.
( Kurapika thinking )
THERE'S NO CHANCE
THE NEXT PHASE
WILL TAKE PLACE ON THE AIRSHIP.
IF THAT WERE THEIR INTENTION,
THEY WOULDN'T
HAVE TOLD US WE WERE FREE
TO DO AS WE PLEASED
AND ENJOY THE AMENITIES,
BUT TO STAND BY
AND WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
( Leorio snoring )
( utensils clattering )
Menchi: SO HOW MANY APPLICANTS
DO YOU THINK'LL MAKE IT
THIS YEAR?
Buhara: YOU MEAN
WHO'LL PASS THE EXAM?
Menchi: YEP.
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT
A PRETTY IMPRESSIVE GROUP HERE,
THOUGH I DID TRY TO FAIL THEM
ALL, SURE, BUT STILL...
Buhara: GEE, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS IT DEPENDS
ON WHAT THE OTHER PHASES ARE.
Menchi: THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
I HADN'T THOUGHT OF THAT.
BUT A FEW OF THEM STAND OUT.
DIDN'T YOU NOTICE?
AND ONE EVEN HAS
THIS WHOLE AURA THING GOING ON.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, SATOTZ?
Satotz: I'M INCLINED TO AGREE.
I QUITE LIKE
THE ROOKIES THIS YEAR.
Menchi: YEAH, SAME HERE!
I LIKE NUMBER 294.
HE'S BALD,
BUT HE'S STILL GOT A GOOD SHOT.
Satotz: I'M PARTIAL
TO NUMBER 99 MYSELF.
Menchi: HE LOOKS LIKE A SPOILED,
SELFISH BRAT IF YOU ASK ME.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, BUHARA?
Buhara: WHO I THINK'LL PASS?
WELL, HE'S NOT A ROOKIE,
BUT MY MONEY'S ON NUMBER 44.
I'M SURE YOU GUYS
MUST'VE NOTICED IT, TOO,
BUT WHEN NUMBER 255
WAS THROWING A FIT,
44 WAS THE ONE WHO LOOKED
LIKE HE WANTED TO KILL SOMEBODY.
HE HAD THIS COLD,
INTENSE BLOODLUST.
Menchi: OF COURSE
I NOTICED THAT.
HOW COULD I NOT?
IT LOOKED LIKE HE COULD
BARELY RESTRAIN HIMSELF.
HOLD ON. DIDN'T YOU REALIZE?
HE'S BEEN LIKE THAT
EVER SINCE WE SHOWED UP.
I'VE HAD A BAD FEELING
ABOUT HIM THIS WHOLE TIME.
Buhara: REALLY?
Menchi: YEAH.
HE'S THE REAL REASON
I WAS SO EDGY DURING THE EXAM.
I MEAN, HE KEPT TRYING
TO PICK A FIGHT WITH ME.
Satotz: I HAD
A SIMILAR EXPERIENCE.
HE SHOULD BE
CAREFULLY MONITORED.
THOUGH IT PAINS ME
TO ADMIT THIS,
I FEEL WE ARE ALL
BIRDS OF A FEATHER WITH HIM,
BUT HIS AFFINITY FOR DARKNESS
IS INFINITELY STRONGER
THAN OURS.
WE HUNTERS, AS YOU KNOW,
ARE CONSTANTLY
SEEKING OUT NEW RIVALS,
AND THE HUNTER EXAM
HAS NO SHORTAGE OF OPPONENTS,
EACH PERFECTLY QUALIFIED
AND WORTHY OF RESPECT.
AND EVERY NOW AND THEN,
IN OUR SEARCHES,
WE ENCOUNTER SOMEONE,
SOMEONE WHO CHOOSES
TO SURGE FORWARD
WHEN YOU OR I
WOULD OPT FOR THE BRAKES,
AN ANOMALY OF SORTS.
♪♪♪
( Hisoka chuckles )
‐ Man: HEY, KIDS!
‐ ( metal clattering )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STAY OUT OF THE KITCHEN!
GO EAT IN THE DINING HALL
WITH THE OTHERS!
Killua: HMM?
HEY! AWESOME! GON, LOOK!
Gon: HMM? WHAT IS IT?
WHOA!
IT'S LIKE
IT'S COVERED IN JEWELS!
Killua: YEAH.
Gon: HEY, SO I WAS WONDERING...
Killua: HMM?
Gon: YOUR PARENTS. ARE THEY‐‐
I MEAN, WHERE ARE THEY?
( Killua groans )
THEY'RE ALIVE, PROBABLY.
Gon: WHAT DO THEY DO?
Killua: THEY'RE ASSASSINS.
( Gon gasps )
THEY BOTH ARE?
( Killua laughs )
THAT'S YOUR RESPONSE?
( laughs )
YOU REALLY ARE A RIOT,
AREN'T YOU?
Gon: EH?
Killua: YOU'RE NOT
THE FIRST PERSON
I'VE TOLD ABOUT MY PARENTS,
BUT YOU'RE THE FIRST
TO TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
Gon: BUT IT'S TRUE, ISN'T IT?
Killua: WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
Gon: IT'S JUST A HUNCH.
Killua: WEIRD. MOST OF THE TIME,
PEOPLE ONLY LIKE ME
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T TELL
IF I'M SERIOUS OR NOT.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: I'M FROM A FAMILY
OF ASSASSINS,
SO, YEAH, THEY'RE ALL
IN THE BUSINESS OF MURDER,
AND MY ENTIRE FAMILY,
THEY'VE GOT
REAL HIGH HOPES FOR ME,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I CAN'T STAND IT.
WHO WANTS THEIR WHOLE LIFE
MAPPED OUT FOR 'EM?
WHEN I TOLD THEM I WANTED
TO DECIDE MY OWN FUTURE,
THEY ALL FLIPPED OUT.
IT WAS CRAZY!
MY MOM HAD TEARS
JUST STREAMING DOWN HER FACE,
AND SHE KEPT SCREAMING AT ME
HOW I HAD THE POTENTIAL
TO BE A TOP ASSASSIN.
( Gon laughs )
Killua: HORRIBLE PARENTS, RIGHT?
NO WONDER I'M ROTTEN.
THEN WE STARTED FIGHTING,
SO I SLASHED MY MOM
IN THE FACE,
STABBED MY BROTHER IN THE SIDE,
AND RAN AWAY FROM HOME.
I'M SURE
THEY'RE OUT FOR BLOOD NOW.
IF THEY ALL COME AFTER ME,
I'LL KILL 'EM.
( Gon laughs nervously )
Killua: WHEN I GET MY LICENSE,
I'LL HUNT 'EM DOWN
TO THE LAST ONE.
I'M WILLING TO BET
THEY'VE GOT PRETTY HEFTY
BOUNTIES ON THEIR HEADS.
Netero: HMM?
HMM.
Netero: SOMETHING WRONG?
Gon: MR. NETERO.
YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYONE
COMING FROM THAT SIDE, DID YOU?
Netero: NO, I DIDN'T.
( Killua thinking )
WHEN DID HE‐‐
YOU'RE FAST FOR AN OLD‐TIMER.
Netero: OH? THAT TRICK?
I JUST BARELY MOVED. THAT'S ALL.
Killua: WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
UNTIL THE LAST PHASE,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
Netero: NOW, NOW,
NO NEED TO BE SO UNKIND.
I JUST GOT A LITTLE BORED,
SO I DECIDED
TO LOOK FOR SOME COMPANY.
BY THE WAY,
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK YOU,
ANY THOUGHTS ON YOUR FIRST
ATTEMPT AT THE HUNTER EXAM?
Gon: YEAH! IT'S A LOT OF FUN!
THERE HAVEN'T BEEN
ANY WRITTEN TESTS YET,
AND I WAS KINDA
WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
Killua: I'M DISAPPOINTED,
HONESTLY.
I EXPECTED THIS TO BE
A LOT MORE CHALLENGING.
BUT I ASSUME THE NEXT PHASE'LL
BE MORE INTERESTING?
Netero: OH, WELL. WE'LL SEE.
Killua: LET'S GO, GON.
‐ Netero: WAIT! JUST A MOMENT.
‐ Killua: HMM?
Netero: WOULD YOU LIKE TO PLAY
A LITTLE GAME WITH ME?
Gon: GAME?
Netero:
AND TO MAKE IT INTERESTING,
IF YOU TWO CAN BEAT ME,
I'LL MAKE YOU HUNTERS
ON THE SPOT.
Gon: REALLY?! I'LL PLAY!
Netero: WHAT DO YOU SAY? WELL?
♪♪♪
Leorio: HMM.
( chuckles )
Netero: NOW LET'S GO OVER
THE RULES OF THE GAME.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SIMPLY
TAKE THIS BALL AWAY FROM ME.
IF YOU CAN DO THAT BEFORE
THE AIRSHIP ARRIVES, YOU WIN.
SO LET'S SEE.
WE'RE SCHEDULED
FOR AN 8 A. M. ARRIVAL, YES?
WELL, THAT'S NOT TOO BAD.
YOU STILL HAVE NINE HOURS LEFT.
AND FEEL FREE TO USE
ANY TACTICS YOU WANT.
I WILL ONLY DEFEND. I PROMISE.
Gon: HUH? THAT'S TOO EASY.
IT'S BARELY EVEN A GAME.
Netero: THEN WHY NOT GIVE IT
A TRY AND SEE IF YOU'RE RIGHT?
Killua: ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS TAKE THE BALL?
‐ Netero: YES.
‐ Killua: THEN...
I'LL GIVE IT A SHOT.
Netero: GO RIGHT AHEAD.
( Killua thinking )
HE THINKS I'M WEAK.
♪♪♪
Netero: AH.
Gon: I SEE A BUNCH OF KILLUAS.
( Netero thinking )
ONE OF THE ASSASSINATION ARTS...
THE RHYTHM ECHO.
IT CONFUSES THE ENEMY
WITH AFTERIMAGES
CREATED BY A VARYING
CADENCE OF STEPS.
TO THINK HE'S ALREADY MASTERED
THE TECHNIQUE AT HIS AGE.
WHAT A DREADFUL CHILD.
♪♪♪
( Netero chuckles )
Gon: OH, WOW!
( Killua thinking )
HE SURE MOVES AROUND A LOT.
HOW OLD IS THIS GUY?
Netero: IS THAT ALL?
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
( Killua thinking )
IN THAT CASE,
I'LL JUST HAVE TO SLOW HIM DOWN!
( Netero grunts )
Gon: OW! HIS PIVOT LEG!
( Killua chuckles )
( groans )
( yells )
( crying )
( Netero thinking )
HMM.
HE CERTAINLY DIDN'T HOLD BACK
WITH THAT KICK.
IF I WERE AN ORDINARY PERSON,
IT WOULD HAVE SHATTERED MY LEG.
( Killua thinking ) DAMN,
HIS LEGS ARE AS HARD AS IRON.
( winces )
Gon: KILLUA, TAG ME! TAG ME!
COME ON! IT'S MY TURN!
( Netero thinking )
HMM.
THIS ONE SEEMS LIKE
A VERY HONEST YOUNG MAN.
I'M CURIOUS TO SEE
WHAT HE HAS UP HIS SLEEVE.
Gon: OKAY.
♪♪♪
( Netero thinking )
AH.
I SEE HE'S GOT
A QUICK FIRST STEP...
BUT HE'S CHARGING
STRAIGHT AT ME.
VERY FOOLISH INDEED.
HE'S STILL A CHILD.
WAIT! FROM ABOVE?!
Gon: OW!
‐ ( groaning )
‐ Killua: IDIOT!
WE ALREADY KNOW
HOW HIGH YOU CAN JUMP,
SO YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO ALL OUT! FOCUS!
YOU HAD A CHANCE!
HE DROPPED HIS GUARD
FOR A SECOND!
( Netero thinking )
HEH. NO KIDDING.
( Gon sighing )
( Netero thinking )
HE MAY APPEAR SIMPLE‐MINDED,
BUT HE'S CLEARLY USING HIS HEAD.
Gon: WELL, THAT DIDN'T WORK.
( Netero thinking )
THEY SHOULD KEEP ME
ENTERTAINED UNTIL MORNING.
( applicants snoring )
‐ ( applicant coughs )
‐ Tonpa: HMM?
( chuckles )
( thinking )
LAST TIME I SAW THOSE TWO,
THEY WERE PRETTY SHAKEN UP.
THEY WERE BOTH SO NERVOUS,
I BET THEY AREN'T GETTING
A WINK OF SLEEP.
‐ ( Leorio snoring )
‐ THEY'RE SNORING?!
( Killua grunting )
( groans )
OW, OW, OW!
Netero: YOU BOYS
AREN'T GETTING ANYWHERE, HUH?
WHY DON'T YOU BOTH
TRY ATTACKING ME AT ONCE?
( Killua growls )
WHY, YOU!
Gon: OKAY! WE GOT YA NOW!
Netero: NOT BAD,
BUT STILL NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
( laughs )
( Gon thinking ) MR. NETERO
HASN'T EVEN BROKEN A SWEAT.
Both: OW!
( Netero laughs )
( Gon thinking )
IF WE'RE GONNA BEAT HIM,
WE'VE GOTTA GET CREATIVE.
Netero: GOTTA SAY, YOUR ATTACKS
DON'T AMOUNT TO MUCH.
( groans ) WHAT?
HE KICKED OFF HIS SHOE
TO INCREASE HIS RANGE?
( groans )
Killua: NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
Netero: I THINK NOT.
AH! SNEAKY KIDS!
Both: I'VE ALMOST GOT IT!
( Netero growls )
( both laugh )
♪♪♪
Netero: WELL, NOW...
EXCELLENT TEAMWORK.
YOU GET AN "A" FOR EFFORT.
( Gon gasps )
YOU'RE AMAZING, MR. NETERO,
REALLY AMAZING!
Killua: AH, FORGET IT. I QUIT.
‐ YOU BEAT ME, ALL RIGHT?
‐ Gon: HUH?
( Netero thinking )
OH? QUITTING ALREADY?
Gon: DON'T QUIT.
WE STILL GOT LOTS OF TIME,
AND BESIDES,
WE CAME SO CLOSE JUST NOW.
Killua: COME ON.
YOU'RE REALLY CLUELESS,
AREN'T YOU?
IT'S HOPELESS.
‐ Gon: HMM?
‐ Killua: THINK ABOUT IT.
THE OLD GUY'S BARELY USED
HIS RIGHT HAND OR LEFT LEG.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: HE'S WAY TOO POWERFUL
FOR US, GON.
WE COULD KEEP AT THIS
FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR
AND NEVER GET THAT BALL.
Netero: FIGURED IT OUT, DID YOU?
AND HERE I WAS THINKING
I'D BEEN PRETTY SLICK ABOUT IT.
Gon: OH, I GET IT NOW.
Killua: HA HA HA! YOU SURE KNOW
HOW TO PISS ME OFF, OLD MAN.
LET'S GO, GON!
Gon: NAH. I THINK
I'M GONNA PLAY A LITTLE LONGER.
Killua: HUH?! ARE YOU DEAF?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR
WHAT I JUST SAID?
LOOK, IT'S POINTLESS!
YOU'LL NEVER
GET THE BALL FROM HIM!
Gon: IT'S OKAY,
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY CARE.
WE'VE ONLY USED UP
HALF OF THE TIME LIMIT.
I'M GONNA SEE IF I CAN GET HIM
TO USE HIS RIGHT HAND
BEFORE THE REST OF IT
RUNS OUT.
( Killua stammers )
I SEE.
FINE. I GET IT.
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
I'M GOING TO BED.
‐ Gon: HEY, MR. NETERO...
‐ Netero: HMM?
Gon: CAN YOU TELL ME HOW KILLUA
DID THAT THING HE DID,
YOU KNOW, WHEN HE WALKED SLOW
AND THEN THERE WERE
A BUNCH OF HIM?
Netero: THAT WAS A TECHNIQUE
USED BY THOSE ENGAGED
IN ILLEGAL ACTIVITIES.
YOU HAVE NO NEED AT ALL
TO LEARN IT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, YOU SHOULD
NEVER TRY TO LEARN IT.
Gon: BUT IT'S
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE, HUH?
Netero: MM. IT REQUIRES
AN INCREDIBLE AMOUNT
OF TRAINING TO MASTER IT.
Gon: OH, MAN, KILLUA REALLY
IS SOMETHING, ISN'T HE?
Netero: NICE TRY.
( Gon chuckles )
( Killua thinking )
DAMN IT.
NOW I'M IN A BAD MOOD.
( thump )
WELL, IT IS WHAT IT IS.
Applicant #390:
HEY, KID! WAIT UP!
Applicant #391:
YEAH, WHERE ARE YOUR MANNERS?
‐ Applicant #390: HEY!
‐ Applicant #391:
COME BACK HERE!
( airship motor buzzing only )
( Killua thinking )
IF I HADN'T STOPPED WHEN I DID,
I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE ENDED UP
KILLING THE OLD MAN
TO GET THE BALL.
Netero: HMM?
( thinking ) AH.
LOOKS LIKE MY LITTLE PLAYMATE
IS PICKING UP THE PACE A BIT.
NOW.
HE'S FEINTING FOR THE BALL,
BUT HE'S REALLY
GOING FOR MY STOMACH! OH?
Gon: THAT HURT!
ONE MORE!
( Netero thinking ) OHH.
IF HE HEAD‐BUTTS ME
IN THE STOMACH LIKE THAT AGAIN,
HE'LL SHATTER HIS SKULL.
BUT IF I RELAX MY MUSCLES,
HE MIGHT ACTUALLY LAY ME OUT.
HMM.
BEST TO AVOID THAT.
OHH. DID THAT KILL HIM?
( Gon chuckles )
‐ Netero: HMM?
‐ Gon: GOTCHA!
YOU JUST USED YOUR RIGHT HAND!
( Netero gasps )
( groans )
I DID.
( Gon laughs )
I DID IT! YEAH!
( laughing )
YAY!
( snoring )
( Netero chuckles )
( snoring continues )
Netero: HELLO. CAPTAIN?
YES, IT'S ME.
IS THE FLIGHT GOING SMOOTHLY?
I REALLY HATE
TO ASK YOU TO DO THIS.
COULD YOU MAYBE SLOW
THE SHIP DOWN JUST A LITTLE?
Narrator: NETERO HAD PROPOSED
THE GAME TO KILL TIME,
BUT AS THEY PLAYED,
HE SAW SOMETHING IN GON.
THE AIRSHIP AND ALL 42
OF THE REMAINING APPLICANTS
ON BOARD
ARE APPROACHING THE SITE
OF THE EXAM'S THIRD PHASE.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"DECISION BY MAJORITY RULE?"
‐ Killua: MAJOR, MAJOR‐‐
‐ Gon: MAJOR TROUBLE!
Killua: TROUBLEMAKER!
♪♪♪