( beast roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kiriko father: ALL RIGHT!
WE'LL NOW TAKE YOU
STRAIGHT TO THE SITE
OF THE EXAM!
Gon: OH, WOW!
ISN'T IT INCREDIBLE
THAT WE ALL PASSED?
Kurapika: I WOULDN'T
CELEBRATE JUST YET.
WE'VE MERELY EARNED
THE RIGHT TO TAKE THE EXAM.
Leorio: IT'S PROGRESS!
I'D SAY THAT CALLS
FOR A LITTLE CELEBRATION.
♪♪♪
Narrator: WITH THE HELP
OF THE KIRIKO NAVIGATORS,
GON AND HIS NEW FRIENDS
ARRIVE IN ZABAN CITY,
THE LOCATION
OF THIS YEAR'S HUNTER EXAM.
Kiriko son:
A NAVIGATOR'S MAIN JOB
IS TO IDENTIFY WORTHY APPLICANTS
FOR THE HUNTER EXAM.
WE'RE ALSO RESPONSIBLE FOR
GUIDING THEM TO THE EXAM SITE.
YOU SEE, THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO FIND THE LOCATION
WITHOUT A NAVIGATOR.
Vendor: WHO WANTS A TASTE?
IT'S ZABAN'S WORLD‐FAMOUS
PANDA‐FROG ON A STICK!
A DELICACY!
Vendor #2: THIS BROOCH HERE
WAS EXCAVATED
FROM ZABAN'S UNDERGROUND PALACE.
IT'S A REAL FIND.
Leorio: YOU KNOW,
ZABAN CITY IS ONE SHADY PLACE.
Kurapika: A CITY THAT'S
AS PROSPEROUS AS THIS ONE
IS BOUND TO ATTRACT ITS SHARE
OF UNSAVORY CHARACTERS.
Gon: WOW!
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, GON?
LET'S GO!
Gon: RIGHT!
♪♪♪
Kiriko: HERE WE ARE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S THE BUILDING.
Leorio: HUH?
( Gon gasps )
IT'S SO TALL.
WOW, WHAT A NICE PLACE.
Leorio: SO THAT'S
THE EXAM SITE, HUH?
AND THIS IS THE CROWD
THAT IT DRAWS.
Kurapika: HUNTER APPLICANTS
FROM ALL ACROSS THE WORLD
CONGREGATE HERE.
Gon: MY FIRST SHOT
AT THE HUNTER EXAM.
I WONDER
IF THIS IS HOW DAD FELT.
Kiriko: HEY, GUYS!
All: HUH?
‐ Kiriko: OVER HERE.
‐ All: EH?
Kiriko: THIS IS IT.
Leorio: COME ON.
YOU'RE MESSING WITH US, RIGHT?
IT JUST LOOKS
LIKE A REGULAR RESTAURANT.
YOU'RE TELLIN' ME
THAT HUNTER APPLICANTS
FROM ALL OVER THE GLOBE
COME TO THIS OLD DIVE
TO TAKE THE EXAM?
Kiriko: THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE HUNTER EXAM
ATTRACTS MILLIONS
OF APPLICANTS EVERY YEAR,
AND NO ONE WOULD EXPECT THE EXAM
TO BE HELD HERE, RIGHT?
Leorio: GOOD POINT.
( sizzling )
Cook: WELCOME! TAKE A SEAT!
Kiriko: IS THE BACK ROOM
AVAILABLE?
Cook: WHAT ARE YOU HAVING?
Kiriko: THE STEAK COMBO, PLEASE,
THE ONE THAT'LL MAKE US
SEE THE LIGHT.
MAKE IT THREE.
Cook: COMBO FOR THREE, EH?
HOW DO YOU WANT 'EM COOKED?
Kiriko: GRILLED SLOWLY OVER
A LOW FLAME 'TIL DONE, PLEASE.
Cook: GOT IT.
SEE YOURSELVES TO THE BACK ROOM.
Kiriko: OKAY, WAIT HERE.
Leorio: FOR WHAT? WHERE ARE
ALL THE OTHER APPLICANTS?
Gon: I CAN'T WAIT
FOR THAT STEAK COMBO!
Kurapika: GON, THAT WAS JUST
THE PASSWORD TO GET US INSIDE.
THERE'S NO STEAK COMBO.
Gon: OKAY.
SO WE DON'T GET TO EAT?
Kiriko: ONLY ONE IN 10,000.
Gon: EH?
Kiriko: YOU'RE VERY LUCKY.
THAT'S HOW MANY
EVER MAKE IT THIS FAR.
NICE JOB.
YOU DID GREAT FOR FIRST‐TIMERS.
WELL, GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
Gon: THANKS FOR YOUR HELP!
Kiriko: I HOPE THAT NEXT YEAR
I CAN HELP YOU AGAIN.
( rumbling )
Leorio: WHOA!
Kurapika: IT SEEMS THIS ROOM
IS ACTUALLY AN ELEVATOR.
Leorio: THAT EXPLAINS IT.
THAT BASTARD THINKS
HE'LL SEE US AGAIN NEXT YEAR
BECAUSE HE EXPECTS US TO FAIL.
Kurapika:
ONCE EVERY THREE YEARS.
Leorio: WHAT'S THAT?
Kurapika: IT'S HOW OFTEN
A ROOKIE PASSES THE EXAM.
Gon: IT'S THAT UNUSUAL?
Kurapika: IT IS.
SOME CAN'T HANDLE IT.
IT'S TOO MENTALLY
AND PHYSICALLY TAXING.
IT'S ALSO NOT TOO UNCOMMON
FOR VETERANS
TO BREAK THE ROOKIES SO BADLY
THAT THEY NEVER RETAKE THE TEST.
Gon: SO THAT'S WHY PEOPLE
WHO WANT TO BE HUNTERS
ARE WILLING
TO RISK EVERYTHING FOR IT.
Leorio: YOU'VE HIT THE NAIL
RIGHT ON THE HEAD,
MY LITTLE FRIEND!
BEING A HUNTER
MEANS MAKING MORE MONEY
THAN ANYONE IN THE WORLD!
Kurapika: WRONG!
PEOPLE BECOME HUNTERS
TO JOIN THE WORLD'S
MOST NOBLE PROFESSION!
Leorio: SHUT UP, GOODY‐GOODY!
Kurapika: SELFISH MONEY GRUBBER!
( both growl )
Leorio: HEY, GON, LISTEN UP!
THERE'S A LIST OF THE 100
RICHEST PEOPLE EVERY YEAR,
AND EVERY SINGLE YEAR,
THERE ARE OVER 50 HUNTERS
WHO MAKE THE LIST.
THAT'S MORE THAN HALF!
( groans )
Kurapika: THERE ARE
SOME HUNTERS, SAD TO SAY,
WHO SEEK TREASURE AND WILD GAME,
BUT THEY'RE SECOND‐RATE.
TRUE HUNTERS WORK TIRELESSLY
TO MAINTAIN ORDER IN SOCIETY
AS WELL AS IN NATURE.
Leorio: OH, SCREW THAT!
ONCE YOU'RE A HUNTER, IT'S FREE
TO ENTER MOST COUNTRIES.
AND FACILITIES, NO CHARGE!
HOW'S THAT FOR BENEFITS, HUH?
( groans )
Kurapika:
HUNTERS HAVE MANY DIFFICULT
AND IMPORTANT RESPONSIBILITIES,
PRESERVING ARTIFACTS
AND SPECIES, CATCHING CROOKS,
AND EVEN APPREHENDING
ROGUE HUNTERS.
Leorio:
IT'S THE FAME AND FORTUNE!
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE
WANT TO BECOME HUNTERS!
Kurapika: NO, IT'S CONVICTION,
PROFOUND KNOWLEDGE,
AND A SOUND MIND AND BODY,
TRAITS THAT ARE
A TRUE HUNTER'S PRIDE!
( both growl )
HEY, GON, WHICH OF US
DO YOU AGREE WITH?!
WHAT KIND OF HUNTER
WILL YOU BE?
Gon: WELL, WHEN YOU PUT IT
THAT WAY, I GUESS I‐‐
‐ ( rumble )
‐ ( ding )
Kurapika: I THINK WE'VE ARRIVED.
Leorio: WE'LL FINISH THIS LATER.
( Gon sighs )
♪♪♪
Leorio: IS IT ME,
OR IS THE MOOD HERE PRETTY GRIM?
Kurapika: WE SAW PLENTY
OF OTHER APPLICANTS IN THE CITY,
BUT THESE GUYS ARE DIFFERENT.
EACH ONE OF THEM IS A MASTER
IN THEIR OWN RIGHT.
Gon: 'SCUSE ME!
LOOKS LIKE EVERYBODY'S
REALLY ON EDGE DOWN HERE.
Secretary: HELLO!
PLEASE TAKE YOUR NUMBER BADGE.
THANK YOU.
HERE YOU GO.
HERE.
BE SURE TO WEAR THIS
ON YOUR CHEST
AT ALL TIMES, PLEASE,
AND BE CAREFUL
NOT TO LOSE IT, OKAY?
Applicant: DON'T THINK
I'VE SEEN YOU BOYS BEFORE.
YO!
Gon: YOU CAN TELL
IT'S OUR FIRST TIME HERE?
Applicant #16: MORE OR LESS.
IT'S GETTING EASIER.
IT'S MY 35th ATTEMPT,
SO IT COMES WITH THE TERRITORY.
All: YOU'VE TRIED 35 TIMES?
Applicant #16: I GUESS YOU COULD
SAY I'M A HUNTER EXAM VETERAN.
Leorio: NOT REALLY
SOMETHING TO BRAG ABOUT.
Kurapika: INDEED.
Applicant #16: ANYWAY,
IF YOU HAVE ANY MORE QUESTIONS,
I'D BE HAPPY TO HELP.
Gon: THANKS A LOT!
Applicant #16: OH, BY THE WAY,
THE NAME'S TONPA.
Gon: HI. I'M GON.
THIS IS KURAPIKA,
AND THIS IS LEORIO.
YOU SURE
HAVE TAKEN THE EXAM A LOT.
ARE YOU THE ONLY ONE HERE
WHO'S TRIED A BUNCH OF TIMES,
OR ARE THERE OTHERS?
Tonpa: I MIGHT HOLD THE RECORD,
BUT, YEAH, THERE ARE OTHERS,
FOR INSTANCE,
THAT GUY OVER THERE,
NUMBER 255, TODO THE WRESTLER.
PROBABLY THE STRONGEST ONE HERE,
AND HE'S SMARTER THAN HE LOOKS.
OVER THERE IS 103,
BOURBON THE SNAKE CHARMER.
HE CAN REALLY HOLD A GRUDGE,
SO TRY NOT TO GET
ON HIS BAD SIDE.
‐ ( snake hisses )
‐ Tonpa: LET'S SEE NOW.
NUMBER 191,
BODORO THE KUNG FU MASTER.
HE'S GETTING OLD, BUT HE'S STILL
THE BEST MARTIAL ARTIST AROUND.
THEN THERE ARE THE BROTHERS,
AMORI, IMORI, AND UMORI.
THEY WORK GREAT AS A TEAM,
SO THEY ALMOST
ALWAYS DO REALLY WELL.
AND 384, GERETTA THE HUNTSMAN.
HE SPECIALIZES IN KILLING
ALL KINDS OF CREATURES
WITH HIS BLOW DART AND CLUB.
THERE ARE MORE, BUT THEY'VE
TAKEN THE EXAM THE MOST TIMES.
Gon: OH, WOW!
( man shrieking )
( applicants murmuring )
Applicant #44: MY, HOW UNUSUAL.
SEEMS THIS POOR MAN'S ARMS
HAVE TURNED INTO FLOWER PETALS.
NOW YOU SEE THEM.
NOW YOU DON'T.
( Gon gasps )
Applicant #44:
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL,
AND DO APOLOGIZE
IF YOU BUMP INTO SOMEONE.
( applicants muttering )
Tonpa: JUST PERFECT.
THE PSYCHOPATH IS BACK AGAIN.
Gon: YOU KNOW THAT GUY?
Kurapika: SO DOES THAT MEAN
HE TRIED LAST YEAR?
Tonpa: NUMBER 44,
HISOKA THE MAGICIAN.
HE WAS THE NUMBER ONE PICK
TO PASS LAST YEAR'S EXAM
UNTIL HE ALMOST KILLED
AN EXAMINER
HE DIDN'T APPROVE OF.
Leorio: THEN WHAT THE HELL
IS HE DOING HERE?!
THEY'RE LETTING HIM
RETAKE THE EXAM
AFTER SOMETHING LIKE THAT?!
Tonpa: OF COURSE THEY ARE.
THEY CHANGE THE CONTENT
AND EXAMINERS EVERY YEAR,
AND THE EXAMINERS
CHOOSE THE NEW MATERIAL.
THE DEVIL HIMSELF
COULD PASS THE HUNTER EXAM
IF THE EXAMINERS SAY IT'S OKAY.
IT'S HOW THE WHOLE THING WORKS.
ANYWAY, NOBODY LIKES THE GUY.
I'D KEEP MY DISTANCE
IF I WERE YOU.
Leorio: WELL, HE DEFINITELY
LOOKS DANGEROUS.
Tonpa: OH! I ALMOST FORGOT!
LET'S HAVE A TOAST
TO FRIENDSHIP.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
Leorio: HEY, THANKS!
YEAH, DON'T MIND IF I DO!
AH, I WAS DYING OF THIRST.
THANKS A LOT, BUDDY.
Gon: YEAH, THANKS A LOT.
Kurapika: THANK YOU.
( applicant #157 chuckles )
WELL, THERE HE GOES.
Second applicant:
PLAYING THE NICE GUY AGAIN,
EVEN THOUGH
HE'S THE NASTIEST ONE HERE.
Third applicant:
TONPA, THE ROOKIE CRUSHER.
Tonpa: HERE'S TO NEW FRIENDS
AND GOOD FORTUNE. CHEERS!
( chuckles )
( thinking )
SORRY, GUYS,
BUT THE JUICE I GAVE YOU
CONTAINS A POWERFUL LAXATIVE.
ONE SIP, AND YOUR GUTS WILL BE
ON A NONSTOP ROLLER COASTER
FOR THREE DAYS.
IF YOU WANT TO TAKE THE EXAM,
I HOPE YOU BROUGHT
PLENTY OF DIAPERS.
( chuckles )
♪♪♪
Leorio: HMM.
( chuckles )
( Tonpa chuckles )
( Gon sips )
MM? ( gasps )
( groans )
( Tonpa gasps )
Gon: I THINK THIS JUICE
MIGHT'VE GONE BAD,
MR. TONPA. IT TASTES FUNNY
Leorio: SERIOUSLY?
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
Tonpa: HUH? THAT'S ODD.
REALLY SORRY ABOUT THAT, FELLAS.
( thinking )
IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT LAXATIVE IS
FLAVORLESS AND ODORLESS.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
I HAD NO IDEA THE JUICE WAS BAD!
Gon: YOU DON'T
HAVE TO APOLOGIZE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
IS YOUR STOMACH OKAY?
Tonpa: I'M ALL RIGHT.
I'M TOTALLY FINE.
Gon: OH, GOOD. I'VE TRIED
ALL KINDS OF PLANTS AND GRASSES
ON THE MOUNTAIN BACK HOME,
SO I CAN USUALLY TASTE
WHEN SOMETHING'S BAD.
Tonpa: THAT'S SOME TALENT
YOU GOT THERE.
HEH HEH.
NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
( thinking )
DAMN IT.
HE JUST HAD TO BE
SOME WILD MOUNTAIN KID.
SORRY AGAIN.
I'LL SEE YOU BOYS AROUND.
Leorio: MAN, I THOUGHT
HE WOULD NEVER SHUT UP.
( Tonpa thinking )
SOMETHING ISN'T QUITE RIGHT
ABOUT THE CROP OF ROOKIES
THIS YEAR.
LIKE 294, HANZO.
THE FIRST TIME I TALKED TO HIM,
HE ACTUALLY SEEMED
PRETTY GULLIBLE.
Hanzo: KEEP THIS TO YOURSELF,
BUT I AM A NINJA.
Tonpa: WHOA, IS THAT SO?
Hanzo: I SEEK
THE LEGENDARY SCROLL.
SHH!
IT IS MY SECRET MISSION
TO TRACK DOWN
THE ULTIMATE NINJA SCROLL.
THAT'S WHY
I'M BECOMING A HUNTER.
RUMOR HAS IT
THAT IT'S HIDDEN SOMEWHERE
THAT'S INACCESSIBLE
TO ORDINARY PEOPLE.
ANYWAY, THIS PLACE
IS PRETTY BORING, HUH?
Tonpa: I GUESS SO.
HEY, WE SHOULD HAVE A TOAST.
TO FRIENDSHIP AND
GOOD FORTUNE, HUH?
Hanzo: I AM A SEASONED NINJA.
I MAKE IT A POINT
NEVER TO DRINK ANYTHING
OFFERED TO ME BY ANOTHER.
YOU UNDERSTAND.
Tonpa: OH, RIGHT.
GOTCHA.
( nervous laugh )
( thinking )
I CAN TELL HE'S NO IDIOT.
ONE WRONG MOVE, AND I COULD'VE
BEEN IN SOME SERIOUS TROUBLE.
‐ ( rattling )
‐ EH?
( neck rattling )
SPEAKING OF TROUBLE,
THERE'S 301.
THAT GUY JUST OOZES DANGER.
I KNOW ONE THING.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE NEAR HIM.
THEN THERE'S THE ONE
I REALLY CAN'T STAND,
107, NICOLAS.
MUST'VE BEEN TOUGH
TO MAKE IT THIS FAR, HUH?
Nicolas: NOT REALLY.
EVERYTHING'S GONE EXACTLY
AS MY DATA PREDICTED.
I USED HISTORICAL DATA
FROM PAST HUNTER EXAMS
TO CALCULATE
THIS YEAR'S LOCATION.
IT WAS REALLY QUITE SIMPLE
AND FRANKLY RATHER BORING.
Tonpa: OH. WELL, GOOD.
IMPRESSIVE WORK THERE, KID.
THE NAME'S TONPA.
IT'S REAL NICE TO MEET YOU.
Nicolas: TONPA, IS IT?
AH! THERE YOU ARE.
THIS IS YOUR 35th ATTEMPT,
THAT'S THE SECOND‐HIGHEST NUMBER
OF ATTEMPTS BY ANYONE.
BUT IT SAYS HERE THAT YOU
DO HOLD THE CURRENT RECORD
FOR THE MOST
CONSECUTIVE ATTEMPTS WITH 30.
THAT'S QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
Tonpa: THANK YOU,
BUT IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU WANNA TOAST TO FRIENDSHIP?
Nicolas: BUT AFTER 35 ATTEMPTS,
YOU HAVE YET
TO SUCCESSFULLY PASS THE EXAM,
AND SO I ASSUME
YOU'RE TOO FOCUSED
ON YOUR OTHER OBJECTIVE.
AM I RIGHT,
TONPA THE ROOKIE‐CRUSHER?
Tonpa: SAY WHAT?
Nicolas: FEAR NOT.
I WON'T DIVULGE
MY FINDINGS WITH ANYONE ELSE.
CONSIDER IT A PRIZE FOR YOUR
CONSECUTIVE APPEARANCE RECORD.
FAREWELL.
( Tonpa growling )
( thinking )
JUST WAIT, YOU LITTLE BASTARD.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S GONNA BREAK
THAT SNOTTY NOSE OF YOURS.
Applicant: HEY! MR. TONPA!
THAT JUICE WAS GREAT!
GOT ANY MORE?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M JUST NERVOUS,
BUT I REALLY AM THIRSTY!
Tonpa: UH, OH!
OF COURSE!
( thinking )
WHAT THE HELL?
THAT LAXATIVE HE DRANK
SHOULD HAVE TAKEN EFFECT BY NOW.
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS KID?
IT'S ONLY A LAXATIVE, BUT STILL,
IF THE KID DRINKS THAT MUCH,
HE COULD DIE OF DEHYDRATION.
Applicant #99: WORRIED?
WELL, DON'T BE. I'LL BE FINE.
I'VE TRAINED FOR THIS.
POISONS DON'T HURT ME.
Tonpa: IMPOSSIBLE.
( thinking ) THAT KID
WAS ACTUALLY ABLE TO TELL
WHAT WAS IN THE JUICE?
BUT IF HE KNEW, THEN WHY
THE HELL DID HE DRINK IT?
NUMBER 99, KILLUA.
DAMN. THIS YEAR'S ROOKIES
ARE COMPLETELY INSANE.
( chuckles )
BUT SO WHAT?
IT JUST MEANS CRUSHING THEM
WILL BE ALL THE MORE SATISFYING.
( alarm bell ringing )
( ringing continues )
Hanzo: HUH?
Examiner: I APOLOGIZE
FOR THE DELAY.
THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
THE ENTRY PERIOD
FOR HUNTER APPLICANTS
IS OFFICIALLY CLOSED,
SO WITH NO FURTHER ADO,
THE HUNTER EXAM WILL NOW BEGIN.
( applicants murmuring )
Examiner:
ONE FINAL WORD OF CAUTION.
IF YOU'RE SHORT
ON LUCK OR ABILITY,
KEEP IN MIND
THAT THERE'S A VERY REAL CHANCE
YOU COULD END UP
SERIOUSLY INJURED.
DEATH IS ANOTHER
DISTINCT POSSIBILITY.
IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO ACCEPT THE RISKS INVOLVED,
I'LL ASK YOU TO FOLLOW ME NOW,
BUT FOR THE REST OF YOU,
KINDLY EXIT THROUGH
THE ELEVATOR LOCATED BEHIND YOU.
RIGHT, THEN. VERY WELL.
ALL 404 APPLICANTS WILL
NOW PARTICIPATE IN PHASE ONE.
♪♪♪
Leorio: YEAH, I DIDN'T THINK
ANYBODY WAS GONNA LEAVE,
BUT I'D HOPED A FEW
WOULD DUCK OUT, AT LEAST.
WHOA. WHAT?
Gon: I THINK THE PEOPLE UP FRONT
HAVE STARTED RUNNING.
Kurapika: THAT'S BECAUSE
HE'S PICKING UP THE PACE.
Examiner: HOW RUDE OF ME.
I NEGLECTED TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM SATOTZ,
YOUR EXAMINER FOR
THE FIRST PHASE OF THE EXAM.
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY TO LEAD
YOU ALL TO THE SECOND PHASE.
Hanzo: SECOND?
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THE FIRST?
THE FIRST PHASE
IS ALREADY UNDER WAY.
( applicants muttering )
Satotz: THE FIRST PHASE
IS QUITE SIMPLE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
FOLLOW ME TO THE SECOND PHASE,
SO TRY TO KEEP UP.
Hanzo: FOLLOW YOU? SO THAT'S IT?
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE?
Satotz: THAT'S RIGHT.
I CANNOT TELL YOU WHERE
OR WHEN YOU MUST ARRIVE.
YOU NEED ONLY TO FOLLOW ME.
Kurapika: I SEE HOW IT IS.
Gon: THIS EXAM IS WEIRD.
Leorio: SOUNDS A LOT LIKE
A BASIC ENDURANCE TEST TO ME.
THAT'S RIGHT UP MY ALLEY.
KEEP RUNNING, PAL!
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
( Kurapika thinking )
NOT KNOWING HOW FAR
WE'LL HAVE TO RUN
IS MENTALLY STRESSFUL,
TO SAY NOTHING
OF THE PHYSICAL STRAIN.
THIS IS A TEST
OF OUR MENTAL FORTITUDE AS WELL.
Narrator: AND SO, AMIDST A SEA
OF WARRIORS AND VILLAINS,
THE FIRST PHASE
OF THE EXAM BEGINS.
ONE CANDIDATE IS DISQUALIFIED
BEFORE THE TEST
EVEN GETS UNDER WAY,
BRINGING THE TOTAL NUMBER
OF HUNTER APPLICANTS TO 404.
( Gon panting )
( singing in Japanese )
♪♪♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"HOPE AND AMBITION."
TIME TO GO FISHIN'! YEAH.
♪♪♪