♪
( both gasp )
Worm:
I AM THE SHADOW BEAST, WORM.
WHICH FAMILY DO YOU BELONG TO?
Dalzollene: WE'RE BODYGUARDS.
WE'VE BEEN HIRED
BY THE NOSTRADE FAMILY.
Worm: I UNDERSTAND.
IT SEEMS THAT YOU CAN USE NEN
A BIT, BUT DON'T BOTHER.
Rabid Dog:
THESE ARE NO ORDINARY THUGS.
TO THEM, KILLING'S
A PART OF THEIR DAILY ROUTINE.
Porcupine: YOU COULD SAY THAT
THEY ARE PROFESSIONAL KILLERS.
Leech: AND AS PROS OURSELVES,
WE'LL HANDLE IT.
Rabid Dog: MY NAME'S RABID DOG.
Leech: AND MINE IS LEECH.
Porcupine: YOU, UH,
CAN CALL ME PORCUPINE.
Rabid Dog: SIT BACK,
AND LEAVE THIS JOB
TO THE SHADOW BEASTS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( man gags )
( man #2 screams )
( all grunting )
Narrator:
AFTER THE PHANTOM TROUPE'S RAID
ON THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION,
UVOGIN HAS SINGLE‐HANDEDLY
ANNIHILATED THE MAFIA PURSUERS.
BUT NOW THEY LOOK ON
AS THE MAFIA'S
SECRET WEAPON ARRIVES,
DISPATCHED BY THE 10 DONS,
THE SHADOW BEASTS.
( man #3 gasping )
( crack )
Uvogin: THAT WAS BORING.
NOT ONE OF 'EM
PUT UP MUCH OF A FIGHT.
Shalnark: UVO!
Uvogin: YEAH?
Shalnark: THEY'RE HERE NOW!
♪
( Uvogin chuckles )
HEY, DON'T INTERFERE!
YOU GOT THAT?
I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD
THE CHANCE TO ENJOY MYSELF.
Feitan: OH, BOY.
Shalnark: OH,
JUST LET UVO HANDLE IT.
WANT IN ON A ROUND, FEITAN?
Squala: WAIT. IS HE PLANNING
TO FIGHT THE SHADOW BEASTS
ALL BY HIMSELF?
Uvogin: THE SHADOW BEASTS, HUH?
WHERE'D YOU HIDE
THE MERCHANDISE?
Rabid Dog: WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE GUARDS AND GUESTS?
Uvogin: WE KILLED THEM.
WHERE'S THE MERCHANDISE?
IF YOU DON'T ANSWER ME...
‐ ( crack )
‐ ( Worm gasping )
Uvogin: THAT ONE STUNG.
( Worm gags )
( Shadow Beasts gasp )
( Uvogin chuckles )
Worm: EH?
Uvogin: HUH?
♪
( Worm laughs )
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE NOW.
WHAT WILL IT BE, HMM,
HAVE ME KILL YOU UNDERGROUND,
OR WOULD YOU RATHER DIE
AT THE HANDS OF THE OTHER THREE
UP ON THE SURFACE?
Uvogin: IDIOT.
( Shadow Beasts gasping )
‐ ( Feitan gasps )
‐ Nobunaga: HERE WE GO.
Shalnark: UVO IS
GETTING PRETTY SERIOUS.
FOUR.
Uvogin: YOU TALK
A PRETTY GOOD GAME,
BUT CAN YOU BACK IT UP?!
( Worm gasps )
( both gasping )
Squala: I‐I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
Basho: I'VE NEVER SEEN
A NEN USER
OF THIS CALIBER BEFORE.
( Shadow Beasts gasp )
( somber chorus humming )
Rabid Dog: IS THAT...
Porcupine: IT'S A SPIDER TATTOO.
Leech: THEN HE'S...
( heart beating )
Kurapika: SPIDERS.
( Melody gasps )
Franklin: THAT POOR GUY.
THERE'S NOT MUCH LEFT OF HIM.
Nobunaga: UVO'S BIG BANG IMPACT
SURE PACKS A POWERFUL PUNCH.
Machi: YEAH, BUT TO BE FAIR,
IT'S JUST A REGULAR PUNCH
WITH NEN ADDED.
EIGHT.
Shizuku: NINE.
Shalnark: 10.
Uvogin: OKAY,
SO WHO WANTS TO DIE NEXT?
Rabid Dog:
THE PHANTOM TROUPE, HUH?
Porcupine: WELL, HE SEEMS
PRETTY CONFIDENT. YUP.
( Rabid Dog spits )
I THINK IT'S YOUR TURN.
Leech: OH, YOU'RE IN FOR IT NOW.
( Uvogin laughs ) NICE!
GOTTA LOVE RECKLESS OPPONENTS.
EASY TO KILL!
EH?
Porcupine: I CAN MANIPULATE
MY BODY HAIR, YOU SEE?
I CAN EVEN TURN IT INTO
THESE NEEDLES IF I WANT TO. YUP.
YOU THROW A MEAN PUNCH,
BUT IT'S POINTLESS
IF YOU CAN'T CONNECT. YUP.
‐ ( Rabid Dog hisses )
‐ ( Uvogin grunts )
( Rabid Dog spits )
Nobunaga: HUH?
Feitan: THEY DAMAGED
UVOGIN'S IRON SKIN
WITH NOTHING MORE
THAN BODY HAIR AND TEETH.
Shalnark: THEY MUST BE
REALLY SKILLED NEN USERS.
I'M IMPRESSED, ACTUALLY.
Shizuku: THAT'S 13.
Shalnark: NO WAY!
Shizuku: SORRY.
( Shalnark sighs )
YOU WANT A HAND OVER THERE, UVO?
‐ Uvogin: STAY OUT OF THIS!
‐ ( Shalnark sighs )
Uvogin: DAMN IT! COME ON!
Porcupine: IT'S FUTILE.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
IN YOUR SKIN.
YOU CAN'T SHAKE THEM OFF. YUP.
Uvogin: THEN I'LL
JUST HAVE TO USE YOU
AS AN EXTENSION OF MY FIST!
EH?
Porcupine: SINCE I
MANIPULATE IT AT WILL,
I CAN RELAX SECTIONS OF MY HAIR
AS NECESSARY. YUP, YUP, YUP.
( Rabid Dog spits )
THIS IS TOO EASY, MUSCLEHEAD!
Uvogin: THAT'S BULL!
♪
HUH?
Rabid Dog:
WHAT'S WRONG, TOUGH GUY?
FINALLY KICK IN?
THE SENSATION
THAT YOU'RE FEELING
IS THE FAST‐ACTING NEUROTOXIN
MY FANGS PUMPED INTO YOU.
( Uvogin groans ) BASTARD.
Rabid Dog: YOU WON'T BE AFFECTED
FROM THE NECK UP,
SO YOU CAN STILL FEEL
FEAR AND PAIN. TRY AND ENJOY IT.
Machi: IF HE WERE USING
LETHAL POISON,
THE FIGHT WOULD BE ALL OVER NOW.
Shalnark: HE PROBABLY
ENJOYS TORTURE.
‐ ( squishing )
‐ Uvogin: HEY.
( Leech laughs )
I KEEP COUNTLESS LEECHES
OF LOTS OF DIFFERENT SIZES
STORED WITHIN MY BODY.
AS WE SPEAK,
THEY'RE ENTERING YOUR BODY
THROUGH YOUR INJURIES,
AND SOON THEY'LL LAY THEIR EGGS
IN YOUR BLADDER.
THESE SPOTTED LEECHES
ARE A GIFT FROM ME TO YOU.
Uvogin: YOU'RE
TOTALLY DISGUSTING.
YOU KNOW THAT?
( Leech laughs )
MOST DIE FROM THE PAIN.
HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF LEECHES
HATCHING INSIDE OF YOUR BODY
IS EXCRUCIATING,
AS YOU'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT
FIRSTHAND.
( laughs )
( both gasp )
( chorus vocalizing )
Uvogin: THAT'S AWFUL.
I THOUGHT THAT UGLY
USUALLY MEANT BETTER‐TASTING.
SURPRISED?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN BITE, YOU KNOW.
( laughs )
( Porcupine gasps )
Uvogin: EVEN WITHOUT MY BODY,
MY NECK AND HEAD ARE
MORE THAN ENOUGH TO BEAT YOU.
( chorus continues )
Kurapika: THEY WILL LOSE.
THE SHADOW BEASTS ARE DEAD.
( chorus vocalizing )
Kurapika: THEY WILL LOSE.
THE SHADOW BEASTS ARE DEAD.
Rabid Dog: YOU REALLY
STILL THINK YOU CAN WIN?
( scoffs )
NO WAY IN HELL YOU CAN BITE ME
WHEN I'M ALL THE WAY OVER HERE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
( Uvogin chuckles )
( inhaling )
( spits )
Rabid Dog: A BULLET? NO.
IT'S A CHUNK
HE BIT OUT OF LEECH'S SKULL.
( grunts )
( both gasp )
( Rabid Dog gasping )
( Porcupine gasps )
( Uvogin inhaling )
Porcupine: IF HE TRIES THAT
ON ME, IT'LL NEVER WORK.
MY BODY HAIR WILL DEFLECT
ANY PROJECTILES, YUP.
( Shalnark gasps )
( Uvogin roaring )
( Kurapika grunts )
Uvogin: CAN'T DEFLECT
BULLETS OF SOUND, CAN YOU?
WHAT'S WRONG? CAN'T YOU HEAR ME?
Basho: HE USED SOUND
TO KILL A SHADOW BEAST.
Squala: THEY'RE CRAZY,
COMPLETELY CRAZY.
Dalzollene: DAMN.
Franklin: HEY, WHAT THE HELL,
YOU IDIOT?!
HOW ABOUT A WARNING NEXT TIME?
Nobunaga: DO YOU WANNA BURST
OUR EARDRUMS, TOO?
Uvogin: SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO GIVE AWAY MY PLAN.
BESIDES, THE SOUND TOOK A WHILE
TO REACH YOU GUYS, DIDN'T IT?
YOU HAD PLENTY OF TIME
TO COVER YOUR EARS.
Machi: THAT'S TRUE.
( Dalzollene gasps )
♪
KURAPIKA, WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Kurapika: ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'M GOING TO CAPTURE HIM.
( bodyguards gasp )
Squala: THAT GUY? NO WAY!
YOU SAW WHAT HE DID.
YOU'RE GONNA
GET YOURSELF KILLED.
Dalzollene: STOP, KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: IT DOESN'T MATTER.
( Dalzollene gasps )
Melody: I HEAR
SUCH VIOLENT RAGE AND HATRED.
HE'S GONE BLIND WITH IT.
Dalzollene: KURAPIKA!
Melody: HE'S WALKING
RIGHT INTO HIS OWN FUNERAL.
I HAVE TO STOP HIM.
Dalzollene: WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
( grunts )
( Melody playing flute )
( Kurapika gasps )
Melody: "FIELD IN SPRING,"
A PERFECT COMPOSITION
FOR RELAXING.
NOW, HAS EVERYONE CALMED DOWN?
IF SO, LET'S PLAN
OUR STRATEGY WITH LEVEL HEADS.
Dalzollene: YEAH.
Basho: WHAT KIND
OF NEN ABILITIES
DO THE OTHER MEMBERS POSSESS?
Squala: I'M WILLING TO BET
THEY'RE ALL RIDICULOUSLY STRONG.
‐ Kurapika: MELODY.
‐ Melody: EH?
Kurapika: THANKS A LOT.
I'VE CALMED DOWN.
( Melody sighs )
Kurapika: BUT I'M STILL
GOING TO CAPTURE THEM.
( Melody gasps )
Kurapika: LEADER!
Dalzollene: HMM?
Kurapika: I STAND A GOOD CHANCE.
‐ ( bodyguards gasp )
‐ Dalzollene: WHAT'S THAT?
Kurapika: LET ME DO IT.
Dalzollene: YOU SAW THAT
INCREDIBLE SHOW OF STRENGTH,
AND YOU STILL THINK
YOU HAVE A SHOT?
Kurapika: I DO.
Dalzollene: UNDERSTOOD.
( Kurapika grunts )
WE MAY NEED TO LEAVE QUICKLY,
SO PLEASE PULL THE CAR AROUND.
Linssen: RIGHT.
Uvogin: SHIZUKU, DO ME A FAVOR,
AND SUCK ALL THE POISON
AND LEECHES OUT OF MY BODY!
YOUR VACUUM COULD DO IT, RIGHT?
Shizuku: BLINKY CAN
SUCK OUT THE POISON,
BUT NOTHING THAT'S STILL ALIVE.
Uvogin: REALLY?!
THEN WHAT DO I DO?
Shalnark: LET ME SEE.
THIS IS KNOWN
AS A SPOTTED LEECH.
IT TAKES A NEARLY A FULL DAY
FOR IT TO MIGRATE
TO THE BLADDER
BEFORE LAYING ITS EGGS
AND DYING.
Uvogin: YEAH? THEN WHAT?
Shalnark: WELL, AFTER THAT,
THE EGGS WILL HATCH
AND EXIT THROUGH
YOUR URINARY TRACT.
YOU'LL MOST LIKELY DIE
FROM THE PAIN.
Uvogin: COME ON.
DON'T JOKE AROUND LIKE THAT.
Shalnark: HOWEVER, THEY REQUIRE
A VERY SPECIFIC CONCENTRATION
OF AMMONIA TO HATCH.
IF THERE ISN'T ENOUGH,
THE EGGS STAY DORMANT AND
CAN BE EXCRETED HARMLESSLY...
WHICH MEANS THAT
UNTIL THIS TIME TOMORROW,
IT'S ABSOLUTELY CRITICAL
THAT YOU DRINK BEER CONSTANTLY
AND PEE AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
Uvogin: IS THAT ALL?
YOU REALLY HAD ME WORRIED.
SHIZUKU, CAN YOU GET THE POISON?
Shizuku: OKAY!
Shalnark: SOMEONE GO INTO TOWN,
AND GET LOTS OF BEER.
Franklin: ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO.
Uvogin: AND MAKE SURE
THOSE SUCKERS ARE ICE‐COLD!
Franklin: YOU'LL GET
WHAT I BRING YOU.
( Blinky cackles )
Uvogin: HURRY,
AND GET THIS POISON OUT OF ME!
HUH?
Shalnark: HUH?
♪
Shizuku: HUH?
( Uvogin screaming )
‐ Shalnark: DID YOU SEE THAT?
‐ Nobunaga: YEAH.
Shizuku: THOSE CHAINS
CAME OUT OF NOWHERE
AND WRAPPED AROUND HIS BODY.
Nobunaga: IS IT
A NEW SHADOW BEAST?
UVO CAN'T MOVE
DUE TO THE NEUROTOXIN,
AND THOSE LEECHES
ARE STILL INSIDE OF HIM, TOO.
Shalnark: THERE'S NO CHOICE.
WE GOTTA GO AND SAVE HIM.
Feitan: OH, BOY.
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
Machi: WE CAN STILL FIND OUT
WHERE HE'S GOING.
I USED IN
TO MAKE MY THREAD INVISIBLE.
I CAN FOLLOW THEM ANYWHERE,
AS LONG AS THEY
DON'T SPOT THE NEEDLE,
AND THEY'D HAVE TO USE GYO
TO DO THAT.
Shalnark: WELL, LET'S FIND THEM
BEFORE THEY FIGURE IT OUT.
Nobunaga: HEH. NOW'S OUR CHANCE
TO FINISH OFF
THE OTHER SHADOW BEASTS.
Shalnark: GET AS MUCH BEER
AS YOU CAN, FRANKLIN.
( Franklin chuckles )
MAN, THE CHASE SOUNDS MORE FUN.
( Shalnark laughs )
COME ON. LET'S GO.
♪
Worm: INDEED, THE SPIDERS.
LISTEN TO ME.
GATHER UP EVERYONE WHO'S LEFT,
OR WE DON'T STAND A CH...
Boss: UNDERSTOOD.
CHAINS, IS IT?
( car engine roars )
Uvogin: HEY, DRIVER,
YOU DON'T REALLY THINK
THESE CHAINS CAN HOLD ME,
DO YOU?
KILL ME NOW,
OR YOU'LL REGRET IT.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
Kurapika: QUIET.
Uvogin: DO YOU HEAR ME?
THIS IS THE ONLY CHANCE
YOU'RE EVER GONNA GET.
STOP WASTING TIME, AND‐‐
( chains crunch )
( grunting )
Kurapika: I THOUGHT
I TOLD YOU TO BE QUIET!
Melody: KURAPIKA, BE CAREFUL!
WATCH THE ROAD!
Uvogin: DAMN.
HOW CAN HE BE THIS STRONG?
EVEN IF MY BODY
WASN'T PARALYZED,
I'D STILL BE HAVING TROUBLE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW, BUT HE'S
INFUSED THESE PUNY CHAINS
WITH ENOUGH NEN
TO KEEP ME IN CHECK.
I'M A MASTER ENHANCER.
THAT SHOULDN'T EVEN BE POSSIBLE.
Kurapika: CHAIN JAIL,
AN ABILITY I WILL USE
ONLY ON THE SPIDERS...
A POWER TO CAPTURE
AND RESTRAIN
THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
I'VE SWORN TO USE IT
FOR NO OTHER PURPOSE.
IF I BREAK MY VOW,
IF I SHOULD USE THIS TECHNIQUE
ON ANYONE OTHER THAN A SPIDER...
‐ ( heart beating )
‐ MY LIFE IS FORFEIT.
I WOULD DIE INSTANTLY...
A SELF‐IMPOSED CONDITION
AND A CONTRACT WITH MYSELF,
THE PROOF OF MY RESOLVE.
Melody: KURAPIKA, LOOK OUT!
‐ PLEASE WATCH THE ROAD!
‐ Kurapika: THE RISK IS HIGH,
BUT THE GREATER
THE STRENGTH OF MY CONVICTION,
THE STRONGER MY NEN.
♪
Narrator: KURAPIKA HAS CAPTURED
A MEMBER OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
ARMED WITH RESOLVE
AND THE WILLINGNESS
TO RISK HIS LIFE,
HE PREPARES FOR THE BATTLE
THAT WILL SOON BEGIN.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: THIS IS OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: WE'RE INTRODUCING
THE SHADOW BEASTS,
A FIGHTING FORCE
FOR THE MAFIA'S TEN DONS.
Killua: OKAY, BUT WHO ARE THEY?
Gon: OWL. THEN THERE'S WORM
AND PORCUPINE. LET ME SEE.
NOW, WHAT WAS
THE OTHER ONE CALLED? LEECH!
♪
NEXT TIME, "RESTRAINT AND VOW."
KILLUA,
DON'T RUN IN THE HALLWAY!
Killua: THE SILENT GAIT
COUNTS AS WALKING.
Gon: FOLLOW THE RULES!
PROMISE ME, OKAY?