( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Gon panting )
♪
( gasping )
( yelling )
( gasps )
( birds chirping )
( Gon panting )
Satotz: OH, GOOD. YOU'RE AWAKE.
Gon: WHERE AM I?
Satotz: IN A WAITING ROOM
THAT IS NEXT TO THE ARENA
FOR THE FINAL PHASE.
ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
Gon: OH, RIGHT.
I WAS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
Satotz: YOUR ARM WILL BE FINE,
BY THE WAY.
THE BREAK WAS CLEAN
AND EASILY SET.
IN FACT, THAT LIMB WILL BE
EVEN STRONGER ONCE IT MENDS.
IN ANY CASE,
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR WIN, GON.
♪
Gon: MR. SATOTZ, I, UH‐‐
Satotz: YOU CAN'T.
JUST AS SOMEONE
WHO HAS FAILED THE HUNTER EXAM
CAN NO LONGER PASS,
SOMEONE WHO HAS PASSED
THE HUNTER EXAM
CAN NO LONGER FAIL.
WHAT YOU MAKE OF IT
IS ENTIRELY UP TO YOU.
IF YOU FEEL YOU'RE UNQUALIFIED
TO BE A PROFESSIONAL,
YOU MAY PUT AWAY YOUR LICENSE
OR DESTROY IT, IF YOU WISH.
YOU CAN EVEN SELL IT,
THOUGH IT'S OF NO PRACTICAL USE
TO ANYONE ELSE.
HOWEVER, YOU HAVE OFFICIALLY
PASSED THE HUNTER EXAM,
AND NO ONE WHO PASSES IT WILL
EVER BE ALLOWED TO RETAKE IT.
DUE TO THE EFFORTS
OF OUR PREDECESSORS,
PROFESSIONAL HUNTERS
ARE TREATED QUITE WELL.
AS A RESULT,
THERE IS NO END OF APPLICANTS
SEEKING A LICENSE
FOR THE WORST INTENTIONS.
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR THE LIKES OF THEM,
WE WOULD GLADLY PASS EVERYONE
WHO APPLIES WITHOUT EXCEPTION.
MOST PROFESSIONAL HUNTERS
VALUE THIS CARD
EVEN ABOVE THEIR OWN LIVES.
ALL THE SAME,
IT'S REALLY NOTHING MORE
THAN A SILLY PIECE OF JUNK.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS NOT THE WAY
THAT YOU BECOME A HUNTER,
BUT WHAT YOU DO.
Gon: WHAT I DO, HUH?
Satotz: GON, YOU MUST
DECIDE FOR YOURSELF
WHEN YOU'RE READY
TO USE THIS CARD.
I'M CONFIDENT THAT YOU'LL
MAKE THE RIGHT CHOICE.
Gon: MM. YOU KNOW, I GOT
A LOT OF HELP TO GET THIS FAR,
AND I OWE A LOT OF PEOPLE
A BUNCH OF FAVORS.
ONCE I'VE PAID EVERYONE BACK,
THEN I THINK I'LL BE READY.
Satotz: THEN PLEASE
ALLOW ME THE HONOR
OF CONGRATULATING YOU
ONCE AGAIN.
Gon: THANK YOU, MR. SATOTZ.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE OTHER APPLICANTS?
THE EXAM'S STILL
GOING ON, RIGHT?
Satotz: OH, NO.
THE EXAM HAS ALREADY ENDED.
Gon: SERIOUSLY?
Satotz: THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'VE BEEN OUT
FOR ALMOST THE ENTIRE DAY.
Gon: THE ENTIRE DAY?
Satotz: THE OTHERS WHO PASSED
ARE COMPLETING
A BRIEF ORIENTATION,
THE SAME ORIENTATION
YOU'LL UNDERGO LATER.
Gon: WHO WOUND UP FAILING?
Satotz: IT WAS...
KILLUA.
Gon: KILLUA FAILED?
BUT WHY?
Satotz: I FEEL I SHOULD BEGIN
BY TELLING YOU
ABOUT ALL THAT TRANSPIRED
AFTER YOU LOST CONSCIOUSNESS.
PERHAPS THAT WAY, YOU'LL BETTER
UNDERSTAND THE OUTCOME.
JUST AS SOON
AS YOU WERE OUT COLD...
♪
Hanzo: WHENEVER HE WAKES UP,
HE'LL PROBABLY DECLINE
HIS ADVANCEMENT.
Leorio: HE'S RIGHT.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
GON WOULD DO.
Hanzo: ONLY ONE PERSON
FAILS THIS ROUND, RIGHT,
SO IF GON IS DISQUALIFIED,
THEN WOULDN'T THAT RENDER
THE REST OF OUR UPCOMING FIGHTS
COMPLETELY MEANINGLESS?
Netero: YOU'VE NO NEED TO WORRY.
GON HAS CERTAINLY PASSED.
NOTHING HE SAYS OR DOES
CAN CHANGE THAT NOW.
( both sigh )
Netero: AS A MATTER OF FACT,
HE COULD EVEN THROW A FIT
AND KILL ME WHERE I STAND,
BUT WE STILL WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO REVOKE HIS LICENSE.
Hanzo: YES, I SEE.
Killua: SO WHY?
WHY'D YOU LET HIM WIN?
Hanzo: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
Killua: YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO KILL HIM.
WITH YOUR SKILLS, YOU COULD'VE
MADE HIM SURRENDER SOMEHOW.
Hanzo: I EXPECT,
WHEN I TORTURE SOMEONE,
MY VICTIM WILL DESPISE ME
FOR THE REST OF THEIR LIFE.
IT'S MORE EFFECTIVE
AND LESS STRESSFUL.
WHEN YOU'RE IN PAIN, YOUR EYES
SHOW A GLEAM OF HOSTILITY
TOWARD THE PERSON RESPONSIBLE.
EVEN WITH THE MOST EXTENSIVE
TRAINING AND DISCIPLINE,
THAT SIGN OF RAGE
IS DIFFICULT TO SUPPRESS.
BUT GON'S EYES
HAD NO SUCH GLEAM.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I HAD JUST BROKEN HIS ARM,
BUT I COULD TELL
JUST BY LOOKING INTO HIS EYES
THAT HE HAD ALREADY
FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT IT.
SO I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
THE LITTLE GUY WON ME OVER.
Hisoka: HMM.
IF YOU NEED A REASON
WHY I LET HIM WIN,
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
Satotz: YOU WON OVER
YOUR OPPONENT, GON.
HANZO ADMITTED AS MUCH HIMSELF.
AFTER THAT, THE SECOND MATCH
OF THE PHASE BEGAN.
Masta: ROUND TWO!
KURAPIKA VERSUS HISOKA.
BEGIN!
Satotz: AFTER THE TWO OF THEM
HAD BEEN FIGHTING FOR A WHILE...
‐ ( Kurapika gasps )
‐ ( no audible whisper )
( Hisoka chuckles )
‐ I LOSE THIS ONE.
‐ ( Masta gasps )
Satotz: AND THAT'S
HOW KURAPIKA WON.
Gon: WHAT DID HISOKA SAY?
Satotz: I COULDN'T SAY,
BUT I DO KNOW
THAT HE CONCEDED VOLUNTARILY.
THE THIRD MATCH
PITTED HANZO AGAINST POKKLE.
POKKLE FOUND HIMSELF IN MUCH
THE SAME POSITION AS YOU,
BUT HE ADMITTED DEFEAT,
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, IN FACT.
Hanzo: I'M SORRY,
BUT I WON'T GO EASY ON YOU.
Satotz: AND WITH THAT,
THE MATCH WAS OVER.
THE FOURTH MATCH
WAS BETWEEN HISOKA AND BODORO.
( Bodoro yells )
Satotz: THE MATCH
WAS EXTREMELY ONE‐SIDED,
BUT BODORO FLATLY
REFUSED TO GIVE IN.
( Bodoro gasping )
Satotz: HOWEVER, WHILE BODORO
WAS LYING ON THE FLOOR,
HISOKA WHISPERED
SOMETHING IN HIS EAR,
AND THIS TIME,
IT WAS BODORO WHO SURRENDERED.
THE FIFTH MATCH
FEATURED KILLUA AND POKKLE,
BUT KILLUA WALKED AWAY
AS SOON AS IT BEGAN.
Masta: HUH?
Satotz: IN A CONFIDENT TONE,
HE DECLARED...
Killua: YEAH, SORRY,
BUT I'M JUST NOT INTERESTED
IN FIGHTING YOU.
Satotz: HE MUST HAVE
FELT CERTAIN
HE COULD WIN HIS NEXT MATCH.
BUT THEN LEORIO REQUESTED THAT
THE SIXTH MATCH BE POSTPONED
WHILE BODORO RECOVERED
FROM HIS INJURIES,
SO IN THE MEANTIME,
THE MATCH BETWEEN KILLUA
AND GITTARACKUR WAS HELD.
Masta: BEGIN!
Satotz: IT BECAME APPARENT
THAT KILLUA HAD MADE
A GRAVE MISCALCULATION.
Gittarackur:
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, KIL.
♪
( Killua gasping )
BIG BROTHER.
♪
HMM?
( chuckles )
Gon: WAIT. SO GITTARACKUR
IS KILLUA'S BROTHER?
Satotz: YES,
AND HIS NAME IS ILLUMI.
♪
( Killua gasping )
Illumi: HEY.
Leorio: HE'S KILLUA'S BROTHER?
Kurapika: THOSE NEEDLES WERE
USED TO CHANGE HIS APPEARANCE?
Illumi: I HEARD
YOU STABBED MOM AND MILLUKI.
Killua: GUESS SO.
Illumi:
MOM COULDN'T STOP CRYING.
Leorio:
WELL, WHO WOULD BLAME HER?
ANYBODY'D CRY
IF THEIR KID DID THAT.
Illumi: SHE WAS JUST SO HAPPY.
( Leorio gasps )
Illumi: SHE WAS DELIGHTED TO SEE
THAT HER SON
HAD FINALLY GROWN UP.
BUT SHE'S CONCERNED ABOUT YOU
BEING OUT ON YOUR OWN,
AND SHE ASKED ME TO CHECK UP
ON YOU WHEN I GOT THE CHANCE.
LUCKY ME, HUH?
I HAD ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
THAT YOU WANTED TO BE A HUNTER.
AS FOR ME,
I'M HERE TO GET A LICENSE
FOR A JOB THAT'S COMING UP.
Killua: I DON'T ACTUALLY
WANT TO BECOME A HUNTER.
I JUST FELT LIKE
TAKING THE EXAM.
Illumi: I SEE.
WELL, THAT'S A RELIEF.
IN THAT CASE,
I HAVE SOME ADVICE FOR YOU.
YOU'RE NOT CUT OUT
TO BE A HUNTER.
YOU WERE BORN FOR ONE PURPOSE...
TO BE AN ASSASSIN.
Gon: THAT'S REALLY WHAT HE SAID?
KILLUA MENTIONED HIS FAMILY,
BUT THEY SOUND CRAZY.
Satotz: BUT THAT
WASN'T THE EXTENT OF IT.
Illumi: YOU'RE A PUPPET
OF DARKNESS DEVOID OF PASSION.
THERE IS NOTHING YOU DESIRE,
NOR IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU WISH FOR.
AS ONE WHO LIVES IN THE SHADOWS,
THE ONLY PLEASURE
YOU'RE CAPABLE OF
IS DERIVED FROM CAUSING DEATH,
BECAUSE THAT'S
HOW DAD AND I RAISED YOU.
♪
WHAT DO YOU IMAGINE
THAT YOU WOULD ACCOMPLISH
BY BECOMING A HUNTER?
Killua: IT'S TRUE. I DON'T
REALLY WANT TO BE A HUNTER.
BUT EVERYONE WANTS SOMETHING,
EVEN ME.
Illumi: YOU DON'T.
Killua: WRONG!
THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I REALLY WANT!
Illumi: HMM.
ENLIGHTEN ME.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?
( Killua exhales )
Illumi: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
THERE REALLY ISN'T ANYTHING,
IS THERE?
Killua: THERE IS!
I...
WANT TO BE...
FRIENDS WITH GON.
♪
I‐I'M JUST SO SICK
OF KILLING PEOPLE.
I WANT TO BE FRIENDS WITH GON,
JUST HAVE FUN.
Illumi: IMPOSSIBLE.
( Killua gasps )
Illumi: YOU ARE INCAPABLE
OF FRIENDSHIP.
THE ONLY THING THAT YOU CAN DO
IS DISCERN WHETHER OR NOT
YOU CAN KILL THEM.
THAT IS ALL
YOU WERE EVER TAUGHT.
GON IS SUCH
A RADIANT PERSONALITY
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO CLASSIFY HIM.
YOU DON'T ACTUALLY DESIRE
HIS FRIENDSHIP.
Killua: NO.
Illumi: IF YOU STAY WITH HIM,
ONE DAY, YOU'LL END UP
WANTING TO KILL HIM.
YOU'LL WONDER IF YOU CAN,
AND YOU'LL WANT TO FIND OUT,
BECAUSE YOU ARE,
BY NATURE, A MURDERER.
( Leorio growls )
Examiner: WE'VE WARNED YOU
ALREADY, SIR, SO PLEASE...
Leorio: YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
KILLUA!
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
IF THIS GUY'S YOUR BROTHER,
ALL RIGHT?
HE'S A WORTHLESS PIECE OF CRAP,
SO DON'T LISTEN TO HIM!
JUST BEAT THE CRAP
OUT OF HIM LIKE USUAL, AND WIN!
YOU WANT TO BECOME FRIENDS
WITH GON? ARE YOU KIDDIN' ME?!
YOU'RE ALREADY FRIENDS!
HOW DO YOU NOT KNOW THAT?!
‐ ( Killua gasps )
‐ Illumi: HUH?
Leorio: GON SURE SEEMS
TO THINK SO, ANYWAY!
Illumi: IS THAT TRUE?
Leorio: HELL, YEAH,
IT'S TRUE, YOU IDIOT!
Illumi: OH, NO. THAT ISN'T GOOD.
SO HE ALREADY
CONSIDERS KIL A FRIEND?
FINE. THEN I'LL JUST KILL GON.
( all gasp )
( chorus vocalizing )
Illumi: ASSASSINS HAVE
NO USE FOR FRIENDS.
THEY ONLY GET IN THE WAY.
WHERE CAN I FIND HIM?
Examiner: PLEASE, WAIT A SECOND!
THE MATCH IS STILL‐‐
( gurgling )
Illumi: WHERE?
( examiner groaning )
HE'S IN THE WAITING ROOM
RIGHT OVER THERE.
Illumi: THANK YOU.
HMM?
OH, WHAT A PAIN.
I NEED TO ACQUIRE
A HUNTER'S LICENSE RIGHT NOW
SO I CAN DO MY JOB,
BUT IF I KILL THEM, I'LL FAIL,
AND THEN KIL
WILL PASS AUTOMATICALLY.
OH, NO.
THE SAME THING WILL HAPPEN
IF I KILL GON.
HMM. WAIT.
I'LL PASS THE EXAM
AND THEN KILL GON.
Leorio: YOU BASTARD.
Illumi: IF I PASS
THE EXAM FIRST,
I CAN KILL EVERYONE HERE
AND STILL KEEP MY LICENSE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
Netero: WELL, YES,
ACCORDING TO THE RULEBOOK.
Illumi: DID YOU HEAR THAT, KIL?
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO SAVE GON,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO BEAT ME.
WILL YOU FIGHT ME
TO SAVE YOUR FRIEND?
YOU CAN'T DO IT, CAN YOU?
BECAUSE DEEP DOWN,
YOU'RE MORE WORRIED
ABOUT WHETHER YOU CAN DEFEAT ME
THAN ANYTHING ELSE, AREN'T YOU?
AND YOU ALREADY KNOW THE ANSWER.
"I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO BEAT MY BIG BROTHER."
REMEMBER THE LESSON
I DRILLED INTO YOU?
NEVER GO UP AGAINST
A SUPERIOR OPPONENT.
( Killua gasping )
Illumi: DON'T MOVE.
MOVE ONE MORE INCH, AND I'LL
ASSUME THE FIGHT HAS BEGUN.
THE SAME GOES FOR IF OUR BODIES
COME IN CONTACT WITH EACH OTHER.
THE FIGHT STARTS.
THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY
TO STOP ME,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
BUT DON'T FORGET,
IF YOU DECIDE
THAT YOU WON'T FIGHT ME,
YOUR DEAR GON
WILL CERTAINLY DIE.
Leorio: TAKE HIM OUT, KILLUA!
WE'LL PROTECT YOU!
HE WON'T KILL YOU OR GON!
WE'LL DO WHATEVER
WE HAVE TO DO TO STOP HIM!
GO ON! LET HIM HAVE IT!
( Killua gasping )
♪
YOU WIN, ILLUMI.
I ADMIT DEFEAT.
( Leorio and Kurapika gasping )
Illumi: OH, EXCELLENT.
NO NEED FOR US
TO FIGHT THEN, HUH?
( laughs )
I LIED, KIL.
I WAS NEVER GOING TO KILL GON.
THAT WAS ONLY A TEST
TO SEE WHAT YOU WERE MADE OF,
AND NOW I KNOW FOR CERTAIN.
YOU ARE SIMPLY
NOT QUALIFIED TO MAKE FRIENDS,
NOT THAT YOU NEED ANY.
YOU'LL KEEP DOING
WHAT YOU'VE ALWAYS DONE,
THE JOB DAD AND I
TRAINED YOU TO DO.
I'LL ORDER YOU
TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
BUT NOT NOW.
Satotz: SOMETHING DRAINED
OUT OF KILLUA THEN.
LEORIO AND KURAPIKA
DID THEIR BEST TO HELP,
BUT HE SIMPLY WOULDN'T RESPOND.
THE SIXTH MATCH WAS BETWEEN
LEORIO AND BODORO.
BODORO HAD RECOVERED,
BUT AT THE ONSET OF THE MATCH...
Masta: BEGIN!
Bodoro: HMM?
♪
Satotz: IT WAS OVER IN A FLASH.
AND SO JUST LIKE THAT,
KILLUA KILLED BODORO.
THE COMMITTEE DISQUALIFIED HIM,
THOUGH THAT GOES WITHOUT SAYING.
GON!
Gon: WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
Satotz: YOU MUST LIE DOWN!
YOU NEED TO REST!
( footsteps )
Leorio: GON.
♪
Gon: APOLOGIZE TO KILLUA!
Narrator: GON WAS ANGRY.
ILLUMI HAD TRAMPLED ON KILLUA'S
DESIRE TO BE GON'S FRIEND,
SENDING HIS YOUNGER BROTHER
INTO DEEP DESPAIR.
IN FACT,
GON WAS MORE THAN ANGRY.
HE WAS FURIOUS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"SOME BROTHER TROUBLE."
DO LEORIO AND I LOOK ALIKE?
Leorio: GET OUT OF HERE.