( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Gon gasps )
Gittarackur: SORRY.
I WAS CARELESS, AND HE GOT AWAY.
Hisoka: DON'T LIE TO ME.
HE PROBABLY BEGGED YOU
TO GRANT HIM A LAST REQUEST,
AND YOU RELENTED. AM I RIGHT?
Gittarackur: WELL, I MAY HAVE
FELT SORRY FOR THE MAN.
HE WAS GOING TO DIE ANYWAY.
Hisoka: YOU REALLY
NEED TO STOP PITYING
THOSE WHO SERVE NO PURPOSE.
I DO HAVE STANDARDS.
WHY WASTE TIME ON PEOPLE
WHO ARE UTTERLY USELESS?
I ONLY SPARE THOSE
WHOSE PREMATURE DEATHS
WOULD BE A WASTE.
( insects chirping )
Narrator: HISOKA TARGETS
KURAPIKA AND LEORIO
AS GON GOES
AFTER HISOKA'S BADGE.
UNDER THE DARK,
SILENT COVER OF NIGHT,
SOMETHING IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
♪
Kurapika: NOW RUN!
( Leorio yells )
Hisoka: YES, I REMEMBER THEM.
THIS SHOULD BE FUN.
( slurps )
Gon: IT LOOKS LIKE HISOKA
HAS FOUND HIS PREY.
LEORIO! KURAPIKA!
I NEVER THOUGHT HE'D BE GOING
AFTER LEORIO AND KURAPIKA.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
DON'T LOSE FOCUS.
STICK TO THE PLAN,
AND THE MOMENT HISOKA ATTACKS,
GO FOR HIS BADGE.
THAT'S THE BEST CHANCE
I'M GONNA GET TO TAKE IT.
IT'S MY ONLY CHANCE.
( panting )
NO, I CAN'T.
IF THEY START FIGHTING,
I'LL HAVE TO CHANGE MY STRATEGY.
( insects chirping )
Leorio: ALL RIGHT,
SO I'VE FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHO MY TARGET IS,
BUT HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO FIND HER
ON AN ISLAND THIS BIG?
ISN'T WANDERING AROUND LIKE THIS
A HUGE WASTE OF ENERGY?
Kurapika: NO MORE
A WASTE OF ENERGY
THAN CONSTANTLY WHINING,
I WOULD IMAGINE.
Leorio: WELL, YOU'VE ALREADY GOT
YOUR SIX POINTS,
SO YOU'RE ALL SET,
BUT I'M PLUMB OUT OF LUCK
IF I DON'T FIND MY TARGET
PRETTY SOON.
( both gasp )
♪
‐ Hisoka: HEY.
‐ Both: HISOKA!
Hisoka: WHAT A COINCIDENCE
MEETING YOU HERE.
‐ HOW FORTUNATE.
‐ ( Leorio chuckles )
WHY DO I RUN INTO PEOPLE
I DON'T WANNA SEE?
Hisoka: YOU SEE, ALL I'M LACKING
IS JUST TWO MORE POINTS.
I WAS HOPING
YOU MIGHT GIVE ME YOURS.
Leorio: GIVE YOU WHAT?!
YOU'RE CRAZY! I'M NOT GONNA‐‐
Kurapika: LEORIO.
YOU SAID
YOU ONLY NEED TWO POINTS,
MEANING NEITHER ONE OF US
IS YOUR PRIMARY TARGET.
AM I RIGHT ABOUT THAT?
Hisoka: LEAVE THE QUESTIONS
TO ME, ALL RIGHT?
WILL YOU GIVE ME YOUR BADGES?
ANSWER CAREFULLY.
Kurapika: I SUPPOSE
THAT DEPENDS.
( Leorio gasps )
Kurapika: BETWEEN THE TWO OF US,
WE CURRENTLY HAVE FOUR BADGES:
MINE, MY TARGET'S, LEORIO'S,
AND ONE THAT'S WORTH
ONLY A SINGLE POINT
TO EITHER HIM OR ME.
OF THE FOUR,
TWO MIGHT POSSIBLY BELONG
TO YOUR SPECIFIC TARGET,
AND ONLY TWO,
MINE OR THE BADGE
THAT'S WORTH A SINGLE POINT.
LEORIO'S NUMBER IS 403.
HE WAS TARGETED
BY NUMBER 16, TONPA,
AND HE, NUMBER 16,
WAS ASSIGNED TO ME AS MY TARGET.
EACH OF US WAS GIVEN
A DIFFERENT TARGET,
SO 16 AND 403 ARE OUT.
Hisoka: INDEED.
NEITHER OF THOSE IS THE TARGET
I WAS SEARCHING FOR.
WHAT OF IT?
Kurapika: THAT JUST LEAVES
THE OTHER TWO BADGES.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO TAKE
THE BADGE THAT'S WORTH ONE POINT
AND LEAVE, YOU ARE
MORE THAN WELCOME TO HAVE IT,
BUT I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO TAKE MINE...
AND THE SAME GOES
FOR THE OTHER TWO.
IF YOU INSIST
ON TAKING THEM BY FORCE,
PREPARE TO FIGHT ME FOR THEM.
♪
( Hisoka laughing )
( sighs )
OUT OF CURIOSITY,
WHAT IS YOUR NUMBER?
Kurapika: 404.
Hisoka: VERY WELL.
YOU HAVE YOURSELF A DEAL.
I'LL TAKE THE BADGE
WORTH A SINGLE POINT.
Kurapika: I'LL LEAVE IT HERE.
Hisoka: DON'T LOOK SO CONCERNED.
I'LL STAY RIGHT HERE
UNTIL YOU'RE OUT OF SIGHT.
( chuckles )
IN A FEW SHORT DAYS,
THEY'VE BOTH GROWN
BEYOND RECOGNITION,
BUT THEY'VE MORE TO LEARN.
I WONDER, WHY MUST UNRIPE FRUIT
BE SO TANTALIZING?
SUCH A PITY.
NOT THE BADGE I WAS HOPING FOR.
( Gon sighs )
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
BUT NOW I'VE ONLY GOT
ONE MORE CHANCE LEFT.
WHENEVER HE FINDS HIS NEXT PREY,
I'LL BE READY.
HEY, WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
WHAT IF THE NEXT PERSON HE FINDS
DECIDES THAT THEY DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT HIM EITHER?
AW, MAN,
IF THE NEXT PERSON SURRENDERS
AND HANDS OVER THEIR BADGE
LIKE WHAT I JUST SAW HAPPEN,
THEN I WON'T GET
ANOTHER CHANCE AT ALL!
MAN, I'M SO STUPID.
JEEZ, WHY DIDN'T
I THINK OF THAT?
( moans )
( Hisoka sighs )
( Gon gasps )
( birds squawking )
♪
( animals chitter )
( Gon gasps )
I'M SO SCARED.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE ANYMORE.
I FEEL HIS BLOODLUST.
( Hisoka shudders )
OH, NO.
( slurps )
THEY HAD TO GO
AND GET ME STIRRED UP.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
TO DO ABOUT IT NOW.
I HAVE TO QUELL IT.
( shudders )
( birds chirping )
( waves crashing )
WELL...
TIME TO GO.
♪
Gon: I CAN DO THIS.
HIS BLOODLUST IS GONE,
BUT THAT LOOK IN HIS EYES
IS NOTHING LIKE BEFORE.
HE'S GONNA ATTACK
THE NEXT PERSON HE SEES,
EVEN IF THEY TRY TO SURRENDER.
I'M SURE OF IT.
I KNOW. I'VE GOTTA MOVE AHEAD
AND FIND HIS NEXT PREY
BEFORE HE DOES.
THEN I NEED TO FIND MYSELF
A GOOD SPOT TO HIDE
AND WAIT FOR MY CHANCE.
THERE.
I'VE ONLY GOT ABOUT A MINUTE
OR SO BEFORE HISOKA SPOTS HIM.
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
THEIR PATHS ARE GONNA CROSS.
GOT IT!
♪
GOTTA HURRY.
HISOKA WILL ATTACK
THE SECOND HE NOTICES THAT GUY.
IF I WANNA STEAL HIS BADGE,
THIS IS IT.
IT'S THE LAST CHANCE
I'M GONNA GET.
♪
Hisoka: HMM?
( waves crashing )
( footsteps scraping )
( footsteps fade )
Gon: IT FEELS LIKE HISOKA HAS
COMPLETELY HIDDEN HIS PRESENCE.
( heart pounding )
HE'S GONNA FIND ME.
I JUST KNOW IT!
( breathing heavily )
( heart pounding )
I'LL HAVE TO CONCEAL
MY PRESENCE, TOO.
( heart pounding )
( footsteps scraping )
( footsteps fade )
( heart pounds )
( footsteps scraping )
( footsteps fade )
( heart pounds )
( footsteps scraping )
( footsteps fade )
( heart pounds )
I HAVE TO STAY HIDDEN.
I CAN'T LET HIM SENSE ME.
( heartbeat fades )
FOCUS.
( silence )
♪
Hisoka: HMM?
Gon: HERE HE COMES.
Applicant #281: HISOKA.
DAMN IT.
BRING IT ON!
Gon: HE'S FIGHTING BACK.
( applicant #281 shudders )
( Hisoka screeches )
♪
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ ( Gon grunts )
( Hisoka sighs )
( Gon panting )
( panting )
I DID IT.
I TOOK HISOKA'S BADGE FROM HIM.
( gasping )
♪
( footsteps approaching )
Geretta: ABOUT 7,000.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT NUMBER REPRESENTS?
THAT IS THE NUMBER OF CHANCES
I HAD TO KILL YOU.
( Gon gasping )
Geretta: IT'S ALSO
ABOUT THE NUMBER OF TIMES
THAT YOU CAST YOUR FISHING ROD
WHILE YOU WERE TRAINING.
EVERY CAST LEFT YOU WIDE OPEN,
BUT YOUR FOCUS AND YOUR ACCURACY
WERE ADMIRABLE.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
AND JUST NOW, YOUR SWING
WAS EQUALLY IMPRESSIVE,
BUT YOU DIDN'T PAY ENOUGH
ATTENTION TO YOUR SURROUNDINGS.
IN THE FUTURE,
REMEMBER TO WATCH YOUR BACK.
SO LONG.
Gon: DAMN IT.
( cloth scraping )
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: YOU SURPRISE ME.
YOU HID YOUR PRESENCE FROM ME
WHILE YOU WERE WAITING
FOR YOUR CHANCE TO STRIKE,
BIDING YOUR TIME
UNTIL THE VERY MOMENT
THAT I ATTACKED SOMEONE ELSE.
DID YOU LEARN HOW TO CONCEAL
YOURSELF ALL ON YOUR OWN?
MARVELOUS.
YOU'RE LIKE A WILD ANIMAL.
AND YOUR TIMING
WAS JUST IMPECCABLE.
YOU WERE ABLE TO CONCEAL
YOUR BLOODLUST
BY CLEVERLY HIDING IT
BEHIND MINE
SO THAT I WOULDN'T NOTICE.
MASTERFULLY DONE.
HIS BLOW DART DELIVERED
A FAST‐ACTING,
POWERFUL MUSCLE RELAXANT.
IN A NORMAL PERSON,
THE EFFECTS LAST ABOUT 10 DAYS.
THERE ARE THREE DAYS LEFT.
I'M SURE BY THEN
YOU'LL MAKE A FULL RECOVERY.
Gon: WAIT.
IF YOU'RE NOT TAKING YOUR BADGE,
THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
Hisoka: TO SAY CONGRATULATIONS.
AS IT TURNS OUT,
HE WAS MY TARGET...
WHICH MEANS
I DON'T NEED MINE ANYMORE.
Gon: WELL, NEITHER DO I.
Hisoka: DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
YOU OWE ME ONE NOW.
YOU CAN PAY ME BACK
WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
SO LONG.
( Gon grunting )
I DON'T OWE YOU OR ANYBODY.
HERE. TAKE IT BACK.
( Hisoka chuckles )
I REFUSE.
I'VE DECIDED
TO LET YOU LIVE FOR NOW,
AND I PLAN
TO LET YOU CONTINUE LIVING
FOR AS LONG AS IT SUITS ME,
UNTIL SOMEDAY YOU BECOME
TRULY WORTHY OF KILLING.
I WILL TAKE IT BACK,
BUT ONLY WHEN YOU CAN PUNCH ME
IN THE FACE LIKE THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU JUST HOLD ON TO IT FOR ME.
( laughing )
( laughter echoing )
♪
Narrator: GON WAS KNOCKED OUT
BY HISOKA'S PUNCH
AND REALIZED
HE WAS UTTERLY HELPLESS
IN THE FACE OF SUCH POWER.
AND NOW ALONE IN THE DARKNESS,
WHAT MUST BE
GOING THROUGH HIS MIND?
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"TRAP IN THE HOLE."
HOLY MOLEY.
I WANT TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
Killua: WHOA, FRIEND?
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING.