♪
Narrator: IN THE DENTORA REGION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA,
THERE IS A DORMANT VOLCANO
SURROUNDED BY FORESTS,
MEASURING 3,722 METERS HIGH,
CALLED KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
IT IS HOME
TO A FAMILY OF FAMOUS ASSASSINS,
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY.
VISITORS ARRIVE EVERY DAY
IN HOPES OF CATCHING
A GLIMPSE OF THE MANSION,
WHICH HAS NEVER BEEN SEEN.
IT'S ONE OF THIS NATION'S MOST
POPULAR TOURIST ATTRACTIONS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Silva: VERY WELL.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO NOW.
BUT, KIL...
( bites )
PROMISE ME ONE THING,
THAT YOU WILL NEVER
BETRAY YOUR FRIENDS.
GOT THAT?
( Killua grunts )
I'LL NEVER BETRAY THEM.
I SWEAR.
♪
Narrator: AFTER SPEAKING
WITH HIS FATHER,
WHOM HE GREATLY ADMIRES,
KILLUA LEAVES HOME ONCE AGAIN
DESPITE HIS MOTHER'S OBJECTIONS.
CANARY LEADS GON AND HIS FRIENDS
TO THE BUTLER'S QUARTERS
IN AN ATTEMPT
TO MEET WITH KILLUA.
( Leorio groans )
ARE WE THERE YET?
Canary: STILL A BIT FARTHER.
( Leorio groans )
BUT WE'VE BEEN WALKING FOREVER.
Mrs. Zoldyck:
OH, I AM POSITIVELY FURIOUS!
KIL FINALLY CAME HOME TO US,
BUT MY HUSBAND'S
ALLOWED HIM TO LEAVE AGAIN!
AND FATHER IS JUST AS GUILTY,
RELEASING HIM
WITHOUT ASKING MY PERMISSION!
HONESTLY, EVERY SINGLE TIME,
THEY ALL JUST ACT
WITHOUT CONSULTING ME FIRST.
UNDERSTAND, GOTOH?
Gotoh: YES, MA'AM.
( Mrs. Zoldyck sobbing )
THIS‐‐THIS IS
THE MOST CRITICAL TIME FOR KIL.
WHY DOESN'T ANYONE UNDERSTAND?
( crying )
HE'S THE ONE CHILD
I SHALL NOT GIVE UP.
( continues crying )
Canary: THERE IT IS.
♪
Leorio: THAT'S IT, HUH?
IT'S STILL A LOT FARTHER AWAY
THAN I'D LIKE.
Gon: HEY, CANARY, AREN'T YOU
GOING TO GET IN A LOT OF TROUBLE
WITH YOUR BOSSES
FOR BRINGING US HERE?
Canary: THEY ARE PERFECTLY AWARE
OF WHAT I'M DOING.
I AM QUITE CERTAIN OF THAT.
I'M PREPARED
FOR THE CONSEQUENCES.
Gon: IF THERE'S ANY TROUBLE,
I'LL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
Canary: NO. I AM MERELY
SERVING AS A GUIDE
FOR MASTER KILLUA'S FRIENDS.
Gotoh: MASTER KILLUA.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
Killua: GOTOH.
WHERE IS GON RIGHT NOW?
YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
Gotoh: CANARY IS
BRINGING MASTER GON
ALONG WITH HIS TWO FRIENDS
EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
( Killua gasps )
SERIOUSLY?
Gotoh: THEY'LL BE
ARRIVING SHORTLY,
SO PLEASE WAIT INSIDE.
Killua: SURE.
‐ GOTOH.
‐ Gotoh: SIR?
Killua: THE SECOND HE'S HERE,
TELL ME.
Gotoh: OF COURSE.
I SHALL NOTIFY YOU IMMEDIATELY.
( thinking ) PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
MASTER KILLUA.
Leorio: EH?
WE FINALLY MADE IT.
Gotoh: WELCOME, GENTLEMEN.
( insects chirping )
WE APOLOGIZE
FOR OUR PREVIOUS DISCOURTESY.
WE HAVE BEEN INFORMED
BY THE LADY OF THE HOUSE
THAT FROM NOW ON, YOU ARE TO BE
TREATED AS OFFICIAL GUESTS.
Butler: THERE.
DOES THAT FEEL BETTER?
Gon: IT DOES! THANK YOU!
( chuckles )
Kurapika: THEN THIS
ISN'T THE MAIN RESIDENCE?
Canary: NO. THIS IS
THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
Gotoh: NOW PLEASE
MAKE YOURSELVES COMFORTABLE.
Leorio: LOOK,
THANKS FOR THE HOSPITALITY,
BUT WE ONLY CAME HERE
TO SEE KILLUA,
SO CAN YOU TAKE US TO HIM,
LIKE, NOW?
Gotoh: THAT WON'T
BE NECESSARY, SIR.
‐ ( all gasp )
‐ Gotoh: MASTER KILLUA
IS ON HIS WAY
THIS VERY MOMENT.
Gon: WAIT! REALLY?!
Gotoh: THAT'S RIGHT,
SO PLEASE BE PATIENT.
Leorio: GREAT NEWS, HUH, GON?
Gon: YEP!
Gotoh: NOW THEN,
IT WOULD BE SO TEDIOUS
TO JUST SIT AND WAIT.
( chuckles ) I PROPOSE
WE PASS THE TIME WITH A GAME.
Kurapika: GAME, YOU SAY?
♪
Gotoh: WHICH HAND
HOLDS THE COIN?
All: THE LEFT HAND.
Gotoh: THAT IS CORRECT.
NOW I'LL MOVE
MORE QUICKLY THIS TIME.
NOW, WHICH HAND?
Gon: IT'S THE LEFT AGAIN.
Gotoh: HOW MARVELOUS.
WELL, I SHALL HAVE
TO TRY HARDER THIS TIME.
( all gasp )
Gotoh: SO, WHICH HAND?
Leorio: I'M NOT SURE,
‐ BUT I'D SAY RIGHT?
‐ Gotoh: YOU SEE,
I'VE KNOWN MASTER KILLUA
HIS ENTIRE LIFE,
AND I CARE FOR HIM
AS I WOULD MY OWN SON.
IN ALL HONESTY, I DESPISE YOU
FOR ATTEMPTING TO TAKE HIM AWAY.
( all grunt )
Gotoh: WELL? WHICH HAND? ANSWER.
Kurapika: THE LEFT HAND.
Gotoh: THE LADY'S VOICE
WAS A BARE WHISPER.
HER SON IS LEAVING,
AND IT'S BREAKING HER HEART.
I CAN'T FORGIVE YOU.
BEFORE MASTER KILLUA ARRIVES,
I SHALL TEST EACH OF YOU
BY MY OWN METHODS.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
( Leorio gasps )
( Canary gasps )
Gon: CANARY!
Gotoh: THIS IS HER PUNISHMENT
FOR DEFYING ORDERS
AND BRINGING YOU HERE.
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN THE RULES.
IF YOU ANSWER INCORRECTLY,
YOU ARE OUT.
SHOULD YOU ALL BE DISQUALIFIED,
WHICH IS QUITE POSSIBLE,
THEN I SHALL TELL MASTER KILLUA
THAT YOU LEFT
AND THAT HE WILL NEVER
SEE ANY OF YOU AGAIN.
‐ Gon: KILLUA'S‐‐
‐ Gotoh: SILENCE.
YOUR VERY LIVES HANG
BY A MOST DELICATE THREAD.
ANSWER MY QUESTION.
I WILL NOT ASK AGAIN.
( somber chorus singing )
‐ ( sizzles )
‐ NOW WHICH HAND?
( all groan )
( Gon thinking )
I COULDN'T SEE IT.
Gotoh: AND TIME
IS OF THE ESSENCE.
YOU ONLY HAVE THREE SECONDS.
YOU, ONCE THREE SECONDS
HAVE PASSED, SLIT HER THROAT.
Butler #2: YES, SIR.
Leorio: HOLD ON!
I PICK THE LEFT HAND!
Gon: I PICK THE RIGHT.
‐ Kurapika: YES, ME, TOO!
‐ ( Leorio gasps )
Gotoh: ONE HAS BEEN
DISQUALIFIED.
( claps )
Gon: THIS IS USELESS.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
Gotoh: WHICH HAND?
Kurapika: I CHOOSE
THE RIGHT HAND.
Gon: AND I PICK THE LEFT.
Gotoh: IT WAS IN MY LEFT HAND.
NOW ONLY ONE REMAINS.
‐ HERE WE GO.
‐ Gon: WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
Gotoh: WHAT IS IT?
IF YOU'RE TRYING TO BUY TIME,
I WILL KILL ONE OF YOU.
Gon: LEORIO, GIVE ME YOUR KNIFE.
Leorio: HUH?
Gon: DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
I'M NOT GONNA USE IT
FOR ANYTHING STUPID.
Kurapika: HE CUT HIMSELF
TO REDUCE THE SWELLING.
( foot thumping )
Killua: DAMN IT.
HOW LONG DO I HAVE TO WAIT?
HEY, GOTOH!
IS ANYBODY OUT HERE?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
Gon: THERE. MUCH BETTER.
I CAN SEE NOW.
OKAY, I'M READY!
Gotoh: HUMPH.
( claps )
♪
WHICH HAND?
Gon: THE LEFT.
Gotoh: VERY GOOD.
NOW...
( all gasp )
Gotoh: NOW,
WHICH ONE OF US HAS IT?
♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
( chuckles )
THAT GUY, RIGHT BEHIND ME.
( Gotoh chuckles )
‐ ( applause )
‐ SPLENDID. WELL DONE!
Killua: GOTOH, IS GON HERE YET?
‐ Gon: KILLUA!
‐ Killua: YOU WERE ALREADY HERE?
GON!
AND THIS GUY, UM...
KURAPIKA?
Kurapika: YOU REMEMBERED.
Killua: REOLIO!
Leorio: IT'S LEORIO!
Killua: IT'S BEEN SO LONG,
BUT YOU MADE IT.
WOW. YOUR FACE IS A MESS.
( Gon laughs )
BACK AT YA!
( boys laughing )
Killua: HEY, GOTOH,
WHAT HAPPENED TO TELLING ME
AS SOON AS THEY GOT HERE, HUH?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
Gotoh: PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I HAD THEM PARTICIPATE
IN A LITTLE GAME.
Killua: A GAME?
( Gon chuckles )
Gotoh: A JOKE, SIR, THOUGH QUITE
A POOR ONE, ADMITTEDLY.
I'M SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE.
I DO HOPE
YOU ENJOYED YOURSELVES.
Leorio: IF THAT WAS A JOKE,
THEN YOU SURE FOOLED ME.
Killua: WAIT.
DID THEY TRY ANYTHING?
Gon: NO. THEY WERE JUST
KEEPING US ALL ENTERTAINED.
Killua: REALLY? WELL, OKAY.
LET'S GO SOMEPLACE ELSE,
LIKE ANYWHERE AT ALL.
IF WE STAY HERE,
MY MOM WILL CHEW ALL OF US OUT.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: HEY, GOTOH, LISTEN.
NO MATTER WHAT MOM SAID,
DON'T FOLLOW ME.
Gotoh: UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
PLEASE TAKE CARE.
Gon: COME ON, GON.
LET'S GO. BYE.
Gon: MR. GOTOH...
YOU'RE GONNA MISS KILLUA
WHEN HE'S GONE, AREN'T YOU?
Gotoh: NO, SIR. IT IS OUR DUTY
TO SERVE OUR EMPLOYERS
AND NOT TO BECOME
EMOTIONALLY ATTACHED TO THEM.
( Gon gasps )
YOU LIAR.
Gotoh: GON.
WELL? WHICH HAND?
Gon: YOUR LEFT ONE, RIGHT?
( gasps )
NO WAY!
Gotoh: INDEED. A DECEPTION.
THE WORLD IS TEEMING
WITH TRICKS AND TRICKSTERS.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL,
AND PLEASE, SIR,
LOOK AFTER MASTER KILLUA.
♪
SEE YA LATER, CANARY!
Killua: HURRY UP, GON!
Gon: COMING! SORRY!
Killua: LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE TROUBLE FINDS US.
( overlapping chatter )
Killua: YEAH. HE PULLED
THAT SAME TRICK ON ME.
ONCE YOU KNOW THE SECRET,
YOU'LL KICK YOURSELF
FOR NOT SEEING IT.
Gon: OH. REALLY?
Kurapika: I BET
THIS IS WHAT HE DID.
WHICH HAND?
Gon: YOUR LEFT, RIGHT?
( Kurapika laughs )
( Gon gasps )
WHAT THE?!
BUT HOW'D YOU DO IT?
Kurapika: GOTOH MUST HAVE HAD
TWO COINS THE ENTIRE TIME.
Gon: BUT IT LOOKED
LIKE HE ONLY HAD ONE.
Kurapika: WELL, HE CONCEALED
A COIN IN HIS RIGHT HAND,
AND THEN HE FLIPPED THE OTHER.
HE LET US SEE HIM GRAB THE COIN
USING HIS LEFT HAND.
NOW, THIS IS WHERE
THE SKILL COMES IN.
BEFORE HE ASKED US TO CHOOSE
WHICH HAND HELD THE COIN,
HE RAISED BOTH OF HIS ARMS
LIKE SO
AND SLIPPED THE FIRST COIN
INTO HIS SLEEVE
WHILE KEEPING HIS HAND
BALLED IN A FIST.
( Gon gasps )
Kurapika: THEN HE JUST SHOWED US
THE COIN IN HIS RIGHT HAND.
Killua: YEP, YOU GOT IT.
( Gon growls )
THAT CHEATER!
Killua: WELL,
NOT THE WHOLE TIME, PROBABLY.
I'M SURE JUST ON THE LAST TURN.
GOTOH HATES CHEATING,
EVEN IF IT'S JUST A GAME.
FEEL BETTER?
( Gon groans )
THAT'S EVEN WORSE!
( train horn blares )
Killua: WHAT?!
WAIT. YOU CAME HERE
ON A TOURIST VISA?
Gon: MM‐HMM.
Killua: BUT YOU PASSED
THE HUNTER EXAM,
DIDN'T YOU? SO WHY DIDN'T YOU
USE YOUR LICENSE?
YOU CAN USE IT
TO GET INTO OTHER COUNTRIES
AND STAY
FOR AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
Leorio: WE ALREADY
TOLD HIM THAT.
Gon: NOT YET. NO LICENSE,
NOT UNTIL I FINISH
WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
Killua: SO, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT DO YOU GOTTA DO?
Gon: WELL, YOU REMEMBER...
WHEN HISOKA GAVE ME
HIS NUMBER BADGE!
Hisoka: I WILL TAKE IT BACK,
BUT ONLY WHEN YOU CAN PUNCH ME
IN THE FACE LIKE THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU JUST HOLD ON TO IT FOR ME.
Gon: I'LL RETURN IT
WHENEVER I CAN PUNCH HISOKA
RIGHT IN HIS STUPID, UGLY FACE!
UNTIL I CAN DO THAT,
I'M NOT GONNA USE
MY HUNTER'S LICENSE
OR GO BACK TO WHALE ISLAND.
Killua: HMM.
SO, WHERE IS HISOKA?
( Gon gasps )
UH, WELL...
Leorio: THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
Kurapika: I KNOW
WHERE HE IS, GON.
( Gon gasps )
REALLY?
Leorio: BUT HOW?
Kurapika: I KNOW,
BECAUSE HE TOLD ME.
Leorio: THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
( Kurapika gasps )
( no audible dialogue )
NO. AFTER THE ORIENTATION.
Leorio: YEAH,
BUT IT'S RELATED, RIGHT?
Kurapika: PERHAPS.
Leorio: OKAY, LOOK,
I'VE BEEN DYING TO ASK.
HISOKA, WHAT DID HE SAY TO YOU?
Kurapika: ALL HE SAID WAS...
Hisoka: I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING
INTERESTING ABOUT SPIDERS.
Leorio: DID HE MEAN
THE PHANTOM TROUPE?
Kurapika: I DON'T RECALL
EVER MENTIONING THEM TO HISOKA.
HE EITHER OVERHEARD
OUR CONVERSATION
DURING THE FIRST PHASE
OR HEARD IT FROM SOMEONE ELSE.
THE TROUPE'S SYMBOL
IS THE SPIDER,
WHICH IS WHAT THEY ARE CALLED
BY ANYONE FAMILIAR WITH THEM.
I WAS INTERESTED
IN WHATEVER INFORMATION HE HAD.
Leorio: I GET IT NOW.
( thinking )
OKAY. THAT ACTUALLY MAKES SENSE.
SO THAT'S WHAT MADE YOU SWALLOW
YOUR PRIDE AND TAKE THE WIN.
Kurapika: I ASKED HIM ABOUT IT
AFTER THE ORIENTATION.
Hisoka: MEET ME IN YORKNEW CITY
ON SEPTEMBER FIRST.
Leorio: BUT WHY THAT DATE?
Gon: THAT'S HALF A YEAR AWAY.
YOU'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
SO WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
IN YORKNEW CITY?
( Leorio gasps ) THEY'RE HOLDING
THE WORLD'S LARGEST AUCTION.
Kurapika: THAT'S RIGHT.
FROM SEPTEMBER FIRST
THROUGH SEPTEMBER THE TENTH,
THERE WILL BE AN AUCTION
WITH RARE AND UNUSUAL ITEMS
AND NATIONAL TREASURES
FROM AROUND THE WORLD.
OF COURSE, THE EVENT ATTRACTS
ALL MANNER OF TRICKSTERS,
WHO COME LOOKING
TO SATISFY THEIR GREED.
IT'S THE BIGGEST GATHERING
OF WEALTH ON THE ENTIRE PLANET.
Gon: OH.
Leorio: DO YOU THINK THAT MEANS
THE TROUPE'S GONNA BE THERE?
Kurapika: WELL,
THEY ARE A GROUP OF BANDITS.
IT'S UNLIKELY THAT THEY WOULD
LET THIS OPPORTUNITY SLIP BY.
REGARDLESS, ON THAT DAY,
HISOKA WILL BE
SOMEWHERE IN YORKNEW CITY.
Gon: OKAY, THEN.
SEPTEMBER THE FIRST.
I GOT IT. THANKS A LOT.
♪
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE LEAVING NOW.
Gon: HUH?
Kurapika: WE ALL
GOT TO SEE KILLUA AGAIN,
SO MY WORK HERE IS FINISHED.
I'LL BE NEEDING A LOT OF MONEY
IF I'M GOING TO ATTEND
THE AUCTION,
SO FROM HERE,
I SHALL SEARCH FOR A PATRON
WILLING TO EMPLOY ME
AS A HUNTER.
Leorio: REALLY?
I GUESS I SHOULD
HEAD BACK HOME THEN.
Gon: WAIT. YOU, TOO?
Leorio: I HAVEN'T GIVEN UP
ON BECOMING A DOCTOR.
IF I'M ACCEPTED TO MED SCHOOL,
THEN THIS WILL PAY
FOR THE OUTRAGEOUS EXPENSES.
I NEED TO GET BACK
AND START HITTING THE BOOKS.
Gon: BEST OF LUCK, LEORIO.
♪
Leorio: 'TIL NEXT TIME.
Kurapika: YES. THAT WILL BE...
All: SEPTEMBER FIRST
IN YORKNEW CITY!
Leorio: SEE YA LATER.
Gon: BYE‐BYE!
GUESS IT'S
JUST YOU AND ME NOW, KILLUA.
SO WHAT'S NEXT?
Killua: YOU SERIOUSLY
HAVE TO ASK ME THAT?
WE GOTTA START TRAINING.
Gon: UH, FOR WHAT?
WHY NOT HAVE FUN? ( gasps )
Killua: YOU REMEMBER WHAT YOU
TOLD ME ABOUT A SECOND AGO?
YOU THINK YOU CAN PUNCH HISOKA
IN THE FACE WITHOUT TRAINING?
THAT'D TAKE 10 YEARS!
FORGET ABOUT SIX MONTHS!
Gon: OKAY.
Killua: HERE.
I'LL BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU.
THIS IS HISOKA,
AND THIS IS HANZO.
Gon: RIGHT. I'M WITH YOU.
Killua: IF THIS
IS THE STRENGTH GAP
BETWEEN HISOKA AND HANZO,
THE GAP BETWEEN YOU
AND HISOKA IS...
♪
THIS WIDE!
AND I'M BEING GENEROUS!
( Gon groans) THAT'S JUST MEAN.
OKAY,
THEN HOW FAR APART ARE YOU?
Killua: WHO, ME? HMM.
WELL, PROBABLY HERE.
( thinking )
WOW. I'M SO HUMBLE.
Gon: AH, SO HANZO'S
THE STRONGER ONE?
WAIT.
Killua: WHAT IS IT?
Gon: YOU REALLY
ARE AWESOME, KILLUA!
Killua: KNOCK IT OFF, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
Gon: IT'S JUST
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL
THE DIFFERENCE IN STRENGTH
BETWEEN MY OPPONENT AND ME.
Killua: IT DOESN'T
REALLY MATTER, DUMMY.
I'M ONLY ESTIMATING, ANYWAY.
BESIDES, YOU GET
THE GENERAL IDEA, RIGHT?
AND WITH EXPERIENCE,
YOUR ESTIMATES
WILL BECOME MORE ACCURATE,
BUT THE STRONGER SOMEONE IS,
THE BETTER THEY CAN HIDE
THAT STRENGTH,
SO IT'S NOT A METHOD
THAT I'D RECOMMEND.
Gon: OKAY, I WON'T.
Killua: POINT IS
HISOKA'S REALLY STRONG.
Gon: YEAH.
Killua: WITH JUST SIX MONTHS,
WE'RE GONNA NEED
TO GET REAL CREATIVE.
( Gon grunts )
‐ Killua: HEY, GOT ANY MONEY?
‐ Gon: AH.
MM, I'M A LITTLE LOW, ACTUALLY.
Killua: I DON'T
HAVE MUCH EITHER,
BUT THERE'S A PLACE WHERE
WE CAN MAKE OURSELVES SOME MONEY
AND TRAIN AT THE SAME TIME.
Gon: MAKE MONEY
WHILE WE'RE TRAINING?
( whoosh )
Killua: AT THE HEAVENS ARENA.
Gon: HEAVENS ARENA?
Killua: YEAH.
I'LL EXPLAIN LATER,
BUT WE REALLY
OUGHT TO GET GOING NOW.
Gon: RIGHT!
♪
Narrator: AFTER BIDDING
FAREWELL TO KURAPIKA AND LEORIO
AS WELL AS PROMISING
TO MEET AGAIN IN YORKNEW CITY,
GON AND KILLUA
MOVE ON TO A NEW STAGE,
THE HEAVENS ARENA.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"THEN AND AFTER."
SWEET AND SPICY.
Mito: SALTY AND SPICY.
Gon: SPICY IS GOOD FOR YOU.