Dalzollene: AT 9:00 TONIGHT,
THE MUMMY OF PRINCESS CORCO
WILL BE SOLD OFF
AT THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
IVLENKOV, TOCINO, AND BAISE,
YOU'LL BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE BIDDING.
Basho: AND THE REST OF US?
Dalzollene: BASHO AND LINSSEN
WILL BE COVERING
THE REAR ENTRANCE.
KURAPIKA AND MELODY
WILL TAKE THE FRONT ENTRANCE.
SQUALA AND I
WILL GUARD THE GIRL.
AND SO THE MISSION
WILL NOW BEGIN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: IT HAS COME
TO THE ATTENTION
OF THE NOSTRADE FAMILY
THAT SOMEONE PLANS TO ATTACK
THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION,
WHICH IS PUT ON
BY THE MAFIA COMMUNITY.
KURAPIKA AND
ALL OF THE OTHER BODYGUARDS
HIRED BY THE NOSTRADES
HAVE BEGUN THEIR ASSIGNMENTS.
( overlapping chatter )
Tocino: LOOKS LIKE
EVERYONE'S HERE.
Ivlenkov: ALMOST ALL OF THEM
ARE MAFIA BOSSES.
WE'VE GOT
SOME REAL HEAVY HITTERS HERE.
Baise: I'M SURPRISED.
Tocino: YEAH? WHY IS THAT?
Baise: WELL,
THIS IS ONLY AN AUCTION,
SO THEY COULD HAVE SENT PROXIES
IN THEIR PLACE.
Tocino: MAYBE IT'S
BECAUSE THEY FEEL
LIKE THEIR HONOR
IS ON THE LINE.
FOR EACH WINNING BID, 5% GOES
BACK INTO THE MAFIA COMMUNITY.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A COMMISSION.
Baise: I SEE. SO IN THAT CASE,
DOES IT ACT AS A BRIBE?
LIKE THE MORE MONEY THEY BID,
THE MORE THEY'LL
GET BACK IN RETURN?
Tocino: YEAH. THE MAFIA HAS
TO FLEX ITS FINANCIAL MUSCLE
SOMEHOW OR OTHER, AND THIS WAY
IS PRETTY EFFECTIVE.
Baise: OH, I GET IT.
IT'S BASICALLY A CHANCE FOR THEM
TO IMPROVE THEIR STANDING.
Tocino: YEAH, AND AS A RESULT,
A FEW OF THE GANGS
HAVE ACTUALLY GONE BANKRUPT
OVERBIDDING THEMSELVES
INTO OBLIVION.
Ivlenkov: IT SHOULD BE STARTING
ANY MINUTE NOW.
( overlapping chatter )
Feitan: UH, I WOULD
LIKE TO WELCOME YOU
TO THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
ENOUGH FORMALITIES.
LET US GET DOWN TO THE BUSINESS
AT HAND, SHALL WE?
‐ ( bodyguards gasp )
‐ ( chorus vocalizing )
Franklin: TIME FOR YOU TO DIE.
( bidders screaming )
Tocino: GET DOWN!
BLACK BALLOONS, PROTECT US!
( gasps )
IS HE USING NEN BULLETS?
THAT MEANS HE'S AN EMITTER, TOO.
IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE THOSE BULLETS
PENETRATE MY NEN BARRIER
AND RIP THROUGH MY BODY.
EVERY ONE OF 'EM PACKS A HELL
OF A PUNCH. THIS ISN'T GOOD!
RUN AWAY!
GO AND TELL THE BOSS
THAT THERE‐‐
GO, BAISE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHI‐‐
( groans )
( Baise gasps )
( mouth cackles )
( chorus continues )
Franklin: THAT WAS A LOT EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
Feitan: I DIDN'T
GET TO DO ANYTHING.
Franklin:
IT'S ALL YOURS, SHIZUKU.
Shizuku: RIGHT.
BLINKY, LET'S GO.
( Blinky cackles )
Shizuku: SUCK UP ALL TRACES
OF THE VICTIMS FROM THE ROOM,
THEIR BLOOD, BODY PARTS,
AND ALL OF THEIR
PERSONAL POSSESSIONS.
GET THE CHAIRS, TOO.
( whooshes )
Feitan: HER NEN ABILITY
IS ALWAYS FUN TO WATCH.
‐ Franklin: HEY.
‐ Feitan: HMM?
( man gasping )
Feitan: SOMEONE IS STILL ALIVE.
Man: WHO‐‐WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU PEOPLE, ANYWAY?
( groans ) IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU'RE ALL DEAD. DO YOU HEAR ME?
THE COMMUNITY
WILL DESTROY YOU FOR THIS,
YOU AND YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY!
THEY'LL TORTURE YOU.
THEY'LL CUT YOU UP...
MAKE YOU TASTE HEL‐‐
( head thumping )
( body thuds )
Feitan: FAMILY?
WHAT'S THAT?
( Blinky swallows )
Melody: I CAN'T HEAR IT
VERY CLEARLY,
BUT THERE'S A COMMOTION
GOING ON INSIDE THE BUILDING.
Kurapika: SOMETHING
MUST HAVE HAPPENED.
CONTACT THE LEADER.
Dalzollene: I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL CALL
LINSSEN AND BASHO, TOO,
AND I WANT THE BOTH OF YOU
TO HEAD INSIDE.
Man: WAIT. WHAT?
Man #2: THERE'S NO ONE HERE.
♪
Man #3: WHERE'D THEY GO?
SEARCH THE PLACE!
Man #4: HEY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MERCHANDISE?!
Man #5: GET OUTTA HERE!
HEAD UNDERGROUND NOW!
( overlapping chatter )
Kurapika: I'M INSIDE,
AND IT APPEARS THAT EVERYONE
IN THE AUCTION HOUSE
HAS DISAPPEARED.
Dalzollene: WHAT?
Kurapika: THE WHOLE PLACE
IS IN A STATE OF PANIC.
IT'S COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL.
Dalzollene: THE MERCHANDISE.
WHAT ABOUT THE MERCHANDISE?
Kurapika: MELODY IS HEADING
TO THE UNDERGROUND SAFE.
Man #6: I‐IT'S EMPTY.
Man #7: THE GOODS
FOR TODAY'S AUCTION,
THEY'VE BEEN STOLEN!
Man #6: WHO COULD
HAVE DONE THIS?
Man #7: DAMN IT!
WHERE THE HELL DID THEY GO?!
Man #8: SPLIT UP,
AND LOOK FOR 'EM, YOU IDIOT!
Man #9: LET'S GO! GET THE WORD
OUT TO EVERY FAMILY, AND QUICK!
♪
Dalzollene: OKAY, UNDERSTOOD.
WE'RE GOING TO CATCH
THOSE THIEVES,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
I'M ON MY WAY NOW.
RENDEZVOUS WITH LINSSEN
AND BASHO BEHIND THE BUILDING.
THEY'LL MEET YOU
IN CENTRAL SQUARE.
SQUALA.
Squala: YES, SIR.
Dalzollene: LEAVE FIVE DOGS
BEHIND JUST IN CASE.
Squala: RIGHT.
Dalzollene: LISTEN UP!
DON'T TAKE YOUR EYES
OFF THE BOSS,
AND DON'T LET ANYONE IN THE ROOM
UNTIL WE'RE BACK!
Maids: YES, SIR.
Man #10: ALL OF THE ROADS
ARE SEALED.
THE ONLY REMAINING ESCAPE ROUTE
IS BY AIR!
IF YOU SEE
ANY SUSPICIOUS AIRCRAFT,
CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY,
BUT MAKE SURE NOT TO KILL THEM.
THE COMMUNITY
HAS OFFERED A LARGE REWARD
TO THE GANG
THAT FINDS THE THIEVES.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE
TO TAKE THEM ALIVE!
( wind blowing )
Boss: NO MERCHANDISE?
Uvogin: NONE. IN FACT,
THE VAULT WAS COMPLETELY EMPTY.
THE AUCTIONEER WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNEW THE WHOLE SITUATION,
AND ACCORDING TO HIM,
ALL OF THE ITEMS
WERE TAKEN TO A NEW LOCATION
A FEW HOURS AGO.
IT'S LIKE
THEY EXPECTED THIS TO HAPPEN
AND WERE FULLY PREPARED FOR IT.
Boss: OH?
Uvogin: DON'T YOU
THINK THE TIMING
IS JUST A LITTLE
TOO COINCIDENTAL?
IF YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT I THINK,
WE'VE GOT A JUDAS AMONG US.
Uvogin: IF YOU WANNA
KNOW WHAT I THINK,
WE'VE GOT A JUDAS AMONG US.
Nobunaga: SO YOU'RE SAYING
THAT ONE OF US IS A TRAITOR?
♪
Boss: NO. THERE ISN'T A TRAITOR.
AND IF YOU ASK ME,
JUDAS WAS NOTHING OF THE SORT.
IT'S SAID THAT JUDAS
BETRAYED JESUS
FOR 30 PIECES OF SILVER.
BUT TO BETRAY ALL OF US,
WHAT WOULD ONE ASK OF THE MAFIA?
THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT WOULD THE TRAITOR GAIN
BY SELLING US OUT TO THEM?
MONEY? FAME? STATUS?
WOULD THAT BE ENOUGH
TO GRATIFY ANY OF US
OR TO SLAKE OUR THIRST
IN ANY WAY?
Uvogin: NOBODY I'VE MET
IS LIKE THAT, NO.
Boss: OF COURSE NOT.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL
THAT DOESN'T ADD UP.
Uvogin: IT'S NOT?
Boss: IF THERE WAS AN INFORMANT,
THE MAFIA'S RESPONSE
WAS PITIFULLY INADEQUATE.
IF THEY HAD KNOWN BEFOREHAND
THAT CLASS‐A BOUNTIES
WOULD APPEAR AT THE AUCTION
FROM OUT OF NOWHERE,
THEY CERTAINLY WOULD HAVE
BOLSTERED THEIR SECURITY.
THE GUESTS CAME UNARMED,
WHICH TELLS ME
NO ONE WARNED THEM.
Uvogin: I CAN'T ARGUE WITH THAT.
Boss: AND THAT IS WHY I BELIEVE
THAT WHILE SOMEONE
DID TIP THEM OFF,
IT WASN'T TERRIBLY SPECIFIC.
HOWEVER, SOMEONE HIGH UP
IN THE MAFIA COMMUNITY
BELIEVED THAT INFORMATION.
Uvogin: OKAY,
I THINK I FOLLOW YOU,
BUT I DON'T SEE
HOW THIS INFORMATION
IS GETTING FROM A TO B.
WHATEVER.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT US TO DO NOW?
Boss: WHEN YOU SPOKE
WITH THE AUCTIONEER,
DID YOU ASK WHERE
THE MERCHANDISE WAS MOVED?
Uvogin: I DID, BUT HE
KEPT INSISTING HE DIDN'T KNOW
ALL THE WAY UP UNTIL HE DIED.
FEITAN TORTURED HIM, SO...
Feitan: HE HAD THE WORST LUCK
OF ANYONE TODAY.
Boss: DID YOU MANAGE
TO GET THE NAMES
OF ANYONE WHO MIGHT KNOW?
Uvogin: DO YOU EVEN HAVE TO ASK?
THE AUCTION IS RUN BY THE HEADS
OF THE MAFIA COMMUNITY,
LEADERS OF GANGS
IN EACH OF THE 10 DISTRICTS
AROUND THE WORLD.
THEY'RE CALLED THE 10 DONS.
THIS IS THE ONE TIME OF YEAR
THAT ALL TEN GATHER IN ONE PLACE
TO DISCUSS BUSINESS
AND ISSUE ORDERS,
ORDERS WHICH ARE
THEN CARRIED OUT
BY A SPECIAL FORCE
CALLED THE SHADOW BEASTS.
THE TEAM IS COMPRISED
OF COMBATANTS
WHICH ARE HAND‐PICKED
BY EACH DON,
THE BEST OF THE BEST.
Boss: AH, I SEE.
AND SINCE THE SHADOW BEASTS
WEREN'T CALLED UPON
TO GUARD THE AUCTION HOUSE,
THE THEORY THAT THEY
DIDN'T KNOW WE WERE COMING
HAS EVEN MORE CREDIBILITY.
Uvogin: THAT DOES MAKE SENSE.
Boss: THE QUESTION REMAINS HOW
DID THEY MOVE THE MERCHANDISE?
Uvogin: THAT'S WHAT
I'M WONDERING.
I HEARD A SINGLE SHADOW BEAST
MEMBER TURNED UP AT THE VAULT.
THE SAFE ITSELF
IS 25 SQUARE METERS,
AND IT WAS PACKED FULL OF ITEMS
WAITING TO BE AUCTIONED OFF.
HE WALKED IN
AND THEN WALKED
RIGHT BACK OUT EMPTY‐HANDED.
THE VAULT WAS COMPLETELY BARE.
IT WAS A GUY IN SUNGLASSES
WHO CALLED HIMSELF THE OWL.
Boss: HE MUST HAVE A NEN ABILITY
QUITE SIMILAR TO SHIZUKU'S.
Uvogin: PROBABLY.
Boss: BUT SURELY
ONCE 500 PEOPLE DISAPPEARED,
THEY HAD TO REALIZE...
THAT THEY'RE DEALING
WITH NEN USERS.
Uvogin: WE CAN TAKE 'EM,
CAN'T WE?
Boss: OF COURSE.
PUT ON A SHOW FOR THE PURSUERS,
A DISTURBANCE BIG ENOUGH
TO DRAW OUT THE SHADOW BEASTS.
( Uvogin laughs )
I CAN HARDLY WAIT!
Man #11: IT'S THEM!
THEY'RE IN THE HOT‐AIR BALLOON!
Man #12: LOOK LIKE IT'S HEADED
FOR THE GORDEAU DESERT!
WE'RE IN PURSUIT!
Lieutenant: A HOT‐AIR BALLOON?
NOT AN AIRSHIP?
Lieutenant #2:
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THEN WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE HUNDREDS OF GUESTS?
Lieutenant #3: YOU KNOW,
I'M STARTING TO THINK
MAYBE WE'RE NOT DEALING
WITH AN ORDINARY BAND
‐ OF ARMED THUGS AFTER ALL.
‐ Lieutenant #2: EH?
GET THE TEN DONS ON THE PHONE.
ASK THEM TO DISPATCH
THE SHADOW BEASTS. GO!
Dalzollene: THEY'RE MOVING.
HEAD FOR THE GORDEAU DESERT.
‐ Squala: OKAY.
‐ ( tires squeal )
Basho: ROGER THAT.
( tires squealing )
♪
Man #13: GET DOWN HERE
RIGHT NOW,
AND WE'LL EVEN LET YOU DECIDE
WHETHER WE DROWN YOU
OR BURY YOU!
( Shalnark laughs )
JUST LOOK AT THE RECEPTION
WE'RE GETTING, HUH?
Shizuku: I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
TO CLEAN ALL THIS UP, AM I?
Feitan: THEY ARE NOT WORTH IT.
Uvogin: HEY!
YOU GUYS CAN STAY OUT OF THIS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF 'EM MYSELF!
( weapons cock )
Man #14: WAIT!
( gun cocks )
ARE YOU THE ONES
WHO KIDNAPPED ALL OF OUR GUESTS?
Uvogin: YEAH.
Man #14: WELL, YOU SURE
HAVE A LOT OF GUTS.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT MUCH.
NOW, WHICH ONE OF YOU
IS THE LEADER?
( Uvogin laughs )
Man #14: YOU PUNK.
( gasps )
Uvogin: EHH.
( laughs )
( man #14 whimpers )
( neck cracks )
( crunch )
♪
( Uvogin growls )
( roars )
( grunts )
AHH.
Nobunaga:
HIS PHILOSOPHY IS SIMPLE,
BE STRONGER THAN ANYONE
OR ANYTHING, NOTHING MORE.
IT'D TAKE A HECK OF A LOT MORE
THAN AN ORDINARY GUN TO LEAVE
EVEN A SMALL SCRATCH ON HIM.
Feitan: PHYSICALLY,
HE'S THE STRONGEST.
Franklin: IT'S LIKE WATCHING
A GORILLA STOMPING ANTS.
( tires squealing )
Nobunaga: THEY JUST
KEEP COMING, HUH?
Franklin:
DON'T THOSE GUYS REALIZE
THEY'RE ONLY GONNA END UP DEAD?
Shalnark: YOU KNOW,
JUST WATCHING ISN'T MUCH FUN.
DOES ANYONE WANT TO PLAY CARDS?
Shizuku: I DO.
Machi: COUNT ME IN.
Squala: LOOK.
Dalzollene: I SEE 'EM.
( Uvogin sighs )
THIS WON'T EVEN GET ME WARMED UP
BEFORE THE SHADOW BEASTS
GET HERE.
( Uvogin grunts )
OW.
A RIFLE?
THAT IS SO ANNOYING.
TRYING TO TAKE ME OUT
FROM AFAR, HUH?
( sniper gasps )
( gags )
Uvogin: OH, YEAH!
THAT WAS A PERFECT SHOT!
Lieutenant #4: THAT'S ENOUGH!
DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF,
YOU MONSTER.
YOU'RE NOT ALL THAT TOUGH.
THIS SUPER‐BAZOOKA IS POWERFUL
ENOUGH TO TAKE OUT A TANK.
I'M ABOUT TO BLOW YOU TO BITS!
Uvogin: THAT...
HURT MY FEELINGS.
SEE, I DON'T LIKE BEING COMPARED
TO SOME MEASLY LITTLE TANK.
Lieutenant #4: YOU'RE DEAD!
♪
DID I GET HIM?
‐ ( gasps )
‐ ( Kurapika gasps )
Uvogin: WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
THAT ACTUALLY KINDA HURT.
( men screaming )
Uvogin: HAH! YOU THINK
I'M GONNA LET YOU GET AWAY?!
Kurapika: IT APPEARS
THAT THE ENEMY CAN USE NEN,
AND HE'S INCREDIBLY POWERFUL.
THE MEN WHO GOT HERE FIRST
ARE ALL DEAD.
FIREARMS ARE USELESS
AGAINST HIM.
Dalzollene: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
Kurapika: TAKE A GOOD LOOK,
AND SEE FOR YOURSELF.
HIS AURA'S
SIMPLY UNBELIEVABLE...
AS IS THE BODY COUNT.
Dalzollene: IT'S INSANE.
JUST WHAT IS HE, ANYWAY?
Squala: DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE'S TEARING
THROUGH ALL THOSE PEOPLE
LIKE SCRAPS OF PAPER.
LOOK, JUST FORGET IT!
NO WAY I'M TRYING
TO CAPTURE THAT!
Basho: HE'S GOT A POINT THERE,
IF WE CAN BEAT HIM.
I DON'T SEE HOW.
‐ Dalzollene: I AGREE.
‐ Squala: HUH?
Dalzollene: HOWEVER,
WE STILL HAVE OUR MISSION,
AND WE CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY NOW.
Squala: BUT STILL...
Melody: HOLD ON!
I CAN'T TELL
WHERE IT'S COMING FROM,
BUT I HEAR ANOTHER HEARTBEAT.
♪
( both gasp )
Worm:
I AM THE SHADOW BEAST, WORM.
WHICH FAMILY DO YOU BELONG TO?
Dalzollene: WE'RE BODYGUARDS.
WE'VE BEEN HIRED
BY THE NOSTRADE FAMILY.
Worm: I UNDERSTAND.
IT SEEMS THAT YOU CAN USE NEN
A BIT, BUT DON'T BOTHER.
Shadow Beast:
THESE ARE NO ORDINARY THUGS.
TO THEM, KILLING'S
A PART OF THEIR DAILY ROUTINE.
Shadow Beast #2: YOU COULD SAY
THAT THEY'RE
PROFESSIONAL KILLERS.
Shadow Beast #3:
AND AS PROS OURSELVES,
WE'LL HANDLE IT.
Rabid Dog: MY NAME'S RABID DOG.
Leech: AND MINE IS LEECH.
Porcupine: YOU, UH,
CAN CALL ME PORCUPINE.
Rabid Dog: SIT BACK,
AND LEAVE THIS JOB
TO THE SHADOW BEASTS.
Kurapika: IT'S THEM,
THE SHADOW BEASTS.
♪
Narrator: THE MAFIA COMMUNITY
HAS UNLEASHED
THE DREADED SHADOW BEASTS
UPON THE BANDITS
WHO ATTACKED THE AUCTION,
AND KURAPIKA HAS YET TO REALIZE
THAT THESE BANDITS
THEY WILL SOON MEET IN BATTLE
ARE IN FACT THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING BAISE.
HER ABILITY'S INSTANT LOVER.
Killua: SHE PRETENDS
SHE'S INTO A GUY,
THEN GOES IN FOR A KISS.
Gon: SO ALL YOU MEN
BETTER BE CAREFUL.
Both: SMOOCH!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"BUILDUP TO A FIERCE BATTLE."
SO, UH,
DO BANANAS COUNT AS A SNACK?
Killua: WHAT ABOUT CHOCOLATE?
IS THAT A SNACK?
Gon: YEAH.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN A SNACK.