( beast roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Hisoka chuckles )
I SEE. I SEE.
THAT SETTLES IT, THEN.
SO YOU ARE THE REAL ONE.
THE EXAMINERS ARE HUNTERS.
EACH IS HAND‐PICKED
BY THE EXAM COMMITTEE
TO DO THIS JOB WITHOUT PAY.
ANYONE WHO HOLDS THE TITLE
WE'RE VYING FOR OURSELVES
COULD HAVE DEFLECTED
THAT ATTACK,
AND QUITE EASILY, I MIGHT ADD.
Satotz: I SHALL TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
THANK YOU.
STILL, SHOULD YOU
CHOOSE TO ATTACK ME AGAIN
FOR ANY REASON,
I WILL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO REPORT YOU
FOR ATTACKING AN EXAMINER
AND HAVE YOU
IMMEDIATELY DISQUALIFIED.
IS THAT CLEAR?
Hisoka: OF COURSE.
♪♪♪
Narrator: THE 368 APPLICANTS
WHO MADE IT
THROUGH THE UNDERGROUND TUNNEL
FIND THEMSELVES
IN AN UNEXPLORED LAND
TEEMING WITH STRANGE CREATURES,
KNOWN AS THE MILSY WETLANDS.
Satotz: NOW, EVERYONE,
PLEASE MAKE SURE
TO FOLLOW CLOSE BEHIND ME.
( monkey chitters )
♪♪♪
( bird squawking )
Kurapika: THE FOG IS GETTING
EVEN THICKER AS WE GO.
Applicant #76:
GUYS, HERE'S OUR CHANCE.
I SAY WE TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE FOG AND GET RID OF HIM.
( applicants grunt )
‐ Killua: GON.
‐ Gon: UH, YEAH?
Killua: LET'S TRY
TO MOVE UP TO THE FRONT.
Gon: RIGHT.
THE LAST THING WE WANT TO DO
IS LOSE SIGHT OF THE EXAMINER
RIGHT NOW.
Killua: I JUST WANT
TO PUT A LITTLE MORE DISTANCE
BETWEEN HISOKA AND US.
STAYING TOO CLOSE IS DANGEROUS.
I CAN SMELL IT.
Gon: SMELL, HUH?
( sniffs )
HUH?
I DON'T THINK HE SMELLS.
HEY, LEORIO, KURAPIKA!
KILLUA SAYS WE SHOULD ALL MOVE
UP TO THE FRONT OF THE PACK!
Killua: HEY, CALM DOWN.
DON'T YOU FEEL
THE TENSION IN THE AIR?
Leorio: YOU IDIOT!
IF I COULD REACH THE FRONT,
I'D ALREADY BE THERE!
Kurapika: GO AHEAD!
WE'LL MEET YOU THERE!
Gon: AWW!
Killua: COME ON. LET'S GO.
Gon: WAIT! HOLD ON!
Kurapika: THIS IS BAD.
WITH THIS FOG,
WE CAN'T TELL
WHICH WAY WE'RE GOING.
Leorio: IT'S OKAY,
AS LONG AS WE DON'T LOSE SIGHT
OF THE GUYS AHEAD OF US.
( gasps )
( shrieks )
WHAT IN THE HELL
IS GOING ON NOW?!
♪♪♪
WHOA. WHAT IS THAT?
Applicant: HUH?
WHAAH!
( screaming )
( applicants screaming )
( applicant screams )
( tortoises roar )
( applicants gasping )
( groaning )
( coughing )
Applicant: HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
Second applicant: BUTTERFLIES?
( applicants groaning )
♪♪♪
Imori: DAMN!
WHICH WAY ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GO?
Amori: DID WE LOSE SIGHT OF HIM?
Satotz: NOW, EVERYONE,
PLEASE MAKE SURE
TO FOLLOW CLOSE BEHIND ME.
Umori: HE'S OVER THERE!
( applicants yelling )
( applicants scream )
( Imori gasps )
( Satotz's voice )
NOW, EVERYONE‐‐CAW!
BE SURE TO FOLLOW
CLOSE BEHIND ME!
CAW!
Amori:
IT CAN IMITATE HUMAN SPEECH?
Umori: THAT SURE
WAS REALLY CLOSE.
Imori: YEAH.
Gon: I WONDER WHAT'S HAPPENING.
I CAN HEAR PEOPLE
SCREAMING ALL AROUND US.
Killua: THAT'S WHY
WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL.
Gon: I HAVEN'T SEEN
THE GUYS IN A WHILE.
I JUST HOPE THEY'RE SAFE.
‐ Killua: EH?
‐ Gon: HUH?
( both scream )
( tortoise roars )
Kurapika: LEORIO!
♪♪♪
( Leorio screaming )
( tortoise roars )
Leorio: OW.
Kurapika: LEORIO,
NOW'S OUR CHANCE! COME ON!
( frog groaning )
( Gon chuckles )
I GUESS HE MUST NOT HAVE LIKED
THE WAY WE TASTED, HUH?
Killua: IT WAS THIS STUFF.
Gon: OH! THE DRINK TONPA HAD!
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT SAVED US.
Killua: YEAH. PROBABLY SO, BUT I
COULD'VE ESCAPED WITHOUT IT.
Gon: I'M STILL PRETTY WORRIED
ABOUT LEORIO AND KURAPIKA.
Killua: FORGET ABOUT 'EM.
WE NEED TO KEEP MOVING.
WE CAN STILL MAKE IT
IF WE START RIGHT NOW.
Kurapika: IT LOOKS
LIKE WE'VE LOST SIGHT
OF THE FRONT‐RUNNERS.
Leorio: DAMN IT.
WHICH WAY SHOULD WE GO?
( gasps ) HOLD ON!
LOOK OVER THERE.
( Kurapika gasps )
Applicant #76:
YOU'RE NOT HUNTER MATERIAL.
I'VE BEEN THINKING THAT
EVER SINCE WE MET LAST YEAR.
Applicant #67:
WE'LL SPARE YOUR LIFE
IF YOU PROMISE YOU'LL NEVER
TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM AGAIN.
‐ Hisoka: SURE, WHY NOT?
‐ ( applicants gasp )
Hisoka: I INTEND TO PASS,
SO THERE'S NO NEED TO RETAKE IT.
Applicant #76:
OH, YEAH? YOU IDIOT.
JUST LOOK AT THIS FOG.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN FIGURE OUT
WHICH WAY THE MAIN PACK WENT
IN ALL THIS?
Applicant #68: HE'S RIGHT.
WE ALL FAILED THIS YEAR.
NO WAY WE CAN CATCH UP
WITH EVERYONE ELSE.
( Hisoka chuckles )
THAT'S IT, THEN?
YOU FAILED, SO NOW
YOU WANT TO PLAY EXAMINER?
HUNTERS REQUIRE PREY, SO WHY
DON'T I PLAY THE EXAMINER?
ALL OF YOU GENTLEMEN
CLAIM TO BE HUNTER MATERIAL,
BUT I'LL BE THE JUDGE.
( applicant #76 grunts )
YOU SHUT THE HELL UP!
( all yelling )
♪♪♪
( applicant #76 gasping )
Hisoka: NOW THEN...
Applicant #76: HELP. HELP ME.
HELP‐‐( groans )
Hisoka: WELL?
HOW ABOUT YOU TWO?
CARE TO PLAY EXAMINER?
♪♪♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
♪♪♪
( Killua chuckles )
ALL RIGHT. WE CAUGHT UP
WITH THE MAIN GROUP, GON! LOOK!
THAT'S WEIRD.
HE WAS RIGHT HERE A MINUTE AGO.
( footsteps )
Kurapika: OKAY, LEORIO,
WAIT FOR MY SIGNAL.
THEN WE RUN
IN OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS.
Leorio: WE WHAT?
Kurapika: THE FACT
OF THE MATTER IS
HE'S FAR MORE EXPERIENCED
IN ACTUAL COMBAT SITUATIONS.
THE TWO OF US WON'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST HIM.
WE'RE SHORT ON TIME, AND WE
CAN'T AFFORD TO WASTE MORE
ON A FIGHT WE CAN'T EVEN WIN.
( Leorio growls )
Kurapika: NOW RUN!
Hisoka: HMM.
I SEE. A WISE DECISION.
( chuckles )
( laughs )
HMM?
♪♪♪
Leorio: I JUST COULDN'T DO IT.
THIS MAY NOT BE MY FIGHT,
BUT I CAN'T SIT BACK
AND PRETEND NOTHING HAPPENED.
THAT'S NOT MY STYLE.
SEE, THE THING IS
I CAN'T RUN AWAY!
Kurapika: LEORIO!
( Leorio yells )
Hisoka: HMM. I ADORE THAT LOOK.
( Leorio growls )
( yells )
WHA?
♪♪♪
GON!
Gon: DID I MAKE IT?
Hisoka: NOT BAD, LITTLE BOY.
IS THAT A FISHING POLE?
HOW ORIGINAL.
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
DO YOU MIND?
Leorio: LEAVE HIM ALONE.
YOUR FIGHT'S WITH ME!
( Gon yells )
Hisoka: DID YOU COME HERE
TO HELP YOUR FRIEND?
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: SUCH A GOOD BOY.
HMM. I ADORE THAT LOOK.
WELL DONE.
VERY NICE.
I'M BEGINNING TO GET EXCITED.
Gon: RIGHT.
( yells )
( groans )
( fishing pole clatters )
( gagging )
( Hisoka chuckles )
IT'S SO DELIGHTFUL.
I LOVE THAT LOOK.
( gasps )
( Gon coughing )
Gon: DON'T WORRY.
I DIDN'T KILL YOUR FRIEND.
HE'S GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
AND THAT'S BECAUSE HE PASSED.
( chuckles )
AND, YES, YOU PASS AS WELL.
NOW GO AND BECOME
A GOOD HUNTER.
( radio beeping )
Man: HISOKA,
YOU SHOULD GET BACK HERE.
WE'VE ALMOST REACHED
THE SITE OF THE SECOND PHASE.
Hisoka: OKAY. BE RIGHT THERE.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE FRIENDS,
ISN'T IT?
( cloth flutters )
CAN YOU FIND YOUR OWN WAY BACK?
GOOD BOY.
( Gon gasping )
Killua: GON! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
( Gon panting )
Killua: AW, MAN. WHERE IS HE?
I WAS SURE GON WOULD BE HERE.
( applicants murmuring )
Applicant: IT'S GONNA
GET WORSE THAN THIS.
( footsteps )
Gon: THIS WAY.
Kurapika: SO YOU CAN
REALLY TELL BY THE SMELL?
Gon: YEAH.
LEORIO'S ALWAYS WEARING
THIS VERY UNIQUE
KIND OF COLOGNE.
I CAN SMELL HIM
FROM A FEW KILOMETERS AWAY,
‐ NO PROBLEM.
‐ Kurapika: HMM.
Gon: HEY, I'VE BEEN THINKING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HISOKA WAS TALKING ABOUT
WHEN HE SAID
THAT WE BOTH PASSED?
Kurapika: I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I THINK HE
MIGHT HAVE BEEN PLAYING JUDGE.
‐ Gon: JUDGE?
‐ Kurapika: YES.
HE MUST HAVE HIS OWN BENCHMARKS
FOR EVALUATING A PERSON'S POWER.
IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT HE WAS MEASURING
THE STRENGTH OF EACH APPLICANT.
APPARENTLY, YOU AND LEORIO
MET HIS STANDARDS,
WHATEVER THOSE HAPPEN TO BE.
OKAY. RIGHT. THAT MAKES SENSE,
BUT I WAS POWERLESS
TO DO ANYTHING TO STOP HIM.
Kurapika: YOU LANDED
YOUR FIRST HIT ON HIM.
THAT'S SOMETHING, RIGHT?
Gon: THAT'S ONLY
BECAUSE I SURPRISED HIM.
AND BESIDES,
LEORIO DIDN'T WIN HIS FIGHT,
BUT HISOKA PASSED HIM ANYWAY.
Kurapika: HMM. I WONDER.
HE COULD HAVE SENSED
THAT THE TWO OF YOU
WERE SORT OF KINDRED SPIRITS.
Gon: HE SENSED IT?
Kurapika:
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT HISOKA
COULD QUALIFY AS A HUNTER,
BUT I SINCERELY DOUBT IT.
HOWEVER, I MUST ADMIT
THAT I'M IMPRESSED
BY HIS SUPERHUMAN AGILITY
AND THE GRACEFULNESS
OF HIS TECHNIQUE.
THOSE WHO ARE BLESSED
WITH UNIQUE TALENTS
ARE OFTEN DRAWN TO OTHERS
WITH UNIQUE GIFTS OF THEIR OWN.
IT'S LIKELY THAT, BASED ON
HIS INTUITION AND EXPERIENCE,
HISOKA COULD TELL YOU BOTH HAD
THE SKILL AND POTENTIAL
TO BECOME HUNTERS.
SO FROM HIS PERSPECTIVE,
KILLING THE TWO OF YOU NOW
WOULD HAVE BEEN A WASTE.
OH, NO. SORRY.
THAT MUST SOUND HORRIBLE.
Gon: MM‐MMM. BUT I'VE GOTTA SAY
IT WAS ACTUALLY
PRETTY EXCITING BACK THERE.
Kurapika: HUH?
Gon: I WAS SO SCARED THAT ALL
I WANTED TO DO WAS RUN AWAY,
BUT I COULDN'T,
'CAUSE I WAS EXCITED
AT THE SAME TIME.
ISN'T THAT WEIRD?
♪♪♪
Narrator: GON HAD EXPERIENCED
MORTAL FEAR FOR THE FIRST TIME,
AND ALTHOUGH
THE UNFAMILIAR FEELINGS
THAT ACCOMPANY THAT FEAR
ARE QUITE CONFUSING TO HIM,
HE CANNOT HELP BUT GIVE IN
TO HIS GROWING CURIOSITY.
AT THIS STAGE, 220 CANDIDATES
HAVE WITHDRAWN FROM THE EXAM,
AND 148 REMAIN.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"A SURPRISING CHALLENGE."
Kurapika:
IT'S SURPRISINGLY CHALLENGING!
WAIT. GON, ARE YOU OKAY?
♪♪♪