( wind blowing )
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
Chrollo: FOREVER SET,
A PRECIOUS MOON IS LOST.
THE OTHERS MOURN HIM
WITH CEREMONY GRAND...
RISING UP TO HEAVEN
THE MIGHTY MOON OF FROST
WITH A MELODY
FROM THE MOURNING BAND.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( train horn blows )
‐ ( brakes squeal )
‐ ( passengers gasp )
( overlapping chatter )
( announcer on P. A. )
ATTENTION, PASSENGERS.
WE WILL BE MAKING
AN EMERGENCY STOP.
‐ PLEASE WATCH YOUR STEP.
‐ Gon: WAIT.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
Killua: DON'T KNOW.
( cell phone rings )
Mafioso: IT'S ME. ARE THEY HERE?
Mafioso #2: YEAH,
IT'S GOTTA BE THEM.
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES
I CAN THINK OF
WHO ARE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO TAKE ON A WHOLE CROWD
ON THEIR OWN.
( screams )
Mafioso #1: HEY. HEY!
‐ ( crash over phone )
‐ ( gasps )
DAMN IT. LISTEN!
FIGURE OUT HOW MANY ENEMIES
WE'RE UP AGAINST.
DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO STOP THEM.
DON'T LET THEM
ANYWHERE NEAR THIS BUILDING!
♪
( footsteps )
( Nostrade growls )
THEY'RE LATE.
( groans )
OUR ESCORTS AREN'T HERE?
THEIR NAMES
ARE MELODY AND BASHO.
Guard: UNFORTUNATELY, SIR,
ALL THE TRAFFIC IN YORKNEW CITY
HAS COME TO A GRINDING HALT.
THEY'RE PROBABLY STUCK.
( Nostrade groans )
IT'S DANGEROUS
FOR NEON TO BE HERE.
ISN'T THERE ANY WAY
TO GET HER OUT?
Guard: THE AMBULANCE WE
REQUESTED IS ALREADY ON ITS WAY.
IT SHOULDN'T BE
MUCH LONGER, SIR.
Nostrade: AMBULANCE?
OH. YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
Kurapika:
SOMETHING'S WRONG HERE.
THE MAN WHO ENTERED
THE BUILDING WITH NEON
AND THEN CALLED FOR A DOCTOR...
WAIT, SIR.
Nostrade: KURAPIKA,
DO NOT LEAVE MY DAUGHTER'S SIDE
UNTIL THE AMBULANCE ARRIVES.
UNDERSTAND?
Kurapika: BUT, SIR,
MY ASSIGNMENT IS TO KILL
THE PHANTOM TROUPE, AND‐‐
Nostrade: THAT WAS
WHEN I THOUGHT
NEON WOULD BE HOME ALREADY.
INSTEAD, SHE'S HERE
AND UNCONSCIOUS,
COMPLETELY EXPOSED
TO THE TROUPE.
I MUST ENSURE HER SAFETY.
I WANT YOU HERE
FOR THE TIME BEING.
PLEASE, KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: I UNDERSTAND.
♪
( blow lands )
( assassin chuckles )
IT'S SUCH A PITY, ISN'T IT?
THEY AREN'T PUTTING UP
MUCH OF A FIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS
IT WAS STUPID TO EXPEC‐‐
( groans )
( siren blaring )
Mafioso #1: DAMN IT.
THEY'RE CRAZIER THAN I THOUGHT.
THEY'RE TRYING TO LAUNCH
A FULL FRONTAL ATTACK
WITH ONLY TEN PEOPLE.
Doctor: MY GOODNESS.
WHEN THE HELL DID THIS PLACE
TURN INTO SUCH
A DAMN WAR ZONE, HUH?
SO WHERE'S THE PATIENT?
( gasps )
‐ ( weapons cock )
‐ ( EMTs gasp )
Mafioso #1: I DON'T HAVE
ANY REASON TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU AREN'T A MEMBER
OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
MAKE JUST ONE FUNNY MOVE,
AND I'LL BLOW YOUR HEAD OFF.
Doctor: UH...
Mafioso #1: FOLLOW ME.
♪
( chains jangle )
Kurapika: I WILL NEED
TO INSPECT ALL OF YOU.
Mafioso #1: WHAT'S THAT?
DAMN YOU.
( passengers chattering )
Passenger: GIVE ME A BREAK.
( announcer on P. A.): ALL TRAINS
HAVE BEEN STOPPED AT THIS TIME.
THE SAFETY OF OUR CUSTOMERS
IS OF UTMOST IMPORTANCE TO US,
SO WE ASK THAT YOU CONTINUE
TO WAIT PATIENTLY FOR NOW.
Passenger: COME ON.
Gon: I'M NOT GETTING
ANY RECEPTION DOWN HERE,
AND WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN THE TRAINS
WILL START MOVING AGAIN.
Killua: THEN I GUESS
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO RUN.
♪
( Nostrade sighs )
Mafioso #1: WEREN'T YOU
HIRED HERE AS AN ASSASSIN?
WHY DON'T YOU QUIT HIDING OUT
IN THIS ROOM AND GO FIGHT?
UNLESS YOU GOT TOO SCARED WHEN
THE PHANTOM TROUPE SHOWED UP.
Nostrade: WELL, ACTUALLY,
I REQUESTED
THAT KURAPIKA STAY HERE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT HE WAS HIRED
BY THE TEN DONS,
BUT I'M A BIT WORRIED
ABOUT MY DAUGHTER.
Mafioso #1 IT'S FINE.
I WON'T SELL YOU OUT.
BUT STILL,
I KNOW YOU'RE BEING PAID WELL,
SO I EXPECT YOU TO DO YOUR JOB.
( Nostrade chuckles )
Kurapika: HE'S RIGHT.
I REALLY SHOULD DO
SOMETHING TO HELP OUT.
I COULD PATROL THE BUILDING
AT THE VERY LEAST.
Nostrade: I SUPPOSE SO,
BUT YOU MUST COME BACK
IMMEDIATELY IF I CALL ON YOU.
MY DAUGHTER'S SAFETY
TAKES PRECEDENCE.
Kurapika: YES, SIR.
Mafioso #3: HOW LONG
DO WE HAVE TO WAIT?
Mafioso #4: HEY!
WHAT'S GOING ON OUTSIDE?!
Mafioso #5: YEAH,
I HEAR EXPLOSIONS NEARBY.
Mafioso #6: WHEN IS
THE AUCTION GONNA START?
Mafioso #7: WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON HERE, ANYWAY?
Auctioneer: P‐PLEASE, SIR.
IT SHOULDN'T BE MUCH LONGER.
Mafioso #6: IS THE AUCTION
STILL ON, OR ISN'T IT?!
Kurapika: EVERYONE HERE
IS EITHER A LEADER
OR AN EXECUTIVE MEMBER.
THEY'RE ENDANGERING THEMSELVES
NEEDLESSLY
ONLY TO PROVE THEY
AREN'T AFRAID OF THE TROUPE.
Mafioso #3:
GIVE ME BACK MY PHONE!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING OUT THERE!
I NEED MY WEAPONS BACK, TOO!
Auctioneer: AS YOU KNOW,
SIR, THE RULES STATE
THAT WEAPONS ARE BANNED
DURING THE AUCTION.
Mafioso #6: WHAT HAPPENS
IF THEY GET INSIDE?
Mafioso #5: WE FIGHT THEM
WITH OUR BARE HANDS?
Kurapika: IT'S STARTING
TO GET CHAOTIC IN HERE.
‐ ( automatic gunfire )
‐ IF THEY'RE NOT CAREFUL,
THE AUCTION ORGANIZERS
WILL LOSE CONTROL
OF THE SITUATION
BEFORE MUCH LONGER.
( cell phone vibrating )
Kurapika: YES? HELLO.
‐ Gon: HEY. KURAPIKA?
‐ ( Kurapika gasps )
Gon: OH, GOOD.
WE FINALLY GOT AHOLD OF YOU.
Kurapika: GON?
Gon: YEAH.
CAN YOU TALK RIGHT NOW?
Kurapika: UH, I'M A LITTLE BUSY,
SO I'LL HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK.
Gon: WAIT!
JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE!
I HAVE SOMETHING
I REALLY NEED TO TELL YOU.
KILLUA AND I FOUND THE TROUPE.
( Kurapika gasps )
Gon: ACTUALLY,
THEY KINDA CAUGHT US.
Kurapika: WHAT IN THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW DANGEROUS THEY ARE?
Killua: MY TURN.
I THOUGHT I KNEW
UNTIL WE MET THEM.
THEY'RE REALLY TOUGH.
AS IT STANDS, WE DON'T HAVE
A CHANCE AGAINST THEM.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED YOUR HELP.
Gon: AND WE WANT
TO HELP YOU, TOO.
Kurapika: THIS ISN'T A GAME.
I'M NOT GOING TO HELP YOU
GET YOURSELVES KILLED.
Killua: WE FOUND THEIR BASE.
WANNA KNOW WHERE IT IS?
Kurapika: I HAVE MY OWN SOURCES.
Killua: WE LEARNED
SOME OF THEIR ABILITIES.
DON'T YOU WANNA KNOW ABOUT THEM?
Kurapika: THAT'S ENOUGH!
JUST STAY AWAY
FROM THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Killua: YOU'RE THE CHAIN USER
WHO KILLED ONE OF THEM, RIGHT?
YOU DO REALIZE THAT
THEY'RE DEAD SET ON FINDING YOU.
BUT IF YOU WON'T EVEN CONSIDER
THINKING OF ME AND GON
AS YOUR FRIENDS AND EQUALS,
WE'LL DO WHATEVER THE HELL
IT TAKES TO MAKE YOU HELP US!
Gon: KURAPIKA...
ONE OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE GUYS,
HE STARTED CRYING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US.
HE SAID HE COULD NEVER FORGIVE
WHOEVER KILLED HIS FRIEND.
( no audible dialogue )
AND THEN WHEN I SAW HIM DO THAT,
IT MADE ME REALLY ANGRY.
I COULDN'T FORGIVE THEM.
LOOK, WE WANT TO STOP THEM, TOO.
SO PLEASE, KURAPIKA...
Kurapika:
I'LL CALL YOU BACK LATER.
Killua: BUT IF YOU
WON'T EVEN CONSIDER
THINKING OF ME AND GON
AS YOUR FRIENDS AND EQUALS...
Gon: LOOK,
WE WANT TO STOP THEM, TOO.
♪
‐ ( men gasp )
‐ Mafioso #7: HERE THEY COME!
Mafioso #8:
DON'T LET THEM ESCAPE!
Mafioso #9: SOMEONE'S COMING!
Mafioso #10:
WHO'S STATIONED HERE?
Mafioso #11: NO, GO BACK!
IT'S NO USE.
THE TROUPE IS TOO POWERFUL.
I'M SERIOUS.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THEM.
DO YOU WANNA SEE
HOW STRONG THEY ARE?
'CAUSE I CAN SHOW YOU!
( Kurapika gasps )
THEY'RE THIS STRONG!
‐ ( laughs )
‐ ( men screaming )
Mafioso #12: DAMN IT!
( mafioso #11 laughing )
Shalnark: OHH. HE BROKE.
I NEED TO FIND MY NEXT PUPPET.
Mafioso #13: ARE YOU OKAY?
I FOUND THE CORPSE
OF ONE OF THE ASSASSINS.
SOMEONE HAS ALREADY GOTTEN
INSIDE THE BUILDING!
Kurapika: DAMN.
♪
( men screaming )
( explosion )
( gunfire )
Mafioso #14:
WHO ARE THESE GUYS?!
Mafioso #15: IT'S HOPELESS!
Mafioso #16: COME ON!
GET BACK HERE, AND FIGHT!
( beep )
( mafioso #1 groans )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S ME!
WHERE THE HELL IS OUR BACKUP?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Mafioso #17: THEY SHOULD
BE THERE ANY MINUTE,
AND WE'LL BE
ARRIVING THERE SHORTLY.
‐ ( crash over phone )
‐ ( screams )
( mafioso #1 gasps )
( explosion )
IS THIS REALLY HAPPENING?
THE 2,000 ARMED MEN THAT WERE
SUPPOSED TO ASSEMBLE HERE,
ARE THEY ALL GETTING KILLED?
NOW WHAT?
THERE ARE TROUPE MEMBERS
INSIDE THE BUILDING ALREADY.
IT'S ME, BEAN.
GET THE TEN DONS ON THE LINE,
AND HURRY!
Kurapika: THE INTRUDER
MUST BE A MEMBER OF THE TROUPE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO STEAL
THE REST OF THE MERCHANDISE
AND AVENGE THEIR COMRADE.
Gon: HE SAID
HE COULD NEVER FORGIVE
WHOEVER KILLED HIS FRIEND.
Kurapika: THAT'S WHAT
I'M HOPING FOR.
( glass shatters )
Mafioso #3: HEY! ENOUGH ALREADY!
GIVE US THE WEAPONS
WE HANDED OVER, AND DO IT NOW!
Auctioneer: BUT, SIR,
THE RULES STATE THAT‐‐
Mafioso #4: TO HELL
WITH THE DAMN RULES, HEAR ME?!
YOU KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING,
DON'T YOU!?
Mafioso #3 I'M NOT STUPID.
YOU'VE GOT
PROFESSIONAL ASSASSINS HERE.
I'VE BEEN SEEING 'EM
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
Mafioso #4: IF YOU'RE
GONNA DEPEND ON THOSE FREAKS,
THEN YOU MIGHT AS WELL
JUST LET US FIGHT!
( all gasping )
( crowd quiets )
Zeno: FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO DON'T KNOW,
MY NAME IS ZENO ZOLDYCK.
Mafioso #4: ZOLDYCK, LIKE
THE FAMOUS FAMILY OF ASSASSINS?
Mafioso #5: DID THE TEN DONS
ACTUALLY CALL IN THESE MONSTERS?
Zeno: AT THE MOMENT, ONE BANDIT
HAS INFILTRATED THIS BUILDING.
‐ ( crowd gasps )
‐ Zeno: HE HAS ALREADY KILLED
A NUMBER OF THE ASSASSINS
THAT WERE HIRED BY YOUR PEOPLE.
♪
IT WOULDN'T MUCH MATTER IF EACH
OF YOU WAS ARMED TO THE TEETH.
I COULD STILL ELIMINATE THE LOT
OF YOU IN UNDER SEVEN SECONDS.
THE ENEMY IS
EVERY BIT AS CAPABLE.
( crowd murmuring )
Zeno: IF YOU UNDERSTAND,
THEN JUST SHUT UP, AND WAIT.
DISREGARD,
IF YOU WOULD RATHER DIE.
WELL, THEN?
Silva: A SINGLE STRIKE
FROM BEHIND. IMPRESSIVE.
HIS BLOODLUST WAS
ONLY EXPOSED FOR AN INSTANT,
AND BARELY A TRACE REMAINS.
( Zeno sighs )
I SUPPOSE I'LL HAVE TO USE EN,
ALTHOUGH IT REALLY IS
SUCH AN EXHAUSTING TECHNIQUE.
LET'S START FROM THE ROOF
AND THEN MAKE OUR WAY DOWN.
Silva: THIS BUILDING'S RADIUS
IS 100 METERS.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT, DAD?
Zeno: YOU FOOL,
I COULD DO 300 METERS EASILY.
‐ ( joints crack )
‐ ONE THING IS CERTAIN.
WE'RE NOT GETTING PAID
ENOUGH FOR THIS.
♪
( explosion )
( cell phone vibrates )
Nostrade: KURAPIKA, YOU'RE LATE!
HURRY BACK AT ONCE,
AND STAY BY NEON'S SIDE!
Kurapika: YES, SIR.
I'M ON MY WAY.
DAMN IT.
( explosion )
♪
Chrollo: WE MEET AGAIN.
Silva: YOU REMEMBER ME?
Chrollo: HOW COULD I FORGET?
YOU DID KILL ONE OF MY PEOPLE.
Silva: IT WASN'T EASY.
( chorus vocalizing )
NOW, DAD, BE CAREFUL.
HE CAN STEAL PEOPLE'S ABILITIES.
( chorus ends )
( Zeno grunts )
( Chrollo gasps )
( Silva gasps )
( Chrollo panting )
TWO ON ONE SURE IS ROUGH.
Silva: HMM. MUST BE A GOOD KNIFE
IF IT CAN SCRATCH MY SKIN,
A MID‐ERA BEN'S KNIFE,
BY THE LOOKS OF IT.
HMM. THE SHAPE
MUST MEAN IT'S POISONED.
Zeno: YOU ALL RIGHT?
Silva: NOT A PROBLEM.
Chrollo: "NOT A PROBLEM"?
POINT‐ONE MILLIGRAMS
OF THAT STUFF
IS MORE THAN ENOUGH
TO PARALYZE A WHALE.
Zeno: SO YOU CAN STEAL
OTHER PEOPLE'S NEN?
THEN YOU'RE A SPECIALIST.
YOU MIGHT EVEN BE A THREAT
IF YOU COULD USE
THOSE STOLEN POWERS FREELY.
HOWEVER, THAT IMPLIES
A HIGHER ACTIVATION COST.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
THE ABILITY OTHERWISE.
IF I HAD TO MAKE A GUESS,
YOU MUST CLEAR
FOUR OR FIVE CONDITIONS
BEFORE STEALING AN ABILITY.
Chrollo: HE'S RIGHT.
THE OLD MAN'S A TOUGH CUSTOMER.
Zeno: TRYING TO MEET
THOSE CONDITIONS
WHILE FIGHTING BOTH OF US
WILL BE DIFFICULT INDEED,
MEANING THAT YOU WON'T
BE ABLE TO STEAL OUR ABILITIES
AS LONG AS WE KEEP YOU
ENGAGED IN BATTLE.
THAT POISONED KNIFE OF YOURS
IS PROOF.
Chrollo: RIGHT AGAIN.
GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
Zeno: HMM.
♪
‐ WATCH MY BACK, SILVA.
‐ Silva: HMM?
Zeno: AS SOON
AS I HAVE HIM PINNED DOWN,
EVEN IF YOU HAVE TO KILL ME,
END HIM.
Silva: GOT IT.
Chrollo: HE FOCUSED HIS AURA
INTO HIS HAND.
THE ENERGY POTENTIAL
WILL BE HUGE.
I DON'T HAVE THE DEFENSES
TO BLOCK IT.
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
( both gasp )
Zeno: A CONJURED CLOAK, EH?
HMM. THIS COULD BE TROUBLE.
EVEN IF IT'S A STOLEN ABILITY,
IT WOULD BE RECKLESS TO ATTACK
WITHOUT KNOWING WHAT IT DOES...
OR SO THE AVERAGE PERSON
WOULD THINK, BUT...
( Chrollo grunts )
( Zeno laughs )
( yells )
I SEE WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE CAN TRAP THE ABILITIES
OF OTHERS IN THE CONJURED BOOK,
TAKE THEM OUT, AND USE THEM
ANY TIME HE PLEASES...
BUT THERE'S A CATCH.
HE CAN'T USE THOSE ABILITIES
UNLESS HE HOLDS THE BOOK OPEN
THE ENTIRE TIME.
THE CLOAK IS ALSO
A CONJURED ITEM.
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE HE'S PLANNING TO ATTACK,
BUT IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT HE'S ATTEMPTING
TO CLOSE THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN US,
SO IT MUST BE A DEFENSIVE TOOL
THAT CAN BE UTILIZED
TO DRAW CLOSER TO AN ENEMY
AND COUNTERATTACK.
WE CAN LOWER THE RISK
IF WE KEEP OUR DISTANCE.
WE'LL WAIT FOR OUR CHANCE,
THEN STRIKE!
Chrollo: THIS OLD MAN
IS REALLY SOMETHING.
HE MANAGED TO READ MY MIND
IN AN INSTANT.
DOUBT I'D CAPTURE HIM ALIVE.
Silva: SO THE ABILITY DISAPPEARS
WHENEVER HE CLOSES THE BOOK.
IN ANY CASE, HE'S IMPRESSIVE.
HE'S DODGING
DAD'S ATTACKS BY A HAIR,
ALL WHILE KEEPING AN EYE ON ME.
HIS ATTACKS HAVE IMPROVED
SINCE LAST TIME,
SO WE DON'T HAVE ANY CLUE
WHAT HE'S CAPABLE OF.
IF WE WANT TO STOP HIM,
WE MAY JUST HAVE TO PAY
WITH OUR LIVES.
( Chrollo gasps )
Zeno: SILVA, DO IT NOW!
( chorus ends )
( laughs )
( Silva grunts )
( explosion )
♪
Narrator: A THUNDEROUS TREMOR
RIPPED THROUGH YORKNEW CITY.
KURAPIKA HAD NO IDEA
THAT THOSE SHOCK WAVES
WOULD LEAD
TO AN UNEXPECTED DEVELOPMENT.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE INTRODUCING
SHALNARK, A MEMBER OF THE TROUPE
WHO'S REALLY SMART,
KNOWLEDGEABLE, AND CUNNING.
Killua: HE CAN PUT A NEN ANTENNA
RIGHT ON HIS TARGETS
AND CONTROL THEM BY PHONE.
Both: BLACK VOICE!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"FAKE AND PSYCHE."
KOPITOR?
Killua: KOTORPI?
Gon: KORTOPI!