( Noggin Lugging Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Gon groans )
( Hisoka chuckles )
IT'S SO DELIGHTFUL.
I LOVE THAT LOOK.
Gon: BUT I'VE GOTTA SAY
IT WAS ACTUALLY
PRETTY EXCITING BACK THERE.
Kurapika: HUH?
Gon: I WAS SO SCARED THAT ALL
I WANTED TO DO WAS RUN AWAY,
BUT I COULDN'T,
'CAUSE I WAS EXCITED
AT THE SAME TIME.
ISN'T THAT WEIRD?
♪♪♪
( applicants panting )
Kurapika: LOOKS LIKE
WE MADE IT IN TIME.
Gon: BUT WHERE'S LEORIO?
( gasps )
THERE HE IS!
Leorio: MAN, THAT STINGS.
HOW THE HELL
DID I GET BEAT UP SO BADLY?
Both: HUH?
Leorio: MY MEMORY'S SO HAZY.
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
Kurapika: WE PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
TELL HIM WHAT HAPPENED.
Gon: YOU'RE RIGHT.
‐ Killua: GON.
‐ Gon: KILLUA!
Killua: I WAS STARTING TO THINK
YOU WEREN'T GONNA MAKE IT HERE
OR THAT YOU
DIDN'T MAKE IT AT ALL.
Gon: I JUST FOLLOWED
THE TRAIL OF LEORIO'S COLOGNE.
Gon: YOU TRACKED HIS SCENT?
THAT'S HOW?
MAN, GON, YOU REALLY
ARE WEIRD, AREN'T YOU?
Satotz:
EXCELLENT WORK, EVERYONE!
THE SECOND PHASE WILL TAKE PLACE
HERE IN THE VISCA FOREST PARK,
SO I SHALL NOW TAKE MY LEAVE.
I WISH YOU ALL
THE VERY BEST OF LUCK.
♪♪♪
( doors rumbling )
Woman: WILL ALL
OF THE APPLICANTS
WHO PASSED THE FIRST PHASE
PLEASE ENTER.
WELCOME, ALL!
I'M MENCHI, YOUR EXAMINER
FOR THE SECOND PHASE.
Buhara: AND LIKEWISE,
I'M BUHARA.
( stomach growls )
Applicant: HEY,
WHAT WAS THAT NOISE?
Menchi: SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE GETTING HUNGRY.
Buhara: NOT JUST HUNGRY.
I'M FAMISHED.
Menchi: WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THE SECOND PHASE...
( applicants murmuring )
Menchi: WILL BE COOKING!
Hanzo: WAIT. WE'RE COOKING?
Todo: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WE'RE COOKING?
WE CAME HERE
TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM.
Menchi: THAT'S RIGHT.
THE SECOND PHASE OF THE EXAM
WILL BE PREPARING A MEAL
THAT'LL SATISFY OUR PALATES.
Applicant:
WHY DO WE HAVE TO COOK?
Menchi: DON'T YOU KNOW?
IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
BECAUSE WE'RE GOURMET HUNTERS.
Todo: HUH? ( laughs )
( applicants laughing )
Todo: MAN,
TALK ABOUT A LETDOWN!
Applicant: YOU HEAR THAT?
THEY'RE GOURMET HUNTERS!
( laughter continues )
( Menchi groans )
Satotz: GOURMET HUNTERS
MENCHI AND BUHARA,
THEIR SELECTION AS EXAMINERS
COULD PROVE QUITE PROBLEMATIC.
ONLY 50 APPLICANTS LEFT,
BUT DEPENDING ON THE TASK,
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT FEWER THAN 10
WILL PASS THE SECOND PHASE.
Todo: SO YOU'RE
BOTH GOURMET HUNTERS.
AND WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU WANT US TO MAKE?
Menchi: BUHARA.
Buhara: TODAY'S REQUIRED
INGREDIENT WILL BE PORK.
Applicant: PORK?
YOU MEAN LIKE PIG MEAT?
Buhara: FEEL FREE TO USE MEAT
FROM ANY SPECIES OF PIG
IN VISCA FOREST.
AS YOU SEE, YOU'LL USE
THESE COOKING FACILITIES
TO PREP YOUR PORK DISHES.
TO PASS THE EXAM,
YOU MUST CREATE A DISH
TO SATISFY
OUR DISCRIMINATING PALATES.
Menchi: BUT WE WON'T
BE EVALUATING TASTE ALONE,
SO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY.
IS THAT CLEAR?
WHEN WE'VE BOTH EATEN OUR FILL,
THIS PORTION OF THE EXAM
WILL BE OVER.
Todo: OKAY, ENOUGH TALK.
LET'S JUST GET TO IT,
ALL RIGHT?
Buhara: LET THE EXAM'S
SECOND PHASE...
‐ ( boom )
‐ BEGIN!
♪♪♪
Menchi:
"ANY SPECIES OF PIG," HUH?
YOU'VE GOT A REAL
MEAN STREAK, DON'T YOU?
Buhara: WELL, YOU DID SAY
I GOT TO PICK THE INGREDIENT.
Menchi: THERE'S ONLY ONE SPECIES
OF PIG IN VISCA FOREST,
BUT YOU ALREADY KNEW THAT.
( Buhara chuckles )
I HOPE NOBODY GETS KILLED.
( overlapping chatter )
Hanzo: HEY! PIGGY!
Leorio: GOTTA CATCH
A PIG AND COOK IT, HUH?
MAN, THIS IS WAY EASIER
THAN THE FIRST PHASE.
Kurapika: I JUST HOPE
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
‐ Killua: AH.
‐ Kurapika: HUH?
Killua: YAHOO!
WHAAH!
UNH.
‐ Leorio: UNH!
‐ Kurapika: UNH!
Killua: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
Gon: I FOUND 'EM.
Leorio: PIGS!
( pigs squealing )
THEY'RE ALL CHEWING ON BONES.
Kurapika: DON'T TELL ME.
THEY'RE CARNIVORES?
( pig roars )
( Leorio yells )
( rumbling )
‐ Applicants: HUH?
Applicant: WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
( applicants yelling )
Leorio: THESE PIGS ARE INSANE!
‐ Buhara: THE GREAT STAMP...
‐ ( applicants groan )
Buhara: THE MOST FEROCIOUS PIG
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
THEY USE
THEIR LARGE, STURDY SNOUTS
TO SEND THEIR PREDATORS FLYING.
YOU'VE GOT TO MOVE REALLY QUICK
UNLESS YOU WANT TO END UP
THE MAIN COURSE
FOR THEIR DINNER.
( Todo roars )
WHAT?
♪♪♪
( Hanzo gasps )
( Gon yells )
( Great Stamp squeals )
Gon: WAIT A SECOND.
( yells )
( Great Stamp wails )
Killua: AH. THAT'S IT.
THEIR FOREHEADS
ARE THEIR WEAK SPOT.
‐ ( Leorio yelling )
‐ Kurapika: I SEE.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
THEY DEVELOPED TOUGH SNOUTS
TO PROTECT
THEIR DELICATE FOREHEADS.
♪♪♪
( Great Stamps wail )
( birds squawk )
Buhara: HUH? OHH!
( chuckles )
Menchi: LOOK AT THAT.
THEY SURE CAUGHT A LOT.
Satotz: HMM.
THIS IS AN EXCEPTIONAL BATCH
OF APPLICANTS INDEED.
BUT THE HARD PART
IS YET TO COME.
Todo: NOW EAT THE PIG,
AND SEND ME TO THE NEXT PHASE.
Menchi: OKAY. TIME TO JUDGE.
TASTE TESTING.
‐ ( Buhara chuckles )
‐ ( bell dings )
Todo: MM.
‐ ( buzzer )
‐ HUH?
Menchi: THE PORK'S OVERCOOKED.
IT'S WAY TOO TOUGH.
IT TOTALLY RUINS THE FLAVOR.
Todo: COME ON!
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN TRIED IT!
Menchi: I DON'T HAVE TO!
IT'S OBVIOUS!
( Todo groans )
Hanzo: THERE.
I HOPE YOU ENJOY IT.
( bell dings )
( buzzer )
( gasps ) BUT WHY?
Menchi: CHARRED AND DRY
ON THE OUTSIDE.
RAW ON THE INSIDE.
YOUR FIRE WAS WAY TOO HOT.
( bell dings )
( buzzer )
‐ ( bell dings )
‐ ( buzzer )
‐ ( buzzers continue )
‐ ( thinking ) HONESTLY,
THEY'RE ALL JUST ROASTING
THE ENTIRE PIG,
LIKE IT'S THE ONLY THING
THEY KNOW HOW TO DO.
NONE OF THEM HAVE
MADE ANY EFFORT AT ALL.
( buzzer )
Leorio: NOT ONE APPLICANT
HAS PASSED YET.
Kurapika: AND MENCHI HAS YET
TO TAKE A SINGLE BITE
OF ANYONE'S ENTRY.
Menchi: SERIOUSLY?!
CAN'T ANYONE OUT THERE
MAKE SOMETHING
THAT'LL SATISFY MY TASTE BUDS?
Kurapika: THAT'S IT!
THE SECOND PHASE
IS A COOKING TEST,
BUT THEY'RE JUDGING US BASED
ON ORIGINALITY AND OBSERVATION.
‐ Gon: HMM.
‐ Leorio: OH, I SEE.
( Buhara laughs )
Leorio: TELL ME
HOW MUCH YOU LOVE IT.
Menchi: IS THIS SUPPOSED
TO BE A KIDS MEAL?!
( Buhara laughs )
Gon: OKAY, MINE IS NEXT.
Menchi: IT'S JUST
LIKE THE LAST ONE!
( Buhara laughs )
Kurapika: THE NEXT ENTRY'S MINE,
READY TO BE JUDGED.
Menchi: WELL...
FINALLY SOMETHING
THAT RESEMBLES AN ACTUAL DISH.
( Kurapika thinking )
THE CHALLENGE IS TO UTILIZE
THE FACILITIES
AND INGREDIENTS PROVIDED
TO HIGHLIGHT
THE MAIN FEATURE, THE PORK.
IN SHORT,
THE TASTE IS INSIGNIFICANT.
Menchi: GROSS!
( Buhara laughs )
( Kurapika gasps )
Menchi: PRESENTATION
IS IMPORTANT,
BUT NOT AT THE EXPENSE
OF THE FLAVOR.
YOU'RE BASICALLY
NO BETTER THAN NUMBER 403!
( buzzer )
( Leorio laughs )
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME!
Kurapika:
"NO BETTER THAN 403," HUH?
( Buhara laughs )
THAT WAS SO MUCH FOOD.
I COULDN'T TAKE ANOTHER BITE.
Menchi: YEAH,
I'M PRETTY STUFFED MYSELF.
SO NONE OF YOU PASS
TO THE NEXT PHASE.
EXAM'S OVER!
‐ ( applicants muttering )
‐ Applicant: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Satotz: JUST AS I FEARED,
SHE'S REVERTED
TO HER BAD HABITS.
( cell phone beeps )
Secretary: WHAT SHOULD
WE DO NOW, CHAIRMAN?
Chairman:
I SUPPOSE I HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT'S TIME FOR A LITTLE OUTING.
♪♪♪
Kurapika: HMM?
( chuckles )
Applicant: NOBODY PASSED?
Second applicant: SERIOUSLY?
Third applicant:
DOES SHE REALLY MEAN THAT?
Fourth applicant:
WAIT. SO THE EXAM'S OVER?
Fifth applicant:
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
( crash )
Todo: THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
I WILL NOT ACCEPT THIS!
Menchi: SAY WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT YOU STILL FAILED.
Todo: SHUT THE HELL UP!
YOU ASKED FOR PORK,
AND WE GAVE IT TO YOU.
WE RISKED OUR LIVES JUST‐‐
Menchi: YOUR CHALLENGE
WAS TO PREPARE A PORK DISH
THAT BOTH EXAMINERS
WOULD FIND DELICIOUS,
AND NONE OF YOU
EVEN CAME CLOSE TO SUCCEEDING.
YOU ALL DID PRETTY MUCH
THE EXACT SAME THING.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE YOU DIDN'T
EVEN TRY TO FIGURE IT OUT!
AND WHEN IT LOOKED
LIKE YOU HAD TRIED,
IT WAS JUST FANCY PLATING
WITH NO FLAVOR TO BACK IT UP!
IT'S CLEAR THAT NONE OF YOU
TOOK THIS SERIOUSLY!
( Hanzo sighs )
YEAH, BUT COME ON, PORK?
NO MATTER HOW YOU COOK IT,
IT'S STILL JUST PORK.
Menchi: YOU WANNA
SAY THAT ONE MORE TIME?
IF I HEAR
ANY MORE CRAP FROM YOU,
I'LL SHOVE MY ARM UP YOUR ASS
AND KNOCK YOUR TEETH OUT!
‐ GOT IT?!
‐ ( Buhara thinking) HMM.
MENCHI'S TEMPER IS GETTING
THE BEST OF HER AGAIN.
BUT I GUESS IT'S NO SURPRISE.
THERE ARE ONLY
A FEW CHEFS IN THE WORLD
WHO ARE GOOD
ENOUGH TO SATISFY HER.
Menchi: I DARE YOU
TO SAY IT ONE MORE TIME!
SO AS I WAS SAYING,
NOT A SINGLE ONE OF YOU
HAS THE GUTS TO COOK ANYTHING
REMOTELY NEW OR INNOVATIVE.
Todo: HEY, SHUT UP!
I'M NOT HERE 'CAUSE I'M TRYING
TO BE SOME GOURMET COOK,
BUT A HUNTER!
Applicants: THAT'S RIGHT, TODO!
YOU TELL HER!
Todo: MY GOAL'S TO BECOME
A BLACK‐LIST HUNTER,
AND NO STUPID GOURMET HUNTER'S
GONNA TELL ME I CAN'T!
Menchi: THEN IT'S TOO BAD
THAT A "STUPID GOURMET HUNTER"
IS YOUR EXAMINER.
WELL, BETTER LUCK
NEXT YEAR, I GUESS.
Todo: EH? WHY, YOU‐‐
DON'T MESS WITH ME!
Menchi: BUHARA,
PLEASE DON'T INTERFERE.
Buhara: I'M SORRY,
BUT IT KINDA LOOKED LIKE
YOU WERE GONNA KILL HIM
IF I DIDN'T STEP IN.
( Menchi chuckles )
PROBABLY.
LET'S GET THIS STRAIGHT.
WE FREQUENTLY VENTURE INTO
THE DENS OF FEROCIOUS BEASTS
IN SEARCH
OF THE FINEST INGREDIENTS,
AND EVERY HUNTER IS PROFICIENT
IN AT LEAST SOME FORM
OF MARTIAL ART.
YOU LACK FOCUS AND THE WILL
TO EXPERIMENT WITH NEW THINGS,
AND THAT ALONE DISQUALIFIES YOU
ALL FROM BECOMING HUNTERS.
♪♪♪
( Chairman on loudspeaker )
WELL, THAT SAID,
IT SEEMS A BIT EXCESSIVE
TO FAIL EVERY SINGLE APPLICANT.
Applicant: THE SYMBOL
OF THE HUNTERS ASSOCIATION.
Second applicant: IT MUST BE
SOMEONE FROM THE EXAM COMMITTEE.
( applicants coughing )
( wooden getas clopping )
First applicant: HEY, WAIT.
WHO'S THE OLD MAN?
Menchi: HE IS THE HEAD
OF THE EXAM COMMITTEE,
AND HE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE HUNTER EXAM...
CHAIRMAN NETERO.
Netero: OH, I JUST WORK
BEHIND THE SCENES.
IT'S NOT ALL THAT IMPRESSIVE.
I ONLY INTERVENE IN THE EXAMS
WHEN LITTLE ISSUES
LIKE THIS ONE POP UP.
NOW, DEAR MENCHI...
Menchi: SIR!
Netero: IT'S COME
TO MY ATTENTION
THAT YOU'VE CHOSEN TO FAIL
ALL OF THIS YEAR'S APPLICANTS,
REASON BEING,
AS I UNDERSTAND IT,
THEIR GENERAL RELUCTANCE
TO CHALLENGE THE UNKNOWN.
Menchi: NO.
I'M SORRY, SIR, BUT I SNAPPED
WHEN A CANDIDATE
INSULTED GOURMET HUNTERS,
AND I'M AFRAID I MADE THE EXAM
HARDER THAN NECESSARY.
Netero: I SEE.
BUT IT SEEMS YOU'RE AWARE
THAT THIS EXAM
WAS COMPLETELY UNACCEPTABLE.
Menchi: YES. IT'S JUST
THAT I GET SO EMOTIONAL
WHEN FOOD IS INVOLVED.
I'M NOT SUITED
FOR THIS POSITION,
SO I MUST RESIGN AS EXAMINER.
PLEASE LET THEM
RETAKE THE SECOND PHASE.
Netero: SADLY, I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHERE WE'D BEGIN TO FIND
ANOTHER EXAMINER
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
Menchi:
MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES, SIR.
Netero: HOLD ON.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
YOU'LL CONTINUE SERVING
AS EXAMINER, BUT YOU YOURSELF
MUST PARTICIPATE
ALONGSIDE THIS YEAR'S APPLICANTS
IN COMPLETING
WHATEVER CHALLENGE YOU CHOOSE.
( Menchi gasps )
Netero: WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SOUND REASONABLE?
SURELY THAT WOULD
MAKE THE APPLICANTS
MORE COMFORTABLE
WITH THE RESULTS.
Menchi: I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I HAVE JUST THE THING
FOR THE NEW CHALLENGE.
WE'LL ALL BE MAKING BOILED EGGS.
Applicant: BOILED EGGS?!
Menchi: CHAIRMAN, SINCE I SEE
YOU BROUGHT YOUR AIRSHIP,
WOULD YOU MIND TAKING US ALL
TO SPLIT MOUNTAIN?
Netero: SPLIT MOUNTAIN?
OH, I SEE. YES, OF COURSE.
♪♪♪
Menchi: THIS IS IT.
TAKE A LOOK
AT WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
Applicant: W‐WHAT IS THAT?
Menchi: A SPIDER EAGLE'S WEB.
Gon: THEY BUILD THEIR WEBS
WAY DOWN THERE?
( Todo winces )
Menchi: LOOK PAST THE WEB
TO WHAT'S UNDERNEATH.
Gon: HEY, THOSE ARE...
Menchi: THOSE ARE
SPIDER EAGLE EGGS.
Netero: SPIDER EAGLES
BUILD THEIR WEBS
IN DEEP RAVINES LIKE THIS ONE.
IT HELPS PROTECT THEIR EGGS
FROM PREDATORS.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES
SPIDER EAGLE EGGS
ONE OF THE MOST DIFFICULT
INGREDIENTS TO OBTAIN.
ALSO THE EGGS ARE COMMONLY
KNOWN AS "DREAM EGGS."
Todo: HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
DO YOU MEAN‐‐
‐ Menchi: YOU BET I DO.
‐ Todo: EHH?
( applicants gasp )
Leorio: EVEN IF
SHE GRABS A FEW EGGS,
HOW'S SHE GONNA CLIMB BACK UP?
HEY! SHE JUMPED DOWN!
IS SHE TRYING
TO GET HERSELF KILLED?
‐ Kurapika: NO, SHE'S NOT.
‐ Leorio: EH?
♪♪♪
( wind gusting )
Killua: THAT LOOKS SO FUN.
Netero: THIS RAVINE HAS UPDRAFTS
THAT ARE CRUCIAL
TO THE SPIDER EAGLES.
ONCE THEY HATCH,
THE WIND CURRENTS
HELP GUIDE THEIR NEWBORN CHICKS
AS THEY FLY UP TO SAFETY.
Menchi: THERE.
NOW I JUST NEED TO BOIL IT,
AND I'LL BE SET.
Todo: YOU‐‐YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
YOU MEAN YOU REALLY EXPECT US
TO JUMP DOWN THERE?
THAT'S CRAZY!
Gon: I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THIS!
( laughs )
( Leorio whoops )
Hanzo: ALL RIGHT! I'M IN!
Menchi: WAIT!
I STILL HAVEN'T FINISHED
EXPLAINING EVERYTHING!
Applicant: HA HA! LATER!
Leorio: WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
Gon: HOLD ON! DON'T LET GO YET.
‐ Leorio: WHY? WHAT'S WRONG?
‐ Killua: NO WIND.
Kurapika: THE UPDRAFTS
DON'T HAPPEN ALL THE TIME.
( applicant gasps )
( screaming echoes )
Leorio: WHEN DO YOU THINK
THE NEXT ONE COMES ALONG?
Gon: ANY MINUTE NOW.
Leorio: OH, CRAP! WHAT THE?
Kurapika: IT APPEARS
THE WEB ISN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO SUPPORT ALL THIS WEIGHT.
Killua: GON, CAN WE GO YET?
Applicant: DAMN!
I CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER!
( all scream )
Leorio: IT'S ABOUT TO SNAP!
Gon: OKAY, NOW!
♪♪♪
Netero: AH.
( chuckles )
Menchi: WHAT ABOUT YOU GUYS?
I'M GUESSING YOU QUIT?
Netero: CONCEDING
TAKES COURAGE, TOO.
( Hanzo gobbling )
UNBELIEVABLE!
THIS IS WAY BETTER
THAN THEY SELL IN THE STORE!
( applicants murmuring )
Kurapika: I CAN SEE
WHY THEY'RE CALLED DREAM EGGS.
‐ Gon: HEY, MR. TODO!
‐ Todo: HUH?
Gon: THIS EGG'S REALLY GOOD.
YOU WANNA TRY IT?
( Todo gasps )
IT'S DELICIOUS.
Menchi: THE JOY OF DISCOVERING
SOMETHING DELICIOUS.
AND NOW YOU KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
THAT FEELING IS WHAT
WE RISK OUR LIVES FOR.
( Todo growls )
I LOST FAIR AND SQUARE.
NEXT YEAR, I'LL BE BACK.
( Gon laughs )
Narrator: THE APPLICANTS
HAVE LEARNED A VALUABLE LESSON.
WHETHER BLACK LIST OR GOURMET,
NO ONE COMES
BY THE TITLE OF HUNTER EASILY.
IT REQUIRES A STAGGERING AMOUNT
OF DETERMINATION.
ONLY 42 CANDIDATES REMAIN.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"SHOWDOWN ON THE AIRSHIP."
HEY, USE SOAP
WHEN YOU WASH YOUR HANDS!
Killua: UH, RIGHT!
♪♪♪