♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( beast roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
Man: IS GON STILL ANGLING
FOR THE MASTER OF THE SWAMP?
( woman gasps )
UH, YES.
HE'S BEEN AT IT NONSTOP
FOR A WHOLE WEEK NOW.
Man #2: SO I GOTTA KNOW.
DID YOU REALLY PROMISE
HE COULD TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM
IF HE CAUGHT THE THING?
Man #1: HE'S A FOOL.
FIVE ADULTS WORKING TOGETHER
COULDN'T REEL THAT MONSTER IN,
SO WHAT CHANCE
DOES A LITTLE KID HAVE, EH?
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE MITO
DOESN'T REALLY WANT HIM
TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM AT ALL.
Man #2: MAYBE SO,
BUT WASN'T GON'S OLD MAN HIS AGE
WHEN HE CAUGHT
THE MASTER OF THE SWAMP?
( man #1 laughs )
HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE.
( Gon gasps )
YEAH!
AH, YES! HERE HE COMES!
( grunting )
( yelps )
( yells )
( yelling )
( laughs )
Man: LOOK AT THE SIZE OF IT!
THAT'S THE MASTER OF THE SWAMP?
Man #2: WOW! IT'S BEEN 20 YEARS.
Man #3: YEAH,
AND IT WAS GON'S DAD
WHO CAUGHT HIM LAST TIME, RIGHT?
Man #4: LIKE FATHER, LIKE SON.
Man #5: GON REALLY DID IT.
HE ACTUALLY CAUGHT THE MASTER.
MITO, OVER HERE!
Gon: AUNT MITO, LOOK!
I CAUGHT HIM
JUST LIKE I SAID I WOULD.
THAT MEANS I CAN FINALLY
TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM, RIGHT?
( Mito sighs )
Gon: I'LL DO MY BEST.
I'M GONNA BE A HUNTER.
JUST YOU WAIT AND SEE!
Woman: IT MUST BE IN HIS BLOOD.
GING WAS ONLY 12 YEARS OLD
WHEN HE CAUGHT THE MASTER,
AND NO ONE HAS BEEN ABLE
TO LAND HIM SINCE.
AND NOW HIS SON HAS ACCOMPLISHED
THE VERY SAME FEAT
AT THE SAME AGE.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT HIS EYES SPARKLE
THE SAME WAY AS HIS FATHER'S.
IT WON'T BE LONG NOW
BEFORE WE HAVE TO LET HIM GO.
Mito: ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
Gon: YEAH.
Mito: WHEN YOU WERE JUST A BABY,
YOUR FATHER ABANDONED YOU
TO BE A HUNTER.
YOU KNOW THAT, DON'T YOU?
Gon: I DO.
Mito: HE CHOSE BEING A HUNTER
OVER HIS OWN SON.
Gon: YEAH, ISN'T THAT AMAZING?
Mito: HUH?
Gon: IT MUST BE AN AWESOME JOB
IF IT WAS WORTH LEAVING HIS KID,
DON'T YOU THINK?
Mito: BEING A HUNTER IS
A DANGEROUS JOB!
YOU COULD DIE AT ANY TIME
FOR ANY NUMBER
OF RIDICULOUS REASONS!
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
Gon: NO, I DON'T.
BUT I WANT TO UNDERSTAND!
I WANT TO FIND OUT WHY IT
WAS SO IMPORTANT TO MY DAD!
THAT'S WHY I'VE GOTTA DO IT!
( Mito chuckles )
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE GING.
♪♪♪
Gon: I PROMISE YOU
I'LL PASS THE EXAM.
THE NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME,
I WILL BE A HUNTER.
Mito: INSTEAD,
PROMISE YOU'LL COME HOME SAFE.
THINK YOU CAN DO THAT FOR ME?
Gon: YEP! I SURE CAN!
Both: PINKY SWEAR, SO IF I LIE,
STICK A THOUSAND NEEDLES
IN MY EYE.
AND SEAL IT WITH A...
KISS!
Gon: ...IIIISS!
( laughs )
HUH? ( yelps )
Mito: GON.
Gon: AUNT MITO, THANK YOU.
( sea crane calling )
♪♪♪
( islanders chattering )
Man: GOOD LUCK, GON!
Man #2: GET OUT THERE,
AND KNOCK 'EM DEAD!
DO YOU HEAR ME?!
WE BELIEVE IN YOU, BUDDY!
Gon: THANKS, EVERYBODY!
I'M GONNA BE THE BEST HUNTER
IN THE WORLD!
AND AS SOON AS I
MAKE THAT HAPPEN, I'LL BE BACK!
I'LL SEE YOU ALL AGAIN!
( man laughs )
THE BEST HUNTER
IN THE WORLD, HUH? HO!
KID THINKS THIS'LL BE EASY.
Man #2: EVERY SINGLE YEAR,
MILLIONS OF THE WORLD'S
MOST SKILLED APPLICANTS
APPLY FOR THE HUNTER EXAM,
BUT ONLY A HANDFUL MAKE THE CUT.
BE CAREFUL ABOUT SAYING STUFF
YOU CAN'T BACK UP, KID.
( men laugh )
Man #3: WHAT YOU DOING, KATZO?
Man #4: WITH THE WAY
THINGS ARE GOING FOR YOU,
YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA MAKE IT AS A SAILOR.
( sailors laugh )
Katzo: WHOA!
‐ ( sailors laugh )
‐ Man #4: WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY YOU BENT OVER LIKE THAT?
Captain: HEY, SLACKERS!
GET BACK TO WORK!
Both: AYE, AYE, SIR!
( Katzo groaning )
Captain: YOU...
GOT WAX IN YOUR EARS?
GET MOVING!
Katzo: AYE, AYE, SIR!
RIGHT AWAY!
Gon: WAIT!
( Katzo gasps )
THANKS A LOT.
( sea cranes squawking )
THERE'S A STORM COMING.
Captain: EH? AND HOW EXACTLY
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
Gon: SEA CRANES. THAT'S WHAT
ALL OF THEM ARE SAYING.
Captain: WHAT?
Gon: ALSO...
( sniffs )
THERE'S A REALLY BIG ONE
HEADING RIGHT FOR US!
Captain: EH?
Gon: IT'S TRUE!
I CAN TELL BY THE WAY IT SMELLS!
( Captain thinking )
THIS BOY...
HMM?
THOSE EYES. COULD HE BE...
♪♪♪
( thunder crashing )
( all yell )
Sailor: CAPTAIN, THE MAST
WON'T HOLD OUT FOR MUCH LONGER!
‐ WE SHOULD LOWER THE SAILS!
‐ Captain: DON'T BE STUPID!
WE CAN'T QUIT WHEN THE FUN'S
JUST ABOUT TO START.
( chuckles )
HERE WE GO.
NOW TAKE HER HARD TO PORT!
LET'S FLY!
♪♪♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
( sailors groaning )
( Captain sighs )
I'VE FACED BIGGER WAVES
THAN THAT AND LIVED.
HEY! TAKE OVER THE HELM.
Sailor: AYE, AYE, SIR!
( gulps )
Captain: DAMNED IF THIS AIN'T
THE MOST WORTHLESS CREW
I'VE SEEN IN YEARS.
( passengers groaning )
Captain: NOT A ONE OF 'EM'S
GOT HIS SEA LEGS. PATHETIC.
AND THEY THINK
THEY CAN PASS THE HUNTER EXAM?
THEY'RE GOOD FOR A LAUGH.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
‐ Gon: HERE. TRY THESE HERBS.
‐ Captain: HMM?
Gon: CHEW 'EM UP REAL GOOD,
AND YOU'LL FEEL BETTER.
Man: W‐WATER.
Gon: SIT TIGHT. IT'S ON ITS WAY.
Captain: EHH. THAT BOY AGAIN.
MM.
‐ ( bite )
‐ Captain: HMM?
( man #2 groans )
THAT'S WHAT I CALL A SOUR APPLE.
( Captain thinking )
AH, I SEE.
SEEMS THERE ARE A FEW
WITH SOME IRON IN 'EM AFTER ALL.
‐ Katzo: COMIN' THROUGH!
‐ ( Captain groans )
Katzo: HERE. I GOT YOUR WATER.
Gon: THANK YOU.
THERE. DRINK UP.
Captain: MM. ( chuckles )
Gon: YOU'RE THE BEST.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP, MR. KATZO.
Captain: RIGHT, THEN.
GO DOWN THE LINE,
AND TELL ME ALL YOUR NAMES.
Gon: MY NAME'S GON!
Kurapika: I AM CALLED KURAPIKA.
Leorio: THE NAME IS LEORIO.
Captain: GOOD, GOOD.
NOW, WHY DO YOU BOYS
WANT TO BECOME HUNTERS?
Leorio: WHOA!
YOU'RE NOT AN EXAMINER,
SO WHAT'S WITH THE THIRD DEGREE?
Captain: JUST ANSWER
THE QUESTION, DUMMY.
Gon: I WILL!
BECAUSE MY DAD IS A HUNTER!
Captain: HMM?
Gon: BEING A HUNTER WAS
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IN THE WORLD TO MY DAD,
AND I WANT TO KNOW WHY.
THAT'S WHY I LEFT WHALE ISLAND!
( Captain thinking )
WHALE ISLAND?
SO IT IS HIM.
THIS IS GING'S SON.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE DAY
HAS COME AT LAST.
Leorio: HEY! KID!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL
THAT OLD GUY NOTHIN'!
Gon: BUT HE ASKED WHY I'M HERE.
IT'S NOT A SECRET.
Leorio: LOOK,
GET WITH THE PROGRAM.
IT'S US VERSUS HIM,
AND I AM NOT TELLING HIM
WHY I'M HERE.
Kurapika: I'M AFRAID
I AGREE WITH LEORIO.
Leorio: EH?
THAT'S MR. LEORIO TO YOU,
YOU BRAT!
SHOW A LITTLE RESPECT
FOR YOUR ELDERS!
Kurapika: BUT WHY NOT
DODGE THE QUESTION
BY SIMPLY OFFERING THE MAN
A PLAUSIBLE LIE?
Leorio: HEY, ARE YOU
EVEN LISTENING TO ME?!
Kurapika: HOWEVER, IT IS QUITE
SHAMEFUL TO RELY UPON DECEIT.
AS FOR ME, I CANNOT REVEAL
MY REASONS HERE.
I HAVE MY SHARE OF SECRETS,
DEEP SECRETS WHICH I DO NOT
INTEND TO EXPOSE AT THIS TIME.
THAT IS WHY
I WILL NOT ANSWER YOUR QUESTION.
Leorio: HEY,
I WAS TALKING TO YOU, PUNK!
Captain: SO BOTH OF YOU FLAT OUT
REFUSE TO ANSWER MY QUESTION.
HEY, KATZO.
Katzo: YES, WHAT IS IT, CAPTAIN?
Captain: GET AHOLD
OF THE EXAM COMMITTEE FOR ME.
LET 'EM KNOW WE GOT
TWO MORE DROPOUTS.
( both gasp )
Leorio: WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Captain: STILL HAVEN'T
FIGURED IT OUT, HUH?
YOU SEE, THE HUNTER EXAM
HAS ALREADY STARTED.
Both: IT HAS?
Captain: THERE ARE AS MANY
HUNTER WANNABES IN THIS WORLD
AS THERE ARE STARS IN THE SKY.
AND THE EXAMINERS, WELL,
FACT IS THEY DON'T HAVE THE TIME
NOR THE RESOURCES
TO GO THROUGH 'EM ALL.
THAT'S WHERE PEOPLE LIKE ME
COME IN TO PICK UP THE SLACK,
SCREEN ALL OF THE APPLICANTS,
AND TRIM THE FAT.
I'VE ALREADY NOTIFIED
THE COMMITTEE
ABOUT THE REST OF THE LOT.
NOT A ONE OF 'EM MADE THE CUT.
Leorio: WHAT?
Captain:
THAT WAS JUST A LITTLE STORM,
AND LOOK HOW THEY HANDLED IT.
THEY'D NEVER SURVIVE
THE LATER STAGES OF THE EXAM.
IN OTHER WORDS, THE ONLY WAY
YOU THREE ARE MOVING ON
TO THE NEXT PORTION OF THE EXAM
IS IF I GIVE YOU THE GO‐AHEAD.
SO I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN,
AND THINK CAREFULLY
BEFORE YOU ANSWER.
Gon: YOU CATCH ALL THAT?
( Leorio groans )
YOU COULD'VE
TOLD US THAT SOONER.
Kurapika: I AM THE SOLE SURVIVOR
OF THE KURTA CLAN.
FOUR YEARS AGO, MY ENTIRE CLAN
WAS ANNIHILATED
BY A BAND OF CRIMINALS.
THAT IS WHY I WANT
TO BECOME A HUNTER,
TO CAPTURE THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Captain: SOUNDS LIKE YOU WANT
TO BE A BLACK‐LIST HUNTER,
AND THE PHANTOM TROUPE
IS A CLASS‐A BOUNTY.
EVEN THE MOST SEASONED HUNTERS
CAN'T TOUCH 'EM.
YOU KNOW IT'S A SUICIDE MISSION,
RIGHT?
Kurapika: DEATH IS
NOT AMONG MY FEARS,
BUT THERE IS ONE THING I DO FEAR
AND ONE THING ALONE,
THAT TIME WILL QUIET
THE RAGE IN MY HEART.
Leorio: SO IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU'RE OUT FOR REVENGE.
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED
TO BECOME A HUNTER
JUST SO YOU CAN SETTLE
AN OLD SCORE, DO YOU?
Kurapika: THAT IS
THE STUPIDEST QUESTION
I HAVE EVER HEARD, LEORIO.
Leorio: THAT'S MR. LEORIO!
Kurapika: THERE ARE PLACES
ONLY HUNTERS CAN GO,
INTEL ONLY THEY CAN ACCESS,
ACTIONS ONLY THEY CAN TAKE.
THERE ARE MORE REASONS,
BUT THOSE ARE THE ONLY THREE
THAT YOU HAVE A CHANCE
OF COMPREHENDING.
‐ ( Leorio wails )
‐ Gon: HEY!
WHY DO YOU WANT TO BECOME
A HUNTER, MR. LEORIO?
Leorio: WHO, ME?
WELL, IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE,
REALLY.
‐ FOR THE MONEY.
‐ Gon: HUH?
Leorio: MONEY CAN BUY
EVERYTHING YOU'VE EVER WANTED,
A BIG MANSION,
A COOL CAR...
AND TOP‐SHELF BOOZE!
YEE‐HA!
Kurapika: IF ONLY YOU COULD
BUY CLASS AS WELL, LEORIO.
( Leorio groans )
THAT WAS STRIKE THREE.
STEP OUTSIDE.
TIME TO FINISH OFF
THE FILTHY KURTA BLOODLINE
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
Kurapika:
TAKE THAT BACK, LEORIO!
I SAID TAKE IT BACK.
Leorio: IT'S MR. LEORIO.
Captain: HEY, WHERE DO YOU BOYS
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
I'M NOT FINISHED WITH YOU YET!
‐ Gon: LET THEM GO.
‐ Captain: EH?
Gon: THEY'RE FINE.
IT'S LIKE AUNT MITO
TOLD ME ONCE.
Mito: YOU CAN NEVER
UNDERSTAND A PERSON
UNLESS YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
WHAT MAKES THEM ANGRY.
IT'S HOW
YOU GET TO KNOW SOMEONE.
Gon: SO WHATEVER THEY'RE
FEELING SO UPSET ABOUT
IS REALLY IMPORTANT TO THEM.
IT'S UP TO THEM NOW.
NOTHING WE CAN DO
BUT STAY OUT OF THE WAY.
‐ Sailor : CAPTAIN!
‐ Captain: HMM?
Sailor: LOOK. OVER THERE.
( Captain gasps )
Katzo: IF WE GET CAUGHT UP
IN THAT WATERSPOUT,
THE SHIP IS GONNA SINK FOR SURE.
Captain: GET THE SAILS
LOWERED NOW!
Katzo: RIGHT!
Gon: ANYTHING I CAN DO?
Katzo: YEAH!
FOLLOW ME UP ON DECK.
Captain: GO WITH 'EM.
I'LL TAKE THE HELM.
Sailor: AYE!
Captain: ALL RIGHT, THEN,
HARD TO STARBOARD!
Sailor #2: MOVE IT!
IF WE GET CAUGHT IN
THE WATERSPOUT, WE'RE DONE FOR!
( overlapping chatter )
♪♪♪
Kurapika: TAKE BACK
WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT MY CLAN!
I WILL FORGIVE YOU
IF YOU REPENT, LEORIO.
Leorio: YOU OWE ME AN APOLOGY,
AND I'M NOT TELLING YOU AGAIN.
I'M NOT REPENTING FOR ANYTHING,
HEAR ME?
Kurapika: VERY WELL.
‐ ( sailors groan )
‐ Katzo: WHOA!
Gon: MR. KATZO!
( Captain gasps )
Both: DAMN!
♪♪♪
Leorio: COME ON!
LET'S GET 'EM BACK ON DECK!
( Gon chuckles )
Leorio: YOU IDIOT!
IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR US,
YOU'D BE SHARK BAIT!
YOU OWE ME BIG TIME, KID,
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT!
Kurapika: HONESTLY,
HOW RECKLESS CAN YOU BE?
Gon: BUT IT'S FINE.
YOU CAUGHT ME.
‐ Leorio: UH...
‐ Kurapika: UH...
Gon: YOU BOTH DID.
YOU BOTH CAUGHT ME TOGETHER.
Leorio: I GUESS
YOU MIGHT HAVE A POINT.
Katzo: GON!
Gon: HEY, MR. KATZO.
Katzo: THANKS, GON.
YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE BACK THERE.
Gon: YEAH, WELL,
I DIDN'T DO IT ALL ALONE.
THOSE TWO OVER THERE
HELPED RESCUE YOU, TOO.
( both gasp )
Katzo: HE'S RIGHT.
THANK YOU BOTH.
Kurapika: PLEASE,
NO THANKS NECESSARY.
Leorio: YEAH, NO PROB.
WE'RE JUST GLAD
TO SEE YOU MADE IT OKAY.
Katzo: ME, TOO!
IN FACT, I OUGHT TO GET
BACK TO MY POST RIGHT AWAY.
( Leorio chuckles ) HMM?
( Kurapika chuckles )
Leorio: WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Kurapika: I'M EMBARRASSED
AT MY BEHAVIOR.
PARDON MY RUDENESS, MR. LEORIO.
( Leorio gasps )
I WASN'T EXPECTING THAT.
JUST FORGET IT.
YOU CAN DROP THE "MR."
LEORIO'S FINE.
I'M SORRY, TOO,
AND I TAKE BACK EVERYTHING
THAT I SAID TO YOU BEFORE.
THAT WAS WRONG OF ME.
Kurapika: NO, IT'S FINE.
( Captain laughs )
YOU THREE
ARE GROWING ON ME, SO...
I'LL MAKE SURE ALL THREE OF YOU
GET SAFELY DROPPED OFF
AT THE PORT
CLOSEST TO THE EXAM SITE.
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
( laughs )
Gon: YOU WILL?
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOUR TEST?
Captain: IT'S LIKE I SAID.
I DECIDE
WHO GOES ON TO TAKE THE EXAM.
CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU'RE ALL MOVING ON!
( Leorio chuckles )
Gon: ALL RIGHT!
( laughs )
Narrator: AND SO GON
FINALLY BEGAN HIS JOURNEY
TO DO WHAT HIS FATHER
DID BEFORE HIM,
TO BECOME A HUNTER.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"TEST OF TESTS."
DON'T MISS IT!
♪♪♪