Kurapika: CHAIN JAIL,
AN ABILITY I WILL USE
ONLY ON THE SPIDERS...
A POWER TO CAPTURE
AND RESTRAIN
THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
I'VE SWORN TO USE IT
FOR NO OTHER PURPOSE.
IF I BREAK MY VOW,
IF I SHOULD USE THIS TECHNIQUE
ON ANYONE OTHER THAN A SPIDER...
‐ ( heart beating )
‐ MY LIFE IS FORFEIT.
I WOULD DIE INSTANTLY...
A SELF‐IMPOSED CONDITION
AND A CONTRACT WITH MYSELF,
THE PROOF OF MY RESOLVE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( car engine thrumming )
Narrator: AFTER USING CHAIN JAIL
TO CAPTURE UVOGIN,
KURAPIKA AND THE OTHERS
FLEE THE SCENE BY CAR.
( tires squeal )
Basho: THERE'S A CAR
COMING UP BEHIND US.
CAN ANYONE CONFIRM?
Dalzollene: YOU'RE RIGHT.
THINK IT'S THEM?
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT A TAIL.
STEP ON IT!
Kurapika: A TAIL? BUT HOW?
UNLESS...
♪
A THREAD! IT'S MADE OF NEN.
Melody: SOMETHING'S ATTACHED
TO HIS LEFT CALF.
RIGHT THERE!
Squala: DAMN!
( Machi gasps )
THEY FOUND IT.
Feitan: FASTER THAN EXPECTED.
Shalnark: DON'T WORRY.
ALMOST GOT 'EM.
Nobunaga: OH, WHATEVER.
LOOK, WHY ARE WE ALL STUFFED
IN THIS TINY CAR?
Feitan: JUST A BIT LONGER
♪
( Nobunaga groans )
( tires squeal )
( footsteps )
WHAT THE HELL?! HEY!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
( Owl gasps )
YOU GUYS ARE
NO AVERAGE JOES, ARE YOU?
YOU'RE FAST. I'LL GIVE YOU THAT,
FAST ENOUGH TO OPEN THE DOOR
AND ESCAPE IN THE NICK OF TIME.
I'D BETTER STAY ON GUARD.
Feitan: NOBUNAGA WAS
IN A BAD POSITION.
Machi: THAT ABILITY OF YOURS
IS FASCINATING.
Nobunaga: LET ME OUT, DAMN IT!
Shizuku: SO ANYTHING
THAT YOU WRAP UP
IN THAT CLOTH GETS SHRUNKEN.
THAT'S THE PERFECT ACCESSORY
FOR THEFT.
Machi: WITH IT,
ALL OF THE AUCTION MERCH
WOULD FIT RIGHT IN HIS POCKET.
Shalnark: SO HE'S THE ONE
WHO TOOK ALL THE MERCHANDISE
FROM THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
IT ALSO MEANS HE CAN TURN THEM
BACK TO THEIR ORIGINAL SIZE.
Shizuku: IF I
REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
THE BOSS SAID HIS NAME IS OWL.
( whoosh )
( Feitan gasps )
SEEMS HIS FRIENDS
HAVE COME TO HELP.
Machi: YEAH.
♪
( Owl chuckles )
Shalnark: THERE'S MORE
THAN I WAS EXPECTING.
Shadow Beast:
WHO THE HELL ARE THESE GUYS?
THEY CAN'T ACTUALLY BE
THE PHANTOM TROUPE, CAN THEY?
Owl: OH, YEAH.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
Shadow Beast: IT'S JUST
THAT THEY LOOK SO WEAK.
Shizuku: ONE, TWO, THREE...
HOLD ON.
Shalnark: WHAT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
Shizuku: THERE ARE
10 SHADOW BEASTS IN ALL,
AREN'T THERE? AND UVO TOOK
CARE OF FOUR OF THEM BY HIMSELF,
SO THIS SHOULD BE
ALL OF THEM, RIGHT?
Feitan: HOW ODD.
THE CHAIN USER GRABBED UVO
BEFORE ESCAPING BY CAR.
Machi: SO DOES THAT MEAN
THE CHAIN USER
ISN'T A SHADOW BEAST?
Feitan: WELL, WE WILL FIND OUT
ONCE WE ASK THEM.
Shizuku: DO WE NEED
TO KEEP THEM ALIVE?
Feitan: NOT ALL OF THEM.
WE ONLY NEED THE OWL.
Machi: FINE.
THEN LET ME HANDLE IT.
Shadow Beast: THOSE DAMN BRATS,
TALKING SMACK
LIKE IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
LET'S SHOW 'EM WHAT
THE SHADOW BEASTS ARE MADE OF.
Shalnark: WELL,
YOU HEARD THE MAN.
Feitan: YOU STAY THERE,
AND WATCH.
I'LL TAKE THREE, AND, SHIZUKU...
Shizuku: THOSE TWO.
Shadow Beast: LET'S DO THIS!
Owl: TAKE IT EASY!
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE THEIR POWER!
Shadow Beast: OH, SHUT UP!
♪
( tires squeal )
Basho: WE LOST THEM, I THINK,
BUT FOR A SPLIT SECOND,
I THOUGHT I SAW SOMEONE
LANDING ON THEIR CAR.
Dalzollene: PROBABLY
THE OTHER SHADOW BEASTS.
LET'S GET BACK TO THE CITY.
NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
Kurapika: ROGER THAT.
Melody: WE'LL SWITCH
THE LOCATION TO PATTERN C.
AND WE DON'T WANT
THIS ONE PUTTING UP A FIGHT,
SO WE'LL NEED MUSCLE RELAXANTS
AND SLEEPING GAS PREPARED
JUST IN CASE.
Kurapika: I HOPE
THOSE WILL WORK.
Machi: ONE MOVE,
AND YOU'LL GET CUT.
( Owl gasps )
Shizuku: ALL DONE.
WHAT ABOUT THE BODIES?
Feitan: LEAVE THEM.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN HIDING THEM NOW.
Shalnark: WOW, VERY NICE.
WELL, I'M THINKING
MAYBE WE SHOULD FREE NOBUNAGA
BEFORE WE START
TORTURING THIS GUY.
‐ Machi: WAIT A SECOND.
‐ Shalnark: HMM?
Machi: SO THEN WHAT
ARE WE DOING WITH THE OWL?
ARE WE GONNA TAKE THE CAR?
LET'S LEAVE NOBUNAGA AS IS
SO THERE'S ENOUGH ROOM
FOR THE REST OF US.
Nobunaga: SCREW THAT!
LET ME OUT!
Shizuku: I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BE ALL CRAMPED IN THERE.
‐ Nobunaga: COME ON, YOU GUYS!
‐ Shalnark: HEY!
IS THERE ANY WAY YOU CAN
JUST LET THE CAR OUT OF THE BAG?
Owl: NO. THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
‐ Nobunaga: LET ME OUT, DAMN IT!
‐ Machi: TOO BAD.
Shalnark: I SUPPOSE
IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
Nobunaga: YOU GODDAMN JERKS!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT, HUH?!
Feitan: TROUPE MEMBERS
DON'T SNAP AT EACH OTHER.
Nobunaga: YOU SHUT UP!
Feitan: ANYWAY, THIS ABILITY
COULD COME IN HANDY FOR OUR JOB.
Nobunaga: WHO CARES?! I'M GONNA
CUT THIS GUY TO SHREDS!
Feitan: NOT YET.
FIRST HE IS GOING TO TELL US
WHERE THE TREASURE IS.
Shalnark: SO FEITAN'S GOING
TO USE HIS TORTURE SKILLS?
YOU'VE GOT TERRIBLE LUCK.
( Nobunaga groans )
DAMN IT!
Dalzollene: HEY, WAKE UP!
♪
I'M SURE YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL US WHERE
YOU HID THAT STOLEN MERCHANDISE.
Uvogin: DOES ANYBODY
KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS?
‐ ( Kurapika gasps )
‐ Basho: HUH?
Uvogin: HOW LONG
HAVE I BEEN ASLEEP?
Dalzollene: SOUNDS LIKE YOU
DON'T UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION.
YOU SEE...
I ASK THE QUESTIONS HERE!
♪
( all gasping )
Kurapika:
WHAT INCREDIBLE WILLPOWER.
HE KNOWS HE'S
ABOUT TO BE TORTURED,
YET THERE'S NOT EVEN
THE SLIGHTEST HINT
OF APPREHENSION
IN THE AURA SURROUNDING HIM.
HIS UNFLINCHING SPIRIT
IS WHAT'S BEHIND
HIS SEEMINGLY INVINCIBLE BODY,
AS WELL
AS THE SOURCE OF HIS AURA.
HE'S THE PRODUCT
OF COUNTLESS BATTLES.
♪
Dalzollene:
I ASK THE QUESTIONS HERE!
( gasps )
Kurapika:
WHAT INCREDIBLE WILLPOWER.
HE KNOWS HE'S
ABOUT TO BE TORTURED,
YET THERE'S NOT EVEN
THE SLIGHTEST HINT
OF APPREHENSION
IN THE AURA SURROUNDING HIM.
HIS UNFLINCHING SPIRIT
IS WHAT'S BEHIND
HIS SEEMINGLY INVINCIBLE BODY,
AS WELL
AS THE SOURCE OF HIS AURA.
HE'S THE PRODUCT
OF COUNTLESS BATTLES.
Uvogin: CAN I MOVE?
NO.
THAT'S PROBABLY
GONNA TAKE A WHILE LONGER.
I ATE DINNER AT ABOUT 8:00.
MY STOMACH'S TELLING ME
IT'S AROUND MIDNIGHT NOW.
( Squala gasps )
Uvogin: LET'S MAKE A DEAL,
SHALL WE?
( Squala gasps )
Uvogin:
YOU RELEASE ME RIGHT NOW,
AND I'LL SPARE
ALL OF YOUR LIVES.
( Squala gasps )
HEY, WHAT IS HE SAYING?
HE CRAZY OR WHAT?
‐ Melody: HE'S SERIOUS...
‐ ( Squala gasps )
OR HE SEEMS TO BE.
Squala: HE IS?
BUT THAT'S INSANE.
Basho: HE'S THE ONE
THAT SHOULD BE BEGGING
FOR HIS LIFE RIGHT NOW.
Uvogin: NOW LET ME
MAKE THIS CRYSTAL CLEAR.
WE'RE AFTER
THE AUCTION MERCHANDISE
THAT WAS STORED UNDERGROUND.
IF YOU GUYS
DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS,
THEN I'VE GOT
NO BUSINESS WITH YOU.
Basho: WHAT?!
Melody: JUST WAIT A MOMENT.
SO YOU DIDN'T STEAL
ALL THE MERCHANDISE?
Uvogin: THE VAULT WAS EMPTY
WHEN WE GOT THERE.
I GUESS THE SHADOW BEASTS
HAD ALREADY TAKEN ALL OF IT.
IT MAKES SENSE
THAT THEY DIDN'T STOP TO THINK
ABOUT TELLING GRUNTS LIKE YOU.
( Squala gasps )
Melody: I THINK THAT
HE'S TELLING US THE TRUTH.
( Squala gasps )
WAIT. THEN HE'S SERIOUS?
SO HE WASN'T BLUFFING WHEN HE
OFFERED TO MAKE US A DEAL?
( wails )
( Uvogin chuckles )
EVERYONE MAKES MISTAKES,
RIGHT?
NOW YOU KNOW
WE HAVEN'T STOLEN ANYTHING YET,
SO JUST TAKE THESE THINGS OFF,
AND TURN A BLIND EYE
TO WHAT WE'RE ABOUT TO DO.
IF YOU DO THAT,
THEN I'LL LET YOU LIVE.
Kurapika: WHAT ABOUT THE GUESTS?
Uvogin: WHAT GUESTS?
Kurapika: THE GUESTS WHO WERE
PRESENT IN THE AUCTION HALL.
OUR COLLEAGUES
WERE AMONG THE CROWD.
ANSWER ME.
♪
Uvogin: I SEE.
REALLY SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
THEY'RE DEAD. THAT WAS
THE PLAN FROM THE BEGI‐‐
( both gasp )
Kurapika: HOW MANY PEOPLE
DID YOU MURDER?!
HOW MANY DIED
FOR YOUR SELFISH PLAN?!
Basho: KURAPIKA! STOP!
HEY, KNOCK IT OFF!
Dalzollene: IF THE MERCHANDISE
IS IN SAFE HANDS,
WE HAVE NO USE FOR HIM.
WE'LL JUST HAND HIM OVER
TO THE COMMUNITY.
Uvogin: SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE NOT ACCEPTING MY OFFER.
♪
( Machi gasps )
( Nobunaga growling )
Machi: HEY, DID YOU LEARN WHERE
ALL THE AUCTION MERCHANDISE‐‐
Nobunaga: SHUT UP!
GO ASK FEITAN!
( Owl breathing slowly )
Machi: DID HE
TELL YOU WHERE IT IS?
Feitan: IT WAS NO FUN AT ALL.
I HAD BARELY GOTTEN STARTED
WHEN HE GAVE IT UP.
Machi: OH. SO THAT'S IT.
Hisoka: AH, RIGHT. I'M SUPPOSED
TO MEET SOMEONE TODAY.
I'LL BE LEAVING FOR A BIT.
Boss: SURE. GO AHEAD,
AS LONG AS YOU'RE BACK
BY 6:00 P. M. TOMORROW.
UP TO NO GOOD, HISOKA?
Hisoka: OF COURSE I AM.
♪
Kurapika: DAMN IT.
( gasps )
( sighs )
( cell phone buzzing )
"MEET AS PROMISED
AT THE AGREED‐UPON PLACE"?
( breathes deeply )
Feitan: HEY, WHERE IS SHALNARK?
Machi: HE CALLED IN
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
HE SAID THAT HE
FINALLY SUCCEEDED
IN LOCATING
A MAFIA COMMUNITY ROOM.
♪
Dalzollene: THIS IS DALZOLLENE
OF THE NOSTRADE FAMILY.
WE'VE CAPTURED
ONE OF THE THIEVES
WHO ATTACKED THE AUCTION
AND WOULD LIKE
TO HAND HIM OVER TO YOU.
Man: REALLY?
HOW'D YOU MANAGE THAT?
Dalzollene:
I'LL FILL YOU IN LATER.
Man: VERY IMPRESSIVE.
EVEN THE SHADOW BEASTS
COULDN'T DO THAT.
Dalzollene: THE SHADOW BEASTS?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Man: YEAH.
IN FACT, THEY'RE ALL DEAD.
ALL OF THEM?
Man: WELL,
WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
OKAY, GOT IT.
Dalzollene: PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO HURRY.
Man: RIGHT. WE'LL BE SURE
TO BRING OUR BEST PEOPLE.
♪
Squala: I GAVE HIM
THREE CANISTERS
OF MUSCLE‐RELAXANT GAS.
Dalzollene: UNDERSTOOD.
SOME MEN FROM THE COMMUNITY
WILL BE HERE SHORTLY.
I'LL WATCH OVER HIM
'TIL THEY GET HERE,
SO EVERYONE GET SOME REST.
‐ Basho: RIGHT.
‐ Squala: RIGHT.
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
( footsteps shuffling )
( card flutters )
( Kurapika gasps )
Hisoka: EARLY, AREN'T YOU?
Kurapika: HE'S NOT USING IN.
Hisoka: DON'T LOOK SO WORRIED.
I'VE NO INTEREST
IN FIGHTING YOU NOW.
Kurapika: THEN LET'S
JUST GET RIGHT TO THE POINT.
THE TROUPE, TELL ME EVERYTHING
YOU KNOW ABOUT THEM.
Hisoka: OH, COME NOW. ALREADY?
I DO JUST ADORE IDLE CHITCHAT.
( chuckles )
THERE ARE 13 SPIDERS IN ALL,
EACH IDENTIFIABLE BY
THEIR NUMBERED SPIDER TATTOOS.
MEMBERS CAN BE REPLACED
AT A MOMENT'S NOTICE.
AN APPLICANT NEED ONLY
DEFEAT A CURRENT MEMBER
IN ORDER TO JOIN.
IF THE TROUPE LOSES ONE
FOR OTHER REASONS,
IT FALLS TO THE BOSS
TO FILL THE VACANCY.
WELL, TO BE HONEST,
THEY MAINLY STEAL AND KILL,
THOUGH THEY DO DABBLE
IN PHILANTHROPY.
Kurapika: THAT MUCH,
I KNOW ALREADY.
Hisoka: WHAT YOU
MIGHT NOT KNOW ALREADY
IS THAT I REPLACED NUMBER FOUR
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
Kurapika: FOR WHAT PURPOSE?
Hisoka: I WANTED
THE CHANCE TO FIGHT THE BOSS.
Kurapika: THE BOSS?
BUT WHY WOULD YOU WANT THAT?
Hisoka: BECAUSE HE'S POWERFUL.
Kurapika: YOU WANTED
TO TEST YOUR STRENGTH?
THAT WAS YOUR ONLY REASON?
Hisoka: WHO KNOWS? IT‐‐IT‐‐
IT JUST GETS ME SO EXCITED.
EVEN THE MERE THOUGHT OF
FIGHTING THE BOSS TURNS ME ON.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
I HAVEN'T HAD THE CHANCE YET.
HE NEVER LOWERS HIS GUARD.
HE'S WITH AT LEAST
TWO OTHERS AT ALL TIMES.
AND AS SOON AS A JOB ENDS,
HE VANISHES INSTANTLY
AND WITHOUT A TRACE.
SO I BELIEVE YOU AND I
CAN HELP EACH OTHER.
DON'T YOU THINK
OUR GOALS ARE TOO DIFFICULT
TO ACHIEVE ALL BY OURSELVES?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
Hisoka: I CAN TELL YOU
THE TROUPE MEMBERS' ABILITIES.
THERE ARE SEVEN WHOSE POWERS
I ALREADY KNOW ABOUT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE WORK TOGETHER?
♪
‐ ( intercom buzzes )
‐ ( Dalzollene gasps )
YES, WE'RE ON FLOOR B2.
( elevator chimes )
FOLLOW ME.
Phinks: YOU HAVEN'T
KILLED HIM YET, HAVE YOU?
Dalzollene: NO. THIS WAY.
WE COULDN'T
GET A NEEDLE INTO HIM,
WHICH MEANT WE HAD TO
PARALYZE HIM WITH GAS INSTEAD.
Uvogin:
CLOTHES REALLY MAKE THE MAN.
Dalzollene: HUH?
( gagging )
Phinks: I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT
WHEN I HEARD.
NEVER PEGGED YOU AS THE TYPE
TO GET YOURSELF KIDNAPPED.
( Uvogin chuckles )
Shizuku: IT'S TIME
FOR WORK, BLINKY.
( Blinky chuckles )
Shizuku: NOW GET IN THERE
AND SUCK OUT ALL THE POISON
THAT'S PARALYZING UVO.
( Blinky growls )
Shizuku: OKAY, ALL DONE.
( Uvogin sighs )
DAMN IT!
I'M GONNA FIND THAT CHAIN USER,
AND WHEN I DO,
I'M GONNA MAKE HIM PAY FOR THIS!
Melody: EVERYONE, WAKE UP!
WHERE IS HE?!
Shalnark: I THINK
HE JUST RAN AWAY.
Shizuku: IT'S PROBABLY
BECAUSE YOU WERE SO DARN LOUD.
Phinks: WE'RE HEADING BACK.
OUR JOB HERE'S DONE.
Machi: WE TOOK CARE
OF THE SHADOW BEASTS.
Shalnark: OH, YEAH,
AND WE GOT THE TREASURE, TOO.
‐ Uvogin: NO!
‐ Shizuku: HUH?
Uvogin: YOU TELL THE BOSS...
I'M NOT LEAVING.
I CAN'T GO BACK
UNTIL I SETTLE THE SCORE
WITH THAT DAMN CHAIN USER!
♪
Narrator: UVOGIN HAS BEEN
FREED FROM HIS BONDS,
AND KURAPIKA, HAVING JUST BEEN
INVITED TO TEAM UP WITH HISOKA,
IS COMPLETELY UNAWARE.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE
INTRODUCING DALZOLLENE,
LEADER OF NEON'S BODYGUARDS.
Killua: MUST BE A REAL DRAG
TAKING CARE
OF THAT SELFISH BRAT.
Gon: I KNOW. TAKING CARE
OF YOU IS A REAL DRAG.
Killua: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, YOU LITTLE‐‐
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"CHASING AND WAITING."
HEY, KILLUA, LET'S PLAY
DROP THE HANDKERCHIEF, OKAY?
I'LL DROP IT,
AND YOU SIT AND WAIT.
Killua: THAT'S NOT
A TWO‐PLAYER GAME, IDIOT!