( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Gon grunting )
Kurapika: WE ENTERED
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
BROKE DOWN THE WALL,
AND FROM THERE,
WE SNUCK
INTO THE SHORT AND EASY ONE.
EVEN UNDER PRESSURE,
YOU WERE ABLE
TO CALMLY ASSESS OUR OPTIONS
AND THINK OF A WAY
TO GET AROUND THEM,
AND THAT IS WHAT
MAKES YOU SO SPECIAL.
♪
Narrator: ONE BY ONE,
EACH OF THE 24 APPLICANTS
WHO PASSED THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM
EXITED TRICK TOWER,
EAGER FOR A LONG‐AWAITED
BREATH OF FRESH AIR.
♪
( Gon gasps )
( Leorio chuckles )
‐ Gon: HUH?
‐ ( Tonpa chuckles )
Lippo: CONGRATULATIONS ON
ESCAPING TRICK TOWER, EVERYONE.
ALL THAT REMAIN NOW
ARE THE FOURTH PHASE
AND THE FINAL PHASE.
Hanzo: ONLY TWO MORE.
Lippo: THE FOURTH PHASE
WILL TAKE PLACE
RIGHT OVER THERE
ON ZEVIL ISLAND.
NOW LET'S PROCEED.
( snaps fingers )
( applicants murmuring )
Lippo TO BEGIN WITH, I WILL NEED
EACH OF YOU TO DRAW LOTS NOW.
Geretta: REALLY?
Pokkle: DRAW LOTS FOR WHAT?
WHAT'LL THAT DECIDE?
( Lippo chuckles )
WHO YOU HUNT AND WHO HUNTS YOU.
IN THIS BOX
ARE EXACTLY 24 NUMBERED CARDS,
WHICH MEANS
THAT ONE OF THE NUMBERED CARDS
WILL CORRESPOND
WITH YOUR BADGE.
NOW EACH OF YOU WILL DRAW A CARD
IN THE ORDER
YOU EXITED THE TOWER.
ALL RIGHT,
WHICH OF YOU WAS FIRST?
( rattling )
Hanzo: GUESS THAT MEANS
I'M NEXT.
Pokkle: AFTER HIM, I'M NEXT.
♪
‐ Gon: OH, HEY, KILLUA.
‐ Killua: HUH?
Gon: HE MENTIONED US
HUNTING AND BEING HUNTED.
DO YOU THINK THAT MEANS WE'RE
GONNA BE FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
Killua: YEAH, PROBABLY DOES.
( whistles )
Leorio: NOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT,
BUT I KNOW YOU GOTTA DRAW IT
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
YEAH.
Lippo: HAS EVERYONE DRAWN?
VERY WELL. NOW IF YOU WOULD,
PLEASE GO AHEAD,
AND REMOVE THE STICKER.
♪
( chuckles )
THE NUMBER YOU SEE
IS YOUR TARGET.
( applicants murmur )
( Gon shudders )
( shudders )
Lippo: THIS BOX HAS RECORDED
THE NUMBER
THAT EACH OF YOU DREW.
EACH CARD WAS TALLIED
AND THEN STORED IN MEMORY.
SO IF YOU LIKE, YOU'RE FREE
TO DISPOSE OF THE CARDS.
IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE
AT THIS POINT.
THE OBJECTIVE IS TO STEAL
YOUR TARGET'S I. D. BADGE.
Imori: OH, GOOD. SO WE DON'T
HAVE TO KILL EACH OTHER THEN.
Lippo: THE METHOD IS UP TO YOU.
PROCURE THE BADGE
HOWEVER YOU SEE FIT,
BUT IF YOU KILL YOUR TARGET,
YOU CAN TAKE THEIR BADGE EASILY.
Amori: YEAH, THAT SURE SOUNDS
LIKE THE FASTEST WAY TO ME.
Imori: SO THAT'S
HOW IT'S GONNA BE?
Umori: COME ON.
THERE'S NOTHIN' TO BE SCARED OF.
Lippo: LISTEN CAREFULLY.
COLLECTING THE I. D. BADGE
OF YOUR SPECIFIED TARGET
WILL EARN YOU THREE POINTS.
UNDERSTAND?
YOUR OWN BADGE
IS ALSO WORTH THREE POINTS,
AND ALL THE OTHER BADGES
ARE WORTH ONE POINT.
IN ORDER TO MOVE ON
TO THE FINAL PHASE,
YOU WILL HAVE TO COLLECT
SIX POINTS,
SO DURING YOUR TIME
THERE ON ZEVIL ISLAND,
GATHER ENOUGH BADGES
TO COLLECT SIX POINTS,
OR FAIL THE EXAM.
ONLY THOSE WHO DO
WILL CLEAR THE FOURTH PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
♪
Woman: I'D LIKE
TO COMMEND ALL OF YOU
ON YOUR WORK
IN THE EXAM'S THIRD PHASE.
I'LL BE YOUR GUIDE.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU CAN CALL ME KHARA.
IT WILL TAKE TWO HOURS
FOR THIS BOAT
TO REACH ITS DESTINATION,
ZEVIL ISLAND.
ALL 24 APPLICANTS
WHO'VE MADE IT THIS FAR
ARE GRANTED AN OPEN INVITATION
TO PARTICIPATE AGAIN
IN NEXT YEAR'S EXAM,
NO MATTER WHAT.
SO EVEN IF YOU
DON'T PASS THIS TIME,
WE REALLY HOPE
YOU'LL TRY AGAIN.
NEVER SAY DIE!
‐ RIGHT, EVERYBODY?
‐ ( music slows, stops )
UH, WOW.
THAT WENT OVER WELL.
Kurapika: IT APPEARS
THE BATTLE HAS ALREADY BEGUN.
Leorio: YOU'RE RIGHT.
EVERYBODY'S ALREADY
TAKEN OFF THEIR BADGES
AND TUCKED 'EM AWAY
SO THEY WON'T GET STOLEN YET.
Khara: ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE!
FOR THE NEXT TWO HOURS,
YOU'RE ALL FREE
TO DO WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
THANK YOU, AND I HOPE YOU ALL
ENJOY THE REST OF THE VOYAGE!
Leorio: HMM?
SO, UH, HYPOTHETICALLY,
IF YOU HAPPEN
TO BE MY TARGET, I MEAN,
DON'T EXPECT ME
TO SHOW YOU ANY MERCY, 'KAY?
Kurapika: WELL, OF COURSE NOT.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO BE MY TARGET,
I WOULD SAY
THE SAME THING TO YOU.
Leorio: AM I YOUR TARGET?
REALLY?
( Kurapika chuckles )
I'M SPEAKING HYPOTHETICALLY.
Leorio: OH, YEAH, I KNEW THAT.
WE'RE SPEAKING HYPOTHETICALLY.
Kurapika: HEH.
YOU NEEDN'T WORRY.
YOU'RE NOT MY TARGET, LEORIO.
Leorio: OH. I SEE. UH, OH!
SO YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE NOT MY TARGET, EITHER!
( Kurapika laughs )
( sea cranes calling )
Killua: HEY.
SO, UH, WHO DID YOU GET?
Gon: WHAT DID YOU DRAW?
Killua: IT'S A SECRET.
( Gon sighs )
( both laugh )
Killua: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT MY TARGET, GON.
I PROMISE.
Gon: THAT'S GOOD,
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT MINE, EITHER.
Killua: YOU WANNA SHOW
OUR NUMBERS AT THE SAME TIME?
Gon: OKAY.
Both: READY, AND...
( Killua gasps )
NUMBER 44 IS...
( Hisoka slurps )
Gon: REALLY?
Killua: YOU'VE GOT
SERIOUSLY BAD LUCK.
Gon: HEH. OH, DO YOU THINK SO?
SO WHO'S NUMBER 199, ANYWAY?
Killua: I'M NOT SURE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU KNEW.
Gon: NOPE.
Killua: IF I'D HAVE
JUST BEEN SMARTER ABOUT IT,
I WOULD HAVE MEMORIZED
EVERYBODY'S NUMBERS.
ONCE HE EXPLAINED IT,
THAT'S WHEN
I STARTED PAYING ATTENTION,
BUT EVERYONE HAD TAKEN OFF
THEIR BADGES ALREADY.
PRETTY LAME, HUH?
( Gon shuddering )
Killua: GON.
Gon: OH, WHAT'S UP?
Killua: ARE YOU HAPPY OR SCARED
RIGHT NOW? WHICH ONE IS IT?
Gon: KINDA BOTH, I GUESS.
IF I HAD TO FIGHT
WITH HISOKA ONE‐ON‐ONE,
I WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM,
BUT IF ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS JUST STEAL HIS BADGE,
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK I MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE A REAL SHOT.
Killua: YEAH.
Gon: THE WAY IT IS NOW,
WELL, AT LEAST
I'VE GOT A CHANCE.
AND TO BE HONEST,
IT DOES SCARE ME A LITTLE BIT,
BUT I THINK IT'S WORTH IT.
Killua: I GOT YA.
WELL, LET'S DO OUR BEST.
DON'T DIE, 'KAY?
Gon: YEAH, AND SAME TO YOU!
( sea cranes calling )
Khara: THANKS FOR BEING PATIENT,
EVERYONE!
WE'VE ARRIVED AT ZEVIL ISLAND.
OKAY, THEN.
YOU WILL BE DISEMBARKING
IN THE ORDER
YOU COMPLETED THE THIRD PHASE,
FROM THE SHORTEST
TO THE LONGEST.
( Leorio groans )
NOT THIS AGAIN.
Khara: YOU'LL GO ASHORE
ONE AT A TIME,
WITH TWO‐MINUTE INTERVALS
SEPARATING EACH
OF THE APPLICANTS, ALL RIGHT?
Killua: I GUESS THAT MEANS
WE'LL BE WAITING HERE A WHILE.
Gon: YEAH.
Khara: YOU'LL BE ON THE ISLAND
EXACTLY ONE WEEK.
THAT MEANS
YOU ONLY HAVE SEVEN DAYS
TO COLLECT YOUR SIX POINTS
AND THEN RETURN
TO THIS LOCATION.
FIRST APPLICANT,
GET READY TO DISEMBARK NOW!
♪
Kurapika: NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THE FIRST TO GO ASHORE
HAVE THE ADVANTAGE.
Leorio: RIGHT. THEY CAN HIDE
AND WATCH EVERYONE'S MOVEMENTS,
INCLUDING THEIR TARGET'S,
BEFORE THEY MAKE THEIR MOVE.
‐ ( timer beeps )
‐ Khara: THAT'S TWO MINUTES.
THE SECOND PERSON MAY GO.
( rattling )
UH...
( groans )
( rattling )
THE THIRD PERSON MAY GO!
Hanzo: YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
Khara: THE SEVENTH PERSON...
THE 11th PERSON...
THE 15th PERSON...
THE 20th PERSON MAY GO!
THAT'S TWO MINUTES.
THE 21st PERSON MAY GO!
Killua: BYE.
Gon: BYE.
Killua: OKAY.
I GUESS I'LL START OFF
BY SCOUTING THE ISLAND.
Khara: THAT'S TWO MINUTES!
THE 22nd PERSON MAY GO!
Gon: GREAT! SEE YA.
Leorio: GOOD LUCK.
( Gon thinking )
FIRST, I'VE GOTTA FIND HISOKA.
♪
Kurapika: HMM?
( chuckles )
♪
( Gon thinking ) HOW AM I
GONNA STEAL HISOKA'S BADGE?
Hisoka: SUCH A GOOD BOY.
VERY NICE.
I'M BEGINNING TO GET EXCITED.
( Gon gagging )
( coughs )
( sighs )
I DEFINITELY CAN'T GET HIS BADGE
IN A HEAD‐TO‐HEAD FIGHT.
( gasps )
IT'S AN APPLICANT.
AND THERE'S
ANOTHER ONE BEHIND HIM.
HE'S TARGETING THE GUY IN FRONT.
( grass rustles )
( Pokkle grunts )
( applicant #105 grunts )
( grunts )
Gon: HE MISSED.
Applicant #105: THAT WAS CLOSE,
A LITTLE TOO CLOSE, EVEN.
SORRY, PAL,
BUT I DON'T GO DOWN
( woozy )
THAT EASY.
( groans )
WHAT THE...
( gasping ) YOU BASTARD.
Pokkle: I COATED THE ARROW
WITH A FAST‐ACTING TRANQUILIZER,
SO YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO WALK MUCH FOR ABOUT A WEEK.
DON'T WORRY, THOUGH.
THERE'S FRESH WATER NEARBY,
SO YOU PROBABLY WON'T DIE. HEH.
BUT I'LL BE
TAKING THIS OF COURSE.
LATER!
Gon: WOW.
HE WAS ABLE TO HIDE HIS PRESENCE
WHILE HE QUIETLY STALKED
HIS PREY.
AND HIS TARGET
SENSED THE SHOT BEING FIRED
AND WAS ABLE TO DODGE IT,
AVOIDING WHAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A SERIOUS INJURY,
BUT THE STALKER
HAD THAT COVERED,
COATING HIS ARROW WITH POISON.
SO THAT'S HOW YOU HUNT.
IF I'M GONNA HAVE ANY CHANCE
OF STEALING HISOKA'S BADGE,
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY.
♪
( fishing line fluttering )
FIRST, I'LL HAVE TO SNEAK UP
ON HIM WITHOUT BEING NOTICED...
THEN WAIT FOR MY CHANCE
AND TAKE IT.
ALL RIGHT!
BUT THIS TARGET'S
NOT MOVING LIKE HISOKA WILL BE.
( groans )
EITHER WAY,
I'LL ONLY GET ONE SHOT.
I'VE GOTTA HOOK HIS BADGE
WHILE HE'S NOT PAYING ATTENTION,
OR I DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
OKAY.
TRY TO READ HIS MOVEMENTS.
AND NOW!
( groans )
THIS WON'T DO IT.
IT'S WAY TOO EASY
TO FOLLOW A SWINGING TARGET.
I ALREADY KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE IT'S GONNA GO.
( frog croaks )
OHH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE GOTTA REMEMBER HE'LL
TRY TO MOVE OUT OF THE WAY.
( birds chirping )
IF I CAN'T A FLYING BIRD
BY WATCHING HOW IT MOVES,
THEN I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO STEAL HISOKA'S BADGE.
ALMOST.
OH, WELL. I REALLY CAN'T EXPECT
TO CATCH A BIRD
ON MY VERY FIRST TRY.
‐ THERE!
‐ ( chirping )
ALL RIGHT! UNH!
♪
( Leorio sighs )
GOTTA FIGURE OUT
WHOSE NUMBER THIS IS.
Kurapika: THE SUN
IS JUST ABOUT TO SET.
I SHOULD PROBABLY STAY
IN ONE LOCATION UNTIL MORNING.
( Gon panting )
DAMN! I DIDN'T THINK ALL THIS
WAS GONNA BE SO HARD.
IT'S WAY TOO DARK
FOR ME TO SEE ANYTHING,
AND THERE AREN'T
ANY BIRDS OUT ANYMORE.
GUESS I'LL START FRESH
IN THE MORNING!
( birds chirping )
( sputters )
ALL RIGHT!
NOW IT'S BACK TO TRAINING!
‐ ( birds chirping )
‐ ( Gon grunts )
( grunting )
( grunting,
line fluttering continue )
IT'S HOPELESS.
MAYBE THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
CATCHING A BIRD
MIDFLIGHT ACCURATELY,
WHAT WAS I EVEN THINKING?
‐ ( splash )
‐ HMM?
( gasps )
BUT IF A BIRD CAN CATCH A FISH
WHILE IT'S SWIMMING...
THERE IT GOES.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE KEY.
THAT'S HOW I CAN TELL
WHERE MY TARGET'S GONNA MOVE.
NOW!
♪
I DID IT!
I FIGURED IT OUT.
I'VE JUST GOTTA GO
FOR THE TARGET
THE MOMENT IT GOES FOR ITS PREY!
Geretta: HUH.
THE KID'S IMPRESSIVE.
HE ACTUALLY MASTERED
THE ART OF THE HUNT.
BUT CONCENTRATION LIKE THAT
WILL COME BACK TO BITE YOU.
HEH.
Narrator: GON FINALLY
MASTERED THE TRICK
THAT WOULD AID HIM
IN HIS HUNT FOR HISOKA.
HOWEVER, UNBEKNOWNST TO HIM,
GON WAS BEING HUNTED HIMSELF.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"EXPLOSION OF DECEPTION."
‐ EXPLODE!
‐ Killua: EXPLODE.
‐ Gon: KABOOM!
‐ Killua: OH. MUSHROOM.