( Noggin Lugging Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Netero: OHH!
Gon: ONE MORE!
♪♪♪
( laughs )
‐ Netero: HMM?
‐ Gon: GOTCHA!
YOU JUST USED YOUR RIGHT HAND.
Netero: I DID.
( Gon laughs )
I DID IT! YEAH!
( laughs )
YAY!
( groans )
( snoring )
Narrator: AS DAWN BREAKS,
THE AIRSHIP CARRYING GON
AND HIS FRIENDS
APPROACHES ITS DESTINATION.
THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
‐ ( Gon snoring )
‐ ( chimes ring )
HMM?
( crewman on P. A. ) I SINCERELY
APOLOGIZE FOR THE LONG WAIT.
THE AIRSHIP WILL BE ARRIVING
AT ITS DESTINATION SHORTLY.
( Gon gasps )
IS THIS WHERE THE NEXT TEST
IS GONNA BE HELD?
Applicant: WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
Second applicant:
THERE'S NOTHING HERE
Beans: AH‐‐AHEM.
EVERYONE, THIS IS THE SITE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM'S
THIRD PHASE.
YOU'LL BE COMPETING HERE
AT THE TOP OF THE TRICK TOWER.
Applicant #107:
DID YOU SAY, "TRICK TOWER"?
Beans: IN ORDER
TO PASS THIS PHASE,
YOU MUST REACH
THE BASE OF THE TOWER ALIVE.
THE TIME LIMIT IS 72 HOURS.
AND WITH THAT, THE EXAM'S
THIRD PHASE WILL NOW BEGIN.
GOOD LUCK TO EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF YOU.
Leorio: HE'S GOTTA BE KIDDING.
( man laughs )
SO IT'S FINALLY MY TURN, EH?
( chip crunches )
( laughs )
( Beans on loudspeaker )
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE!
DO YOUR BEST!
Gon: WHOA.
Leorio: NOW WHAT?
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO CLIMB DOWN?
Kurapika: WELL, I HOPE NOT.
THAT WOULD BE SUICIDE.
( applicant #86 laughs )
SURE, FOR MOST GUYS.
FOR AN EXPERT
ROCK CLIMBER LIKE ME,
THIS IS GONNA BE
A PIECE OF CAKE.
Killua: OH, WOW.
Gon: LOOK AT HOW FAST
HE'S GOING.
( applicant #86 chuckles )
BY THE LOOK OF THINGS,
I'M ABOUT TO BE THE FIRST ONE
TO PASS THE THIRD PHASE.
‐ ( whooshing )
‐ HUH?
( rhythmic whooshing )
( gasping )
NO, STOP!
GO AWAY! YAAH!
HELP ME!
Leorio: UH, SO I GUESS
WE CAN'T CLIMB DOWN,
NOT THIS WAY, AT LEAST.
Kurapika: YEAH.
( birds squawking )
( tapping )
( rapping )
Leorio: HUH? WHAT'S UP?
Kurapika: THERE ARE
FEWER PEOPLE AROUND.
Leorio: WHAT?
Kurapika: I COUNT 23,
SO NEARLY HALF OF THE APPLICANTS
HAVE ALREADY FOUND AN EXIT.
Leorio: NO WAY.
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
Kurapika: WE'RE MISSING
SOMETHING, BUT WHAT IS IT?
THERE MUST BE HIDDEN DOORS
UP HERE SOMEWHERE
THAT LEAD TO THE LOWER FLOORS
OF THE TOWER.
Gon: KURAPIKA! LEORIO!
WHAT IS IT, GON?
Gon: LOOK AT THIS.
WE FOUND A TRAPDOOR.
CHECK IT OUT.
Kurapika: I SEE.
SO THE ONLY WAY THAT WE
CAN REACH THE LOWER LEVELS
IS BY TURNING OVER
THESE STONES.
Leorio: OKAY! GOOD JOB.
NOW WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE HEAD ON DOWN?
Gon: 'KAY,
BUT I'M SORTA CONFUSED.
Leorio: WHY? WHAT IS THERE
TO BE CONFUSED ABOUT?
Gon: THERE'S ONE
AND ANOTHER AND ANOTHER
AND ANOTHER ONE
RIGHT OVER THERE.
THERE'S A LOT OF 'EM.
Leorio: THAT MANY?
Kurapika: FIVE HIDDEN DOORS
LOCATED IN THE SAME AREA.
SOUNDS A BIT SUSPICIOUS.
NO DOUBT A FEW OF THEM
ARE TRAPS.
Killua: FROM WHAT I CAN TELL,
EACH OF THESE TRAPDOORS
CAN ONLY BE USED ONE TIME.
Leorio: SERIOUSLY?
Killua: WE SAW SOMEBODY
FALL THROUGH ONE EARLIER,
BUT WHEN WE TRIED TO OPEN IT,
IT WOULDN'T BUDGE AN INCH.
Kurapika:
JUDGING BY THE DOOR'S SIZE,
ONLY ONE APPLICANT
CAN GO THROUGH IT AT A TIME.
Killua: WHICH MEANS ONLY
ONE PERSON CAN USE EACH DOOR.
IT'S BEGINNING TO LOOK
LIKE WE'RE ALL
GONNA HAVE TO SPLIT UP.
WE DECIDED THAT WE'LL EACH PICK
A DOOR AND SEE HOW IT GOES.
Gon: AND NO HARD FEELINGS
IF ONE OF 'EM'S A TRAP.
HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
Leorio: WORKS FOR ME.
SEEMS LIKE LUCK IS
PART OF THE GAME OR SOMETHING.
Kurapika: NO OBJECTION HERE.
THAT SETTLES IT.
♪♪♪
Leorio: ON THE COUNT OF THREE,
WE ALL HOP IN
AT EXACTLY THE SAME TIME, OKAY?
Gon: I GUESS THAT MEANS
THIS IS GOOD‐BYE FOR NOW, GUYS.
Kurapika: WE'LL MEET UP
AT THE BASE OF THE TOWER.
Killua: LET'S DO THIS.
ONE...
Gon: TWO...
All: THREE!
( Leorio groaning )
HUH?
WAIT. WHAT?
( both laugh )
Kurapika: THAT WAS
CERTAINLY A BRIEF FAREWELL.
Leorio: YEAH, NO KIDDING.
I DON'T THINK ANY OF US
EXPECTED ALL THOSE HIDDEN DOORS
TO LEAD US ALL TO THE SAME ROOM.
EH?
Gon: HEY, LOOK AT THIS.
"THE FIVE WHO DROP
INTO THIS CHAMBER MUST FIND
THEIR WAY DOWN TOGETHER
BY CONSENSUS OF THE MAJORITY."
Leorio: WAIT. FIVE?
Gon: LOOK. THEY EVEN
LEFT US FIVE WRIST TIMERS.
Killua: WITH BUTTONS
MARKED "X" AND "O."
Kurapika: DO YOU THINK
IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO LEAVE THIS ROOM AT ALL
UNTIL SOMEONE ELSE DROPS IN
AND JOINS US DOWN HERE?
Man: VERY GOOD.
Leorio: WHO'S THERE?
Lippo: MY NAME IS LIPPO.
I'M THE PRISON WARDEN HERE,
NOT TO MENTION YOUR EXAMINER
FOR THE THIRD PHASE OF THE EXAM.
Kurapika: DID HE SAY,
"PRISON WARDEN"?
Lippo: WE'VE GONE TO THE TROUBLE
OF PREPARING MULTIPLE ROUTES
THROUGH THE TOWER,
AND THE ONE YOU'VE CHOSEN
IS THE PATH OF MAJORITY RULE.
IF YOU WANT TO PASS‐‐
AND I'M SURE YOU DO‐‐
COOPERATION IS
THE ESSENCE OF SUCCESS.
ONE PERSON ACTING SELFISHLY
COULD DERAIL THE ENTIRE GROUP,
AND OF COURSE YOU
WON'T BE PERMITTED TO START
UNTIL YOU
HAVE FIVE MEMBERS PRESENT.
THAT'S IT, GENTLEMEN!
BEST OF LUCK.
( click )
( Leorio groans )
WE SERIOUSLY CAN'T START
'TIL SOMEBODY ELSE SHOWS UP?
SO WHAT NOW?
Kurapika: I GUESS
WE JUST HAVE TO WAIT.
( Lippo whistles )
♪♪♪
Prisoner: YOU WANTED
TO SEE US, WARDEN?
Lippo: THE TEST BEGINS NOW,
SO GO, TAKE YOUR POSITIONS.
Prisoners: OKAY.
( tapping )
( shoe tapping )
‐ Leorio: OH, COME ON!
‐ Gon: HMM?
Leorio: WE'VE BEEN
SITTING HERE FOR TWO HOURS!
WHAT IF EVERYBODY ELSE
ALREADY FOUND THEIR WAY DOWN?
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO, HUH?
WE CAN'T BE THE ONLY ONES
STUCK AT THE TOP.
WE'LL LOOK LIKE TOTAL IDIOTS!
Kurapika: CALM DOWN, LEORIO.
COMPLAINING WON'T HELP.
Leorio: "CALM DOWN"?
WHAT IF NOBODY ELSE SHOWS UP
BEFORE WE REACH THE END
OF OUR TIME LIMIT, HUH?!
‐ ( tapping )
‐ ( groans )
I CAN'T JUST SIT HERE‐‐
Kurapika: SHH! BE QUIET!
Leorio: HUH?!
Kurapika:
DO YOU HEAR THAT SOUND?
( tapping )
( Tonpa groans )
WOW, GOOD GRIEF.
Gon: MR. TONPA.
Killua: OH, GREAT.
Leorio: LOOK WHO IT IS.
Tonpa: OKAY.
( grinding )
Kurapika: I SEE. SO THE DOOR
MUST BE PROGRAMMED TO APPEAR
ONCE ALL FIVE TIMERS
ARE PUT ON.
Gon: "AT THIS DOOR,
SELECT 'O' TO OPEN,
'X' NOT TO OPEN."
Leorio:
USING MAJORITY RULE ALREADY?
ALL RIGHT. AT LEAST
THE ANSWER IS OBVIOUS.
WHAT?!
FESS UP. WHICH ONE OF YOU JOKERS
HIT THE "X" BUTTON?
Tonpa: HEH. THAT WAS ME.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I GUESS I PRESSED
THE WRONG BUTTON.
Leorio: STOP SCREWIN' AROUND,
OLD MAN!
WHAT, ARE YOU BLIND
OR SOMETHIN'?
Tonpa: I SAID IT WAS
JUST AN HONEST MISTAKE.
Leorio: HOW IN THE HELL DO YOU
PRESS THE WRONG DAMN BUTTON?!
HUH?!
Gon: IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S OKAY. THE DOOR'S OPEN NOW.
Leorio: IT DOES MATTER.
HE PRESSED THE WRONG BUTTON
ON PURPOSE.
HE'S TRYING TO SABOTAGE US.
Kurapika: LET'S GO. WE DON'T
HAVE TIME FOR PETTY BICKERING.
Killua: YEAH, HE'S RIGHT.
LET HIM KEEP PRESSING
THE WRONG BUTTON IF HE WANTS TO.
THE REST OF US JUST
HAVE TO PRESS THE RIGHT ONE.
( Leorio growls )
FINE, I GUESS.
( Tonpa laughs )
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
( Leorio growls )
SERIOUSLY?
I DIDN'T THINK WE'D GET
ANOTHER QUESTION SO SOON.
Gon: "WHICH WAY
DO YOU WANT TO GO?
'O' FOR RIGHT. 'X' FOR LEFT."
Leorio: RIGHT...
OR LEFT.
( wrist timers beep )
HUH?!
HEY! WHY WOULD YOU
WANNA GO RIGHT?
YOU ALWAYS GO LEFT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
Kurapika: THAT'S TRUE.
AS RESEARCH HAS SHOWN,
PEOPLE WHO ARE LOST OR
FIND THEMSELVES AT A CROSSROADS
TEND TO CHOOSE TO GO TO THE LEFT
MUCH MORE FREQUENTLY
THAN THE RIGHT.
Killua: YOU KNOW,
I THINK I'VE HEARD THAT BEFORE.
Leorio: HOLD ON A SECOND!
THE NUMBERS JUST DON'T ADD UP.
WHICH DIRECTION
DID THE TWO OF YOU PICK?
Kurapika: RIGHT.
Killua: RIGHT.
( Leorio groans )
YOU LITTLE MONSTERS.
Tonpa: GOING RIGHT
MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
THE EXAMINER
WILL NEVER SEE IT COMING.
IF THEY'VE SEEN THE SAME
RESEARCH THAT THOSE TWO HAVE,
I BET THEY MADE THE LEFT PATH
WAY HARDER.
( Leorio growls )
OKAY, SO WE'RE BOTH
SIMPLEMINDED. SO WHAT?
Gon: WE?
Leorio: WHOA.
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE?
Killua: SEE THAT? OVER THERE.
♪♪♪
Prisoner:
THE APPLICANTS ARE HERE.
UNLOCK MY HANDCUFFS.
HERE WE GO.
THERE. NOW LET'S
GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
♪♪♪
Killua: HMM?
( chuckles )
♪♪♪
( Leorio swallows )
Lippo: GENTLEMEN,
LET ME EXPLAIN.
YOU'VE PROBABLY ALREADY NOTICED
THAT SOME OF THE PRISONERS
OF TRICK TOWER
ARE STANDING BEFORE YOU.
Kurapika: THEY'RE PRISONERS?
Lippo: NOT JUST PRISONERS.
THE HUNTER EXAM COMMITTEE
HAS ALSO OFFICIALLY
HIRED THEM ON AS EXAMINERS.
IN THIS PHASE,
YOU'LL BE FIGHTING
AGAINST ALL FIVE OF THEM.
THE FIGHTS WILL BE ONE‐ON‐ONE,
WITH EACH PERSON
FIGHTING ONLY ONCE.
USE ANY STYLE YOU LIKE.
THERE WILL BE NO DRAWS.
TO BE DECLARED THE VICTOR,
YOUR OPPONENT MUST ADMIT DEFEAT.
Prisoner: YOU CAN DECIDE
WHICH OF YOU
WILL BE THE FIRST CONTENDER,
AND THIS IS MAJORITY RULE,
WHICH MEANS YOU HAVE TO SECURE
THREE WINS IN ORDER TO PASS.
THE RULES ARE SIMPLE.
( Leorio growls )
I'M GETTIN' REAL TIRED OF THIS.
Killua: MEH. SEEMS PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD TO ME.
( Lippo chuckles )
WELL, THE FIGHTS THEMSELVES
WILL BE ANYTHING BUT.
FOR EVERY HOUR THE PRISONERS
KEEP YOU OCCUPIED HERE,
THEIR SENTENCES
WILL BE REDUCED BY ONE YEAR.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THEIR GOAL IN THIS PHASE
IS TO LITERALLY BUY TIME.
Kurapika: I UNDERSTAND.
WE'RE ON THE CLOCK,
AND IF WE DON'T REACH THE GOAL
OF GETTING OUT OF HERE
IN 72 HOURS, WE FAIL.
SO AS YOU'RE FIGHTING, REMEMBER,
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
Bendot: OKAY,
I'M FIGHTING WHOEVER'S FIRST.
NOW WHO'S IT GONNA BE?
Killua: NOW WHAT? HE SAID
TO FIGHT HOWEVER WE WANT,
SO I'M GUESSING THAT PRETTY MUCH
MEANS ANYTHING GOES.
Leorio: EVERYBODY BE CAREFUL.
NO TELLING
WHAT THEY'LL TRY TO PULL.
Kurapika: WITHOUT KNOWING
WHAT'S UP THEIR SLEEVES,
THERE'S FAR TOO MUCH AT STAKE.
GIVEN THAT, I'LL‐‐
Tonpa: NOPE. I'LL GO.
Gon: MR. TONPA?
Tonpa: I'LL BE THE GUINEA PIG,
SEE IF I CAN FIGURE OUT
WHAT THEY'RE UP TO.
CONSIDER IT
AN APOLOGY FOR EARLIER.
Leorio: HOLD ON. YOU'RE SERIOUS?
Tonpa: SURE.
YOU GUYS DON'T TRUST ME YET,
AND I KNOW I'VE GIVEN YOU
PLENTY OF REASONS NOT TO.
IF THE SCORE
ENDS UP BEING TWO‐TO‐TWO,
WHO DO YOU WANT
GOING IN THERE TO BREAK THE TIE?
'CAUSE IT AIN'T ME.
Leorio: THAT ACTUALLY
MAKES SENSE.
Tonpa: GOOD.
SO IT'S SETTLED, THEN.
Leorio: TONPA. SO YOU'RE...
( Bendot chuckles )
Leorio: WELL,
THAT WAS A SURPRISE.
NEVER THOUGHT HE'D VOLUNTEER.
Kurapika: HE DIDN'T
REALLY STRIKE ME
AS THE GUINEA‐PIG TYPE.
Gon: DO YOU GUYS
THINK HE'LL BE OKAY?
Bendot: NOW, THEN,
LET'S DETERMINE
THE METHOD OF COMBAT.
MY CHOICE WOULD BE
A BATTLE TO THE DEATH.
Tonpa: HUH?
Gon: A DEATH MATCH?
Leorio: THEY'RE GONNA FIGHT
'TIL ONE OF THEM DIES?
Kurapika: THIS IS BAD.
DON'T LET HIM
PROVOKE YOU, TONPA.
Bendot: WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I ACCEPT.
TO THE DEATH, THEN.
LET'S GO!
Leorio: SERIOUSLY?
Bendot: YOU'RE A BRAVE MAN.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
♪♪♪
( Tonpa grunting )
Leorio: T‐TONPA.
Bendot: NOW BEGIN!
( growls )
( Tonpa growls )
I‐‐
I GIVE UP!
Killua: HUH?
Leorio: WHAT?
Gon: DID HE JUST SAY
THAT HE GIVES UP?
Leorio: UH, MAYBE HE MEANT,
"GIVE ME A SEC."
Bendot: WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
Tonpa: I SAID I ADMIT DEFEAT.
THAT MEANS YOU WIN, RIGHT?
SO I GIVE UP. I LOSE.
( laughs )
Leorio: WHA‐WHA‐WHA...
( Bendot chuckles )
( laughs )
ALL RIGHT.
GUESS THE FIRST ROUND
GOES TO ME, THEN.
IF WE WIN TWO MORE ROUNDS,
THAT'S IT.
YOU ALL FAIL THE EXAM.
YOU CAN'T ADVANCE,
AND YOU CAN'T TURN BACK.
YOU'LL BE STUCK HERE
FOR THE NEXT 72 HOURS
UNTIL THE EXAM IS OVER,
AND IF THAT HAPPENS,
OUR SENTENCES WILL BE REDUCED
BY A GRAND TOTAL OF 72 YEARS.
( laughs )
Tonpa: OH, MAN,
AM I EMBARRASSED.
HE LOOKED A HELL OF A LOT
TOUGHER WHEN I GOT UP CLOSE.
Leorio: BASTARD!
I KNEW WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE TRUSTED YOU!
ALL YOU'RE GOOD FOR IS
SABOTAGING THE OTHER APPLICANTS.
YOU'RE JUST
A WORTHLESS PIECE OF GARBAGE!
Tonpa: IT TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
THAT'S WHAT I DO EVERY YEAR,
AND I'LL KEEP DOING IT
FOR AS LONG AS I CAN.
Leorio: WAIT. SAY WHAT?
Tonpa: I DON'T CARE
ABOUT PASSING THE HUNTER EXAM.
I'M IN IT FOR THE THRILLS.
SORRY TO DISAPPOINT.
Leorio: THE THRILLS?
Tonpa: THAT'S RIGHT.
THE EXAM IS A PROVING GROUND
DESIGNED TO CRUSH THE DREAMS
OF THE YOUNG AND OVERCONFIDENT,
AND THAT MOMENT WHEN HOPE
AND AMBITION GIVE WAY
TO ABSOLUTE DESPAIR‐‐HEH‐‐
I GET A KICK OUT OF THAT.
THE JOY I FEEL
IS JUST EXQUISITE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN I'M THE ONE
ACTIVELY SHATTERING
THE NEWBIES' DREAMS.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE THAT RUSH.
I'VE NO DESIRE TO BE A HUNTER.
DOESN'T REALLY INTEREST ME.
AND I'VE ALREADY HAD
ENOUGH FUN FOR THIS YEAR.
BESIDES, I USUALLY STOP
AT THIS POINT ANYWAY.
Leorio: BASTARD!
Kurapika: LEORIO, STOP!
Leorio: WHY?!
Kurapika: WE'RE WASTING TIME
FIGHTING EACH OTHER.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THEY WANT.
( Leorio groans )
Killua: YEAH, BUT...
IF THEIR GOAL WAS TO KILL
AS MUCH TIME AS POSSIBLE,
THEN THE MOVE THE OLD MAN MADE
WAS ACTUALLY THE RIGHT ONE.
THAT BALD GUY LOOKS EX‐MILITARY,
PROBABLY A MERCENARY.
IF YOU'D FOUGHT WITH HIM,
HE'D HAVE STARTED
BY CRUSHING YOUR LARYNX.
PRETTY HARD TO GIVE UP
IF YOU CAN'T EVEN TALK.
THEN HE'D HAVE TORTURED YOU
WITHOUT KILLING YOU
FOR AS LONG AS HE LIKED.
Tonpa: YEP. I CONSIDERED
THAT POSSIBILITY.
YOU LOOK SICK, OLD MAN.
Bendot: WELL, SO MUCH
FOR THAT PLAN, I GUESS.
I WAS GONNA TAKE MY SWEET TIME
TORTURING THE GUY
UNTIL THE CLOCK RAN OUT.
Prisoner: DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
IF WE DEFEAT
TWO OF THE NEXT FOUR,
THEN VICTORY WILL BE OURS.
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT,
WE NEED TO WIN THREE ROUNDS.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL BE ABLE TO ADVANCE.
Killua: SO WHO WANTS TO GO NEXT?
Gon: ME! I'LL GIVE IT A TRY!
‐ Leorio: ARE YOU SURE?
‐ Gon: YEAH!
Killua: WELL, THE NEXT OPPONENT
DOESN'T LOOK TOO STRONG.
Leorio: I WOULDN'T LET
MY GUARD DOWN IF I WERE YOU.
HE'S STILL A HARDENED CRIMINAL.
NO TELLING
WHAT HE'S CAPABLE OF.
Gon: YEAH, I'LL BE CAREFUL.
♪♪♪
Narrator: TONPA'S ACTIONS
HAVE PLACED GON AND HIS FRIENDS
AT A SERIOUS DISADVANTAGE.
THEIR NEXT OPPONENT IS SEDOKAN.
AS FOR WHAT EXACTLY
HE PLANS TO DO IN THIS MATCH,
IT'S ANYBODY'S GUESS.
AT THE START OF THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM,
THERE WERE 40 APPLICANTS,
AND NOW, WITH ONE ELIMINATED,
ONLY 39 REMAIN.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"BEWARE OF PRISONERS."
OH, AND WATCH YOUR BACK, OKAY?
Kurapika: BE CAREFUL
WHEN YOU'RE OUT LATE.
♪♪♪