♪
Narrator: IN THE FORESTS
OF THE DENTORA REGION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA
LIES A DORMANT VOLCANO
MEASURING 3,722 METERS HIGH.
IT IS KNOWN AS KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
IT IS HOME
TO A FAMILY OF FAMOUS ASSASSINS,
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY.
VISITORS ARRIVE EVERY DAY
IN HOPES OF CATCHING
A GLIMPSE OF THE MANSION,
WHICH HAS NEVER BEEN SEEN.
IT'S ONE OF THIS NATION'S MOST
POPULAR TOURIST ATTRACTIONS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Mrs. Zoldyck:
I HAVE A MESSAGE FROM KILLUA
THAT HE ASKED ME
TO RELAY TO YOU.
"THANK YOU FOR COMING.
"I'M HAPPY THAT YOU DID,
"BUT I CAN'T SEE YOU RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY."
( somber chorus singing )
Narrator: GON,
KURAPIKA, AND LEORIO
HAVE ADVANCED A LITTLE CLOSER
TO THEIR DESTINATION,
THE ZOLDYCK MANSION.
MEANWHILE...
( chorus continues )
Killua: I'M HOME.
HAH. NOT LIKE ANYONE'S AROUND.
Illumi: WELCOME BACK.
SO HOW DID WORK GO TODAY?
Killua: JUST FINE.
Illumi: DOES THAT MEAN
YOU FLAWLESSLY DISPATCHED
YOUR TARGET?
Killua: WHY ASK?
I'M SURE YOU ALREADY KNOW.
‐ YOU WERE SPYING, RIGHT?
‐ ( Illumi chuckles )
MOM IS WAITING
TO TALK TO YOU INSIDE.
Killua: DON'T WANNA SEE HER.
Illumi: I SEE.
( girl chuckles )
UH...
♪
Killua: EH?
DID YOU NEED SOMETHING?
Girl: OH. I WANTED TO SAY HELLO.
Killua: ARE YOU NEW HERE?
Girl: I AM. WHILE YOU WERE AWAY,
I WAS HIRED ON AS AN APPRENTICE
BUTLER, MASTER KILLUA.
MY NAME IS CANARY.
Killua: OH, HEY.
YOU CAN HAVE THIS.
Canary: NO, THANKS,
BUT I DO APPRECIATE
THE GESTURE, MASTER KILLUA.
Killua: YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BE SO FORMAL.
JUST CALL ME KILLUA.
Canary: I'M AFRAID
I CAN'T DO THAT.
YOU ARE MY EMPLOYER,
AND I AM JUST A HUMBLE EMPLOYEE.
Killua: WOW.
THAT'S PRETTY STUPID.
( Canary giggles )
Killua: YOU WERE USING
THE SILENT GAIT, WEREN'T YOU?
Canary: THE SILENT GAIT?
Killua: THE ONE
WHERE YOU MOVE SILENTLY
SO YOU'RE
COMPLETELY UNDETECTABLE.
IN THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY,
IT'S ONE OF THE FIRST TECHNIQUES
THAT WE EVER LEARN,
PERFECT FOR ASSASSINATION.
Canary: I DIDN'T REALIZE.
I SUPPOSE IT'S ONE
OF THE MANY TECHNIQUES I LEARNED
WHILE I WAS GROWING UP
IN METEOR CITY.
Killua: METEOR CITY?
Canary: YES.
THAT'S WHERE I WAS BORN...
A CITY THAT'S BEEN ERASED
FROM THIS WORLD.
Killua: HUH.
WELL, NEVER HEARD OF IT.
Canary: WHERE I COME FROM,
YOU'RE ALLOWED
TO DUMP ANYTHING THERE,
WHICH SORT OF EXPLAINS
WHY SO MANY MEMBERS OF THE MAFIA
AND THE PHANTOM TROUPE
COME FROM THERE.
Killua: I'D LIKE TO SEE IT
ONE OF THESE DAYS.
Canary: WHEN YOU DO, I'D BE
HAPPY TO SERVE AS YOUR GUIDE.
( giggles )
( Killua chuckles )
YOU KNOW THE RHYTHM ECHO?
Canary: THE RHYTHM ECHO?
WHAT IS THAT?
Killua: A TECHNIQUE
USING THE SILENT GAIT.
( Canary gasps )
Killua: IF YOU JUST KEEP MOVING
AT A PARTICULAR RHYTHM,
IT MAKES AFTERIMAGES.
Canary: I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
( grunts )
IT SEEMS WE HAVE INTRUDERS,
QUITE A FEW OF THEM, IN FACT.
Killua: DON'T WORRY.
MIKE CAN HANDLE IT.
Canary:
MIKE IS RESTRAINED TODAY.
THOSE ARE THE ORDERS
I WAS GIVEN.
THEY WISH TO TEST MY ABILITIES,
SO I MUST COMPLY.
Killua: HMM.
♪
Leader: WE'LL SPLIT UP HERE
AND KEEP SEARCHING THE MOUNTAIN
UNTIL WE FIND THEIR MANSION. EH?
Canary: PLEASE LEAVE RIGHT NOW.
Leader: AND JUST
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
Canary: WHO I AM
IS NONE OF YOUR CONCERN.
YOU'RE TRESPASSING
ON PRIVATE PROPERTY.
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO PASS
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
Leader: YOU REALLY THINK
A BRAT LIKE YOU CAN STOP US?
LOOK, YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
STAND ASIDE,
AND WE'LL SPARE YOUR LIFE.
HOW'S THAT FOR A DEAL?
Canary: TAKE ONE STEP
PAST THIS LINE,
AND I'LL REMOVE YOU BY FORCE.
Seaquant: WHAT WAS THAT?
LEAVE THIS ONE TO US, BOSS.
NO REASON
TO GET YOUR HANDS DIRTY.
‐ LET'S GO!
‐ Intruders: YAH!
Seaquant: YOU MESSED
WITH THE WRONG CREW!
♪
‐ ( Leader gasps )
‐ Intruder: DAMN IT!
‐ Intruder #2: GET HER!
‐ ( all yelling )
( all groaning )
( scattered groaning )
Canary: DO YOU WISH TO CONTINUE?
Leader: SHE TOOK DOWN
ALL THESE GROWN MEN
WITHOUT EVEN BREAKING A SWEAT.
ARE YOU A MEMBER
OF THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY?
Canary: CERTAINLY NOT.
I AM MERELY
AN APPRENTICE BUTLER.
WITH YOUR LIMITED ABILITIES,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN A MATCH
FOR THE BUTLERS,
NOT TO MENTION
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY.
( leader growls )
( yells )
Canary: HOW UTTERLY MEANINGLESS.
♪
AS I SAID, THIS IS MEANINGLESS.
( Leader chuckles )
I'M A HUNTER, KID,
AND THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LOSE TO A LITTLE GIRL.
( Canary grunts )
( leader laughs )
PREPARE YOURSELF, KID!
♪
WHAT THE...
( growls )
IT'S TIME TO DIE!
( coughs )
( screams )
( Seaquant whimpers )
( yelps ) I'M SORRY!
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
I'M BEGGING YOU!
‐ Canary: ZEBRO.
‐ Seaquant: HUH?
Zebro: SO YOU KNEW I WAS HERE,
DID YOU?
Canary: WOULD YOU MIND
TAKING CARE OF THE REST?
Zebro: AH. OF COURSE.
CLEANUP'S MY JOB, AFTER ALL.
BESIDES, MIKE IS STARVING.
( Seaquant gasps )
HUH?
( screams )
NO! SOMEBODY HELP ME, PLEASE!
( sobs )
( Zebro chuckles )
♪
Killua: SO YOU KNEW
THE RHYTHM ECHO ALREADY.
Canary: YES, I DID.
I HOPE YOU'LL FORGIVE ME.
Killua: HUMPH.
YOU THINK
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN I AM.
Canary: ABSOLUTELY NOT.
Killua: OH, REALLY?
I DON'T...
HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
WILL YOU BE MY FRIEND, CANARY?
( Canary gasps )
♪
( somber chorus singing )
I'M SORRY, MASTER KILLUA.
I HONESTLY AM.
( Killua scoffs )
THAT'S SO STUPID.
( chorus continues )
Gon: LET'S BE FRIENDS!
( chorus ends )
( chains clink )
Killua: GON.
♪
HMM?
HEH.
♪
Gon: IS SHE OKAY?
Leorio: SHE'S FINE.
SHE'S JUST LOST CONSCIOUSNESS.
( Gon gasps )
( Milluki growls )
WAKE UP!
Killua: AH.
OH.
HEY, GOOD MORNING, BIG BRO.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
( Milluki growls )
YOU ARROGANT LITTLE PUNK!
Killua: ARROGANT? COME ON.
LOOK, I FEEL REALLY AWFUL
ABOUT STABBING YOU, BIG BRO.
SORRY. I REALIZE
I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
Milluki: YOU LIAR!
( Killua spits )
CAN'T FOOL YOU, HUH?
( Milluki growls )
( cell phone beeping )
YES?
OH! HI, MAMA!
UH‐HUH.
( gasps )
YEP. I UNDERSTAND.
WELL, KIL, YOU MIGHT WANNA KNOW
THOSE FRIENDS OF YOURS ARE
OVER AT THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
( laughs )
HOW 'BOUT IT, KIL?
SHOULD I ASK MAMA
TO HAVE THE THREE OF 'EM‐‐
Killua: MILLUKI...
IF YOU SO MUCH AS TOUCH THEM,
( echoing )
I'LL KILL YOU.
...KILL YOU.
Mrs. Zoldyck: I'M SORRY.
HOW RUDE OF ME.
I AM KILLUA'S MOTHER, YOU SEE,
AND THIS IS KALLUTO.
Gon: WHY CAN'T KILLUA
COME TO SEE US?
WHERE IS HE?
Mrs. Zoldyck:
IN SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
Leorio: WAIT. WHAT?
Mrs. Zoldyck:
BEFORE HE RAN AWAY FROM HOME,
KILLUA STABBED
HIS BROTHER AND ME.
Kurapika:
YES, THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD US.
‐ ( beep )
‐ Mrs. Zoldyck: AND THEN,
BECAUSE HE REGRETTED
WHAT HE HAD DONE,
OUR KILLUA RETURNED TO US
AND ENTERED SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT VOLUNTARILY.
IN ANY CASE, WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN HE WILL CHOOSE TO LEAVE.
‐ ( beeps )
‐ ( gasps ) WHAT?!
WHAT IS HAPPENING?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, FATHER?
PLEASE! DON'T DO ANYTHING HASTY!
HE'S ONLY JUST RETURNED!
( knock on door )
Milluki: HMM?
Man: I'M COMING IN.
( door scraping )
I BELIEVE THAT WILL DO FOR NOW.
THANK YOU.
Milluki: BUT, GRANDPA ZENO,
HE ISN'T EVEN SORRY,
NOT ONE BIT!
Zeno: YES, I'M AWARE OF THAT.
YOU MAY GO NOW, KIL.
Killua: OKAY.
♪
MAN, THAT REALLY HURT.
HEY, MILLUKI, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT SORRY,
BUT I DO FEEL BAD.
THAT'S WHY I LET YOU SLAP ME
AROUND FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Milluki: WHAT WAS THAT?
Zeno: OH, KIL,
SILVA WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU NOW.
Killua: DAD SAID THAT?
OKAY, THEN.
( Milluki groans )
DAMN IT, GRANDPA!
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO GO
AND SPOIL HIM ALL THE TIME?!
THAT'S WHY HE'S BECOME
SUCH A LITTLE PUNK!
( gasps )
Zeno: BECAUSE KILLUA
IS SPECIAL, MIL.
TELL ME. IN YOUR OPINION,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF KIL'S POTENTIAL?
Milluki: IT'S INCREDIBLE, SURE.
Zeno: YES. GO ON.
Milluki: I THINK
IT'S SAFE TO SAY
HE'S THE MOST TALENTED ZOLDYCK
IN THE HISTORY
OF OUR FAMILY, RIGHT?
EVEN MAMA THINKS SO,
AND I HAVE TO AGREE.
Zeno: VERY GOOD ASSESSMENT.
Milluki: BUT THERE'S JUST NO WAY
HE'LL EVER BE A GOOD ASSASSIN.
‐ HE'S WAY TOO ERRATIC.
‐ Zeno: ERRATIC?
Milluki: A KID WHO WANTS TO GO
AND MAKE FRIENDS
COULD NEVER LEAD
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY.
IN THE END, HE'S TOO WEAK,
WELL, MENTALLY, AT LEAST.
Zeno: HMM.
YES. THAT IS TRUE.
Milluki: RIGHT?
TAKE ME, FOR EXAMPLE.
I'LL KILL ANYONE YOU WANT ME TO,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
OH! I ALMOST FORGOT!
MY NEWEST BOMB
IS A REAL WINNER, GRANDPA.
IT'S TINY ENOUGH THAT I CAN
ATTACH IT TO A FEMALE MOSQUITO,
AND I RIGGED IT TO EXPLODE
WHENEVER IT SUCKS
ON THE TARGET'S BLOOD.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT MOSQUITOES
AREN'T GREAT
FOR PRECISION TARGETING.
Zeno: MIL.
Milluki: WHAT?
Zeno: YOU'RE A SHARP BOY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE NOT AN IDIOT, TOO.
Mrs. Zoldyck: OH,
WHY MUST FATHER BE THIS WAY?
( sighs )
I'M AFRAID
THAT SOMETHING HAS COME UP.
FAREWELL.
Gon: WAIT! HOLD ON!
IT'S JUST THAT WE'LL BE STAYING
IN TOWN FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
PLEASE LET KILLUA KNOW.
Mrs. Zoldyck: YES, VERY WELL.
I'LL BE SURE TO TELL HIM.
GOOD DAY.
Kalluto: WHO ARE ALL OF YOU?
TELL ME.
Gon: WE'RE ALL
FRIENDS WITH KILLUA.
Kalluto: YOU'RE HIS FRIENDS?
Mrs. Zoldyck: KALLUTO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
COME ALONG THIS INSTANT!
Kalluto: COMING! SORRY, MOTHER.
♪
Leorio: IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING,
BUT THESE PEOPLE
REALLY CREEP ME OUT.
AND I BET THEY WERE LYING
ABOUT KILLUA
NOT WANTING TO SEE US.
GON, WE CAN'T
GO BACK THERE JUST YET.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TAIL THOSE TWO.
Gon: YEAH,
BUT IF WE GO FOLLOW THEM,
I'M WORRIED THAT IT WOULD MEAN
A WHOLE LOT OF TROUBLE
FOR HER LATER ON.
Leorio: YEAH. GOOD POINT.
Canary: I WILL...
TAKE YOU
TO THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
THERE'S A PHONE THAT CONNECTS
DIRECTLY TO THE MANSION.
IF MASTER ZENO ANSWERS IT,
YOU MIGHT‐‐
Gon: WHO'S MASTER ZENO?
Canary: HE'S MASTER KILLUA'S
GRANDFATHER.
( animal snoring )
Silva: SO, KIL,
I HEAR YOU'VE MADE SOME FRIENDS.
Killua: YEAH.
Silva: AND WHAT ARE THEY LIKE?
Killua: WHAT ARE THEY LIKE?
THEY'RE A LOT OF FUN TO BE WITH.
Silva: I SEE.
HOW WAS THE HUNTER EXAM?
( Killua gasps )
OH, IT WAS EASY.
Silva: SIT OVER HERE BY ME, KIL.
( Killua gasps )
Silva: I WANT TO HEAR
ALL ABOUT IT.
( Killua gasps )
Silva: YOUR EXAM EXPERIENCES,
WHO YOU MET, HOW YOU FELT...
YOU CAN TELL ME
ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING.
Killua: 'KAY.
( brush rustling )
Mrs. Zoldyck:
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
FATHER DIDN'T EVEN ASK ME,
AND NOW KIL HAS GONE OFF
TO LARK ABOUT WITH PAPA!
UNFORGIVEABLE.
Killua: AND THEN
YOU KNOW WHAT GON SAID TO HIM?
HE DIDN'T WANT HIS LEGS CUT OFF,
BUT HE DIDN'T WANT
TO SURRENDER, EITHER.
( Silva laughs )
Killua: HEH HEH.
HE'S SO SELFISH.
Gon: HE'S INTERESTING,
ALL RIGHT.
Killua: AND THEN GON'S OPPONENT
POINTED A BLADE AT HIS FOREHEAD,
AND THAT'S WHEN GON‐‐
Silva: KIL...
DO YOU WANT TO SEE YOUR FRIENDS?
♪
NO NEED TO HOLD BACK.
BE HONEST.
THINKING BACK,
YOU AND I HAVE NEVER REALLY HAD
A FATHER‐SON CHAT BEFORE.
I WAS RAISED BY MY PARENTS
TO BE AN ASSASSIN,
AND I RAISED YOU THE SAME WAY.
BUT YOU AND I ARE DIFFERENT,
AND IT TOOK YOU LEAVING HOME
FOR ME TO REALIZE THAT.
( Killua gasps )
Silva: YOU ARE INDEED MY SON
AND STILL A PERSON ALL YOUR OWN.
LIVE YOUR LIFE.
REMEMBER, YOU CAN COME HOME
IF YOU GET TIRED, SO...
I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE YOUR FRIENDS?
Killua: MM‐HMM.
Silva: VERY WELL.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO NOW.
BUT, KIL...
PROMISE ME ONE THING,
THAT YOU WILL NEVER BETRAY
YOUR FRIENDS.
GOT THAT?
Killua: I'LL NEVER BETRAY THEM.
I SWEAR.
Mrs. Zoldyck: KIL.
IT'S TOO LATE.
THOSE THREE HAVE ALREADY LEFT.
RETURN TO YOUR CELL.
Killua: NO WAY. I'M LEAVING.
Mrs. Zoldyck: KIL!
‐ ( beeps )
‐ ( gasps )
( somber chorus singing )
Killua: STEP ASIDE.
( Mrs. Zoldyck laughs )
OH, KIL, WHAT A SPLENDID
ICY GLARE YOU HAVE.
( chorus continues )
Mrs. Zoldyck: WHAT IN THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?
KIL FINALLY CAME HOME!
Silva: LET THE BOY DO
WHAT HE WANTS FOR NOW.
Mrs. Zoldyck: YOU'RE MAD!
LISTEN TO YOURSELF!
IF KIL IS TO BE
HEAD OF THE FAMILY,
THIS STAGE
IS ABSOLUTELY CRITICAL!
Silva: SO YOU KNOW
WHAT'S AT STAKE. GOOD.
THEN STOP YOUR GRIPING,
AND KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
( laughs )
DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL COME BACK HOME ONE DAY.
AFTER ALL, HE IS MY SON.
Narrator:
KILLUA HAS BEEN SET FREE,
BUT SILVA CONFIDENTLY DECLARES
THAT HE WILL RETURN
AS AN ASSASSIN.
MEANWHILE, GON AND COMPANY
HEAD TO THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
WHETHER THEY WILL MAKE CONTACT
WITH KILLUA REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"CAN'T SEE IF YOU'RE BLIND."
EYE FOR AN EYE?
EYE FOR A TOOTH?
Killua: THAT'S TOOTH
FOR A TOOTH.