Narrator: HEAVENS ARENA.
THE 251‐STORY BUILDING,
WHICH STANDS 991 METERS TALL,
‐ IS A MECCA FOR FIGHTERS.
‐ ( crowd cheering )
WHEN COMBATANTS WIN A FIGHT,
THEY MAY ADVANCE BY ONE CLASS
AND RECEIVE
A CORRESPONDING REWARD.
AFTER REACHING THE 100th FLOOR,
THEY ARE ASSIGNED
A PRIVATE ROOM.
AND THOSE CONTESTANTS WHO ARE
SKILLED AND FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO REACH THE 200th FLOOR
EARN THE RIGHT TO CHALLENGE
THE STRONGEST FIGHTERS,
THE FLOOR MASTERS, IN AN INTENSE
BATTLE FOR SURVIVAL.
THIS IS, WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE BEST STAGE
A WARRIOR COULD ASK FOR.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Wing: ONLY ONE THING CAN
PROTECT YOU FROM A USER OF NEN.
YOU MUST LEARN
TO USE IT YOURSELF
AND USE TEN FOR DEFENSE.
OTHERWISE...
( both gasp )
Wing: YOUR BODY
WILL BE SHATTERED
BEYOND ALL RECOGNITION.
♪
Narrator:
AS THE HOUR GROWS LATE,
WING'S LECTURE
HAS REACHED ITS CLIMAX.
THEY HAVE UNTIL MIDNIGHT.
GON AND KILLUA
MUST LEARN HOW TO USE NEN
BEFORE THE CLOCK STRIKES 12:00.
Wing: NEN IS A POWER
THAT DWELLS WITHIN
EVERY SINGLE HUMAN PERSON.
HOWEVER, AT THE PRESENT TIME,
ONLY A FEW ARE CAPABLE
OF USING THAT POWER.
AND BECAUSE OF THEIR ABILITY,
THEY ARE TREATED
AS GENIUSES, LEADERS,
PSYCHICS, SAGES,
AND EVEN SUPERHUMANS.
Gon: A POWER THAT DWELLS
WITHIN EVERYONE?
Wing: YES, AND THERE ARE MEANS
BY WHICH TO AWAKEN THIS POWER,
BUT ONLY TWO,
EITHER SLOWLY AND CAREFULLY
OR BY FORCE.
ZUSHI OPTED
FOR THE SLOW AND CAREFUL PATH.
NOT ONLY WAS HE A QUICK LEARNER,
BUT HE WAS TIRELESS
IN HIS TRAINING.
SO HE WAS ABLE TO MASTER TEN
IN A VERY SHORT TIME,
ABOUT SIX MONTHS.
( Killua gasps )
BUT THAT'S WAY TOO LONG.
WE NEED TO LEARN TEN
AND PASS HISOKA,
AND WE'VE GOTTA DO IT
BEFORE MIDNIGHT!
Wing: THEN IT SEEMS FORCE
IS OUR ONLY CHOICE.
Killua: BUT IS THAT
GONNA BE FAST ENOUGH?
Wing: EXACTLY HOW LONG
IT TAKES IS UP TO YOU
AND HOW WELL YOU LEARN
TO CONTAIN YOUR AURA
IN THAT SHORT TIME,
SO LET'S GET RIGHT TO IT,
SHALL WE?
I WILL BEGIN YOUR TRAINING
BY TRANSMITTING MY AURA
IN YOUR DIRECTION.
THIS IS HATSU,
WHICH YOU SAW EARLIER.
( both gasp )
Wing: AND OF COURSE
IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
THAT BECAUSE I WISH YOU NO HARM,
I'LL GO EASY ON YOU.
BUT THIS METHOD
IS STILL A DRASTIC ONE.
‐ ( Gon gulps )
‐ Wing: IN OTHER WORDS,
I WILL ATTEMPT
TO SHOCK YOU INTO AWAKENING.
I WILL ROUSE YOUR
SLEEPING BODIES WITH A JOLT,
MAKING IT SO THAT YOU
CAN PERFORM TEN EASILY.
THE REASON I SAY, "SLEEPING,"
IS THAT YOUR AURA NODES
ARE CURRENTLY CLOSED,
PREVENTING
THE FREE FLOW OF AURA.
AND SO, YOU SEE, BY TRANSMITTING
MY AURA THROUGH YOU,
I AM HOPING TO JOLT THOSE NODES
INTO AN OPEN POSITION.
UNDER NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES,
YOU WOULD SPEND YOUR TIME
TRAINING IN MEDITATION,
LEARNING HOW TO SENSE
YOUR OWN AURA
THAT SURROUNDS YOU,
SLOWLY AND CAREFULLY ALLOWING
THOSE NODES TO FULLY OPEN.
EVEN A NATURAL TALENT LIKE ZUSHI
HERE REQUIRED THREE MONTHS.
BUT CONSIDERING YOUR ABILITIES,
YOU COULD HAVE ACCOMPLISHED IT
IN A WEEK OR LESS.
( both gasp )
Wing: WHICH IS WHY
IT'S UNFORTUNATE
THAT WE ARE BEING FORCED
TO USE THE DRASTIC METHOD.
Killua: I DON'T REALLY GET IT.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I THOUGHT FASTER IS
ALWAYS BETTER, ISN'T IT?
Wing: THIS METHOD IS A CHEAT
AND IS HIGHLY FROWNED UPON.
WE ARE SKIPPING
THE PROPER STEPS.
IF I WAS INEXPERIENCED
OR BORE ANY MALICIOUS INTENT,
I COULD KILL YOU.
Gon: YEAH, BUT YOU AREN'T
INEXPERIENCED OR MALICIOUS,
SO WE'RE SAFE WITH YOU, RIGHT?
( Wing sighs )
Killua: AND THAT'S WHY
I'VE BEEN WONDERING.
WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE TO TEACH US
THE REAL FOUR EXERCISES
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
Wing: BECAUSE YOU ARE
VERY CLOSE TO GETTING IT.
IF YOU WERE TO ENTER
THE 200th FLOOR
WITHOUT ANY OF THIS KNOWLEDGE,
YOU WOULD SUFFER GREATLY.
YOU SEE, UP THERE, EVERYONE
KNOWS HOW TO MANIPULATE NEN.
AND IT IS CUSTOMARY
TO INITIATE ANY NEW ARRIVALS
WHO ARE IGNORANT OF NEN
BY ATTACKING WITH IT.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THEY DO WHAT I AM ABOUT TO,
BUT WITHOUT
THE NECESSARY RESTRAINT.
THEY DO NOT CARE IF PEOPLE DIE.
IT'S ALL THE SAME TO THEM.
( both grunt )
Wing: ONLY THOSE WHO PROVE THEY
ARE STRONG ENOUGH TO SURVIVE
ARE WELCOME TO STAY THERE
AS THE CHOSEN.
THEY HAVE PAID A HIGH PRICE
FOR THE PRIVILEGE.
THAT IS WHY IT'S IMPORTANT
FOR YOU TO BE PREPARED.
I DON'T EXPECT ANY OF THAT
WAS VERY ENCOURAGING,
BUT THROUGH THIS METHOD,
I BELIEVE YOU WILL AWAKEN.
IT IS CLEAR YOU HAVE
THE TALENT AND ABILITY.
TAKE OFF YOUR JACKETS,
FACE AWAY FROM ME,
AND PUT DOWN
ALL YOUR BELONGINGS.
( Gon thinking )
IT'S SO HOT,
AND I CAN FEEL THIS PRESSURE,
EVEN THOUGH I KNOW MR. WING
ISN'T TOUCHING ME.
Killua: THIS IS IT,
THAT SENSATION.
IT'S LIKE
SOME SLIMY, INVISIBLE THING
CRAWLING ACROSS MY SKIN.
MULTIPLY THIS BY A FEW MILLION,
AND IT'D FEEL EXACTLY
LIKE MY BROTHER'S NEN.
Wing: NOW I'LL BEGIN.
( chorus vocalizing )
( Gon screams )
( Killua grunts )
Wing: AND NOW EVERY AURA NODE
IN YOUR BODY HAS BEEN OPENED.
( both gasp )
Killua: THIS‐‐THIS IS...
Wing: THAT, GENTLEMEN,
IS YOUR AURA,
ALSO KNOWN AS LIFE ENERGY.
YOU CAN SEE IT NOW,
BECAUSE THE NODES IN YOUR EYES
WERE ALSO OPENED.
Gon: IT ALMOST LOOKS LIKE STEAM
RISING OFF THE SPOUT
OF A TEAKETTLE.
IT'S SO CRAZY.
Killua: IT'S RUSHING OUT
FROM EVERY PART OF MY BODY,
AND IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE IT'S STOPPING.
NO WAY. THIS CAN'T BE GOOD!
Wing: WHAT YOU SEE
IS YOUR LIFE ENERGY,
SO IF IT CONTINUES TO ESCAPE,
YOU WILL BECOME QUITE TIRED.
EXPEND ALL OF YOUR AURA,
AND YOU WILL COLLAPSE
FROM EXTREME FATIGUE.
Killua: OH, I GET IT.
Wing: LISTEN TO ME CAREFULLY.
YOU MUST KEEP YOUR FOCUS
ON CONTAINING YOUR AURA
WITHIN YOUR BODY.
NOW CLOSE YOUR EYES.
( chorus continues )
USE ANY STANCE YOU PREFER,
WHATEVER HELPS YOU
TO MAINTAIN YOUR FOCUS.
VISUALIZE YOUR AURA
FLOWING THROUGH YOU
AS IF IT WERE BLOOD
FLOWING THROUGH YOUR BODY,
FROM THE TOP OF YOUR HEAD
TO YOUR RIGHT SHOULDER,
TO YOUR HAND,
THROUGH YOUR LEGS,
THEN UP YOUR LEFT SIDE.
( chorus silent )
AND NOW VISUALIZE THAT FLOW
AS, LITTLE BY LITTLE,
IT BEGINS TO GRADUALLY SLOW DOWN
AND SWIRL AROUND YOUR BODY.
( drip echoes )
♪
( Zushi gasps )
( Wing thinking )
THESE BOYS ARE INCREDIBLE.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN NEED ME
TO TELL THEM
THAT A NATURAL STANCE
WOULD BE THE MOST EFFECTIVE.
THEY'VE MASTERED THE TECHNIQUE
AFTER ONLY
A FEW SIMPLE DIRECTIONS.
IT'S MAGNIFICENT
AND TERRIFYING.
NOW SLOWLY OPEN YOUR EYES.
TELL ME HOW YOU FEEL.
Gon: I FEEL LIKE‐‐
LIKE I'M SURROUNDED
BY SOME VISCOUS LIQUID.
Killua: MM.
IT FEELS LIKE I'M WEARING
WEIGHTLESS CLOTHES.
Wing: I WANT YOU BOTH
TO CONTINUE HOLDING ON
TO THOSE IMAGES.
ONCE YOU ASSIMILATE THEM,
YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO DO THIS IN YOUR SLEEP.
( breathes deeply )
( both gasp )
Wing: NEXT, I WILL PROCEED
TO EMIT MALICIOUS NEN
AGAINST YOU.
♪
BEFORE YOUR NODES
WERE FORCED OPEN,
STANDING WITHIN THIS WOULD HAVE
CAUSED EXCRUCIATING PAIN.
Killua: YEAH, OKAY.
I GET IT NOW.
YOUR WHOLE BLIZZARD ANALOGY,
IT MAKES SENSE.
Wing: IF YOU CAN
FEND OFF MY NEN,
YOU WILL FINALLY BE ABLE
TO BREAK THROUGH
HIS BARRIER AS WELL.
PREPARE YOURSELVES!
( both grunt )
( both scream )
( footsteps )
( Hisoka chuckles )
( grunts )
WELCOME TO THE 200th FLOOR.
SEEMS I NEEDN'T BOTHER WITH
THE TRADITIONAL INITIATION.
I THINK I CAN GUESS WHY
YOU'VE COME TO HEAVENS ARENA.
YOU INTENDED
TO GET SOME TRAINING IN
BEFORE CHALLENGING ME, CORRECT?
Gon: THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT I DIDN'T EXPECT
I WAS GONNA FIND YOU HERE.
THAT SAVES ME SOME TROUBLE.
( Hisoka chuckles )
I WOULDN'T GET TOO BRASH JUST
BECAUSE YOU LEARNED TO USE TEN.
THERE IS MUCH
TO LEARN ABOUT NEN.
TO BE HONEST,
I FEEL ABSOLUTELY NO URGE
TO FIGHT YOU RIGHT NOW.
HOWEVER...
IF YOU MANAGE TO WIN
A SINGLE MATCH ON THIS FLOOR,
I'LL ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
Killua: LET'S GO.
Gon: UH...
Man: NEWCOMERS?
Man #2: LOOKS LIKE IT, HUH?
Man #1: IT APPEARS
THEY CAN USE "IT."
Man #2: INDEED...
Receptionist:
WELCOME TO THE 200th FLOOR!
PLEASE GO AHEAD
AND FILL OUT ALL THESE FORMS.
SO WOULD YOU LIKE TO REGISTER
FOR A MATCH RIGHT NOW?
AND BECAUSE
THIS LEVEL INCORPORATES
A SELF‐SERVICE SYSTEM,
YOU'RE PERMITTED 90 WHOLE DAYS
OF FIGHT PREPARATION.
DURING THOSE 90 DAYS,
YOU CAN CALL ME FOR A FIGHT
ANY TIME YOU DESIRE.
YOU'RE FREE TO FIGHT
EVERY DAY, OF COURSE,
OR IF YOU'D PREFER, YOU CAN WAIT
UNTIL THE VERY LAST MINUTE.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
ONCE YOU'VE PARTICIPATED
IN A FIGHT,
YOUR 90 DAYS OF PREPARATION TIME
STARTS OVER AGAIN.
HOWEVER, IF YOU DON'T FIGHT
BEFORE THE END OF THE 90 DAYS,
YOU'LL BE DISQUALIFIED,
AND YOUR NAME WILL BE STRICKEN
FROM ALL
OF THE OFFICIAL RECORDS.
Gon: WAIT.
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE MORE THAN
ONE FIGHT UP ON THIS LEVEL?
Receptionist: YES! THE ONLY WAY
FOR YOU TO CLEAR THIS FLOOR
IS TO RACK UP 10 VICTORIES!
HOWEVER, IF YOU LOSE FOUR TIMES
BEFORE YOU SECURE 10 WINS,
YOU'LL BE DISQUALIFIED.
( buzzer sounds )
ALSO, IF YOU DO WIN 10 TIMES,
YOUR REWARD IS THAT
YOU'LL HAVE A CHANCE
TO CHALLENGE THE FLOOR MASTERS!
THE FLOOR MASTERS
ARE THE 21 STRONGEST FIGHTERS
THAT HEAVENS ARENA HAS TO OFFER.
EACH ONE GETS
ONE WHOLE FLOOR TO THEMSELVES,
FROM 230 ALL THE WAY TO 250.
ARE YOU STARTING
TO UNDERSTAND NOW?
IF YOU'RE ABLE
TO BEAT A FLOOR MASTER,
YOU WIN THE HONOR
AND PRIVILEGE
OF BECOMING THE NEW MASTER
OF THAT FLOOR!
UH, BUT WAIT. THERE'S MORE!
THE FLOOR MASTERS
ENJOY OTHER PERKS!
NOT THE LEAST OF WHICH
IS YOU'LL BE ELIGIBLE
TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE BATTLE OLYMPIA,
THE BIENNIAL FESTIVAL OF COMBAT!
ISN'T THAT SO EXCITING?
( gasps )
NO REACTION?
Killua: SURE,
WHATEVER YOU SAY, LADY.
IS THERE ANYTHING SPECIAL
ABOUT THE TOP FLOOR?
Receptionist:
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT TO KNOW?!
THE CHAMPION
OF THE BATTLE OLYMPIA
GETS TO LIVE ON THE TOP FLOOR.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
IT'S AN INCREDIBLE HONOR!
( both grunt )
Receptionist: A PENTHOUSE
THAT'S A THOUSAND METERS UP!
IT'S A LIFE OF LUXURY!
DON'T YOU GET IT?!
Gon: YEAH, BUT, KILLUA,
YOUR HOUSE IS, LIKE,
3,700 METERS UP, ISN'T IT?
( receptionist groans )
B‐BUT WAIT!
THERE ARE OTHER PRIZES.
THE CHAMPION ALWAYS RECEIVES‐‐
Killua: WELL? WHAT DO YA THINK?
I DON'T KNOW. IF THAT'S
THE FLOOR'S BIG SECRET,
I DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
Gon: YEAH! I JUST WANT
TO FIGHT WITH HISOKA.
FORGET ALL THAT OTHER STUFF.
Receptionist: I DON'T GET IT.
WHY DID THE TWO OF YOU
EVEN BOTHER TO COME HERE?
Killua: WELL, I GUESS THAT MEANS
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO WIN A FIGHT.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA WAIT
A LITTLE WHILE FIRST,
AREN'T YOU?
Gon: NO WAY.
I'M READY!
THESE OPPONENTS ARE DIFFERENT,
AND I'M NOT LEAVING
'TIL I FIND OUT
JUST HOW DIFFERENT.
( Killua chuckles )
Receptionist: IN THAT CASE,
I'LL NEED YOU TO FILL OUT
THIS FORM AS WELL.
Gon: 'KAY!
‐ ( motor whirs )
‐ ( peg leg thumping )
♪
Killua: YOU WANT SOMETHING?
Man #1: OH, NO. NOT REALLY.
Man #2: WE'RE SIMPLY
WAITING IN LINE
SO WE CAN REGISTER
FOR A MATCH, RIGHT?
( man #3 cackles )
( man #2 laughs )
Killua: OH, I GET IT NOW.
HEY, GON, I THINK THESE GUYS
WANNA FIGHT
ON THE SAME DAY YOU DO.
( man #3 cackles )
Gon: I'M READY.
JUST LET ME KNOW WHEN I FIGHT.
Killua: WELL, YOU HEARD HIM.
Man #2: THAT BOY IS
BRIMMING WITH ENERGY, HUH?
( man #3 cackles )
( man #1 chuckles )
Receptionist: NOW MR. GON
WILL BE IN ROOM 2,207,
AND MR. KILLUA IN 2,223.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHICH DAY YOUR MATCH IS SET.
Gon: THANKS A LOT, MISS.
Killua: I'M WILLING TO BET
THAT THOSE GUYS
MUST HAVE GONE THROUGH
THE SAME TOUGH INITIATION
FOUR‐EYES WAS TALKING ABOUT.
( keys jangle )
IF WE'D GONE IN BLIND,
WE BOTH COULD HAVE ENDED UP
EXACTLY LIKE THEY DID.
Gon: WOW! THIS ROOM IS HUGE!
Killua: HEY!
AREN'T YOU LISTENING?
Gon: LOOK AT HOW SPARKLY
THE BATHROOM IS!
OH, WOW! I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH A BIG BED IN MY WHOLE LIFE!
LOOK, KILLUA!
( television chimes )
Killua: HMM?
HEY, GON.
WHAT? TOMORROW? THAT'S FAST.
( aura whooshes )
( Killua gasps )
♪
I DON'T THINK I CAN WIN YET,
BUT THAT'S OKAY!
I JUST NEED THE EXPERIENCE.
I NEED TO FIND OUT WHAT I CAN DO
NOW THAT I HAVE THIS POWER.
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: WE'VE GOT A THRILLING
MATCH FOR YOU TODAY, EVERYONE!
FIRST UP IS GON,
WHO MANAGED TO ZIP STRAIGHT
TO THIS FLOOR IN NO TIME AT ALL!
( cheering continues )
Cocco: HIS OPPONENT
WILL BE GIDO,
WHO CURRENTLY HOLDS
A RESPECTABLE RECORD
OF FOUR WINS AND ONE LOSS!
( peg leg and cane tapping )
( Gido cackles )
Wing: GON, KILLUA, LISTEN TO ME.
TEN IS ONLY DEFENSIVE.
IN TERMS OF OFFENSE,
IT WILL OFFER YOU NO ADVANTAGE.
IT IS ALSO IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER
PHYSICAL ATTACKS
WILL STILL CAUSE DAMAGE.
AN OPPONENT WHO IS HIGHLY
SKILLED IN THE USE OF NEN
WILL BE ABLE
TO PENETRATE YOUR TEN
AND CAN EASILY DEAL YOU
A LETHAL BLOW.
THAT'S WHY
YOU SHOULD WAIT TWO MONTHS
BEFORE YOU START FIGHTING.
DURING THAT TIME,
I WILL TEACH YOU
AS MUCH AS I'M ABLE.
Gon: I'M REALLY SORRY, MR. WING,
BUT I'M ITCHING
FOR A FIGHT RIGHT NOW!
Wing: GOODNESS GRACIOUS.
THAT BOY'S A REAL HANDFUL.
Referee: AND BEGIN!
( crowd cheering )
( Gon growls )
( Gido cackles )
♪
( Gon grunts )
Cocco: THERE THEY ARE,
GIDO'S DANCING TOPS!
HE USES AN ARSENAL
OF DANGEROUS SPINNING TOPS
TO ATTACK HIS OPPONENT
AND CRUSH THEM INTO SUBMISSION.
Gido: HERE WE GO!
BATTLE WALTZ!
( Gon gasps )
( gasps )
( crowd cheering )
Referee: CLEAN HIT!
Cocco: GON GIVES UP A HIT.
ONE POINT TO GIDO.
HE'S SURE NOT WASTING ANY TIME!
GON'S OFF TO A ROUGH START.
Gido: I CAN USE NEN
TO KEEP THESE TOPS
ATTACKING YOU FOR HOURS.
THE ATTACK PATTERN
IS SO INCREDIBLY COMPLEX
THAT NO ONE KNOWS WHAT THEY'LL
DO NEXT, NOT EVEN ME!
Gon: THE TOPS ARE BOUNCING OFF
EACH OTHER AND ATTACKING ME.
THEY MIGHT BE SMALL,
BUT THEY PACK A BIG PUNCH,
LIKE A HAMMER!
♪
Narrator: GON HAS BEGUN
HIS FIRST BATTLE
ON THE 200th FLOOR,
WHICH IS FILLED WITH NEN USERS.
IT'S NOTHING AT ALL
LIKE HE EXPECTED.
WILL GON SURVIVE
THIS PREDICAMENT
OR SUFFER DEFEAT?
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'LL
BE INTRODUCING GIDO.
HE FIGHTS WITH TOPS
CONTROLLED BY NEN.
Killua: MAYBE HE'LL TURN HIMSELF
INTO ONE AND SPIN INTO YOU.
Both: SPIN ROUND AND ROUND!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"FIERCE AND FEROCIOUS."
Killua: JUST DON'T BE
TOO RECKLESS.
Gon: A REAL FRIEND
WOULD WANT ME TO BE RECKLESS.
Killua: OKAY, THAT'S RECKLESS.