Uvogin: YOU'RE BY YOURSELF?
THAT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
I'LL LET YOU
DECIDE THE LOCATION.
Kurapika: I WOULD PREFER
SOMEWHERE REMOTE
SO WE WON'T BE A NUISANCE.
I WOULDN'T WANT YOUR SCREAMS
TO BOTHER ANYONE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: UVOGIN SEEKS TO
UNLEASH HIS RAGE UPON KURAPIKA,
WHO SEEKS HIS OWN REVENGE
AGAINST THE PHANTOM TROUPE
FOR HIS LOST BRETHREN.
BOTH ARE EAGER FOR THE BATTLE,
WHICH IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
( wind blowing )
( Uvogin laughs )
THERE WE GO.
THESE ALL LEECH EGGS?
( chuckles ) GROSS.
( footsteps )
SORRY FOR THE HOLDUP.
( sighs )
( chains jangle )
GOT A QUESTION FOR YOU.
( can crinkles )
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
YOU'RE NOT NORMAL.
I FEEL EXTRAORDINARY
DETERMINATION IN YOUR NEN.
Kurapika: BEFORE I
ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME.
DO YOU REMEMBER THOSE
YOU'VE KILLED, ANY OF THEM?
( Uvogin groans )
YEAH, SOME OF 'EM,
BUT MOSTLY JUST THE ONES WHO
MADE A LASTING IMPRESSION ON ME.
THIS IS SOME KIND OF VENDETTA?
WHO ARE YOU TRYING TO AVENGE?
Kurapika: THE KURTA CLAN.
Uvogin: MM.
I NEVER HEARD OF 'EM.
Kurapika: THE LUKSO PROVINCE,
A SMALL CLAN
WITH SCARLET‐COLORED EYES,
AND FIVE YEARS AGO,
YOU ATTACKED US.
Uvogin: SCARLET EYES?
WHAT'S THAT,
NAME OF A JEWEL OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, SORRY,
THAT DOESN'T RING A BELL,
BUT I WAS DEFINITELY
A MEMBER FIVE YEARS AGO.
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
Kurapika: WHEN YOU KILL PEOPLE,
PEOPLE WHO HAVE DONE
NO WRONG IN ANY WAY,
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
WHAT GOES THROUGH YOUR MIND?
Uvogin: NOTHING, REALLY,
NOT A THING.
Kurapika: YOU ARE SCUM.
FOR YOUR SINS...
YOU'LL PAY WITH YOUR LIFE!
♪
Uvogin: COMING ACROSS
PEOPLE LIKE YOU
IS THE REASON
KILLING NEVER GETS OLD.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT GIVES ME
THE MOST PLEASURE, THOUGH?
WHEN SOMEONE LIKE YOU
COMES FOR REVENGE
AND I TURN THE TABLES ON 'EM!
THOSE CHAINS ARE TROUBLE.
I'VE GOT NO IDEA WHAT KIND
OF TRICKERY HE USED ON 'EM,
BUT THOSE THINGS ARE INFUSED
WITH AN UNREAL AMOUNT OF NEN,
WHICH MEANS...
THAT I'VE GOTTA LAND
THE FIRST BLOW!
( Kurapika gasps )
Uvogin: THAT GOT HIM.
HMM?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
EVEN AFTER TAKING THAT PUNCH,
HE STILL HAD
THE ENERGY TO ATTACK?
LEAST I BUSTED HIS LEFT ARM.
( stammers )
( gasps ) NOT A SCRATCH? HOW?
BY HOW MUCH NEN'S
IN THOSE CHAINS,
I'D SAY HE'S A MANIPULATOR
WHO CONTROLS THINGS
OR A CONJURER
WHO CAN MATERIALIZE AURA.
IF I HAD TO GUESS,
I'D SAY IT'S THE FORMER,
BUT ONLY AN ENHANCER SHOULD
BE ABLE TO BLOCK MY ATTACK.
WHAT IS HE?
‐ Kurapika: THAT PUNCH...
‐ Uvogin: EH?
WAS IT THE BEST YOU'VE GOT?
( Uvogin sputters )
( laughs )
WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
THAT WAS ONLY 20%
OF MY STRENGTH.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
THIS TIME,
I'LL BE SURE TO USE HALF.
♪
( roars )
( gasps )
WHY, YOU...
( roars )
DAMN IT. LITTLE PUNK
KEEPS DARTING AROUND.
KNOW WHAT?
Kurapika: LET ME GUESS.
"YOU'LL REGRET THAT YOU DIDN'T
USE THE CHAIN JUST NOW." RIGHT?
Uvogin: HUH?
Kurapika: STOP MAKING EXCUSES,
AND FIGHT ME.
YOU'RE WASTING MY TIME.
Uvogin: YOU WANT IT? FINE.
FULL THROTTLE!
Kurapika: THAT'S
SOME INTENSE AURA HE HAS.
A SMOKE SCREEN?
HIS PRESENCE VANISHED.
HE'S USING IN.
( gasps )
( cracks )
Uvogin: I SHATTERED
YOUR ARM THIS TIME.
WHEN I USE MY BIG BANG IMPACT
AT FULL POWER,
NO EXPOSED FLESH IN THE WORLD
CAN STOP IT.
BUT I'M STILL IMPRESSED.
YOU WERE QUICK TO REACT.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
I'M GUESSING YOU NOTICED
THE SLIGHT CHANGES
IN THE SMOKE AND DUST.
Kurapika:
I AM IMPRESSED AS WELL.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU KNEW HOW TO USE IN.
STRIKING THE GROUND
TO RAISE A SMOKE SCREEN
WAS INTENDED TO CONCEAL
NOT ONLY YOUR PHYSICAL BODY,
BUT YOUR ENTIRE PRESENCE.
HOWEVER...
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN USE IN.
Uvogin: EH?
( grunts )
( gasps ) NO WAY!
( chains clinking )
Kurapika: SEE THEM?
( Uvogin grunts )
Kurapika: SO YOU
CAN USE GYO, TOO.
AS YOU MAY HAVE GUESSED,
THESE CHAINS
HAVE BEEN CONJURED OUT OF NEN,
MEANING I CAN USE IN
TO RENDER THEM INVISIBLE.
Uvogin: SO THAT'S WHY
YOU KEPT THEM
OUT IN THE OPEN ALL THE TIME,
TO TRICK US ALL
INTO THINKING THEY WERE REAL?
Kurapika: THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
I PRETENDED I WAS A MANIPULATOR
UTILIZING NEN‐CONTROLLED CHAINS
SO MY ENEMIES WOULD FOCUS
ON WHAT THEY SAW,
AND YOU JUST PROVED
THAT IT WAS EFFECTIVE.
YOU SEE,
WHILE YOU TOOK YOUR TIME
MAKING EMPTY THREATS,
MY CHAINS WERE ALREADY WRAPPED
AROUND YOUR BODY.
CAPTURE PHASE IS COMPLETE.
( Uvogin growls )
DAMN IT. BUT HOW?
HE HAS AN ENHANCER'S DEFENSES,
AND THE NEN IN HIS CONJURED
CHAINS IS INCREDIBLY STRONG.
HAS HE ACTUALLY MAXIMIZED
BOTH ENHANCEMENT
AND CONJURATION ABILITIES?
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
ISN'T IT?
A NEN USER IS ONLY CAPABLE
OF ACHIEVING 100% MASTERY
IN THE TYPE THEY WERE BORN WITH.
THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
Kurapika: SEEMS YOU'RE
HAVING TROUBLE UNDERSTANDING.
Uvogin: HUH?
Kurapika: LET ME EXPLAIN IT
AS A PARTING GIFT.
♪
Uvogin: HUH?
THOSE EYES.
HEY, NOW I REMEMBER.
A BUNCH OF 'EM LIVING
OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
THE BOSS REALLY LIKED
THOSE EYES.
AND THEY WERE ALL
PRETTY STRONG, TOO!
YOU A SURVIVOR?
( laughs )
I'M FIRED UP NOW!
HOW ABOUT WE SEE
WHAT'S STRONGER,
YOUR SILLY GRUDGE
OR MY BODY, HUH?!
Kurapika: FILTHY BASTARD,
IS THAT SERIOUSLY
ALL YOU CAN THINK ABOUT?
YOU WILL NEVER BREAK
THESE CHAINS.
( Uvogin roaring )
( panting )
WHAT THE‐‐‐WHAT'S WRONG?
SEE, I'M NOT ALWAYS
A SPECIALIST.
IT'S ONLY WHEN
MY EYES TURN SCARLET.
Uvogin: WAIT. WHAT?
Kurapika:
WITH MY SPECIALIST ABILITY,
I USE 100% OF ALL TYPES OF NEN,
AND THE NAME OF MY POWER IS...
EMPEROR TIME!
( Uvogin gasping )
Mizuken: CHAINS?
Kurapika: YES. WHEN YOU SAID
I WAS A CONJURER,
THAT WAS THE FIRST THING
THAT CAME TO MIND.
Mizuken: INTERESTING,
BUT WHY CHAINS?
Kurapika: IT'S BECAUSE
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE AT LARGE
IN THE WORLD RIGHT NOW
WHO NEED TO BE CHAINED TO HELL.
Mizuken: OH, IS THAT SO?
BECAUSE I CAN'T SHAKE
THE NAGGING SUSPICION
THAT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'LL BE CHAINED DOWN.
Kurapika: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW?
Mizuken: WAIT A SECOND!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M YOUR TEACHER! DO AS I SAY!
I'M NOT DONE TALKING TO YOU!
HOLD ON, DAMN IT!
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
ORDINARY CHAINS ARE POINTLESS!
THEY'RE INFERIOR!
NOT ONLY THAT,
CONJURING AN UNBREAKABLE CHAIN
IS IMPOSSIBLE!
REALLY?
AH, MAN.
YOU REALLY ARE STUBBORN,
AREN'T YOU?
CONJURING UNBREAKABLE CHAINS
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT BEING SAID, YOU CAN CONJURE
SOMETHING THAT'S VERY CLOSE.
Kurapika: IS THAT SO?
Mizuken: WOW. YOU ONLY HEAR
WHAT YOU WANT, HUH?
Kurapika: TELL ME HOW!
Mizuken: MAKE A CONTRACT
WITH CONDITIONS.
Kurapika: A CONTRACT?
WITH CONDITIONS?
Mizuken: YES.
DECIDE ON A CONDITION,
A RULE, IN OTHER WORDS,
AND SWEAR TO ABIDE BY IT
AT ANY COST, A CONTRACT.
THE STRICTER THE LIMITATION,
THE MORE POWER YOUR ABILITY
WILL BE ABLE TO GAIN FROM IT.
NEN IS AN ADDITIVE PROPERTY
IN MOST CASES.
IF NEN ADDS TO YOUR POWER,
A NEN CONTRACT
MULTIPLIES IT EXPONENTIALLY.
YOU'LL NEED TO COME UP WITH
A CONDITION FOR YOUR CHAINS,
ONE THAT YOU'RE
PREPARED TO KEEP,
BUT IT CAN BE DANGEROUS.
THIS TECHNIQUE
CAN BE INCREDIBLY VOLATILE.
IT'S A DOUBLE‐EDGED SWORD.
IF YOU BREAK
THE CONDITION THAT YOU SET,
YOU STAND TO LOSE
YOUR NEN ABILITIES ENTIRELY.
( Kurapika sighs )
MY ONLY OBJECTIVE IS TO FIND
MY BRETHREN'S SCARLET EYES
AND CAPTURE THE SPIDERS.
SO I WANT CHAINS THAT THEY,
THE PHANTOM TROUPE,
WILL NEVER BE ABLE TO BREAK.
THEY WILL BE MY ONLY TARGETS.
Mizuken: YOU'LL USE THESE CHAINS
SOLELY FOR THAT OBJECTIVE?
SEEMS RATHER WEAK TO ME.
Kurapika: LET ME FINISH.
USING THE CHAINS EXCLUSIVELY
ON THE PHANTOM TROUPE
IS NOTHING MORE
THAN A PREREQUISITE.
Mizuken: ALL RIGHT.
THEN WHAT IS YOUR RULE?
Kurapika: I STAKE MY LIFE ON IT.
Mizuken: HEY, KURAPIKA,
WHEN YOUR EYES
TURN SCARLET LIKE THAT,
IT MAKES YOUR AURA
LOOK A LOT BIGGER.
HOLD ON A MINUTE!
LET'S TRY
THE WATER DIVINATION AGAIN.
Uvogin: A SPECIALIST?
MOST PEOPLE CAN ONLY USE
ONE TYPE OF NEN,
BUT YOU USE ALL OF 'EM?
Kurapika: THAT'S CORRECT.
♪
( Uvogin gasps )
I CAN RECOVER
USING ENHANCED
SELF‐HEALING EASILY.
Uvogin: I COMPLETELY
SHATTERED HIS LEFT ARM,
BUT HE HEALED IT INSTANTLY.
Kurapika: THERE WERE
A NUMBER OF REASONS
I CHOSE YOU
AS MY FIRST TARGET.
AS YOU FOUGHT THE MAFIA
AND THE SHADOW BEASTS,
THE OTHER SPIDERS
STAYED COMPLETELY
OUT OF THE BATTLE ALTOGETHER.
THAT TOLD ME THAT YOU
PREFERRED TO FIGHT ALONE.
IT ALSO MADE IT CLEAR THAT THEY
TRUSTED YOUR ABILITIES.
I ALSO PREFER
TO FIGHT ONE‐ON‐ONE.
THAT MADE YOU
THE IDEAL OPPONENT.
YOU'RE AN ENHANCER,
AND YOU'RE PROUD
OF YOUR ABSOLUTE PHYSICAL
ATTACKS AND DEFENSE STRENGTH.
IN SHORT, YOU MET
EVERY CONDITION I REQUIRED
FOR MY FIRST TARGET.
YOU'RE A TEST. IF MY CHAIN JAIL
WORKS AGAINST YOU,
THEN IT'S A SAFE BET
THAT IT WOULD WORK
AGAINST THE REST OF YOU SPIDERS.
THE CHAIN JAIL STRIPS CAPTURED
SPIDERS OF THEIR FREEDOM
AND, AS YOU MAY HAVE REALIZED,
ENFORCES ZETSU.
( Uvogin grunts )
I GET IT.
SO THAT'S WHY
I COULDN'T PRODUCE ANY AURA.
( growls )
Kurapika: ZETSU, AS I'M SURE
YOU'RE AWARE BY NOW,
SHUTS OFF AURA COMPLETELY,
MEANING THAT YOU WOULD NEED
TO USE BRUTE STRENGTH ALONE
TO BREAK THESE CHAINS.
Uvogin: DAMN IT!
Kurapika: IF THE TROUPE MEMBER
WITH THE MOST PHYSICAL STRENGTH
CAN'T BREAK THEM,
IT STANDS TO REASON
THE OTHERS WON'T BE ABLE
TO ESCAPE THEM, EITHER.
Uvogin: HIS ENFORCED ZETSU
IS BAD...
REALLY BAD.
NEN DRAWS ITS ENERGY FROM AURA,
AND IF IT'S SHUT OFF,
YOU CAN'T USE YOUR POWER.
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
A TECHNIQUE
FOR SEALING NEN ABILITIES.
THIS GUY'S
THOUGHT OF EVERYTHING.
( gasps )
( gags )
WELL, THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
IT WOULD APPEAR
THAT MY ENHANCED FIST
IS SLIGHTLY STRONGER
THAN YOUR NORMAL FLESH.
THAT'S VALUABLE INFORMATION.
( Uvogin chuckles )
PROVIDED I'VE CHAINED THEM,
I CAN DEFEAT
EVERY TROUPE MEMBER BAREHANDED.
NOW TELL ME
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
DO NOT LEAVE ANYTHING OUT.
( Uvogin scoffs )
( gags )
Kurapika: WHERE CAN
I FIND THE OTHERS?
Uvogin: KILL ME.
‐ ( cracks )
‐ ( gasps )
Kurapika: WHAT ABILITIES
DO THEY EACH HAVE?
( Uvogin sighs ) JUST KILL ME.
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
( blows striking )
( grunting )
( coughs )
Kurapika: ALL OF THIS
MAKES ME SICK.
THE WAY MY HAND FEELS,
THE GRATING SOUND
OF EACH STRIKE,
THE SMELL OF BLOOD,
EVERY SENSATION MAKES ME SICK.
HOW CAN YOU COMMIT
SUCH ATROCITIES
AND NOT FEEL ANYTHING?!
HOW IS IT POSSIBLE?!
ANSWER ME!
( Uvogin groans )
KILL ME.
( gasps )
( heart beats )
Kurapika: THIS IS
YOUR FINAL CHANCE.
I HAVE PIERCED YOUR HEART
WITH THE STAKE OF RETRIBUTION.
I AM NOW GOING TO SET A RULE.
BREAKING IT WILL ACTIVATE
THE CHAIN AND CRUSH YOUR HEART.
AND THE RULE IS...
THAT YOU HAVE TO ANSWER
ALL OF MY QUESTIONS TRUTHFULLY.
ABIDE BY THAT RULE, AND I
WILL LET YOU LIVE A BIT LONGER.
TELL ME
WHERE I CAN FIND THE OTHERS.
( Uvogin chuckles )
GO TO HELL, YOU SON OF A BITCH.
( gags )
( Kurapika gasping )
THAT PROBABLY TOOK ME
LONGER THAN IT SHOULD HAVE.
( dials cell phone )
IT'S ME.
Melody: KURAPIKA,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL?
ARE YOU OKAY?
Kurapika: YEAH.
Melody: OH, GOOD.
Kurapika: HOW ARE THINGS THERE?
Melody: THE BOSS IS SAFE.
SHE'S ASLEEP IN HER ROOM.
UNFORTUNATELY,
DUE TO THE WEATHER,
HER FATHER WON'T BE ARRIVING
UNTIL LATE TONIGHT.
Kurapika: UNDERSTOOD. THANKS.
( shovel scraping )
♪
Chrollo: A CHAIN USER.
PROBABLY A MANIPULATOR
OR A CONJURER.
UVOGIN CAN HOLD HIS OWN
IN A FIGHT,
BUT ONE‐ON‐ONE,
HE'S MOST VULNERABLE
TO THOSE TWO CATEGORIES.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON FOR A CONJURER
TO ENHANCE
THE THINGS HE CREATES.
MANY DO...
AND SOME OF THOSE ABILITIES
COULD EASILY
RENDER UVO HELPLESS.
AND A MANIPULATOR
COULD MANIPULATE UVO HIMSELF.
Shalnark: I KNEW IT!
I JUST KNEW I SHOULD HAVE
GONE WITH HIM! DAMN IT!
Chrollo: IF HE FAILS
TO RETURN HERE BY DAWN,
THEN WE'LL SWITCH PLANS.
♪
Narrator: SHALNARK SENSES DANGER
AS UVOGIN FAILS TO RETURN,
AND THEIR LEADER CHROLLO
BEGINS FORMULATING A PLAN
TO TERMINATE THE CHAIN USER.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING UVOGIN.
HE'S REALLY BIG AND
A MEMBER OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Killua: HIS ULTIMATE ATTACK
IS A NEN‐INFUSED
STRAIGHT RIGHT PUNCH.
Both: SO WATCH OUT
FOR THE BIG BANG IMPACT!
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"VERY SHARP EYE."
IT'S SO SHARP, IT'S LIKE
A RAZOR BLADE OR SOMETHING.
Killua: WHOA!
THAT SOUNDS AWESOME!