Neon: OH! THIS IS
THE FOUNDATION I WANTED!
AND THIS LIPSTICK,
THIS SPRAY‐ON MANICURE.
OOH, AND THIS WIG IS SO CUTE!
Melody: UM, BOSS, WE REALLY
SHOULD GET GOING SOON.
Neon: JUST A SECOND!
I WANT THIS CAMISOLE, TOO.
( Basho sighs )
ALL THIS SHOPPING'S
GONNA BE THE DEATH OF ME.
Melody: I AGREE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Neon: IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I SHOULD BUY WHILE WE'RE HERE?
WHAT ABOUT YOU, ELIZA?
YOU WANT ANYTHING?
Eliza: OH, NO.
I'M FINE. THANK YOU.
‐ ( overlapping chatter )
‐ Neon: HUH? HMM.
I'M GOING TO THE RESTROOM.
DON'T WORRY.
JUST WATCH MY STUFF, OKAY?
Basho: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WILL KURAPIKA BE OKAY?
Melody: I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
MY FLUTE SHOULD HAVE HELPED
ALLEVIATE HIS FATIGUE,
AT LEAST A LITTLE.
Basho: HMM.
THIS ASSASSINATION...
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT IT?
Nostrade: THE TEN DONS WILL HIRE
PROS TO HANDLE THE TROUPE.
Kurapika: SIR?
Nostrade: AND SO...
I WANT YOU TO JOIN
THE ASSASSIN TEAM.
Melody: JUDGING BY
THE PACE OF HIS HEARTBEAT,
HE WASN'T
ALL THAT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
I DON'T BELIEVE HE WANTED
TO JOIN THE ASSASSIN TEAM.
Basho: OF COURSE HE DIDN'T.
Melody: BUT AS YOU WELL KNOW,
KURAPIKA IS
EXTREMELY DETERMINED,
AND HE IS WILLING
TO SACRIFICE EVERYTHING
IF IT MEANS THAT HE'S ABLE
TO ACHIEVE HIS DESIRED GOAL.
Basho: NOT AN EASY ROAD TO WALK.
I COULDN'T LIVE THAT WAY.
A LIFE WHERE YOU'RE
BASICALLY KILLING YOURSELF,
WHAT'S THE POINT?
Eliza: IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
I HOPE SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
Basho: ONCE WE FINISH THIS JOB,
I'M CASHING OUT AND
SEEING THE WORLD ON MY BIKE.
Melody: THAT DOES
SOUND DELIGHTFUL.
Basho: NOT ENJOYING LIFE
IS A CRIME.
Melody: THERE ARE
MANY WAYS TO LIVE.
NOT EVERYONE HAS THE SAME IDEAS
ABOUT WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
( Eliza gasping )
Basho: HMM?
Melody: SOMETHING WRONG?
Eliza: THE BOSS IS GONE!
‐ Basho: WAIT. WHAT?!
‐ Melody: HUH?
Neon: DADDY'S A BIG LIAR.
HE WASN'T GOING TO TAKE ME
TO THE AUCTION,
AND HE PROMISED AND EVERYTHING.
FINE, THEN.
I'LL JUST GO BY MYSELF.
♪
( knock on door )
Mafioso: COME IN.
( door opens, closes )
ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, SIX.
IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE IS HERE.
Mafioso #2: NO. NOT YET.
Mafioso #1: WHAT? I THOUGHT
THE TEAM HAD EIGHT MEMBERS.
Mafioso #2: NOSTRADE
WILL BE SENDING OVER
ONE ADDITIONAL PERSON.
Mafioso #1: EH, THAT BROWN‐NOSER
THE FAKE FORTUNETELLING, EH?
ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT EVERYONE ALL TOGETHER.
YOUR MISSION IS TO WIPE OUT
THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
WHEN THE AUCTION
KICKS OFF AGAIN TONIGHT,
THEY MAY COME OUT OF HIDING,
AND IF THEY DO, ELIMINATE THEM
ANY WAY YOU SEE FIT.
Assassin: SO ALL OF US ARE
GOING AFTER THE SAME TARGET.
WE SHOULD PICK OUT
SOME CODE NAMES
TO USE FOR EACH OTHER.
Assassin #2: LET'S USE COLORS.
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME BLUE.
Red: I'LL BE RED.
Zeno: IT'S LIKE A GAME,
ISN'T IT?
Assassin #1: HMM?
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
‐ Silva: SILVA.
‐ Zeno: ZENO.
Assassin #1: ZENO, EH?
WHAT COLOR'S THAT?
Zeno: WE WILL BOTH USE
OUR REAL NAMES.
Blue: YOU WILL?
Silva: YOU ARE WELCOME
TO CALL ME BY MY NAME,
BUT I WON'T TAKE ORDERS,
AND WE'LL DO THIS OUR OWN WAY.
Assassin #3: HOLD ON.
SILVA AND ZENO?
LIKE OF THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY?
( Kurapika gasps )
Zeno: LET ME KNOW
IF YOU WANT SOMEONE KILLED.
YOU GET 30% OFF
FOR BEING IN THE SAME INDUSTRY.
( assassins gasp )
Kurapika:
SO THEY'RE KILLUA'S FAMILY.
Assassin #4:
WE COULD USE CODE NAMES,
BUT DOES IT MATTER?
Assassin #5: HE HAS A POINT.
THERE'S NO RULE THAT SAYS
WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
Assassin #1: BUT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE TROUPE HERE.
ATTACKING ALONE
WILL BE DANGEROUS.
( assassins grunt )
Assassin #4: AND YOU?
Kurapika: SLOPPY TEAMWORK WILL
ONLY SERVE TO CAUSE CONFUSION.
I'LL BE FINE BY MYSELF.
( assassin #4 chuckles )
IT'S FIVE TO FOUR.
THERE YOU GO.
Mafioso #2: THE AUCTION
BEGINS AT 9:00.
WE'LL ESCORT YOU
TO THE AUCTION HALL.
WAIT HERE UNTIL IT'S TIME.
( door opens )
Mafioso #1: HEY, NOSTRADE.
HOW DO YOU FEEL, MY FRIEND?
Nostrade: NOT TOO BAD.
Mafioso #1: NOT TOO BAD, HUH?
YOU'RE A BIG SHOT NOW,
AREN'T YOU?
NOT LONG AGO, YOU WERE JUST
HEADING UP A SMALL COUNTRY GANG,
AND NOW YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE YOU'RE MY EQUAL.
I HEAR THAT YOU'VE BEEN
WRINGING YOUR HANDS SO MUCH,
YOUR SKIN'S RUBBED OFF.
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
( laughs )
Nostrade: JEALOUSY AMONG MEN
IS PATHETIC.
Mafioso #1: BASTARD!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS,
YOU LITTLE PUNK?
IF YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME,
GO AHEAD!
Nostrade: KURAPIKA,
THAT'S ENOUGH!
( chains jangle )
Mafioso #1:
GET ONE THING STRAIGHT.
NO ONE IS IMPRESSED BY YOU.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
( car door closes )
Nostrade:
MANY RESENT MY SUCCESS,
BECAUSE THEY'RE UNAWARE
OF THEIR OWN INCOMPETENCE,
BUT I PLAN TO CONTINUE
MY RISE TO THE TOP
USING NEON'S FORTUNETELLING.
I'M DEPENDING ON YOU,
TOO, KURAPIKA.
YOU'LL BE REWARDED
GENEROUSLY IN TIME.
Kurapika: YES, SIR.
( whistle blows )
Kurapika: ARE THE POLICE
HELPING YOU?
Nostrade: 60% OF THE VOTES
IN THE YORKNEW CITY MAYOR'S
ELECTION WERE BOUGHT,
AND THE POLICE CHIEF
IS THE MAYOR'S LAPDOG.
IMPOSING TRAFFIC RESTRICTIONS
IS SIMPLE.
( cell phone rings )
Kurapika: YES? HELLO.
Melody: KURAPIKA, BAD NEWS!
THE BOSS RAN AWAY!
SHE CHANGED CLOTHES
WHEN SHE WENT TO THE RESTROOM,
SO SHE MUST HAVE PLANNED AHEAD.
Kurapika: DON'T WORRY. I THINK
I MIGHT KNOW WHERE SHE WENT.
GO BACK TO THE HOTEL,
AND STAND BY.
Nostrade: WHAT NOW?
Kurapika: YOUR DAUGHTER
HAS RUN AWAY.
Nostrade: SHE WHAT?!
( coughs )
Kurapika: SHE'LL LIKELY HEAD
TO OUR DESTINATION.
Nostrade: THE AUCTION?
( beeping )
( growls )
DAMN. SHE TURNED OFF
HER CELL PHONE.
BUT NEON DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
A PASS TO THE AUCTION.
THEY'LL TURN HER AWAY
WHEN SHE REACHES THE CHECKPOINT.
THIS IS LIGHT NOSTRADE.
I NEED FOR YOU TO GIVE AN ORDER
TO THE GUARDS AT THE GATE.
IF A GIRL AROUND 17 OR 18
TRIES TO ENTER WITHOUT A PASS,
TAKE HER INTO CUSTODY.
HER DESCRIPTION IS...
( scanner beeps )
Officer: YOU'RE ALL SET. THANKS.
YOU CAN GO AHEAD NOW.
Neon: WHEW!
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW
TO GET THROUGH THAT GATE,
SO THANKS A LOT FOR THE HELP.
Man: HAPPY TO BE OF SERVICE.
Nostrade: REALLY?!
WHEN WAS THAT?
Officer #2:
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES AGO.
HER HAIR AND CLOTHES
WERE A LITTLE DIFFERENT,
BUT IT WAS PROBABLY HER.
Nostrade: AND SHE
DIDN'T HAVE A PASS?
Officer #2:
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
IT DIDN'T SEEM TO ME LIKE SHE
EVEN KNEW SHE NEEDED ONE.
SHE MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT WHO HER DADDY WAS,
BUT THEN SHE JUST LEFT.
YES, SHE GOT INTO A TAXI ALONE.
RIGHT. YES, SIR.
Shalnark: THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.
( Nostrade groans )
WHERE COULD SHE HAVE GONE?
Kurapika: I'LL SEARCH FOR HER.
DO YOU HAVE A MAP
OF YORKNEW CITY?
Nostrade: EH?
♪
Man: I HEAR YOU'RE
A GOOD FORTUNETELLER.
‐ Neon: HUH?
‐ ( man chuckles )
SOMEONE TOLD ME ONCE.
I CAN'T RECALL WHO.
Neon: I AM GOOD.
IMPORTANT PEOPLE
ARE ALWAYS COMING TO ME.
Man: HOW ACCURATE ARE YOU?
Neon: THEY SAY I'M ALWAYS RIGHT.
( man chuckles )
"THEY"? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SHOULDN'T
THE FORTUNETELLER KNOW?
Neon: MY HAND MOVES ON ITS OWN.
Man: AH. IMPRESSIVE!
WOULD YOU TELL ME MINE?
Neon: OKAY.
JUST WRITE DOWN YOUR NAME,
YOUR BIRTH DATE,
AND BLOOD TYPE,
AND THEN I'LL TAKE IT
FROM THERE.
Man: THINK THIS'LL WORK?
Neon: LET'S SEE.
YOUR NAME'S
REALLY CHROLLO LUCILFER?
WHAT KIND OF NAME IS THAT?
Chrollo: WELL, MY FRIENDS
JUST CALL ME "BOSS."
( Neon laughs ) BOSS?
WOW! THAT'S EVEN WEIRDER!
( Chrollo chuckles )
Neon: OKAY, HERE GOES.
Kurapika: IT APPEARS
YOUR DAUGHTER IS ALREADY
IN THE CEMETERY BUILDING
ON THE AUCTION SITE.
Nostrade: SHE IS?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
Kurapika: NOT SURE,
BUT WE NEED TO HURRY.
♪
Neon: THERE. ALL DONE.
Chrollo: THEN CAN I READ IT?
Neon: YEAH, SURE!
MY FORTUNES ARE KINDA STRANGE.
THEY'RE USUALLY MADE UP
OF FOUR OR FIVE POEMS.
EACH ONE CORRESPONDS
TO A WEEK OF THAT MONTH,
SO THE FIRST ONE MIGHT JUST BE
SOME STUFF
THAT HAPPENED ALREADY.
Chrollo: AH.
FOREVER SET,
A PRECIOUS MOON IS LOST.
THE OTHERS MOURN HIM
WITH CEREMONY GRAND...
RISING UP TO HEAVEN
THE MIGHTY MOON OF FROST
WITH A MELODY
FROM THE MOURNING BAND.
( Neon gasps )
♪
Chrollo: IT'S AMAZING...
AND CORRECT.
ABOUT THIS FIRST POEM...
Neon: DON'T TELL ME,
PLEASE! REALLY.
I NEVER LOOK
AT THE FORTUNES I WRITE.
‐ Chrollo: WHY NOT?
‐ Neon: I JUST GET THE FEELING
THEY'LL BE A LOT MORE ACCURATE
IF I DON'T GET INVOLVED.
Chrollo: THEN WOULD YOU MIND
IF I ASKED YOU A QUESTION?
Neon: SURE.
Chrollo: THIS VERSE,
IT MAKES REFERENCE
TO A REQUIEM FOR THE DEAD.
DO YOU BELIEVE
IN AN AFTERLIFE, NEON?
Neon: HMM.
I GUESS I DON'T, NOT REALLY.
FORTUNES ARE ONLY WRITTEN
TO HELP THE LIVING,
AND IN THIS CASE,
THAT'S YOU, MISTER CHROLLO.
A REQUIEM DOESN'T HELP
A DEAD PERSON.
IT COMFORTS THOSE
WHO ARE LEFT BEHIND.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK, ANYWAY.
Chrollo: AND YOU'RE
PROBABLY RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
THE AUCTION PREVIEW
IS ABOUT TO START.
Neon: WHAT I SAID,
I HEARD FROM SOMEONE ELSE.
Chrollo: WHAT?
Neon: A FORTUNETELLER ON TV
SAID IT WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
YOU KNOW, WHAT I SAID BEFORE
ABOUT HOW
THE PURPOSE OF FORTUNES
IS TO MAKE
LIVING PEOPLE HAPPY.
Chrollo: OH?
Neon: AND SO THE FORTUNETELLER
TRIED REALLY HARD
TO GIVE
NEGATIVE FORTUNES TO PEOPLE.
Chrollo: NEGATIVE?
Neon: YOU SEE, THAT WAY,
PEOPLE WOULD MAKE AN EFFORT
TO IMPROVE THEIR LIVES
AND TO AVOID MISFORTUNE.
BACK THEN, I CAN REMEMBER
BEING REALLY INSPIRED
BY HOW TRUE THAT WAS.
THAT'S WHEN I DECIDED
I WOULD BE A FORTUNETELLER.
Chrollo: FOREVER SET,
A PRECIOUS MOON IS LOST.
THE OTHERS MOURN HIM
WITH CEREMONY GRAND...
RISING UP TO HEAVEN
THE MIGHTY MOON OF FROST
WITH A MELODY
FROM THE MOURNING BAND.
HARVEST BARREN, WINE SPILLED,
LOVERS SLUMBER
BESIDE THE BLOODY SCARLET EYES.
THOUGH CUT IN HALF
SHALL BE YOUR NUMBER,
'TIS NOT LOST
WHEREIN YOUR ADVANTAGE LIES.
AMUSE YOURSELF
WITH THE ENTR'ACTE.
SEEK OUT NEW FRIENDS
ONCE IN A BIND.
PERHAPS TO THE EAST,
ONE CAN BE TRACKED.
THE ONE MOST NEEDED,
YOU'RE SURE TO FIND.
Neon: A FEW YEARS LATER,
THAT FORTUNETELLER ENDED UP
GETTING ARRESTED FOR FRAUD.
Chrollo: DO YOU MEAN
THE GALACTIC MATRON?
Neon: THAT'S THE ONE.
Chrollo: IF MEMORY SERVES,
SHE DIDN'T BELIEVE
IN THE AFTERLIFE.
Neon: SHE DIDN'T, AND THAT'S WHY
I DON'T BELIEVE IN IT EITHER.
( elevator chimes )
Chrollo: PERSONALLY,
I BELIEVE WE HAVE A SOUL.
Neon: HUH?
Chrollo: SEE, THAT'S THE REASON
I WANTED TO FULFILL
MY DEAD FRIEND'S WISH.
IT'S WHAT HE WOULD HAVE WANTED.
Neon: WHAT WISH?
Chrollo: TO WREAK HAVOC.
♪
( gasps )
ARE YOU OKAY?!
CALL A DOCTOR, QUICKLY!
Guard: FIRST FLOOR. WE'RE OVER
BY THE NORTH ELEVATOR.
SOMEONE'S SICK.
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
Mafioso #3: WE CAN'T.
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY'RE GONNA LET
AN AMBULANCE COME IN HERE,
NOT IF THEY DON'T HAVE
AN AUCTION PASS ON 'EM.
Chrollo: YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
WHAT IF SHE DIES?
WHAT HAPPENS THEN, HUH?!
SHE'S THE DAUGHTER
OF THE NOSTRADE FAMILY BOSS!
IF SHE DIES HERE,
IT'S ON YOUR HEAD, UNDERSTAND?
( mafioso #3 scoffs )
YEAH, I HEARD YOU.
SOME OF THE TEN DONS
ARE BIG FANS OF HERS.
WE'RE ON IT. JUST SIT TIGHT.
HEY! CALL FOR AN AMBULANCE!
Mafioso #4: RIGHT!
Assassin #4:
HEY, TELL ME SOMETHING.
CAN YOU REWIND
WHAT'S ON THIS MONITOR?
Mafioso #5: HMM? SURE.
Assassin #4: THE SWIFTEST CHOP.
ANYONE ELSE
WOULD'VE MISSED IT.
I'VE MISSED THIS EXCITEMENT.
( chuckles )
I FOUND MY PREY.
Mafioso #6: MASTER NOSTRADE,
YOUR DAUGHTER IS RESTING
IN ROOM 501
UP ON THE FIFTH FLOOR.
Nostrade: THERE'S SIMPLY NO WAY
SHE COULD HAVE GOTTEN
HER HANDS ON A PASS.
HOW DID SHE GET IN?
Kurapika:
YOUR DAUGHTER'S PICTURE
IS ACCESSIBLE
ON THE HUNTER WEBSITE.
Nostrade: WHAT?!
Kurapika: MOST LIKELY, SOMEONE
LOCATED THIS PICTURE OF HER
ON THE WEBSITE, FOUND HER,
AND BROUGHT HER HERE SOON AFTER.
( Nostrade growls )
I'LL FIND THAT SCUM
AND KILL HIM.
Kurapika: CALM DOWN, SIR.
I DON'T THINK
CAPTURING YOUR DAUGHTER
WAS THEIR PRIMARY OBJECTIVE.
IT'S POSSIBLE
THEY USED HER AS A HOSTAGE,
IN CASE THEY COULDN'T
GET INTO THE BUILDING.
( Nostrade grunts )
Kurapika: IT'S DANGEROUS HERE,
SO I'VE CALLED MELODY AND BASHO.
THEY'LL BE HERE SOON.
Nostrade: ARE YOU SURE IT'S WISE
TO LEAVE IT TO THEM?
Kurapika: YOU SHOULD STAY
WITH HER, TOO, SIR.
Nostrade: BUT THE AUCTION‐‐
‐ Kurapika: THERE WON'T BE ONE.
‐ Nostrade: HMM?
Kurapika: THIS WILL BE
A BATTLEFIELD.
THE AUCTION IS SURE
TO BE CANCELED AGAIN.
♪
Assassin #4: A TRAIL OF BLOOD
DRIPPED ON PURPOSE,
ENOUGH TO BE DETECTED, SMELLED
BY ONE OF THE SAME BREED.
WE ARE THE SAME, HE AND I.
WE'RE PREDATORS,
BOTH ADDICTED TO KILLING.
Chrollo: DON'T WORRY.
I DON'T USE CHEAP TRAPS.
ONE‐ON‐ONE?
Assassin #4: SOUNDS GOOD.
Feitan: I HAVE A MESSAGE.
THE BOSS SAID,
"COME TO THE CEMETERY BUILDING
AND WREAK HAVOC."
( bone cracks )
Phinks: THE CEMETERY BUILDING'S
NOT TOO FAR FROM HERE.
WHERE ARE THE OTHERS?
Feitan: THINKING
THE SAME THING AS US,
CLEANING UP THE TRASH
ON THE WAY TO THE BUILDING.
Phinks: OKAY. THEN, LET'S GO.
Feitan: THERE'S MORE. THE BOSS
ADDED AN UNUSUAL RULE THIS TIME.
Phinks: OH, YEAH? WHAT?
Chrollo: MAKE IT A BIG SHOW.
♪
( music playing only )
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
Chrollo: FOREVER SET,
A PRECIOUS MOON IS LOST.
THE OTHERS MOURN HIM
WITH CEREMONY GRAND,
RISING UP TO HEAVEN
THE MIGHTY MOON OF FROST
WITH A MELODY
FROM THE MOURNING BAND.
HARVEST BARREN, WINE SPILLED,
LOVERS SLUMBER
BESIDE THE BLOODY SCARLET EYES.
THOUGH CUT IN HALF YOUR NUMBER,
'TIS NOT LOST,
WHEREIN YOUR ADVANTAGE LIES.
AMUSE YOURSELF
WITH THE ENTR'ACTE.
SEEK NEW FRIENDS ONCE IN A BIND.
PERHAPS TO THE EAST,
ONE CAN BE TRACKED.
THE ONE MOST NEEDED,
YOU'RE SURE TO FIND.
( chorus continues singing )
( assassin #4 sputters )
( laughing )
WHY, HUH? TELL ME WHY?!
( laughs )
WHY?
WHY AM I ALIVE?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Chrollo: THIS IS AN INDOOR FISH,
A NEN FISH THAT CAN ONLY LIVE
IN ENCLOSED SPACES,
A CARNIVORE
THAT PREFERS HUMAN FLESH.
YOU DON'T BLEED OR FEEL PAIN
AS YOU'RE EATEN.
YOU CAN'T DIE
UNTIL THE NEN FISH DISAPPEARS.
( assassin #4 laughs )
WON'T DIE?
( laughs )
( wind blowing )
( body thuds )
( Chrollo sighs )
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
FOREVER SET,
A PRECIOUS MOON IS LOST.
THE OTHERS MOURN HIM
WITH CEREMONY GRAND...
RISING UP TO HEAVEN
THE MIGHTY MOON OF FROST
WITH A MELODY
FROM THE MOURNING BAND.
( chorus continues )
WELL, UVO, CAN YOU HEAR IT?
WE DEDICATE THIS REQUIEM TO YOU.
Narrator: IT WAS THE BEGINNING
OF A STORMY NIGHT THAT,
WHILE FIERCE
AND DRENCHED WITH BLOOD,
WAS SOMEHOW OVERWHELMINGLY SAD.
( orchestra and chorus
continue )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING PHINKS,
A TROUPE MEMBER,
AND HE'S ALSO AN ENHANCER.
Killua: HE'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO PUNCH
STRAIGHT THROUGH A HUMAN BODY.
Gon: AND SOMETIMES
HE DRESSES IN EGYPTIAN CLOTHING.
Killua: YOU'RE THINKING
OF "SPHINX."
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"ASSAULT AND IMPACT."
Killua: OH, GON,
WHEREFORE ART THOU, GON?
Gon: KILLUA, I'M GON.
THAT'S WHEREFORE.
Killua: WAIT. THAT'S IT?!