( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Johness: I'LL TEAR
YOUR BODY APART.
( heart beats )
( heart beating )
( Johness gasps )
♪♪♪
Announcer: THE EXAM'S
THIRD PHASE REQUIRED APPLICANTS
TO REACH TRICK TOWER'S BASE
WITHIN 72 HOURS,
BUT GON AND HIS FRIENDS
INCURRED A PENALTY
AND WERE FORCED
TO WAIT FOR 50 HOURS.
MEANWHILE...
Announcer: GERETTA,
APPLICANT 384,
IS THE FOURTH TO PASS.
TIME ELAPSED,
12 HOURS AND 27 MINUTES.
Geretta: WELL, NOT BAD, I GUESS.
Killua: BE CAREFUL NOT
TO HESITATE ON THE FIRST STEP,
OR YOU'RE GONNA HURT YOURSELF.
‐ HERE.
‐ Gon: I GOT YA.
Leorio: HEY, KURAPIKA,
ONCE WE'VE FINISHED
SPENDING OUR 50 HOURS HERE,
WE'LL HAVE LESS
THAN 10 HOURS LEFT, RIGHT?
Kurapika: YES. THAT'S CORRECT.
Leorio: GREAT! THAT'S WAY
MORE TIME THAN WE'LL NEED,
SO NO HARM DONE!
Tonpa: YOU'RE A FOOL.
Leorio: WHAT'S THAT?
Tonpa: THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM
IS SUPPOSED TO TAKE 72 HOURS,
AND EACH NEW PHASE WEEDS OUT
MORE OF THE APPLICANTS,
CUTTING THE FIELD
ROUGHLY IN HALF EVERY TIME.
IN OTHER WORDS, IT'S MEANT
TO TAKE 72 HOURS ON AVERAGE.
THE FACT YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT
IS PROOF THAT YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
( Leorio growls )
Kurapika: THEN OUR CHANCES
OF REACHING THE FINISH
WITHIN 10 HOURS WILL DEPEND
ON THE REMAINING TRIALS.
Leorio: YEAH. I GUESS
YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
Tonpa: HUMPH.
IT'S TOO BAD YOU'RE SO UNLUCKY
YOU CAN'T EVEN WIN
A GAME OF ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS
‐ WHEN IT COUNTS.
‐ Leorio: WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
Tonpa: YOU DELIBERATELY LOST
A BET SO YOU COULD COP A FEEL.
THEN YOU PICKED A GAME
YOU DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE
OF WINNING.
Leorio: HEY, SHUT UP!
YOU SURRENDERED
BEFORE YOUR FIGHT
EVEN GOT STARTED!
Tonpa: I...
GIVE UP!
SURE, I THREW IN THE TOWEL.
I CAN ADMIT THAT.
BUT I ONLY WASTED
A COUPLE OF SECONDS.
‐ ( Leorio growls )
‐ Tonpa: YOU DIDN'T JUST LOSE.
YOU SQUANDERED 50 HOURS
WE COULD REALLY USE RIGHT NOW.
THE LEAST YOU COULD DO
IS TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
( Leorio growls )
Tonpa: AND BESIDES,
WHO EVER HEARD OF A HUNTER
WHO SUCKED AT GAMBLING?
Leorio: SHUT UP! YOU DON'T
EVEN WANT TO BECOME A HUNTER!
THE ONLY REASON YOU'RE HERE
IS TO RUIN OUR CHANCES!
( Tonpa chuckles )
AND NOW YOU'LL HAVE
THAT GUILT EATING AWAY AT YOU
FOR THE REST OF THIS PHASE.
( crash )
Leorio: HEY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Gon: OOPS! SORRY.
Leorio: THIS ROOM ISN'T
BIG ENOUGH FOR SKATEBOARDING,
SO KNOCK IT OFF!
Gon: AWW!
( Leorio snoring )
( Tonpa grunts )
Kurapika: MM?
CAN'T SLEEP?
Killua: NOT REALLY.
THING IS I CAN STAY AWAKE
TWO OR THREE DAYS AT A TIME.
Kurapika: 10 HOURS DOWN, HUH?
Killua: WITH NO WINDOWS,
IT'S HARD TO TELL,
BUT IT'S PROBABLY MORNING.
Kurapika: MOST LIKELY.
( Killua snickers )
( gasps ) HUH?
( both grunting )
( Killua laughs )
( grunting, laughing continues )
Leorio: KNOCK IT OFF, YOU GUYS!
( both laugh )
Leorio: SOME OF US
ARE TRYIN' TO SLEEP.
UGH. GROSS!
( both laugh )
( Kurapika chuckling )
Leorio: NOT FUNNY! WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU GUYS?
‐ ( Tonpa snoring )
‐ Leorio: YOU BASTARD.
YOU'D BETTER NOT JUST
BE PRETENDING TO BE ASLEEP.
DAMN IT.
WELL, I GUESS I'M AWAKE NOW,
AND WE'VE STILL GOT
40 MORE HOURS LEFT TO GO.
( snoring )
( clicking )
Killua: HMM.
I THOUGHT FISHING WAS JUST
PUTTING SOME BAIT ON A HOOK
AND THROWING IT IN THE WATER.
Gon: MM‐HMM, BUT YOU'VE ALSO
GOTTA THINK LIKE A FISH.
Killua: AND THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO WORK?
Gon: YUP! HOW WOULD A FISH FEEL
IF IT SAW BAIT
DANGLING IN FRONT OF IT?
GIMME!
Tonpa: UH...
HUH?
Killua: OH, WOW.
LET ME GIVE IT A TRY.
SO LIKE THIS?
( Gon laughs ) YOU MISSED.
Killua: YEAH, BUT WATCH THIS.
( Leorio grunts )
HEY! WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING? STOP!
‐ Killua: RIGHT ON TARGET.
‐ Gon: NICE!
Leorio: WAIT!
YOU'RE GONNA TEAR MY PANTS!
KNOCK IT OFF!
Killua: YOU SEE?
I LANDED A BIG ONE.
Gon: YEP.
Leorio: DO I LOOK
LIKE A FISH TO YOU?!
COME ON! GROW UP!
Killua: WELL, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GET SO MAD.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GONNA
GRILL YOU AND EAT YOU.
Leorio: JUST LEAVE ME
THE HELL ALONE!
CAN'T A GUY
JUST TAKE A NAP AROUND HERE?
( both laugh )
( Leorio growls )
Tonpa: HMM.
Leorio: WHAT ARE YOU
SMILING ABOUT?
Tonpa: HUH? UH, NOTHING.
Leorio: YOU'RE UP TO SOMETHING
AGAIN, AREN'T YOU?
Tonpa: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
ALL I WANT IS TO SPEND
THE REST OF OUR TIME HERE
IN PEACE AND QUIET.
Leorio: YOU LIAR.
I DON'T TRUST YOU
AS FAR AS I CAN THROW YOU.
GOT IT?
Tonpa: HMM.
( thinking )
FEELING'S MUTUAL.
( doors sliding )
Pokkle: ALL RIGHT! GOAL!
HMM?
Announcer: POKKLE,
APPLICANT NUMBER 53,
AND GOZ, APPLICANT NUMBER 371,
ARRIVED SIMULTANEOUSLY.
TIME ELAPSED,
30 HOURS AND 4 MINUTES.
Pokkle: DAMN. TOUGH LUCK.
A TIE GOES
TO WHICHEVER APPLICANT
HAS THE LOWER NUMBER, OLD MAN.
Goz: HUMPH.
( thinking ) THESE GUYS
MUST BE QUITE SKILLED INDEED.
HOPE I GET A CHANCE
TO FIGHT THEM.
( flying beasts shrieking )
( Killua snoring )
( Kurapika grunts )
Tonpa: YOU DIDN'T JUST LOSE.
YOU SQUANDERED 50 HOURS
WE COULD REALLY USE RIGHT NOW.
THE LEAST YOU COULD DO
IS TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
♪♪♪
( Killua grunts )
( both laugh )
( Leorio groaning )
( Tonpa groaning )
( boys grunting )
♪♪♪
‐ ( Gon groans )
‐ ( Killua laughs )
( Gon groans ) THAT HURT!
( Tonpa yawns )
Leorio: ONE MORE HOUR.
( sighs )
( monkey chitters )
Geretta: HMM?
Announcer: SOMMY,
APPLICANT NUMBER 118,
IS THE 13th TO PASS.
TIME ELAPSED,
61 HOURS AND 54 MINUTES.
( Pokkle scoffs )
WE'VE STILL GOT 10 HOURS LEFT?
MAN, I REALLY SHOULD'VE
TAKEN MORE TIME.
( Gon groaning )
OKAY!
I'M READY TO GO!
♪♪♪
Kurapika: ONE MORE MINUTE.
Leorio: THIS ONE MINUTE'S
TAKING FOREVER, HUH?
( lock buzzes )
( gasps ) WAIT FOR US, GON!
( Gon laughs )
♪♪♪
Killua: HMM?
HEH.
( all panting )
Leorio: 30 MINUTES OF RUNNING,
AND WE'RE RIGHT BACK
WHERE WE STARTED.
Killua: DIDN'T I TELL YOU WE
SHOULD'VE TAKEN THE STAIRS DOWN?
Leorio: THIS IS THE ROUTE
WE ALL AGREED UPON,
SO WHY DON'T YOU
SHUT THE HELL UP?!
( Leorio and Tonpa yelling )
( Kurapika coughs )
Killua: MAN,
I'M ALL COVERED IN DUST.
Leorio: DAMN. ONLY AN HOUR LEFT.
IF WE DON'T HURRY,
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO VOTE
ON WHETHER TO OPEN THE DOOR?
WE NEED TO MOVE ON,
SO THE CHOICE IS PRETTY CLEAR.
( wrist timers beep )
( screen beeps )
( Leorio growls )
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR CRAP.
Tonpa: WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I PRESSED "O," TOO.
Leorio: DON'T YOU LIE TO ME.
SABOTAGING OUR CHANCES
IS YOUR FREAKIN' SPECIALTY.
Gon: SORRY, LEORIO.
Leorio: HUH?
Gon: I ACCIDENTALLY PRESSED
THE WRONG BUTTON.
Leorio: WHAT?
FINE. I SEE HOW IT IS.
Tonpa: HOLD ON.
Leorio: HMM?
Tonpa: I THINK
YOU OWE ME AN APOLOGY.
YOU THINK
I'M JUST GONNA LET THAT SLIDE?
Leorio: MAYBE IF YOU WEREN'T
ALWAYS DOING SHADY STUFF,
THIS KIND OF THING
WOULDN'T HAPPEN.
I DON'T OWE YOU A THING.
Tonpa: ALMOST SOUNDS
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY
I'M THE ONE TO BLAME FOR
EVERYTHING THAT'S GONE WRONG.
Leorio: WHAT'S THAT?
Tonpa: DON'T TELL ME.
HAVE YOU ALREADY FORGOTTEN
WHO IT WAS THAT COST US
THOSE 50 HOURS?
IF MEMORY SERVES, I'M PRETTY
SURE THAT HONOR GOES TO YOU.
( Leorio growls )
Kurapika: LEORIO, CALM DOWN.
Leorio: SHUT UP, KURAPIKA.
Gon: COME ON, GUYS.
KNOCK IT OFF!
I'M THE ONE WHO PRESSED
THE WRONG BUTTON,
‐ SO IT'S MY FAULT!
‐ [lock opens]
Killua: THIS IS STUPID.
I'M GOING ON AHEAD.
Gon: KILLUA, DON'T GO!
Killua: HEY, GON, WE MUST BE
GETTING REAL CLOSE TO THE END.
Gon: WHOA! REALLY?
♪♪♪
Killua: LET'S SEE.
"THIS WILL BE THE LAST DECISION
MADE BY MAJORITY RULE.
"ARE YOU READY?
CHOOSE 'O' OR 'X.'"
AND THAT'S IT.
Leorio: AM I READY?
OF COURSE I AM! LET'S DO THIS!
‐ BASTARD!
‐ Kurapika: LET IT GO!
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO ARGUE!
( beeps )
Announcer: PLEASE SELECT A PATH.
THERE ARE TWO AVAILABLE OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM,
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
WHICH THE ENTIRE GROUP CAN TAKE,
OR THE SHORT AND EASY PATH,
WHICH WILL BE LIMITED
TO ONLY THREE OF YOU.
( all gasp )
Announcer: INCIDENTALLY,
IF YOU CHOOSE
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
IT WILL REQUIRE A MINIMUM
OF 45 HOURS TO COMPLETE,
WHILE THE SHORT AND EASY PATH
WILL LEAD YOU
DIRECTLY TO THE GOAL
IN APPROXIMATELY
THREE MINUTES.
PRESS "O" TO SELECT
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
OR PRESS "X" TO CHOOSE
THE SHORT AND EASY PATH.
IF "X" IS SELECTED,
TWO APPLICANTS FROM YOUR GROUP
MUST BE CHAINED TO THE WALL
WITH HANDCUFFS
BEFORE THE DOOR WILL OPEN.
THOSE APPLICANTS
WILL BE UNABLE TO MOVE
UNTIL THE TIME LIMIT
HAS EXPIRED.
Killua: THE EXAMINERS
THOUGHT OF EVERYTHING.
LOOK AROUND.
EVERY WEAPON I'VE EVER
HEARD OF IS DOWN HERE.
Kurapika: SO TWO
OUT OF FIVE, HUH?
THEN THEY
MUST EXPECT US TO FIGHT
TO DECIDE WHICH THREE PASS.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO MAKE THIS CLEAR.
I'M PRESSING THE "X" BUTTON,
BUT I'M NOT STAYING BEHIND.
I'M ONE OF THE THREE
THAT'S MOVING ON,
AND I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
Tonpa: YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
WE COULD'VE TAKEN THE LONG PATH
IF YOU HADN'T WASTED 50 HOURS.
WHY DON'T YOU DO THE RIGHT THING
AND MAKE UP FOR IT
BY STAYING BEHIND?
Leorio: WHAT'S THAT?!
Tonpa: I'M SURE WE ALL AGREE.
WHAT ABOUT IT, GUYS? DID I LIE?
Gon: HOLD ON A SECOND.
I'M GOING TO PRESS "O."
IT'S JUST WE ALL MADE IT
THIS FAR BY WORKING TOGETHER.
WE SHOULD FINISH TOGETHER.
Kurapika: GON.
Gon: IT'S A BIG RISK.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT STILL, WE'VE GOTTA TRY!
Killua: AW, COME ON.
IT'S NOT A QUESTION
OF BEING A RISK.
WE'VE GOT LESS THAN AN HOUR.
( Gon sighs )
Killua: GON,
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO PASS.
I MEAN, IT'S OBVIOUS.
Leorio: WELL,
THERE YOU HAVE IT, KID.
Killua: SO NOW WE HAVE TO PICK
WHICH THREE ADVANCE.
IF IT WAS UP TO ME,
YOU AND I ARE TWO OF 'EM, GON.
( Tonpa scoffs )
( thinking )
WELL, I'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
NO WAY I'M STOPPING NOW.
WHOEVER MAKES
THE FIRST MOVE WINS.
( Kurapika thinking ) IS THIS
REALLY WHAT IT'S COME TO?
WE HAVE TO FIGHT
AMONGST OURSELVES?
( Tonpa yells )
Leorio: THAT WAS A CHEAP SHOT!
Tonpa: IN A FIGHT, THERE'S
NO SUCH THING AS A CHEAP SHOT!
Leorio: BASTARD!
Kurapika: STOP IT, BOTH OF YOU!
Gon: YEAH! COME ON!
LET'S ALL DO THIS TOGETHER!
Leorio: WE DON'T
HAVE TO START FIGHTING
UNTIL WE CHOOSE "O"
OR "X," YOU IDIOT!
Tonpa: IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT!
Leorio: THEN I GUESS I'LL
JUST HAVE TO CHOOSE FOR YOU!
Tonpa: WELL,
TWO CAN PLAY AT THAT GAME. HUHH!
Killua: LOOKS LIKE FIGHTING
IS OUR ONLY OPTION.
( Kurapika thinking )
WHAT DO WE DO?
Announcer: THREE MINUTES REMAIN.
Umori: IT'S FINALLY OVER, HUH?
Imori: YEAH.
FEELS LIKE IT TOOK FOREVER.
HUH?
( applicant shuddering )
I‐‐
I...
MADE...
IT.
Imori: HE'S DEAD.
Umori: DAMN, WHAT A MORON.
IT'S BETTER TO SURVIVE
AND TRY AGAIN NEXT YEAR
THAN TO PASS AND DIE TRYIN'.
Announcer: ONE MINUTE REMAINS.
Imori: THAT'S IT, THEN.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST THE 19
OF US THAT ARE ALREADY HERE.
Hisoka: HMM.
Umori: HUH?
Announcer: KURAPIKA, NUMBER 404,
IS THE 20th TO PASS.
KILLUA, NUMBER 99,
IS THE 21st TO PASS.
GON, NUMBER 405,
IS THE 22nd TO PASS.
TIME ELAPSED,
71 HOURS, 59 MINUTES.
Killua: BOY, MY BUTT HURTS!
I CERTAINLY WASN'T EXPECTING
THE SHORT AND EASY PATH
TO BE A SLIDE.
Hisoka: THREE OF THEM, EH?
Announcer: 30 SECONDS REMAIN.
Gon: EVEN WITH THAT BIG SLIDE,
THAT WAS REALLY CLOSE.
( Kurapika laughs ) MY HANDS
ARE COVERED IN BLISTERS.
Leorio: SAME HERE.
( both grunting )
Announcer: LEORIO, NUMBER 403,
IS THE 23rd TO PASS.
TONPA, NUMBER 16,
IS THE 24th TO PASS.
TIME ELAPSED,
71 HOURS, 59 MINUTES.
Leorio: MY HANDS ARE WRECKED,
BUT ALL FIVE OF US CLEARED
THE TOWER TOGETHER, DIDN'T WE?
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO GON.
( Gon laughs )
( screen beeps )
Kurapika: WE ENTERED
THE LONG AND DIFFICULT PATH,
BROKE DOWN THE WALL,
AND FROM THERE,
WE SNUCK
INTO THE SHORT AND EASY ONE.
Leorio: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU CAME UP WITH THAT PLAN
ON THE SPOT.
( Gon laughs ) I FIGURED
WE COULD USE THE WEAPONS
TO BREAK THROUGH THE WALLS.
BUT IT DID TAKE ALMOST
ALL THE TIME WE HAD LEFT.
( Kurapika thinking )
EVEN UNDER PRESSURE,
YOU WERE ABLE
TO CALMLY ASSESS OUR OPTIONS
AND THINK OF A WAY
TO GET AROUND THEM,
AND THAT IS
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SPECIAL.
( chime sounds )
Announcer: THE THIRD PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM IS OVER.
25 APPLICANTS HAVE PASSED,
INCLUDING ONE DECEASED.
Narrator: ALTHOUGH THEY
HAD THEIR DIFFERENCES,
GON FOUND A WAY
TO BRING THEM ALL TOGETHER
AND COMPLETE THE TRIAL
AS A TEAM.
BUT TODAY'S FRIEND
MAY BE TOMORROW'S FOE.
WHAT GON DOESN'T KNOW
IS THAT BEFORE LONG,
THEY WILL BE FORCED
TO FACE EACH OTHER
IN SAVAGE INDIVIDUAL BATTLES.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"LETTER FROM GON."
Mito: ALWAYS GONE.
Gon: WHO, ME?
♪♪♪