Leorio: NO GOOD.
I'VE GOT NOTHING.
Killua: THAT TWO BILLION
PER SPIDER REWARD
IS PRETTY ATTRACTIVE, BUT
FINDING THEM WILL BE IMPOSSIBLE.
Gon: YEAH.
HEY! WE COULD ASK FOR CONCRETE
INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE.
MAYBE WE COULD EVEN ASK
ABOUT THE PHANTOM TROUPE'S
CURRENT LOCATION.
IT MIGHT HELP IF WE OFFERED
A REALLY BIG REWARD.
Leorio: WE COULD,
BUT WE DON'T HAVE
NEARLY ENOUGH MONEY FOR THAT.
Gon: NOT A PROBLEM.
( both gasp )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: GON AND HIS FRIENDS
ARE IN PURSUIT
OF THE ELUSIVE PHANTOM TROUPE
AND HAVE NOW OBTAINED THE FUNDS
TO BUY THE INFORMATION
THEY NEED.
Leorio: THAT'S CRAZY!
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE THE MONEY.
Killua: IDIOT. I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY PAWNED
YOUR HUNTER'S LICENSE.
YOU'RE INSANE. YOU KNOW THAT?
Gon: SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO FIRST?
Leorio: TO START WITH,
WE SHOULD BUY OURSELVES
A SOUTHERNBEES CATALOG.
Receptionist:
HERE IS THIS YEAR'S
OFFICIAL SOUTHERNBEES
AUCTION CATALOG, GENTLEMEN.
Gon: THANK YOU!
HMM.
GOT IT!
"GREED ISLAND'S" RIGHT HERE!
Leorio:
SEVEN TOTAL UNITS ON SALE.
Killua: WOW. MINIMUM
STARTING BID IS 8.9 BILLION.
NO CHANGE THERE.
Leorio: NOW WE JUST HAVE TO WAIT
FOR THE INFORMATION
TO START ROLLIN' IN.
SO FIRST,
WE'LL CATCH ONE OF THE SPIDERS.
AFTER THAT, ALL WE
HAVE TO DO IS MAKE 'EM TELL US
WHERE THE REST OF 'EM
ARE HIDING.
EASY! WHAT THE...
WHAT'S WRONG? GON?
Gon: THIS THING IS...
Killua: LOOK AT THAT.
YOU FOUND A BEN'S KNIFE, HUH?
Gon: WAIT.
WHAT'S A BEN'S KNIFE?
Killua: IT'S A KNIFE
THAT A MASS MURDERER DESIGNED
ABOUT A HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
THE GUY WAS ALSO
A FAMOUS BLACKSMITH.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
ONE OF HIS ORIGINAL WORKS.
IT'S A LESSER‐KNOWN PIECE A LOT
OF RABID COLLECTORS ARE AFTER.
GOOD EYE, GON.
Gon: I DIDN'T HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT IT WAS.
( both gasp )
Gon: IT JUST CAUGHT
MY ATTENTION IS ALL.
I GUESS I GOT CURIOUS,
SO I USED GYO ON IT,
AND THAT'S
WHEN I NOTICED A FAINT AURA.
Leorio: WHAT'S GYO?
Killua: GYO'S A FORM OF NEN.
IT'S BASICALLY WHEN YOU LOOK
REALLY, REALLY CLOSELY
AT SOMETHING.
( Leorio groans )
Killua: WOW,
YOU WEREN'T KIDDING!
Leorio: HERE. LET ME SEE THAT.
( grunts )
NOPE. I DON'T SEE A THING.
Gon: YOU WILL ONCE YOU GET
MORE TRAINING IN REN.
Killua: OH, YEAH!
THERE'S ANOTHER WAY TO DO IT!
Gon: DO WHAT?
Killua: ANOTHER WAY
WE CAN MAKE MONEY.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT FOUR‐EYES SAID TO US
WHEN WE WERE AT HEAVENS ARENA?
HE SAID
SOME REALLY TALENTED PEOPLE
CAN USE NEN
WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING.
Leorio: WHO THE HELL
IS FOUR‐EYES?
Killua: WING.
HE'S THE ONE WHO TAUGHT US NEN.
SO THIS KNIFE HAD AURA.
I SAY WE SEARCH
FOR OTHER THINGS THAT DO, TOO.
FIND ONE, AND IT'S A GOOD BET
THAT IT WAS MADE
BY A REAL MASTER.
Gon: I GET IT!
SO WE CAN FIND HIDDEN GEMS,
BUT WITHOUT
HAVING TO GO THROUGH
A BUNCH OF TRAINING
TO BE PROFESSIONAL APPRAISERS,
AND THEN WE JUST AUCTION OFF
WHAT WE FIND AT A HIGHER PRICE.
Vendor: IF YOU WANT IT,
ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS WRITE YOUR PRICE DOWN.
‐ Gon: EH?
‐ Killua: YOU MEAN,
CUSTOMERS GET TO NAME
THEIR OWN PRICES?
Vendor: YEAH. THAT'S THE WAY
THIS MARKET WORKS.
YOU WRITE DOWN WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'RE WILLING TO PAY,
AND WHEN THE TIME EXPIRES,
THE ITEM GOES
TO WHOEVER HAD THE HIGHEST BID.
SEE? THIS HERE IS
A REALLY POPULAR ITEM.
JUST LOOK AT HOW THE PRICE
SHOT UP NEAR THE END.
♪
Killua: I GET IT NOW.
WELL, LET'S GET STARTED.
Leorio: SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL CHECK OUT
THE ONLINE FORUMS.
Gon: HMM.
HMM.
THIS VASE IS PRETTY WEIRD,
BUT I'M PICKING UP AURA FROM IT.
( gasps )
THERE'S A BID.
Killua: IF THERE'S
ALREADY A BID,
THEN YOU SHOULD ENTER ONE
THAT'S 2 1/2 TIMES HIGHER.
YOU MIGHT END UP
BIDDING TOO HIGH,
BUT AT LEAST THAT WAY,
YOU'LL SCARE OFF ANY RIVALS.
Gon: 500 TIMES 2 1/2...
LET ME SEE.
( gasps )
IT'S THE SAME PERSON!
SAME THERE?
YEAH, I FOUND
A COUPLE OF ITEMS,
BUT BOTH OF 'EM HAD BIDS
PLACED BY "ZEPILE" ALREADY.
I BID 2 1/2 TIMES HIGHER,
BUT AS SOON AS I DID,
HE QUADRUPLED IT.
Gon: THEN IT'S
NOT A COINCIDENCE.
‐ Killua: NO.
‐ Gon: WHAT NOW?
Killua: WE NEED
TO KEEP PLACING BIDS
ALL THE WAY UP TO THE DEADLINE.
THERE ARE TWO OF US, SO I'M SURE
WE'RE BOUND TO WIN SOMETHING.
Gon: YEAH, OKAY.
Killua: IN THE END,
WE WON THREE AND LOST ONE.
Gon: YEAH. THEY GOT THAT
WEIRD VASE AT THE LAST MINUTE.
Killua: NOT TOO BAD,
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED.
COME ON. LET'S TAKE 'EM
TO THE AUCTION HOUSE NOW.
Auctioneer:
OH, I'M TERRIBLY SORRY,
BUT THE AUCTION HOUSE
SIMPLY CAN'T ACCEPT
ANY ADDITIONAL ITEMS ONCE
THE CATALOG HAS BEEN PUBLISHED.
YOU'RE TOO LATE, I'M AFRAID.
( Gon groans )
Killua: CAN YOU
MAKE AN EXCEPTION?
SEE, WE REALLY
HAD OUR HEARTS SET
ON AUCTIONING OFF
THESE ITEMS.
Auctioneer: HMM.
PERHAPS YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED
IN TRYING YOUR LUCK
OVER AT THE DEALERS' MARKET.
Both: THE DEALERS' MARKET?
♪
Gon: SO THIS IS IT.
THE PROS WILL BE HERE,
SO IF ANY OF THESE ARE GENUINE,
WE SHOULD GET A GREAT PRICE.
Killua: YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT I REALLY WANTED
TO SELL THESE AT THE AUCTION.
Gon: HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK
WE'RE GONNA GET?
Killua: THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
Dealer: OH.
YOU SAY YOU FOUND THESE
IN YOUR STOREHOUSE?
Killua: YEAH! AND MY DAD SAID
THAT WE SHOULD SELL 'EM
‐ IF THE PRICE WAS GOOD ENOUGH.
‐ ( Gon chuckles )
Dealer: THESE ARE
EXCELLENT PIECES.
ONLY 50 COPIES WERE PRINTED,
AND YOURS HAS
A SINGLE‐DIGIT SERIAL NUMBER,
NOT TO MENTION
AN AUTHENTIC AUTOGRAPH.
( Killua thinking )
YEAH, WE KNOW.
( Gon thinking ) THAT'S WHERE
THE AURA WAS COMING FROM.
Dealer: IT'S WORTH
AT LEAST 150,000.
( both gasp, chuckle )
Dealer: AND LOOK
AT THIS ANTIQUE DOLL.
IT'S IN GREAT SHAPE.
BOTH THE DOLL AND BOX
ARE PRISTINE,
WHICH RAISES THE VALUE.
300,000, I'D GUESS.
( Gon laughs )
Dealer: BUT I'M SORRY TO SAY
THIS ONE
ISN'T WORTH NEARLY AS MUCH.
( both gasp )
Dealer: THE BOX AND STATUE
ARE FROM DIFFERENT PERIODS.
THE BOX WAS MADE RECENTLY.
THE STATUE IS ROUGHLY CARVED
AND DOESN'T ADHERE TO ANY THEME.
I'D SAY IT'S
ONLY WORTH 1,500 JENNY.
( Killua scoffs )
( Gon thinking ) BUT THERE'S
A LITTLE AURA COMING FROM IT.
Dealer: NOW DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S JUST THE PRICE
AS AN ARTWORK,
BUT THE WOOD IT'S MADE OF
IS ACTUALLY QUITE VALUABLE.
Both: HUH?
Dealer: I WOULD BE
MORE THAN HAPPY
TO MAKE YOU AN OFFER ON IT.
SELL ME THE PAINTING
AND THE DOLL FOR 420,000,
AND I'LL THROW IN
ANOTHER 80,000 FOR THE WOOD.
Killua: SO 500,000 TOTAL?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Dealer: THERE'S NO RUSH.
TAKE YOUR TIME,
BUT I DOUBT YOU'RE
GOING TO FIND A BETTER OFFER
FROM ANYONE ELSE AROUND HERE.
IN THE MEANTIME,
LET ME ANALYZE THIS
AND FIND OUT
THE EXACT AGE OF THE WOOD.
Man: STOP RIGHT THERE!
( boys gasp )
Man: PUT THAT STATUE DOWN NOW.
Dealer: I'M SORRY,
BUT WHO ARE YOU?
Man: WATCH OUT.
THIS GUY IS A SCAMMER.
THAT'S A FAIR PRICE
FOR THE DOLL AND PAINTING,
BUT HE'S LYING TO YOUR FACE
ABOUT THE STATUE.
Dealer: I‐I'M NOT LYING.
I SWEAR I'M NOT.
Man: YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
BECAUSE NO COLLECTOR
WOULD PAY 80,000 FOR THAT WOOD.
ALL YOU'RE INTERESTED IN
IS THE CONTENTS OF THAT STATUE!
( all gasp )
Man: THAT'S ACTUALLY
A WOODEN VAULT.
Boys: WAIT. ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Man: AROUND 300 YEARS AGO,
SECRET VAULTS LIKE THIS
WERE A POPULAR WAY
FOR THE WEALTHY TO EVADE TAXES.
Gon: I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
Man: IF IT'S THE REAL DEAL,
THEN THERE SHOULD BE SOME SORT
OF VALUABLE STUFFED INSIDE.
( boys gasp )
Man: YOU PLANNED
ON STEALING ITS CONTENTS
WHILE YOU WERE JUST PRETENDING
TO ANALYZE ITS AGE!
Dealer: NO!
NO, I WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
Man #2: HOLD ON!
DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF AT ALL
THAT THAT THING'S
A GENUINE WOODEN VAULT?
Man #1: WHAT WAS THAT?
Dealer #2: IT'S FAIRLY OBVIOUS
THAT THE WOOD
IS OVER 300 YEARS OLD,
BUT ALL THAT TELLS US
IS THE AGE OF THE RAW MATERIAL.
IT COULD HAVE
BEEN CARVED RECENTLY.
THAT'S A DOCTORING METHOD
CALLED A FACE‐LIFT, BOYS.
Gon: A DOCTORING METHOD?
Man: HE MEANS
WHEN A COUNTERFEITER
TRIES TO TRICK
A PROFESSIONAL APPRAISER,
BUT THAT ISN'T WHAT I'M DOING.
AN AMATEUR WOULD NEVER RECOGNIZE
THIS SEAM HERE,
A SEAM WHICH CONTAINS
A TYPE OF GLUE
THAT WAS COMMONLY USED
IN THAT TIME PERIOD.
Dealer #2: YOU'RE INSISTING THIS
IS A REAL WOODEN VAULT, ARE YOU?
Man: YEAH.
Dealer #2: BUT IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT IT'S BEEN OPENED,
THE CONTENTS SWAPPED OUT,
AND THEN THE STATUE
WAS REASSEMBLED,
SOMETHING WE CALL A TRANSPLANT.
WHEN A COUNTERFEITER
PERFORMS A TRANSPLANT,
THEY PUT A NEW COAT OF GLUE
ON TOP OF THE OLD ONE,
CREATING A SECONDARY SEAL,
BUT ONLY A RANK AMATEUR
WOULD EVEN THINK OF TRYING THAT.
A PRO WOULD MELT THE GLUE
WITH A FLAME,
THEN RESEAL IT.
THAT WOULD MAKE IT LOOK
LIKE THE STATUE
HAD NEVER BEEN OPENED.
IT'S KNOWN AS CAUTERIZATION.
Gon: OH.
Man: IT'S NOT CAUTERIZED.
IF SOMEONE HAD USED A FLAME,
THE WOOD WOULD BE SCORCHED,
OR AT THE VERY LEAST,
THE GLUE WOULD BE DISCOLORED.
Dealer #2: EVEN PROS
WOULD HAVE A HARD TIME
SPOTTING THOSE DETAILS.
DOESN'T PROVE ANYTHING.
Man: I AM A PRO APPRAISER.
I SWEAR BY MY EYES
THIS IS A REAL WOODEN VAULT.
IT HAS NEVER BEEN OPENED,
AND THE TREASURE THAT'S INSIDE
HAS NEVER BEEN SWAPPED OUT.
Dealer #2: OKAY.
JUST FOR THE SAKE OF ARGUMENT,
LET'S SAY IT IS
A GENUINE WOODEN VAULT.
IF THE CONTENTS HAVE BEEN
SWAPPED OUT, WHAT'LL YOU DO?
WHAT ARE YOU WILLING TO BET?
♪
Appraiser: IF YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'LL BE YOUR LACKEY
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
( dealer #2 chuckles )
GIVE IT UP.
( dealer #1 sighs )
( tapping )
( appraiser chuckles )
( objects clatter )
( both gasp )
♪
WHOA! AWESOME!
Killua: OH, SO YOU'RE ZEPILE.
Gon: THANKS A LOT, MR. ZEPILE.
Zepile: OH,
THERE'S NO NEED TO THANK ME.
IT'S JUST A MATTER
OF GIVE AND TAKE, SAY 20%?
Gon: HUH?
Zepile: MY CUT OF THE PROFIT
‐ WHEN YOU SELL THE TREASURE.
‐ Killua: WHAT?!
ARE YOU TRYING
TO RIP US OFF, OLD MAN?
Zepile: NOW,
THAT WAS UNCALLED FOR.
LOOK, I'VE GOTTA CHARGE
SOMETHING FOR ADVISING YOU.
Gon: IT'S OKAY. HE DID HELP
US OUT BACK THERE, AFTER ALL.
Killua: GIVE ME A BREAK, MAN.
WE NEED TO COLLECT AS MUCH JENNY
AS POSSIBLE, REMEMBER?
WE CAN MAYBE BUY HIM LUNCH.
Zepile: OH, YEAH?
SURE, WORKS FOR ME.
Both: HUH?
( utensils clatter )
Gon: SO, MR. ZEPILE...
‐ Zepile: MM?
‐ Gon: I FEEL KINDA BAD,
SO WE WILL PAY YOU A COMMISSION.
Killua: DUDE!
YOU'RE SUCH A PUSHOVER!
Zepile: NAH. REALLY,
IT'S PERFECTLY OKAY.
JUST TELL ME ONE THING,
AND WE'LL BE EVEN.
WHAT WAS IT THAT MADE YOU GUYS
BID ON ALL THESE ITEMS?
SOMETHING TIPPED YOU OFF.
Both: UH...
Gon: WELL?
SHOULD WE TELL HIM THE TRUTH?
Killua: SURE.
IT BEATS PAYING HIM, ANYWAY.
Zepile: AH. NEN AURA, HUH?
WELL, IF YOU'RE BEING HONEST,
THAT DOES EXPLAIN
WHY YOU PURCHASED THAT STATUE.
IT WAS PRETTY OBVIOUS
YOU HAD NO IDEA
SOMETHING WAS HIDDEN INSIDE.
SO WHY DO YOU TWO
NEED MONEY SO BADLY?
Killua: WE CAN TELL YOU,
BUT NOT FOR FREE.
YOU'VE GOTTA ANSWER
ONE OF OUR QUESTIONS, TOO.
Zepile: GREAT. YOU START.
Killua: AT THE AUCTION,
THERE'S AN ITEM WE WANT TO BUY,
SO WE NEED MONEY.
Zepile: OH. WHICH ITEM IS IT?
Killua: IT'S OUR TURN NOW.
300 MILLION JENNY,
THAT'S HOW MUCH YOU ESTIMATED
THIS TREASURE'S WORTH.
SO DO YOU THINK THAT'S
HOW MUCH WE COULD GET FOR IT
AT THE DEALERS' MARKET?
Zepile: AT THE DEALERS' MARKET?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
THEY DEAL MAINLY IN HARD CASH,
SO IF YOU SHOW UP EARLY ON,
IT'S UNLIKELY THAT YOU'LL GET
A FAIR PRICE FOR IT.
Gon: WHAT?!
Killua: SERIOUSLY?
Zepile: NOW IT'S MY TURN.
I'LL REPEAT THE QUESTION.
WHICH ITEM ARE YOU
LOOKING TO BID ON?
Killua: IT'S A VIDEO GAME
CALLED "GREED ISLAND."
Zepile: AH! YOU MEAN THE ONE
THAT'S SUPER EXPENSIVE.
Killua: I'M REAL CURIOUS ABOUT
THAT WEIRD VASE YOU BOUGHT.
HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK
THAT IT'S WORTH?
Zepile: WHAT? THIS THING?
IT'S JUST A PIECE OF JUNK,
TOTALLY WORTHLESS.
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ Zepile: I DON'T GET
WHY YOU'D WANT
SUCH AN EXPENSIVE GAME.
DOESN'T IT COST,
LIKE, 6 BILLION JENNY?
Killua: STARTS AT 8.9.
THING IS WE'RE TRYING
TO FIND GON'S FATHER.
WE NEED TO BUY THE GAME,
BECAUSE IT HAS A CLUE INSIDE.
Zepile: OH.
Killua: SO WHY DID YOU
PICK THAT VASE?
Zepile: UH...
Killua: WELL, YOU KNEW
THAT WOODEN VAULT
WAS THE REAL THING, DIDN'T YOU?
SO YOU COULD'VE BID ON THAT,
BUT YOU DIDN'T.
YOU BID ON THAT WEIRD VASE
INSTEAD. WHY?
( Zepile sighs )
WELL, YOU SEE...
I SORT OF MADE
THIS VASE MYSELF.
( both gasp )
Zepile: "SORT OF,"
BECAUSE IT ISN'T
MY ORIGINAL WORK.
THIS IS A KNOCKOFF.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IT'S COUNTERFEIT.
WHEN I WAS POOR, THIS WAS
HOW I MADE MY JENNY UNTIL...
I BECAME AN APPRAISER
AND STARTED EARNING MONEY.
AS SOON AS THAT HAPPENED,
I QUIT ALL THAT.
BUT WHEN I SEE HOW POORLY MADE
THESE THINGS ARE,
OH, BOY,
IT'S REALLY EMBARRASSING.
I SWORE I'D BUY THEM BACK
WHENEVER I SAW THEM
AT THE MARKET.
Killua: ANY CLUE
WHAT A REAL ONE WOULD COST?
‐ Zepile: MY TURN.
‐ ( Killua groans )
Zepile: WHAT DOES
YOUR DAD DO FOR A LIVING?
Gon: HE'S A PROFESSIONAL HUNTER.
Killua: I ASKED HOW MUCH
A REAL ONE WOULD COST!
Zepile: 40, 50K.
( Killua groans )
Zepile: IS THAT SO?
A PRO HUNTER, HUH?
THERE ARE A COUPLE OF THEM
IN THE ANTIQUES COMMUNITY,
AND NOT ONE OF 'EM IS SOMEONE
YOU WOULD DESCRIBE AS NORMAL.
WON'T IT BE IMPOSSIBLE
FOR YOU TO FIND HIM ON YOUR OWN?
Gon: WE'LL BE FINE.
SEE, I'M A PRO HUNTER MYSELF.
Zepile: WAIT. REALLY?!
Gon: 'KAY. IT'S YOUR TURN
TO ASK US A QUESTION NOW.
Zepile: HMM.
RIGHT. THIS ONE'LL BE
MY FINAL QUESTION.
IS THERE ANYTHING AT ALL
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
‐ ( Gon gasps )
‐ Killua: HUH?
Zepile: IF YOU WANT
TO MAKE MONEY AT AN AUCTION,
YOU'LL NEED SOMEONE
WITH APPRAISAL EXPERIENCE.
YOU COULD SAY THAT TEAMING UP
WITH THE RIGHT APPRAISER
CAN GUARANTEE YOU
A PROFIT EVERY TIME.
YOU CHOOSE HOW MUCH
YOU WANT TO PAY ME,
WHATEVER YOU THINK'S FAIR.
HOW'S THAT?
Gon: FINE. THEN YOU HAVE
TO ANSWER OUR LAST QUESTION.
WHAT MADE YOU
WANT TO HELP US OUT?
WHAT'S IN IT FOR YOU?
( Zepile chuckles )
IT JUST MADE ME HAPPY.
( both gasp )
Zepile: FELT NICE
THAT SOMEONE
WAS BIDDING ON MY WORK,
EVEN IF IT IS
JUST A WORTHLESS PIECE OF JUNK.
Gon: IT IS NOT A PIECE OF JUNK!
‐ Zepile: HUH?
‐ Gon: THAT VASE YOU MADE,
IT'S OVERFLOWING
WITH YOUR NEN, MR. ZEPILE!
AURA'S COMMON,
AND ANYBODY CAN PRODUCE IT,
BUT IT'S INCREDIBLY DIFFICULT
TO CONTROL, LIKE, REALLY HARD!
YOU HAVE TO CONCENTRATE AND
TRAIN FOR A REALLY LONG TIME.
ANYBODY CAN SEE HOW MUCH EFFORT
YOU PUT INTO MAKING THAT VASE.
I KNOW I SURE CAN.
THIS KIND OF WORK TAKES TALENT.
AND I'M SORRY FOR SAYING
IT WAS WEIRD EARLIER.
♪
( Zepile sighs )
I CAN TRUST MY EYES.
THEY'VE NEVER FOOLED ME.
WHEN YOU APPRAISE THINGS
LONG ENOUGH,
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT BECOME
A GOOD JUDGE OF CHARACTER.
I LOOK AT THE SELLERS AND
THE BUYERS, NOT JUST THE GOODS.
IF THERE'S
ONE THING I'VE LEARNED
AFTER ALL THIS TIME
APPRAISING ANTIQUES,
IT'S THAT IT'S A LOT HARDER
TO APPRAISE PEOPLE,
AND WHEN I SAW YOU,
THE APPRAISER IN ME
KNEW RIGHT AWAY
THAT I REALLY WANTED
TO WORK WITH YOU, TRULY.
SO THAT'S MY ANSWER.
WHAT'S YOURS?
Gon: WE'RE LOOKING
FORWARD TO IT.
Killua: WE'LL DECIDE ON YOUR FEE
ONCE WE SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO.
( Zepile chuckles )
GREAT! NOW THAT WE'VE
GOT THAT SETTLED‐‐
‐ Gon: FIRST THINGS FIRST.
‐ Zepile: HUH?
Gon: CAN YOU TEACH ME
THE DOCTORING METHODS
YOU TALKED ABOUT
IN THE STORE EARLIER?
Zepile: YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
Gon: YEP! CAUTERIZING
AND TRANSPLANT AND FACE‐LIFT.
IS THAT IT, OR ARE THERE OTHERS?
Killua: YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
NONE OF THAT CRAP MATTERS!
Gon: BUT THEY SOUND FUN,
KINDA LIKE MAGIC TRICKS!
Killua: YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE NOT HERE TO HAVE FUN!
Zepile: I THINK I GET IT NOW,
WHY THIS KID INTRIGUED ME.
HE'S NOT CONCERNED WITH WHETHER
SOMETHING IS GOOD OR BAD.
WHEN I CAME CLEAN
ABOUT MAKING COUNTERFEITS
OR WHEN THE MEN IN THE STORE
WERE TALKING ABOUT THE VAULT,
I DIDN'T SEE
A HINT OF DISAPPROVAL
OR GREED ON HIS FACE, NOT ONE,
BUT WHAT I DID SEE
WAS PURE CURIOSITY.
IF SOMETHING IMPRESSES HIM,
HE DOESN'T START JUDGING
WHETHER IT'S GOOD OR BAD,
WHICH MEANS
HE'S WALKING A FINE LINE.
HE'S THAT RARE KIND OF PERSON
WHO CAN NEVER
TRULY BE APPRAISED.
CAUTERIZATION,
DEFINITELY THE HARDEST
DOCTORING METHOD TO DETECT.
BUT NOT TOO LONG AGO,
A NEW METHOD SURFACED.
IT'S CALLED AN AUTOPSY.
THAT'S WHEN YOU PLAINLY REVEAL
THE OPENED STATUE
ALONG WITH A FAKE TREASURE.
IT'S BASED
ON MOST PEOPLE'S ASSUMPTION
THAT YOU WOULDN'T OPEN
THE STATUE
IF THE TREASURE WERE FAKE,
AND THAT MAKES THEM
EASY TO FOOL.
BUT THIS METHOD
IS STARTING TO GET OLD NOW.
PEOPLE WERE GETTING SUSPICIOUS,
SO OF COURSE
A NEW DOCTORING METHOD EMERGED.
THINK YOU CAN GUESS?
GIVE IT A TRY.
Gon: OH, I KNOW!
THE STATUE'S FAKE,
AND THE TREASURE
INSIDE OF IT'S FAKE, TOO!
‐ Zepile: WRONG!
‐ Gon: AWW.
Killua: WAIT. I GOT IT.
YOU TAKE THE TREASURE OUT
FROM A DIFFERENT OPENING.
Zepile: BINGO.
YOU START
BY CREATING A NEW OPENING
AND REMOVING THE TREASURE.
THEN YOU JUST INSERT
THE FAKE TREASURE
AND CAREFULLY SEAL
THE HOLE BACK UP AGAIN.
THAT'S KNOWN AS AN OSTOMY.
Gon: AN OSTOMY.
Zepile: MANY VETERAN APPRAISERS
HAVE BEEN DECEIVED BY IT.
IF THERE ARE NO SIGNS
THAT THE ADHESIVE
WAS DISCOLORED BY FIRE,
THEY ASSUME THAT IT'S REAL.
AND THAT, GENTLEMEN,
IS HOW YOU FOOL THE PROS.
( Gon sighs )
WHAT AN AWESOME WORLD!
( cell phone rings )
UH, HELLO?
( grunts ) A SPIDER?
Leorio: YEAH. IT LOOKS REAL,
AND THERE'S A VIDEO
ATTACHED TO IT.
WE'VE GOT TWO TARGETS,
A MAN AND A WOMAN.
I'LL HEAD OUT RIGHT NOW,
SO MEET ME THERE.
Gon: GOT IT.
COME ON. LET'S GO!
Killua: OKAY.
Zepile: HEY, WAIT A SECOND!
WHAT ABOUT THE AUCTION?!
Gon: YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
Killua: YEAH, JUST TRY
TO GET US A GOOD PRICE.
Zepile: HUH?!
HEH. ALL RIGHT!
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME!
♪
Narrator: GON AND KILLUA
HAVE HAD THEIR EYES OPENED
TO A BRAND‐NEW WORLD,
AND THEY ARE
ABOUT TO MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'LL INTRODUCE SHIZUKU,
PHANTOM TROUPE MEMBER WITH
A VACUUM CLEANER NAMED BLINKY.
Killua: BUT IT
CAN'T SUCK UP THE LIVING.
Gon: AND ITS CAPACITY IS HUGE!
Killua: WHERE DO YOU GO
IF YOU GET SUCKED UP IN IT?
Gon: NOBODY KNOWS!
♪
NEXT TIME,
"PURSUIT AND ANALYSIS."
‐ RIGHT OR LEFT?
‐ Killua: RIGHT.
Gon: DO WE FOLLOW
THE MAN OR THE WOMAN?
‐ Killua: THE WOMAN.
‐ Gon: WHAT'S BETTER,
RED OR BLUE?
Killua: I DON'T KNOW!
YOU PICK!