( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: WHAT'S THAT?
Mito: IT'S SOMETHING
GING LEFT WITH ME.
Gon: WHAT?
Mito: HE ASKED ME
TO GIVE THIS TO YOU
WHEN YOU BECAME A HUNTER.
Gon: SO DAD LEFT THIS FOR ME?
♪
Narrator: THREE MYSTERIOUS ITEMS
WERE INSIDE THE BOX
THAT HAD BEEN SEALED WITH NEN.
ONE OF THESE ITEMS,
AN OLD CASSETTE TAPE,
GAVE GON
A LONG‐AWAITED OPPORTUNITY,
THE CHANCE TO HEAR HIS FATHER'S
VOICE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
Ging: HEY, GON.
SO YOU BECAME A HUNTER,
TOO, HUH?
Gon: THIS IS MY DAD'S VOICE.
Ging: ANYWAY,
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
DO YOU...
WANT TO SEE ME?
♪
IF YOU DO, KEEP LISTENING.
IF YOU DON'T,
JUST PRESS THE STOP BUTTON.
I'M GUESSING THAT'S A YES,
BUT I'LL ASK YOU ONE MORE TIME.
ARE YOU SURE?
HUNTERS ARE SELFISH CREATURES.
WE'RE WILLING TO SACRIFICE
ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING
TO GET WHAT WE WANT.
IF YOU JUST THINK
IT WOULD BE NICE TO SEE ME,
STOP THE TAPE HERE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE.
Killua: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
( chuckles )
Mito: WHEW.
( Ging sighs ) YOU WANT
TO SEE ME THAT MUCH, HUH?
WELL, I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU.
( both gasp )
Ging: HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW
HOW I COULD FACE YOU.
AFTER ALL, I WALKED AWAY
FROM BEING A PARENT
FOR PURELY SELFISH REASONS.
I'M NOT A DECENT GUY.
( birds chirp )
I DON'T HAVE ANY WAY OF KNOWING
HOW MUCH TIME WILL PASS
BEFORE YOU LISTEN TO THIS TAPE.
I FIGURE IT'LL BE
AT LEAST 10 YEARS.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THERE'S ONE THING
THAT WILL NEVER CHANGE.
I'LL ALWAYS BE THE GUY I AM.
♪
BO!
( monster grunts )
( monster #2 bellows )
AS YOU SIT THERE
LISTENING TO THIS TAPE,
I'M SURE I'LL BE OFF
HORSING AROUND SOMEWHERE.
IF YOU STILL WANT
TO SEE ME, FIND ME.
BUT LIKE I SAID,
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU.
IF I HEAR YOU COMING,
I'M GONNA BOLT.
CATCH ME IF YOU CAN.
YOU ARE A HUNTER NOW,
AREN'T YOU?
( Killua chuckles )
IF YOU THOUGHT YOUR DAD
WOULD BE EASY TO TRACK,
THEN YOU BETTER THINK AGAIN.
Gon: HEY, WAIT.
GING'S STILL THERE.
LET IT PLAY.
Ging: OH, THERE'S ONE MORE THING
I FORGOT TO MENTION.
IT'S ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW MORE,
KEEP LISTENING.
IF YOU DON'T, THEN‐‐
Killua: ARE YOU SURE?
Gon: MM‐HMM.
Killua: BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE REST OF IT?
WHAT IF HE LEFT YOU
ANOTHER CLUE?
Gon: NO WAY. NOT HIM.
I CAN FEEL IT.
AND LIKE I SAID BEFORE,
I DO HAVE A MOM, AUNT MITO.
Killua: I SEE.
Gon: HEY, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I'LL GO GET US SOMETHING TO EAT.
Killua: SURE.
‐ ( chorus vocalizing )
‐ ( click )
‐ HEY, GON!
‐ Gon: EH?
Killua: THE TAPE
STARTED MOVING ALL BY ITSELF!
Gon: WAIT! WHAT?!
IS THAT AURA?
Killua: IT'S NEN,
AND IT'S REWINDING THE TAPE.
Gon: NEN? HE'S CLOSE.
HE'S GOTTA BE!
Killua: NO. OVER 10 YEARS AGO,
HE IMBUED IT WITH AURA
SO IT WOULD START REWINDING
THE MINUTE THAT IT STOPPED.
Gon: BUT WHY?
Killua: I'VE NO IDEA.
LOOK! NOW IT'S RECORDING!
WAIT. I THINK I GET IT.
‐ HE'S ERASING HIS VOICE.
‐ Gon: WHAT?!
( grunts )
IT WON'T STOP, DAMN IT!
Killua: IT'S STILL GOING.
Gon: EVEN WHEN I UNPLUG IT?
I'M BREAKING IT. SORRY!
CRAP.
IT'S NO USE.
THE NEN'S PROTECTING IT.
( thumping )
Mito: HUH?
( Killua grunts )
( chorus ends )
Gon: IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S FINISHED.
( Killua sighs )
( on tape )
LOOK! NOW IT'S RECORDING!
WAIT. I THINK I GET IT.
HE'S ERASING HIS VOICE.
Gon: WHAT?!
Killua: THE DUPLICATE
CASSETTE TAPE
WAS COMPLETELY WIPED, TOO.
Gon: I JUST DON'T GET
WHY HE WOULD GO
THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE.
Killua: HE PROBABLY
DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE
ANY CLUES OR ANYTHING FOR US.
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Killua: YOU CAN EXTRACT
A WHOLE LOT OF INFORMATION
‐ FROM A SIMPLE AUDIO CLIP.
‐ Gon: REALLY?
Killua: YOU CAN DETERMINE ABOUT
HOW TALL THE SPEAKER LIKELY IS,
THEIR WEIGHT, THEIR AGE,
DISEASES, FACIAL FEATURES,
EVEN A PSYCH PROFILE.
Gon: OH.
Killua: FROM THE NOISE
IN THE BACKGROUND,
YOU CAN EVEN DETERMINE
THEIR EXACT LOCATION.
BUT THAT'S
NOT WHAT HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
Gon: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
Killua: HIS NEN ABILITIES.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: THERE MIGHT BE
A NEN USER SOMEWHERE
WHO CAN ANALYZE DATA
BETTER THAN A MACHINE.
I BET THERE IS.
THEY CAN HEAR YOUR VOICE,
AND IT WOULD TELL THEM
EVERYTHING THEY'D EVER
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT YOU.
Gon: I SEE.
Killua: YOUR DAD IS TOUGH,
LIKE, REALLY TOUGH.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: THIS IS USELESS.
LUCKY IT WASN'T THE ONLY CLUE.
WE'VE STILL GOT TWO MORE LEFT...
♪
THE RING AND THE MEMORY CARD.
THE RING PROBABLY WON'T HELP,
BUT THE MEMORY CARD MIGHT.
Gon: YEAH, BUT IT'S SMALLER
THAN A NORMAL ONE.
YOU THINK WE'RE GONNA NEED
SPECIAL HARDWARE FOR IT?
Killua: WAIT.
YOU MEAN YOU CAN'T TELL?
THIS IS ONLY DESIGNED
TO WORK WITH THE J. S.
Gon: WHAT'S A J. S.?
Killua: A GAMING CONSOLE
CALLED THE JOYSTATION
FROM THREE GENERATIONS BACK.
MAN, DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
IF THIS ISLAND
STILL HAS CASSETTE PLAYERS,
THERE'S GOTTA BE AN OLD CONSOLE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
THERE A TOY STORE HERE?
Gon: I'M PRETTY SURE THERE IS.
‐ Killua: OKAY. HOLD ON.
‐ Gon: HUH?
Mito: OH. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
‐ Killua: TO THE TOY STORE.
‐ Mito: HMM?
Gon: IT'S OUTSIDE THE PORT!
‐ Mito: HUH?
‐ Killua: GOT IT!
Gon: HAVE A SAFE TRIP, OKAY?!
♪
Gon: OH, SO THIS
IS A JOYSTATION.
Killua: THIS TAKES ME BACK.
I USED TO PLAY IT A LOT.
THERE WERE A BUNCH
OF CULT CLASSICS MADE FOR IT.
Gon: HMM.
THEN IS THIS MEMORY CARD
A CULT CLASSIC?
'CAUSE I DON'T SEE
A TITLE ON IT ANYWHERE.
Killua: YOU'VE NEVER PLAYED
ANY VIDEO GAMES, HAVE YOU?
THAT'S PRETTY WEIRD.
Gon: SERIOUSLY?
Killua: THAT'S NOT A GAME DISC.
IT JUST HOLDS
A GAME'S MEMORY DATA.
Gon: I GUESS THAT MEANS
WE CAN'T USE IT TO PLAY.
Killua: NOPE. YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO PUT THE DISC IN HERE.
BUT IF YOU INSERT
THE MEMORY CARD
AND POWER IT ON
WITHOUT A GAME INSIDE,
YOU CAN SEE
ALL THE DIFFERENT GAMES
THAT ARE USING THAT MEMORY.
Gon: OH, OKAY.
Killua: HUH.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
ONLY ONE GAME SAVED ON IT.
IT'S CALLED "GREED ISLAND."
Gon: "GREED ISLAND"?
Killua: WELL, ANYWAY, THERE ARE
A LOT OF SAVES ON HERE.
IT MIGHT BE POINTLESS,
BUT I'LL TRY TO COPY THE DATA.
Joystation:
COPYING "GREED ISLAND."
Killua: OKAY.
Gon: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Killua: SEARCHING ONLINE.
WE KNOW WHAT IT'S CALLED.
LOOKING FOR A STORE
THAT SELLS IT.
♪
WHAT? NO WAY!
NOT A SINGLE MATCH?
Gon: THAT MEANS
IT'S ALL SOLD OUT?
Killua: BUT I CAN'T FIND
ANY USED COPIES, EITHER.
EVEN A TOTALLY SOLD‐OUT GAME
WOULD BE OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S POSSIBLE
THIS GAME WAS NEVER
ACTUALLY ON THE MARKET.
Gon: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Killua: MAYBE IT WAS
AN INDIE GAME OR SOMETHING
AND IT NEVER GOT DISTRIBUTION,
OR IT COULD EVEN BE A GAME
THAT WAS BANNED FROM SALE
FOR SOME REASON.
I'LL KEEP LOOKING
AND SEE WHAT I CAN FIND.
GOT IT. WELL, IT TURNS OUT
IT WAS ACTUALLY SOLD
THROUGH LEGITIMATE CHANNELS.
Gon: IT SAYS, "'GREED ISLAND,'
A HUNTING GAME
EXCLUSIVELY FOR HUNTERS."
Killua: FOR HUNTERS, HUH?
WHAT THE‐‐
‐ ( cash register dings )
‐ LOOK AT THAT PRICE TAG!
Gon: 580 MILLION?!
Killua: IT'S 5.8 BILLION!
Gon: SAY WHAT?!
Killua: THAT'S CRAZY.
NO GAME HAS EVER
COST THAT MUCH MONEY.
Gon: ONLY 100 COPIES WERE MADE.
THAT'S NOT VERY MANY, IS IT?
Killua: NO,
IT'S PRACTICALLY NOTHING,
WHICH MEANS THE DEVELOPERS
WERE REALLY COCKY.
BUT IT MAKES SENSE.
THE PRICE TAG IS RIDICULOUS,
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU'RE A HUNTER.
THAT EXPLAINS HOW THEY SOLD OUT.
Gon: DO THE DEVELOPERS
HAVE ANY MORE LEFT IN STOCK?
Killua: GOOD QUESTION. I GUESS
IT'S WORTH A SHOT TO ASK THEM.
Woman: I'M SORRY.
THE GAME YOU'RE INQUIRING ABOUT
IS NO LONGER IN STOCK,
AND UNFORTUNATELY
THERE ARE NO PLANS
TO RE‐RELEASE IT AT THIS TIME.
Killua: OH, OKAY. THANK YOU.
THAT WAS A DEAD END.
Gon: THEN WE'LL HAVE TO FIND
SOMEONE WHO HAS A COPY
AND SEE IF THEY'LL
LET US HAVE IT.
Killua: YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO FIRST WE'RE GONNA NEED
TO LOCATE A SELLER.
WHY DON'T WE POST AN AD
ON A REVERSE AUCTION WEBSITE?
Gon: BUT WHERE WILL WE
GET THE MONEY?
Killua: WE'LL POOL OUR MONEY
FROM THE ARENA,
AND THAT GETS US
TO JUST OVER 800 MILLION.
Gon: WE STILL NEED
ANOTHER 5 BILLION.
Killua: NOT NECESSARILY.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: WITH THESE
PRIVATE DEALS,
THE SELLER HAS ALL THE POWER,
AND THEY USUALLY
SET A HIGHER PRICE
THAN WHAT THEY
ORIGINALLY PAID FOR IT.
Gon: THEN IT'LL COST EVEN MORE?
Killua: PROBABLY.
Both: HMM.
Gon: WELL, WE CAN STILL POST
A WANT AD, JUST IN CASE.
Killua: YEAH, BUT I DOUBT
ANYBODY IS GONNA CLICK ON IT.
Gon: "WE ARE LOOKING FOR A GAME.
"DOES ANYBODY HAVE
'GREED ISLAND' FOR SALE?
PRICE NEGOTIABLE."
( both gasp )
Gon: WOW, LOOK! WE ALREADY
HAVE MORE THAN 10,000 HITS.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
Killua: I THOUGHT SO.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE ALL TRYING
TO UNLOAD
COUNTERFEIT COPIES ON US.
CONSIDERING THE HIGH PRICE,
WE REALLY SHOULD HAVE
SEEN THIS COMING.
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
NO WAY WE CAN VERIFY
EVERY ONE OF THESE OFFERS.
BESIDES, WHAT'S THE POINT
IF WE CAN'T EVEN TELL
IF IT'S THE REAL GAME?
Gon: THEN WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO NOW?
Killua: WELL, WE NEED TO UNCOVER
A LOT MORE INFORMATION.
LET'S DIG DEEPER ONLINE.
BUT I'M REALLY NO EXPERT
IN ALL THAT STUFF.
Gon: SO WHO DO WE KNOW WHO'S
INTO GAMING AND THE INTERNET?
( Killua gasps )
I THINK I MIGHT KNOW SOMEBODY.
Gon: HUH?
Killua: IN FACT,
HE MIGHT EVEN OWN
A COPY OF "GREED ISLAND"
ALREADY.
Gon: REALLY? YOU THINK SO?
Killua: EH, GUESS I'LL ASK HIM,
BUT I REALLY DON'T WANNA.
Gon: WHO IS IT? WHO IS IT?
( phone line rings )
Killua: HEY. GOTOH, IT'S KILLUA.
Gon: MR. GOTOH?
Killua: YEAH.
YEAH, I'M DOING GREAT.
NOW? WHO CARES WHERE I AM?
IF I TELL YOU, MOM'S GONNA
FIND OUT SOONER OR LATER.
ANYWAY, CAN YOU
GET PIGGY FOR ME?
Gon: WHO'S PIGGY?
( pig oinks )
Milluki: WHAT?!
KILLUA WANTS TO TALK TO ME?
SCREW THAT! TELL HIM
I STEPPED OUT OR SOMETHING.
Killua: SHUT UP! YOU'RE LYING!
HE HASN'T
LEFT THE HOUSE IN AGES.
YOU GO TELL HIM IF HE DOESN'T
PICK UP THE PHONE IN 10 SECONDS,
I'LL BREAK
ALL OF HIS FIGURINES!
( Milluki growls )
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
JUST PUT HIM ON.
HEY, KIL, IF YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT LAYING A FINGER
ON MY COLLECTION,
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
Killua: CHILL OUT, BRO.
I WAS ONLY KIDDING.
YOU'RE SO SCARY
WHEN YOU GET MAD.
Gon: WAIT. YOUR BROTHER?
Milluki: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU WANT, ANYWAY?
HURRY UP. I'M BUSY.
OH, YEAH. "GREED ISLAND"?
I'VE HEARD OF IT.
IT'S A SUPER‐RARE GAME.
WHY? YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
INTERESTED IN RARE GAMES.
Killua: DO YOU OWN A COPY?
‐ Milluki: NO, I DON'T.
‐ ( Killua sighs )
Milluki: I WANTED ONE, BUT I
WAS FIVE WHEN IT WENT ON SALE,
AND I DIDN'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
BUT I HEARD THERE WERE
OVER 20,000 REQUESTS
AND ONLY 100 COPIES.
BECAUSE OF THAT, EACH COPY
COSTS A WHOLE LOT OF JENNY,
ABOUT 5.8 BIL.
I TRIED TO TRACK ONE DOWN
RIGHT AFTER THE THRILL WORE OFF,
BUT I COULDN'T EVEN
FIND AN OWNER.
IT'S LEGENDARY
FOR ALL KINDS OF REASONS.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?
YOU LOOKING FOR A COPY, OR WHAT?
Killua: KINDA.
Milluki: WELL, FORGET IT!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN I HAD TO GIVE UP.
Killua: OH?
YOU HAD TO ADMIT DEFEAT
'CAUSE IT WAS TOO MUCH
FOR YOU TO HANDLE?
( Milluki growls )
HEH. THAT WAS YEARS AGO.
I'VE GOT A FEW LEADS NOW,
SMART GUY.
BUT CONSIDERING
HOW MUCH EFFORT IT WOULD TAKE,
NOT TO MENTION MONEY,
IT'S NOT WORTH MY TIME.
Killua: SO WHAT WERE THOSE LEADS
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
Milluki: YEAH, RIGHT.
LIKE I'D TELL YOU FOR FREE.
Killua: IF I HAD
A "GREED ISLAND" MEMORY CARD,
WOULD YOU RECONSIDER?
Milluki: HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
Killua: I JUST HAPPENED TO GET
MY HANDS ON A MEMORY CARD.
THAT'S ALL.
I FIGURED WITH YOUR SKILLS,
YOU COULD ANALYZE THE DATA
AND REVERSE‐ENGINEER
THE GAME ITSELF, RIGHT?
Milluki: IS THAT TRUE?
YOU'D BETTER NOT BE LYING.
Killua: I NEVER LIE,
NOT WHEN I'M MAKING DEALS.
♪
Milluki: OKAY, FINE.
I HAVE TWO LEADS.
Killua: WAIT A MINUTE.
NOT OVER THE PHONE.
Milluki: DON'T WORRY, KIL.
IF SOMEBODY IS EAVESDROPPING,
THIS INFORMATION
WON'T DO THEM ANY GOOD.
OKAY. FIRST LEAD...
Killua: YEAH. YEAH. I SEE.
OKAY, GOT IT.
I'LL SEND IT TO YOU
IN THE USUAL WAY.
SORRY, BUT I KINDA
HAD TO PROMISE HIM
THE COPY OF THE MEMORY CARD
IN EXCHANGE.
Gon: SURE. IT'S JUST A COPY,
ANYWAY, SO I DON'T MIND.
Killua: WELL, IN RETURN,
I GOT TWO LEADS
THAT SOUND PRETTY SOLID.
ONE'S A WEBSITE.
IT'S ONLY ACCESSIBLE TO HUNTERS,
WHICH IS NO PROBLEM FOR YOU.
I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
WE CAN FIND MORE LEADS
ON "GREED ISLAND" THERE.
Gon: REALLY?
THAT MEANS I GET
TO USE MY HUNTER'S LICENSE!
Killua: STUPID!
IF YOU USE YOUR HOME COMPUTER,
THEY'RE GONNA KNOW YOUR ADDRESS!
YOU REALLY WANT BAD GUYS
SHOWING UP ON THIS ISLAND
TO STEAL YOUR HUNTER'S LICENSE?
Gon: OH. YEAH, I FORGOT.
Killua: YOU'VE GOTTA
USE PUBLIC COMPUTERS
FOR THIS KIND OF THING,
LIKE AT A HOTEL OR A NET CAF É.
( Gon chuckles )
Killua: WELL, THERE'S NO RUSH.
I STILL DON'T EVEN KNOW
THE ADDRESS.
ONCE MY BROTHER
GETS THE MEMORY CARD,
HE SAID HE'D SEND IT TO ME.
OR LEAD TWO,
THE YORKNEW CITY AUCTION.
Gon: WHAT?! HOLD ON.
ISN'T YORKNEW CITY‐‐
Killua: YEAH, WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
MEET KURAPIKA AND LEORIO THERE.
ALSO THEY'RE HOLDING
THE WORLD'S GREATEST AUCTION
THERE IN SEPTEMBER.
MY BROTHER SAID
IT'S PROBABLY A HOAX,
BUT THERE'S A RUMOR
GOING AROUND THAT SOMEONE'S
GONNA BE AUCTIONING OFF
DOZENS OF COPIES.
Gon: THEN MAYBE
THAT SOMEONE IS GING!
Killua: YEAH.
SO MAYBE IT'S NOT A RUMOR.
IT JUST MIGHT BE CREDIBLE.
Gon: BUT WE'RE GONNA NEED
A CRAZY AMOUNT OF MONEY
TO BUY A COPY.
Killua: YEAH,
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
Gon: I GUESS
IT REALLY WAS OUR DESTINY
TO GO TO YORKNEW CITY.
♪
Milluki: HMM.
BATTERA, THE TYCOON, IS OFFERING
17 BILLION FOR "GREED ISLAND"
AND 50 BILLION MORE
FOR A MEMORY CARD
WITH A COMPLETE
SAVED GAME ON IT.
THAT'S TRULY LEGENDARY.
HEH HEH. INTERESTING.
I'LL PUT AN END
TO THIS LEGEND MYSELF.
Gon: WOW!
THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
WHAT'S THE BIG OCCASION?
Mito: YOU PROBABLY WON'T BE BACK
TO VISIT FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Gon: EH?
AUNT MITO.
Mito: WHO KNOWS WHEN YOU'LL
GET A CHANCE TO EAT AGAIN?
BETTER FILL UP WHILE YOU CAN.
Gon: MM‐HMM.
( Mito chuckles )
♪
Gon: ALL RIGHT!
Boys: THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
( overlapping chatter )
Woman: BYE!
Man: SO LONG!
Man #2: SEE YOU AROUND!
Man #3: SAFE JOURNEY!
Gon: AUNT MITO!
SO LONG!
I'M GONNA GO FIND GING!
I PROMISE!
AND AFTER I MEET HIM, I'M GONNA
COME BACK TO THE ISLAND, OKAY?!
BYE! TAKE CARE!
I'LL MISS YOU!
♪
Narrator: GING TOLD GON
TO FIND HIM,
LEAVING A RIDDLE BEHIND
AS A CLUE TO HIS WHEREABOUTS.
IN ORDER TO SOLVE THAT RIDDLE
AND MEET HIS FATHER,
GON LEAVES HOME ONCE AGAIN
WITH HIS FRIEND
KILLUA BY HIS SIDE
AND SETS SAIL
FOR YORKNEW CITY.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING GING.
HE'S MY DAD, AND I BECAME
A HUNTER TO FIND HIM.
Killua: OH, YEAH? SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOUR DAD WANTS, ANYWAY?
Gon: I REALLY DON'T KNOW,
BUT AS SOON AS I FIND HIM,
I'LL BE SURE TO ASK.
♪
NEXT TIME, "WISH AND PROMISE."
GO TO SLEEP, OR YOU'LL BE LATE.
Killua: WHO, ME?
NAH. I DON'T NEED SLEEP.
Gon: TRY TO GET PLENTY OF REST,
EVERYONE.