♪
Narrator: IN THE FORESTS
OF THE DENTORA REGION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA
LIES A DORMANT VOLCANO
MEASURING 3,722 METERS HIGH.
IT IS KNOWN AS KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
IT IS HOME
TO A FAMILY OF FAMOUS ASSASSINS,
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY.
VISITORS ARRIVE EVERY DAY
IN HOPES OF CATCHING
A GLIMPSE OF THE MANSION,
WHICH HAS NEVER BEEN SEEN.
IT'S ONE OF THIS NATION'S MOST
POPULAR TOURIST ATTRACTIONS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Zebro: WELL, HOW LONG
WILL YOU BE STAYING HERE?
Gon: UNTIL WE SEE KILLUA,
AND WE'RE NOT LEAVING
A SECOND BEFORE!
( Zebro chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, THEN. FOLLOW ME.
♪
Narrator: GON AND HIS FRIENDS
HAVE BEGUN TO CONFRONT
THE OBSTACLES
THAT THEY MUST OVERCOME
IN ORDER TO REUNITE WITH KILLUA.
THEY HEAD TOWARD
THEIR DESTINATION
WITH NO IDEA WHAT AWAITS THEM.
Zebro: HERE WE ARE.
THESE ARE
THE SERVANTS' QUARTERS.
IT'S GETTING PRETTY LATE,
SO YOU CAN STAY HERE TONIGHT.
( scraping )
Kurapika: UH...
Zebro: PLEASE, COME ON IN.
HEY! ANYBODY HOME?
Man: GUESTS, HUH?
DON'T SEE THAT EVERY DAY.
Zebro: THIS IS SEAQUANT.
HE WORKS WITH ME
HERE AT THE ESTATE.
Gon: GOOD EVENING.
Seaquant: HUMPH.
ZEBRO DOESN'T
TAKE A LIKING TO JUST ANYBODY.
MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME,
THOUGH IN THIS HOUSE,
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
YOU WANT TO SEE
YOUNG MASTER KILLUA?
( thump )
( laughs )
NOW, THAT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
Leorio: ACTUALLY,
WE'RE DEAD SERIOUS.
Seaquant: THEN LET ME
GIVE YOU SOME ADVICE.
GIVE UP NOW, AND GO HOME.
Leorio: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
Seaquant: ZEBRO TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE TESTING GATE, RIGHT?
IF YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT THIS PLACE IS LIKE,
THAT'S AN EXAMPLE.
Gon: IT WON'T BE EASY.
WE GET THAT,
BUT STILL, I'M NOT LEAVING YET,
NOT UNTIL I SEE KILLUA.
♪
BEFORE, WHEN HE WAS IN TROUBLE,
I WASN'T THERE FOR HIM
LIKE I SHOULD'VE BEEN.
♪
IF I WAS‐‐
IF I'D JUST BEEN THERE...
I KNOW I COULD HAVE STOPPED HIM.
( both sigh )
Gon: HE'S MY FRIEND, AND HE'S
REALLY IMPORTANT TO ME, OKAY?
( Zebro chuckles )
I UNDERSTAND. IN THAT CASE,
WHY DON'T YOU DO SOME TRAINING
WHILE YOU'RE HERE?
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Seaquant: HEY, NOW, ZEBRO.
Zebro: LISTEN TO ME, GON.
YOU THREE CAN TRY
TO OPEN THE DOOR TOGETHER.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH TEAMWORK.
( both gasp )
Zebro: AND WITH
A LITTLE BIT OF TRAINING,
IT SHOULD BE POSSIBLE.
HOW 'BOUT IT?
Gon: I DON'T LIKE
THE IDEA OF BEING TESTED.
Kurapika: BUT IF THERE'S
TRULY NO OTHER WAY...
Leorio: I GUESS
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO DO IT.
Gon: YEAH.
Zebro: ALL RIGHT.
THEN I'M GOING TO NEED
ALL THREE OF YOU
TO PUT SOMETHING ON.
Kurapika: HUH?
♪
‐ ( clomping )
‐ ( Leorio grunting )
( groans )
HOW IS THIS SO HEAVY?
Zebro: IT WEIGHS 50 KILOGRAMS.
WEAR IT AT ALL TIMES,
EXCEPT WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING.
Leorio: EH?!
Zebro: I'LL MAKE IT HEAVIER
AS YOU GET USED TO IT.
( Leorio screams )
( thump )
Zebro: HERE. HAVE SOME TEA.
( Leorio groans )
( grunting )
WHAT THE?
( all grunting )
Zebro: THE CUPS
WEIGH 20 KILOGRAMS,
‐ AND THIS TEAPOT WEIGHS 40.
‐ Kurapika: WHAT?
Zebro: ALL THE FURNITURE
AND UTENSILS IN THIS HOUSE
WEIGH OVER 20 KILOGRAMS EACH.
Kurapika: I SEE
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING AT.
SO THIS WILL SERVE
AS OUR TRAINING.
Seaquant: WHAT'S THE POINT?
YOU KNOW THEY'RE JUST GONNA
GIVE UP IN TWO OR THREE DAYS.
Leorio: WHAT WAS THAT?!
Zebro: OH, SEAQUANT,
UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN,
YOUR SHIFT'S ALREADY STARTED,
HASN'T IT?
Seaquant: YEAH,
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
( Leorio growls )
( door rumbles )
Zebro: SORRY ABOUT THAT.
HE REALLY
ISN'T SUCH A BAD PERSON.
Leorio: OH, BY THE WAY,
WHERE'S THE BATHROOM?
Zebro: RIGHT THROUGH
THAT DOOR OVER THERE.
( Leorio panting )
LET ME GUESS.
THE BATHROOM DOOR IS ALSO...
Zebro: OF COURSE.
THAT DOOR WEIGHS 500 KILOGRAMS.
Leorio: 500!
WHAT?! YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
I'M GONNA SPRING A LEAK!
( footsteps echoing )
( wooden geta clopping )
Woman: KALLUTO, DEAR,
OPEN THE DOOR.
( door scrapes )
♪
KIL, HAVE YOU LEARNED
YOUR LESSON YET?
Boy: IT'S NO USE, MAMA.
HE ISN'T EVEN
THE LEAST BIT SORRY.
WE NEED TO MAKE HIM SUFFER MORE.
Mrs. Zoldyck: ENOUGH!
SHUT YOUR MOUTH, MILLUKI!
( Milluki scoffs )
Mrs. Zoldyck: KIL, DARLING,
WHY DON'T YOU STOP
BEING SO STUBBORN
AND JUST SAY THAT YOU'RE SORRY?
Milluki: OH, AND ABOUT
THAT FRIEND OF YOURS,
HIS NAME IS GON, ISN'T IT?
HE'D BE BETTER OFF LEAVING,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE
HE WANTS TO TRY HIS HAND
AT THE TESTING GATE.
Killua: GON, HE'S‐‐HE'S HERE?
Mrs. Zoldyck: MILLUKI!
YOU'VE SAID FAR TOO MUCH!
NOW, YOU SEE, KIL‐‐
Killua: WHY THE HELL
DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?!
Milluki: DON'T YOU EVER
TALK TO MAMA LIKE THAT AGAIN!
Mrs. Zoldyck: I TOLD YOU
TO SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
I DIDN'T THINK
TELLING YOU WAS NECESSARY.
HE CAN'T OPEN THE GATE,
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS.
‐ Killua: HE WILL.
‐ ( Mrs. Zoldyck gasps )
Killua: HE'LL DO IT. I KNOW IT.
Mrs. Zoldyck: WELL,
ISN'T THAT ABSOLUTELY DIVINE?
HOWEVER, HE WON'T MAKE IT HERE.
I CAN PROMISE YOU THAT.
Killua: GON WILL.
HE CAN DO IT.
HE'LL PROVE YOU WRONG.
NO QUESTION.
HE'LL DEFINITELY MAKE IT HERE.
( wind blowing )
Leorio: GON, WAIT.
YOU JUST WATCH, OKAY?
Gon: UH, BUT WHY?
Kurapika: YOU NEED TO LET
YOUR ARM HEAL PROPERLY FIRST.
Leorio: IF KURAPIKA AND I
CAN OPEN IT OURSELVES,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
LET US HANDLE IT.
Gon: FINE.
Leorio: YOU READY, KURAPIKA?
Kurapika: YEAH!
( both grunting )
Seaquant: COME ON,
YOU'RE ONLY WASTING YOUR TIME.
Kurapika: NO USE.
IT WON'T BUDGE.
Leorio: DAMN IT.
BUT WE ONLY
JUST STARTED TRAINING.
IF WE WORK HARD ENOUGH,
I KNOW WE CAN DO IT!
( Kurapika sighs )
I WISH I SHARED YOUR OPTIMISM.
♪
( Gon chuckles )
( Leorio snoring )
( Leorio and Kurapika grunting )
( both panting )
Seaquant: I'M TELLING YOU,
THIS IS NEVER GONNA WORK.
YOU'RE JUST KIDDING YOURSELVES.
YOU KNOW THAT.
Leorio: WELL, IF YOU'RE SO SURE,
THEN QUIT WATCHING,
AND GO DO YOUR JOB!
( Seaquant scoffs )
Kurapika: GON IS ONE OF US.
( sighs )
AND HE'S MADE IT QUITE CLEAR
THAT HE WISHES TO SEE
HIS FRIEND, QUITE CLEAR.
IT'S ONLY RIGHT
TO HELP HIM ACHIEVE HIS GOAL.
Leorio: LET'S GIVE IT
ANOTHER SHOT.
Kurapika: YEAH.
( both grunting )
Seaquant: OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU CAN'T KEEP
PUSHING MINDLESSLY.
GET YOUR TIMING IN SYNC.
YOU HAVE TO PUSH
BOTH DOORS SIMULTANEOUSLY
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
OTHERWISE, IT'LL NEVER OPEN.
( Zebro and Gon chuckle )
Leorio: GET OUR TIMING IN SYNC.
Kurapika: PUSH BOTH DOORS
SIMULTANEOUSLY
AND WITH ALL OUR MIGHT.
Leorio: YOU READY?
Kurapika: HMM.
Leorio: ONE!
Kurapika: AND TWO!
Both: THREE!
( both grunting )
‐ ( door scrapes )
‐ ( all gasp )
( both yelp )
Gon: LEORIO! KURAPIKA!
( Kurapika groans )
Leorio: WHEW.
( chuckles )
IT MOVED A LITTLE.
♪
Kurapika: HMM?
( chuckles )
♪
Butler: WHAT'S THAT?
THE TESTING GATE?
ARE YOU CERTAIN?
AND?
Seaquant: OH, WELL,
I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW, IS ALL.
Butler: VERY WELL.
( hangs up )
Seaquant: WHY DOES HE ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE SO DAMN GRUFF?
( Leorio grunting )
Zebro: HEY, YOU TWO.
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TAKING OFF THOSE VESTS TODAY?
( Leorio gasps )
WELL, DON'T MIND IF I DO.
♪
ALL RIGHT!
NOW WE'LL BE ABLE
TO OPEN THE GATE FOR SURE.
LET'S DO THIS, KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: RIGHT.
Leorio: ONE AND TWO...
Both: THREE!
( both grunting )
Seaquant: HUH?
Leorio: DAMN!
THAT'S AS FAR AS IT'LL GO!
Kurapika: YOU CAN'T GIVE UP YET!
KEEP PUSHING!
Leorio: OKAY, I'M WITH YOU!
Kurapika: GON, I‐‐
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOUR ARM, REMEMBER?
Gon: IT'S OKAY.
IT'S HEALED NOW.
Kurapika: WHAT, ALREADY?
Leorio: ARE YOU SURE, GON?
Gon: YEP!
SO ANYWAY,
WE GOTTA MATCH OUR BREATHING?
Leorio: UH, THAT'S RIGHT.
Kurapika: WELL, LET'S PUSH!
Leorio: HEH. HERE GOES!
Kurapika: READY.
Leorio: GET SET.
Gon: GO!
( all grunting )
♪
Seaquant: IT'S OPENING.
( Zebro chuckles )
Gon: OW!
( both panting )
Gon: IT OPENED.
Leorio: HELL, YEAH!
Kurapika: WE REALLY DID IT, GON!
Gon: UH‐HUH!
Zebro: NOW THEN,
JUST FOLLOW THIS PATH,
AND HEAD TOWARD THE MOUNTAIN.
THE MANSION SHOULD BE
UP THERE SOMEWHERE.
NEVER BEEN THERE MYSELF,
WHICH IS KIND OF EMBARRASSING,
CONSIDERING I'VE WORKED HERE
FOR 20 YEARS.
I'M SORRY
I CAN'T BE OF ANY MORE HELP.
Gon: NO, SIR, YOU HAVE BEEN.
MR. ZEBRO, SEAQUANT,
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
( Zebro chuckles )
Gon: THANKS AGAIN!
SEE YOU LATER!
Zebro: THEY'RE REALLY SOMETHING.
THOSE THREE MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO REACH THE MANSION.
( Seaquant laughs )
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
THEY'LL DIE FOR SURE.
Zebro: ARE YOU SPEAKING
FROM YOUR EXPERIENCE BACK THEN?
( birds squawking )
Seaquant: A SINGLE
APPRENTICE BUTLER
WIPED US OUT TO THE LAST MAN,
AND THAT MADE ONE THING
PAINFULLY CLEAR,
THAT I'D GOTTEN MYSELF IN
WAY OVER MY HEAD.
Zebro: I RECALL
YOU WERE SO IMPRESSED
THAT YOU ASKED FOR A JOB HERE.
Seaquant: YEAH, WELL,
EXCUSE ME...
BUT THE BOSSES AND WORKERS HERE,
THEY'RE MONSTERS,
EVERY LAST ONE.
AND ONCE YOU
STEP ONTO THEIR TURF...
♪
Mrs. Zoldyck:
THE TESTING GATE OPENED?
Butler: YES, MA'AM.
Mrs. Zoldyck: THIS IS
A CRITICAL TIME FOR KILLUA.
WE SIMPLY CANNOT ALLOW
ANYONE NEAR HIM,
ESPECIALLY UNNECESSARY
DISTRACTIONS LIKE FRIENDS.
IS THAT CLEAR?
Butler: YES, MA'AM.
( Gon gasps )
Girl: PLEASE LEAVE NOW.
YOU'RE TRESPASSING
ON PRIVATE PROPERTY.
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO PASS
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
Gon: BUT WE CALLED AHEAD,
AND WE CAME
THROUGH THE TESTING GATE.
Girl: THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS
DID NOT GIVE YOU
PERMISSION TO ENTER.
Gon: WHAT THE HECK DO WE
NEED TO DO TO GET PERMISSION?
I EVEN TOLD THEM I WAS
KILLUA'S FRIEND AND EVERYTHING!
Girl: WHO KNOWS? NO ONE
HAS EVER RECEIVED PERMISSION.
Gon: THEN I GUESS WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO TRESPASS!
Girl: I SUPPOSE SO.
IN ANY CASE,
THIS IS WHERE I DRAW THE LINE.
TAKE ONE STEP PAST IT,
AND I WILL REMOVE YOU BY FORCE
IF NECESSARY.
( both grunt )
( both gasp )
♪
Leorio: DAMN IT.
Gon: LEORIO, KURAPIKA,
STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
I'LL HANDLE THIS.
OW, OW!
LOOK, WE DIDN'T COME HERE
TO FIGHT ANYONE.
WE JUST WANT TO SEE KILLUA.
Girl: YOUR MOTIVES DON'T MATTER.
I HAVE MY ORDERS, AND IT
IS MY DUTY TO FOLLOW THEM.
TRY ALL YOU LIKE.
( footsteps )
( club strikes )
( thump )
I'LL NEVER LET YOU PASS.
( Gon gasping )
I WILL PASS.
I'M GONNA SEE KILLUA!
Girl: WELCOME HOME,
MASTER KILLUA.
♪
Killua: YEAH.
I MADE ONE...
Girl: EH?
Killua: ...A FRIEND.
‐ ( club strikes )
‐ ( thump )
( club strikes )
( thump )
♪
( Gon gasping )
Girl: STOP RIGHT THERE.
PLEASE GO AWAY!
WHY WON'T YOU JUST GIVE UP?!
YOU KNOW IT'S POINTLESS!
PLEASE STOP HIM!
YOU'RE HIS FRIENDS!
WHY HA‐‐
Gon: WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I JUST CAME HERE
TO SEE MY FRIEND.
THE ONLY REASON I'M HERE
IS TO SEE KILLUA!
SO WHY ARE YOU MAKING ME
GO THROUGH ALL THIS?!
( birds squawking )
Gon: HEY...
I CROSSED THE LINE.
SHOULDN'T YOU HIT ME?
♪
I CAN TELL
YOU'RE DIFFERENT FROM MIKE.
YOU MAY BE TRYING TO COVER UP
YOUR FEELINGS,
BUT YOU STILL HAVE A HEART.
WHEN I MENTIONED KILLUA'S NAME,
YOUR EYES SOFTENED
JUST FOR A MOMENT.
Girl: PLEASE...
( crying )
HELP HIM.
HELP MASTER KI‐‐
( all gasp )
Mrs. Zoldyck: HONESTLY...
WHAT WAS THAT SERVANT
BABBLING ABOUT?
SHE MADE IT SOUND LIKE
WE WERE BEING MEAN TO KILLUA.
( somber chorus singing )
HOW RUDE.
SHE'S JUST A BLOODY APPRENTICE.
AND YOU MUST BE GON.
ILLUMI TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
KILLUA IS AWARE
THAT YOU'VE BEEN ON THE PREMISES
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
I HAVE A MESSAGE FROM KILLUA
THAT HE ASKED ME
TO RELAY TO YOU.
"THANK YOU FOR COMING.
"I'M HAPPY THAT YOU DID,
"BUT I CAN'T SEE YOU RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY."
Narrator: GON AND HIS FRIENDS
HAVE FINALLY MADE IT
INSIDE THE ZOLDYCK ESTATE,
BUT NOW THEY FACE
THEIR GREATEST OBSTACLE YET,
A SAD MESSAGE
FROM KILLUA HIMSELF
SAYING THAT HE CANNOT SEE THEM.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY."
WHO IS KILLUA TO YOU, ANYWAY?
Kalluto: MY BIG BROTHER.