Gon: MAKE MONEY
WHILE WE'RE TRAINING?
Killua: AT THE HEAVENS ARENA.
Gon: HEAVENS ARENA?
Killua: YEAH.
I'LL EXPLAIN LATER,
BUT WE REALLY
OUGHT TO GET GOING NOW.
Gon: RIGHT!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: WHOA! LOOK! IT'S HUGE!
Killua: YEP.
THAT'S HEAVENS ARENA.
IT'S 251 STORIES
AND 991 METERS TALL,
MAKING IT THE WORLD'S
FOURTH TALLEST BUILDING.
Gon: SO THIS IS
WHERE WE'LL BE TRAINING.
♪
Killua: WELL, THE TICKETS
WE BOUGHT TO GET US HERE
LEFT US COMPLETELY BROKE.
WE'VE GOTTA MAKE MORE
WHILE WE'RE HERE.
WE'LL START FRESH
WHEN WE DISEMBARK.
Gon: RIGHT! I GOT IT.
Killua: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LET'S GO!
Gon: OKAY!
♪
Narrator: GON AND KILLUA
HEAD TO HEAVENS ARENA
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL IN MIND,
TO GET STRONGER.
Killua: GON.
Gon: EH?
THIS IS A REALLY LONG LINE.
IS EVERYONE GOING
TO HEAVENS ARENA?
Killua: THERE AREN'T
ANY RULES TO WORRY ABOUT,
NOT LIKE THERE WERE
FOR THE HUNTER EXAM.
YOU JUST GOTTA
KNOCK YOUR OPPONENT OUT.
Gon: OH.
Killua: THE HIGHER YOU GO,
THE MORE PRIZE MONEY YOU MAKE.
IF YOU WANT TO EARN A LIVING
WITH YOUR FISTS,
THIS IS AS GOOD AS IT GETS.
Receptionist:
WELCOME TO HEAVENS ARENA.
NOW, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND
FILLING OUT THIS FORM.
KILLUA ZOLDYCK,
YOU'RE NUMBER 2,054.
GON FREECSS, YOU'RE 2,055.
ON THE FIRST ARENA FLOOR,
THEY'LL BE CALLING YOU
BY YOUR NUMBER,
SO TRY NOT TO FORGET IT.
PLEASE GO ON AHEAD.
( crowd cheering )
Gon: WOW!
( fighters grunting )
‐ Man: LOOKING GOOD!
‐ Man #2: DO IT!
Killua: IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
BUT THIS PLACE HASN'T CHANGED.
Gon: WAIT. YOU MEAN
YOU'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE?
Killua: YEAH,
WHEN I WAS ABOUT SIX.
MY DAD LEFT ME HERE FLAT BROKE,
TOLD ME TO REACH
THE 200th FLOOR.
TOOK ME TWO WHOLE YEARS.
Gon: TWO YEARS?
I MEAN, SURE, HE WAS ONLY SIX,
BUT IT TOOK HIM THAT LONG?
Killua: THERE ARE GUYS
OF HISOKA'S CALIBER,
BUT ONLY FARTHER UP,
SO DON'T WASTE TIME. YOU GOT IT?
Gon: MM‐HMM.
Announcer: NUMBERS 1,973
AND 2,055 TO RING E.
Gon: 2,055! THAT'S ME!
OH, MAN, I'M GETTING
PRETTY NERVOUS RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
Killua: GON, YOU MADE IT
THROUGH THE TESTING GATE, RIGHT?
Gon: HUH?
Killua: SO RELAX.
Man #3: CHECK IT OUT!
IT'S JUST A KID!
Man #4: HEY! YOU BETTER RUN
WHILE YOU STILL CAN, KID!
Man #5: THIS AIN'T A GAME!
GIVE HIM A PUNCH,
AND SEND HIM FLYING!
( Killua chuckles )
Referee: THIS IS
A FIRST‐FLOOR FIGHT,
SO WE WILL BE APPRAISING
YOUR SKILL LEVELS.
YOU'RE ALLOWED THREE MINUTES
TO DEMONSTRATE
WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
NOW THEN, BEGIN!
Fighter 1,973:
I'M REAL SORRY, KID.
‐ ( knuckles cracking )
‐ BUT I'LL MAKE IT FAST
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO SUFFER!
Killua: YOU MADE IT
THROUGH THE TESTING GATE, RIGHT?
SO RELAX.
GO OUT THERE, AND PUSH HARD.
( Gon thinking )
OKAY, SO JUST...
( aloud )
PUSH HARD!
( fighter 1,973 screams )
♪
Man #5: NO WAY!
Killua: NICE.
( crowd cheering )
Man #4: THAT KID'S INCREDIBLE!
Man #3: WHAT CRAZY POWER!
Gon: WHEN DID I GET SO STRONG?
Referee: HMM.
2,055, PROCEED DIRECTLY
TO FLOOR 50.
Gon: HMM.
HEH. OKAY!
( crowd cheering )
‐ Man #6: GREAT JOB!
‐ Man #7: LOOKING GOOD!
THAT FIRST KID'S NOT
THE ONLY ONE WHO'S A BEAST!
Man #8: GREAT!
Referee #2: WAIT.
THIS SAYS YOU'VE ALREADY BEEN
TO THE 200th FLOOR,
AND THOSE WERE
SOME POWERFUL MOVES.
ALL RIGHT.
GO TO THE 180th FLOOR.
‐ Killua: NAH. I'LL START AT 50.
‐ Referee #2: HUH?
Killua: I WANT TO TAKE IT SLOW.
( crowd yelling )
Referee #3: ENOUGH!
Man #3: WHOA! THAT KID'S
PRETTY POWERFUL, TOO!
Referee #3: YOU'RE PERMITTED
TO ADVANCE TO THE 50th FLOOR.
Boy: OSU! THANK YOU!
Guide: THE FIRST 200 FLOORS
OF HEAVENS ARENA
ARE DIVIDED INTO CLASSES,
10 FLOORS EACH,
WHICH MEANS THAT A FIGHTER
WHO WINS ON THE 50th FLOOR
ADVANCES TO THE 60th.
LOSE, AND THEY AUTOMATICALLY
DROP DOWN TO THE 40th FLOOR.
Gon: SO THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
Killua: ALSO‐‐
Boy: I'VE HEARD ONCE YOU GET
ALL THE WAY TO THE 100th FLOOR,
THEY COMP YOU
YOUR VERY OWN ROOM!
( both gasp )
Boy: OH. I'M SORRY.
HOW IMPOLITE.
OSU!
MY NAME IS ZUSHI.
AND YOU?
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Gon: MY NAME'S GON.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU!
Guide: HERE WE ARE.
Zushi: OH, I WATCHED
YOUR FIGHTS EARLIER.
YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING!
Killua: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU MADE IT UP HERE
WITH ONLY ONE MATCH, TOO.
Gon: HE'S RIGHT.
Zushi: NO, NO.
I STILL HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT DISCIPLINE DO YOU PRACTICE?
I STUDY
THE SHINGEN‐RYU TECHNIQUE.
Killua: A DISCIPLINE?
DON'T HAVE ONE.
Gon: NOPE.
Zushi: YOU'RE KIDDING!
YOU'RE BOTH THAT POWERFUL
WITH NO FORMAL TRAINING?
I'M HUMBLED TO BE
IN YOUR PRESENCE.
I'VE COME A LONG WAY,
BUT I'M NOT FINISHED.
( clapping )
Man: ZUSHI, YOU DID WELL.
Zushi: THANK YOU, MASTER!
Man: I'M VERY HAPPY TO SEE
THAT YOU STUCK TO MY TEACHINGS.
Zushi: OSU!
I AM HONORED.
BUT, MASTER,
YOUR SHIRT'S UNTUCKED.
Man: EH? OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
( chuckles )
WHO ARE THEY?
Zushi: OH.
THIS IS KILLUA AND GON.
Wing: PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS WING.
Both: OSU!
Wing: I REALLY
WASN'T EXPECTING TO SEE
ANY OTHER KIDS HERE
BESIDES ZUSHI.
SO WHAT BRINGS
THE TWO OF YOU HERE?
Killua: UH, WE‐‐WELL,
WE WANT TO BECOME STRONGER,
BUT WE'RE ALSO PRETTY BROKE,
SO WE'RE MAKING MONEY
AT EXACTLY THE SAME TIME.
Gon: YEAH.
KILLUA'S BEEN HERE BEFORE, SIR.
Wing: THAT RIGHT?
YOU MUST BE QUITE TALENTED,
OR ELSE YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE MADE IT TO THIS LEVEL.
EVEN SO, PAY CLOSE ATTENTION
TO YOUR OPPONENT'S BODY
AND YOUR OWN.
Both: OSU!
Worker: KILLUA, GON, AND ZUSHI.
AH, THERE WE ARE.
HAND ME YOUR TICKETS, PLEASE.
( typing )
HERE. THIS IS YOUR PRIZE MONEY
FROM THE EARLIER FIGHT,
Gon: 152 JENNY.
Killua: ON THIS FLOOR,
YOU MAKE JUST ENOUGH
FOR A JUICE, WIN OR LOSE,
BUT ON ALL
OF THE OTHER FLOORS HERE,
A LOSS GETS YOU NOTHING.
WINNING ON THE 50th FLOOR
EARNS 50,000.
‐ Gon: 50,000?
‐ Zushi: THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
Killua: THE HUNDREDTH FLOOR,
I THINK YOU GET A MILLION.
( both gasp )
Killua: ONCE YOU'RE
PAST THE 150th FLOOR,
‐ YOU GET 10 MILLION.
‐ Gon: 10 MILLION?!
DIDN'T YOU MAKE IT
TO THE 200th FLOOR BEFORE?
Zushi: WHOA! THE 200th FLOOR?
Gon: HOW MUCH DO YOU GET
FOR WINNING ON THE 200th FLOOR?
Killua: TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I DON'T ACTUALLY KNOW THAT,
BECAUSE I QUIT PRETTY MUCH
AS SOON AS I QUALIFIED FOR IT.
BUT WHEN I WON
ON THE 190th FLOOR,
I HAD ABOUT 200 MIL TOTAL.
Zushi: 200...
Gon: WHERE'S THAT MONEY NOW?
Killua: THAT WAS FOUR YEARS AGO,
SO IT'S LONG GONE BY NOW.
I SPENT ALL OF IT ON SNACKS.
Gon: THAT MUCH ON SNACKS
IN FOUR YEARS?
Zushi: WHAT KIND
OF SNACKS WERE THEY?
Killua: HEY, LET'S HEAD
UP TO THE WAITING ROOM.
WE GOT THROUGH OUR MATCHES
UNSCATHED ON THE FIRST FLOOR.
THEY'LL PROBABLY
GIVE US ANOTHER ONE TODAY.
♪
Killua: WELL,
IF THESE GUYS ARE OUR OPPONENTS,
IT'LL BE A CINCH.
JUST TAKE IT EASY.
Gon: REALLY?
‐ Zushi: KILLUA.
‐ ( fighter grunts )
QUIET. THEY CAN HEAR YOU.
Announcer: 2,054, MR. KILLUA...
Killua: HEY, I'M ALREADY UP.
Announcer:
AND 1,963, MR. ZUSHI...
Zushi: HUH?!
Announcer:
PLEASE HEAD TO ARENA A
ON THE 57th FLOOR.
Killua: OKAY.
Zushi: OSU!
I AM HONORED TO FACE YOU.
Killua: I BET.
WELL, YOU CAN'T WIN 'EM ALL.
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, RIGHT?
CATCH YOU LATER, GON.
Gon: YEAH. BEST OF LUCK
TO BOTH OF YOU GUYS.
Killua: I'LL WAIT
ON THE FLOOR ABOVE. BYE.
Gon: 'KAY!
( Zushi gasps )
Gon: HE DIDN'T HAVE TO ACT
LIKE IT WAS SUCH A DONE DEAL.
Commentator:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE!
THIS IS THE EVENT
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR,
A UNIQUE MATCHUP
BETWEEN TWO YOUNG BOYS
WHO'VE BOTH GOT
SOMETHING TO PROVE!
BUT DON'T UNDERESTIMATE
THESE FIGHTERS.
BOTH HAD STRONG SHOWINGS
IN THEIR FIRST ROUNDS,
AND NOW THEY'VE JUMPED
ALL THE WAY UP HERE
TO THE 50th FLOOR!
AND NOW LET'S
TAKE A LOOK AT THE BIG SCREEN
FOR THE PLAYBACK
OF THOSE EVENTS!
KILLUA BEAT HIS OPPONENT
IN A FLASH!
ONE CHOP WAS ALL IT TOOK
TO KNOCK HIM OUT!
♪
ZUSHI USED MARTIAL ARTS
TO PUNISH HIS OPPONENT,
SCORING A FLAWLESS KNOCKOUT
AGAINST A GIANT
WEIGHING OVER 200 KILOGRAMS!
OKAY NOW, EVERYONE,
READY TO PRESS
YOUR WAGER BUTTONS?
GO ON!
MAKE YOUR PICKS RIGHT NOW!
ALL THE BETS ARE IN,
AND WE HAVE
A CLEAR FAVORITE, ZUSHI!
( Killua groans )
Commentator: MAYBE HIS KNOWLEDGE
OF MARTIAL ARTS
HAS GIVEN HIM THE EDGE!
( Zushi thinking )
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
KILLUA IS MAD.
Referee: THREE ROUNDS,
THREE MINUTES PER ROUND!
DECIDED BY POINTS OR K. O.!
BEGIN!
( Killua thinking )
I SEE.
HIS STANCE
DOESN'T LEAVE MANY OPENINGS.
HE'S TRAINED HARD TO MASTER IT.
BUT HE DOESN'T
STAND A CHANCE AGAINST ME.
Commentator: WOW!
KILLUA IS WALKING BOLDLY
TOWARD HIS OPPONENT!
( Zushi yelps )
Killua: SORRY, BUT I'M STICKING
TO ONE CHOP PER MATCH
'TIL I REACH THE 150th FLOOR.
Referee: A CLEAN HIT!
( crowd cheering )
Commentator: KILLUA HAS LAID OUT
ANOTHER OPPONENT
WITH A SINGLE BLOW!
A CLEAN HIT AND A KNOCKOUT
EARN HIM TWO POINTS!
AS YOU KNOW, UNDER THE POINTS
AND KNOCKOUT SYSTEM,
THERE ARE CLEAN HITS,
CRITICAL HITS, AND KNOCKDOWNS.
GREAT ATTACKS
COUNT AS "CLEAN HITS,"
WORTH ONE POINT EACH.
SUPERB ATTACKS
ARE "CRITICAL HITS"
AND ARE WORTH TWO POINTS.
KNOCKING YOUR OPPONENT DOWN
IS ONE POINT.
COLLECT 10 POINTS, AND YOU'RE
AWARDED A TECHNICAL KNOCKOUT.
OF COURSE, IF YOUR OPPONENT
CAN'T CONTINUE THE FIGHT
AFTER ONE HIT,
YOU WIN BY KNOCKOUT!
Killua: PRETTY SURE
THAT CHOP ENDED IT. IDIOT.
Referee: CAN YOU FIGHT?
Zushi: YES! I'M ALL RIGHT.
( Killua gasps )
Commentator: HE GOT UP!
ZUSHI WILL CONTINUE THE MATCH!
( Wing grunts )
Referee: AND BEGIN!
Killua: DID I
HOLD BACK TOO MUCH?
( Zushi yelps )
Commentator:
HE'S TAKEN ANOTHER HIT!
ZUSHI IS DOWN!
BUT HE'S GETTING UP
BEFORE THE REFEREE REACHES HIM,
MEANING KILLUA
WON'T BE AWARDED THE POINT!
( Zushi growls )
( Killua grunts )
HE'S GOOD.
I'LL HAVE TO CHANGE MY TACTICS.
BUT SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
THAT ATTACK WAS SO STRONG
THAT EVEN IF I JUST GRAZED HIM,
HE'D BE OUT COLD.
Zushi: UNBELIEVABLE.
SUCH AWESOME POWER AND SPEED.
AT THIS RATE,
I WON'T STAND A CHANCE.
BUT I'VE GOTTA TRY.
I HAVE TO.
♪
( Killua gasps )
( Killua gasping )
Commentator: UH‐OH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT LOOKS LIKE KILLUA
IS ON THE RUN!
( Wing echoing )
ZUSHI!
( silence )
( Zushi gasps )
( grunts )
( Wing grunts )
Commentator: SO A VERY LOUD
AND OVERENTHUSIASTIC SPECTATOR
HAS TEMPORARILY INTERRUPTED
THE FIGHT,
BUT LET'S SEE IF WE
CAN GET IT GOING AGAIN.
COME ON, FOLKS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
( overlapping chatter )
( elevator chimes )
Gon: HMM?
OH, HEY, KILLUA. OVER HERE!
CHECK IT OUT. I GOT 60,000.
HOW 'BOUT YOU?
IT TOOK YOU LONGER TO GET HERE
THAN I EXPECTED.
Killua: YEAH.
I RAN INTO SOME TROUBLE.
Gon: SO WAS ZUSHI
PRETTY STRONG, OR WHAT?
Killua: NO WAY. NO.
HE HAS POTENTIAL.
HE'LL BE STRONG ONE DAY.
FOR NOW, ANYWAY, HE'S JUST
TARGET PRACTICE FOR ME.
PUNCHES THAT WEAK,
I COULD KNOCK HIM AROUND EASY.
BUT I COULDN'T BEAT HIM.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: I WON THE MATCH,
T. K. O. BY POINTS,
BUT STILL,
I JUST COULDN'T KNOCK HIM OUT.
♪
ALSO...
WHEN HE CHANGED HIS STANCE,
I GOT THIS REAL CREEPY FEELING,
LIKE WHEN I FACE MY BROTHER.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT WAS,
BUT IT FELT DANGEROUS.
IT'S GOTTA BE
SOME KIND OF TECHNIQUE.
I HEARD HIS MASTER
CALL IT "REN."
Zushi: PLEASE,
FORGIVE ME, MASTER!
Wing: I THOUGHT
I'D MADE IT CLEAR TO YOU
THAT YOU WERE NOT SUPPOSED
TO USE REN YET, ZUSHI.
Zushi: I'M SORRY. IT'S JUST...
HE‐‐HE WAS SO STRONG,
I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
Wing: YES. I UNDERSTAND
THE URGE TO WIN,
BUT YOU HAVE ANOTHER GOAL,
A GOAL THAT LIES BEYOND THIS
AT THE TOP FLOOR OF THIS TOWER.
DON'T FOCUS TOO MUCH
ON SIMPLY WINNING, ZUSHI.
IMPATIENCE WILL ONLY ERODE
YOUR POTENTIAL
Zushi: OSU!
Wing: YOU MUST BE PREPARED
TO LOSE A THOUSAND TIMES
WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
Zushi: OSU!
Gon: SO HE'S
NOT SUPPOSED TO USE REN?
UNTIL HE GETS ALL THE WAY
UP TO THE TOP FLOOR, I MEAN?
THAT'S WHERE
THE STRONGEST FIGHTERS ARE,
RIGHT? AT THE TOP?
Killua: GON, WE NEED
TO CHANGE OUR PLAN.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: I SAY WE SHOOT
FOR THE TOP FLOOR.
Gon: RIGHT!
♪
( thinking ) ACTUALLY THAT'S
BEEN MY PLAN THIS WHOLE TIME.
( crowd cheering )
( fighter groans )
Commentator:
KILLUA DEFEATS ANOTHER OPPONENT
WITH ONE CHOP
FOR A KNOCKOUT WIN!
AND THERE'S ACTION
OVER IN THE NEXT ARENA.
GON HAS KNOCKED OUT
ANOTHER OPPONENT
WITH A SINGLE PUSH!
EACH OF THEM HAS WON
SIX CONSECUTIVE MATCHES
OVER THE PAST THREE DAYS,
AND THEY'VE REACHED THE HUNDREDS
WITHOUT EVEN A SCRATCH
TO SHOW FOR IT!
( beeps )
KILLUA'S CHOP...
AND GON'S PUSH.
THEY SEEM UNSTOPPABLE,
BUT CAN THEY KEEP IT UP?
BUT THE REAL QUESTION IS,
WHO, IF ANYONE, CAN STOP THEM?
♪
Gon: YAY! OUR OWN ROOM!
( laughs )
WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT MONEY
AND LODGING ANYMORE.
Killua: I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE.
TRY TO REMEMBER.
DROP BELOW THE 100th FLOOR,
AND YOU LOSE THE ROOM.
THERE'S A HUGE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN GETTING HERE
AND STAYING HERE
ON THE HUNDREDTH FLOOR.
IT'S A REAL THRESHOLD.
Gon: THRESHOLD?
Killua: BEYOND
THE HUNDREDTH FLOOR,
YOU GET SPECIAL TREATMENT,
AND SO NATURALLY NO ONE WANTS
TO LOSE THEIR STANDING.
THERE ARE PEOPLE HERE
WHO'LL DO ANYTHING IT TAKES
TO STAY ON THE HUNDREDTH FLOOR.
YOU CAN WASTE
A LOT OF TIME ON 'EM,
TIME WE DON'T HAVE RIGHT NOW,
SO BE CAREFUL, GON.
( Gon grunts )
( crowd cheering )
Commentator:
GON WINS ANOTHER MATCH
WITH A SINGLE PUSH!
Killua: GUESS I DIDN'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT HIM.
♪
( crowd cheering )
Worker: YOUR PRIZE MONEY
HAS BEEN DEPOSITED
INTO YOUR ACCOUNT.
Gon: YOU WERE RIGHT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
SO MANY ZEROES BEFORE.
CRAZY THAT JUST LAST WEEK,
I WAS TOTALLY BROKE.
Killua:
I'M A LITTLE BIT ANNOYED.
Gon: HUH?
Killua:
THE FIRST TIME I WAS HERE,
IT TOOK ME TWO WHOLE MONTHS
TO REACH FLOOR 150.
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND...
Gon: YEAH, BUT BACK THEN,
YOU WERE ONLY SIX.
Killua: WELL, YEAH,
THERE'S THAT.
Gon: OH, BY THE WAY,
I SAW ZUSHI ON TV EARLIER.
Killua: YEAH, SO DID I.
HE'S STILL ON THE 50th FLOOR.
Gon: I WONDER
WHAT THAT REN THING WAS
THAT CREEPED YOU OUT AND WHY.
IT'S WEIRD, HUH?
Killua: HMM.
MAYBE WE'LL MEET SOME OPPONENTS
HIGHER UP WHO USE IT.
Gon: OR MAYBE IT'D BE FASTER
TO JUST ASK ZUSHI.
♪
( Killua laughs )
Zushi: REN IS ONE
OF THE FOUR EXERCISES.
THE FOUR EXERCISES ARE
FUNDAMENTAL TO ALL MARTIAL ARTS.
THEY INSTILL DISCIPLINE
AND DEVELOP CHARACTER.
LEARN TEN,
KNOW ZETSU THROUGH REN
TO ATTAIN HATSU,
AND ALL OF THAT
IS HOW YOU TRAIN FOR NEN.
THAT'S IT.
Killua: START MAKING SENSE!
Wing: ZUSHI.
ARE YOU CERTAIN THAT YOU
ARE SUFFICIENTLY QUALIFIED
TO BE TEACHING OTHERS?
NOW, GON, KILLUA,
AN OLD PROVERB WARNS
THAT IT IS POSSIBLE
A SMATTERING OF KNOWLEDGE
MAY NOT REDUCE ONE'S IGNORANCE,
BUT INCREASE IT.
Killua: SO YOU'RE SAYING
A LITTLE KNOWLEDGE
IS A DANGEROUS THING?
THANKS FOR THE TIP,
BUT I REALLY WANT TO LEARN THIS,
BECAUSE I'M CONVINCED
IT'S BEHIND MY BROTHER'S POWERS.
Wing: YOU SAY THAT YOUR BROTHER
IS ABLE TO USE NEN?
Killua: I NEED TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT NEN AND REN EVEN MEAN,
AND NOT JUST HALFWAY.
I NEED TO KNOW IT.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO TEACH ME,
I WON'T TRY
TO FIGURE IT OUT FOR MYSELF.
Wing: WELL, IN THAT CASE...
LET'S ADJOURN TO MY ROOM.
♪
Narrator: QUESTIONS ABOUND.
WHAT IS NEN? WHAT IS REN?
KILLUA BELIEVES THEY'RE RELATED
TO HIS OLDER BROTHER
ILLUMI'S ABILITIES.
GON WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT THESE WORDS MEAN AS WELL.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'LL BE
INTRODUCING ZUSHI.
HE'S REALLY, REALLY TALENTED.
IN FACT,
HE'S CONSIDERED ONE IN 100,000.
Killua: WHILE GON AND I
ARE ONE IN A HUNDRED MILLION.
Both: OSU!
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME, "NEN AND NEN."
THAT WAS A ROUGH ONE.
Killua: BUT YOU HUNG IN THERE.
Both: OSU.