( beast roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Satotz: WITH NO FURTHER ADO,
THE HUNTER EXAM WILL NOW BEGIN.
I AM SATOTZ,
YOUR EXAMINER FOR
THE FIRST PHASE OF THE EXAM.
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY TO LEAD
YOU ALL TO THE SECOND PHASE.
THE FIRST PHASE
IS ALREADY UNDER WAY.
♪♪♪
Narrator: IT'S BEEN TWO HOURS
SINCE THE EXAM BEGAN,
AND THE APPLICANTS
HAVE TRAVELED
MORE THAN 30 KILOMETERS
FROM THE STARTING LINE.
NO ONE KNOWS HOW FAR
THEY'LL HAVE TO GO.
NEVERTHELESS, THEY STRUGGLE
TO MATCH THE LEADER'S PACE.
IT IS A MONOTONOUS COURSE
WITH NO END IN SIGHT,
AND APPLICANTS HAVE
ALREADY STARTED TO DROP OUT.
( Nicolas thinking )
EXTRAPOLATING FROM
HISTORICAL DATA,
IT'S SAFE TO ASSUME THIS WILL BE
A 40‐KILOMETER COURSE.
AND IF MY CALCULATIONS
ARE CORRECT,
WE SHOULD BE NEARING THE END.
( panting )
( Leorio thinking )
WHAT THE HELL WAS I THINKING?
YOU'VE GOTTA BE A MONSTER
TO PASS THE HUNTER EXAM.
I'M SURROUNDED BY 'EM.
( wheels glide )
‐ HEY! WAIT UP, KID!
‐ Killua: HMM?
Leorio: HOW 'BOUT YOU SHOW
A LITTLE RESPECT FOR THE EXAM?!
Killua: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Leorio: I MEAN
QUIT USING A DAMN SKATEBOARD!
THAT'S CHEATING!
‐ Killua: HOW'S THAT?
‐ Leorio: HOW?
THIS IS AN ENDURANCE TEST!
THAT'S HOW!
‐ Gon: NO, IT'S NOT.
‐ Leorio: HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU
BABBLING ABOUT NOW, GON?!
Gon: THE EXAMINER GUY ONLY SAID
WE HAD TO FOLLOW HIM,
AND THAT'S ALL.
Leorio: HEY, WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON, ANYWAY?!
HUH?
Killua: HEY. HOW OLD ARE YOU?
Gon: 12 YEARS OLD.
Killua: HUH.
( thinking )
SAME AS ME.
I THINK I'LL RUN
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Gon: WHOA! COOL! HA HA!
Killua: MY NAME'S KILLUA.
Gon: HI. I'M GON.
( Leorio thinking )
DAMN KIDS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF ME!
( Nicolas panting )
( thinking )
IMPOSSIBLE.
SIMPLY IMPOSSIBLE!
MY CALCULATIONS ARE NEVER WRONG!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AM I ACTUALLY GOING TO FAIL?
ME, FAIL?!
NO, THAT'S PREPOSTEROUS!
I WON'T ACCEPT THAT. I WON'T!
Brothers: HMM? HEH.
( Nicolas panting )
Amori: HEY, ROOKIE!
( chuckles )
Umori: DAMN, YOU'RE A REAL MESS.
Imori: I DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER SEEN ANYONE
RUN OUT OF STEAM THIS EARLY.
Amori: YEAH, HE'S RIGHT.
YOU MUST REALLY BE PATHETIC.
Umori: THINK SOMEONE LIKE YOU'S
GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO PASS THE HUNTER EXAM?
Imori: DON'T EVER
COME BACK, LOSER!
( Nicolas wailing )
Tonpa: HERE.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
GREAT JOB, GUYS.
Amori: HE WON'T BE RECOVERING
FROM THAT ANYTIME SOON,
I CAN PROMISE YOU.
Umori: AND I BET YOU
HE WON'T BE APPLYING
FOR THE EXAM AGAIN, EITHER.
Imori: I'VE REALLY
GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU.
YOU SURE DO LOVE CRUSHING
ROOKIES, DON'T YOU, TONPA?
( Tonpa chuckles )
IT'S THE ONLY REASON I
GET OUT OF BED IN THE MORNING.
( monkey chitters )
( Kurapika thinking )
IT'S BEEN ABOUT FOUR HOURS
SINCE THE FIRST PHASE BEGAN,
AND WE'VE RUN
AT LEAST 60 KILOMETERS.
HOW MUCH FARTHER
DO WE NEED TO GO?
( Leorio panting )
( thinking ) ROOKIES ALMOST
NEVER PASS THE HUNTER EXAM,
JUST ONE
EVERY THREE YEARS OR SO.
I'M JUST A REGULAR GUY.
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
WHAT THE HELL WAS I THINKING?
DAMN IT.
( Gon gasps )
♪♪♪
Killua: HEY, FORGET ABOUT HIM.
YOU GOTTA KEEP MOVING.
Leorio: MAN, SCREW THIS!
I'M BECOMING A HUNTER,
NO MATTER WHAT!
DAMN IT ALL!
( Gon chuckles )
GOT IT!
Killua: THAT WAS AWESOME!
CAN I TRY THAT LATER?
Gon: SURE, IF I CAN TRY
YOUR SKATEBOARD.
( monkey chitters )
Satotz: WE'VE REACHED
THE 80‐KILOMETER MARK.
NOW, LET'S PICK UP
THE PACE A BIT, SHALL WE?
( applicants muttering )
Geretta: HE CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
Hanzo: HE'S INSANE.
LOOK AT HIM
PRANCE UP THOSE STAIRS
LIKE IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
HE'S NOT EVEN OUT OF BREATH.
Geretta: IF HE DOESN'T EASE UP,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA START
DROPPING LIKE FLIES.
Killua: HEY, I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
LET'S RACE TO THE FINISH,
SEE WHO'S FASTER!
Gon: SURE, OKAY!
BUT THE LOSER HAS TO BUY DINNER.
Killua: YEAH! YOU'RE ON!
Both: READY? GO!
Kurapika: ARE YOU OKAY, LEORIO?
Leorio: I'M GREAT!
I'VE NEVER BEEN BETTER!
IF I FORGET HOW STUPID I LOOK,
IT'S A WHOLE LOT EASIER
TO KEEP GOING!
( yells )
( Kurapika chuckles )
( thinking ) I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD PROBABLY FOLLOW SUIT.
LEORIO, I HAVE
A QUESTION FOR YOU.
Leorio: WHAT'S UP?
FIRST PHASE TOO EASY FOR YOU,
SO YOU GOTTA MAKE IT HARDER?
SAVE YOUR BREATH, KURAPIKA.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
Kurapika: WHY DO YOU
WANT TO BE A HUNTER?
IS IT REALLY
JUST ABOUT THE MONEY?
IT CAN'T BE.
WE HAVEN'T KNOWN
EACH OTHER VERY LONG,
BUT THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
I MEAN, SURE,
YOUR ATTITUDE IS TERRIBLE,
AND YOU AREN'T
TOO BRIGHT, EITHER...
( Leorio growls )
Kurapika: BUT I KNOW SHALLOWNESS
ISN'T AMONG YOUR DOWNFALLS.
I'VE KNOWN MANY PEOPLE WHOSE
ONLY PASSION IN LIFE WAS MONEY,
AND I CAN TELL
YOU'RE NOTHING LIKE THEM.
Leorio: YOU GOT IT ALL
FIGURED OUT, DON'T YOU?
‐ Kurapika: THE SCARLET EYES.
‐ Leorio: HUH?
Kurapika: THAT'S WHY
THE KURTA CLAN WAS TARGETED.
THE SCARLET EYES
ARE A SPECIAL TRAIT
POSSESSED ONLY BY THE KURTA.
WHEN OUR EMOTIONS
ARE HEIGHTENED,
THE COLOR OF OUR EYES
WILL CHANGE,
TAKING ON A SHADE OF SCARLET.
IN THAT STATE, THE COLOR
OF OUR EYES IS CONSIDERED
ONE OF THE SEVEN MOST BEAUTIFUL
COLORS IN THE WORLD,
AND THEY COMMAND A HEFTY PRICE
ON THE BLACK MARKET.
Leorio: SO THAT'S WHY
THE PHANTOM TROUPE ATTACKED YOU?
YOUR EYES?
Kurapika: THEY PLUCKED THE EYES
FROM EACH
OF MY BRETHREN'S CORPSES.
NOT A SINGLE ONE
ESCAPED DESECRATION.
EVEN NOW, I CAN HEAR THEM,
THE ANGUISHED SCREAMS
OF THEIR DARKENED EYES.
I SWEAR ON MY LIFE
THAT I WILL CAPTURE
THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
ONCE I DO, I'LL AVENGE MY CLAN
BY TAKING BACK THEIR EYES.
Leorio: THAT'S WHY
YOU WANT TO BE A HUNTER?
Kurapika: THAT'S RIGHT.
IF I BECOME A CONTRACT HUNTER
WITH WEALTHY CLIENTELE,
I'LL HAVE ACCESS
TO BLACK‐MARKET INFORMATION.
Leorio: BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO BE
THE KIND OF HUNTER YOU HATE.
YOU THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE
WHEN YOU NEED TO?
Kurapika: THE BLOW
TO MY PRIDE IS NOTHING,
NOT WHEN COMPARED
TO MY CLAN'S SUFFERING.
Leorio: WELL, SORRY,
BUT I DON'T HAVE
SOME BIG NOBLE CAUSE
LIKE YOU DO.
THE ONLY THING
I'M AFTER IS MONEY.
Kurapika: THAT'S NOT TRUE!
Leorio: OF COURSE IT IS.
Kurapika: IT'S NOT. BE HONEST.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THAT MONEY CAN BUY EVERYTHING?
TELL THE TRUTH!
Leorio: DAMN RIGHT, I DO!
FOR THE RIGHT PRICE,
YOU CAN BUY TREASURES,
DREAMS, HEARTS,
AND EVEN PEOPLE'S LIVES!
( Kurapika gasps )
TAKE THAT BACK, LEORIO!
I WILL NOT STAND HERE
AND ALLOW YOU
TO INSULT THE KURTA!
Leorio: WHAT?
IT'S THE TRUTH, ISN'T IT?
IF I HAD MONEY, MY FRIEND
WOULD STILL BE ALIVE TODAY!
( Kurapika gasps )
♪♪♪
WAS HE ILL?
Leorio: YEAH.
IT WAS A CURABLE DISEASE.
( insects buzzing )
THE PROBLEM WAS THAT
THE OPERATION COST A FORTUNE.
I WAS NAIVE.
I FIGURED
I COULD BECOME A DOCTOR
SO I COULD CURE KIDS
WITH THE SAME DISEASE
AND TELL THEIR PARENTS
THEY OWED ME NOTHING...
THAT IT WAS FREE OF CHARGE!
THAT WAS MY DREAM.
( growls )
PRETTY GOOD JOKE, RIGHT?
TURNS OUT TO BECOME A DOCTOR,
YOU ALREADY HAVE TO HAVE
AN OBSCENE AMOUNT OF MONEY!
GET IT NOW?
THE WHOLE WORLD RUNS ON MONEY,
SO I'M GONNA GET
AS MUCH AS I CAN!
Gon: SEE YOU AT THE FINISH LINE!
Killua: YEAH,
CATCH YOU LATER, OLD MAN.
Leorio: HEY, I'M NOT OLD!
CAN'T YOU TELL
I'M A TEENAGER JUST LIKE YOU?!
‐ Killua: HUH?
‐ Gon: NO WAY!
♪♪♪
Killua: HMM?
( chuckles )
( applicants panting )
Applicant #174: I CAN'T GO ON.
Applicant #140: THIS‐‐
THIS IS IT. I'M FINISHED.
Killua:
I'VE GOTTA TELL YOU, GON,
I'M PRETTY IMPRESSED
THAT YOU CAN KEEP UP WITH ME.
Gon: YOU ARE? ( laughs )
Killua: OR MAYBE
THEY'RE ALL SO SLOW,
YOU JUST SEEM FAST.
MAN, I THOUGHT THE HUNTER EXAM
WAS GONNA BE MORE OF
A CHALLENGE. THIS IS BORING.
Gon: HEY, WHY DO YOU WANT
TO BE A HUNTER, ANYWAY?
Killua: WHO, ME?
I NEVER SAID
I WANTED TO BE A HUNTER.
I JUST HEARD THE EXAM
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE REALLY HARD.
IT SOUNDED KINDA FUN,
SO HERE I AM,
BUT IT'S NOT
AS FUN AS I THOUGHT.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: WHAT ABOUT YOU?
Gon: WELL, THE THING IS
MY DAD'S A HUNTER,
SO I DECIDED I WAS GONNA BE
A HUNTER JUST LIKE HIM,
NO MATTER WHAT!
Killua: HMM.
SO WHAT KIND OF HUNTER IS HE?
Gon: NO IDEA.
( Killua laughs )
IT'S THE WEIRDEST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD!
YOU WANT TO BE THE SAME
KIND OF HUNTER AS YOUR DAD,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT HIM? THAT'S NUTS!
Gon: MITO'S THE ONE
WHO RAISED ME,
AND SHE SHOWED ME A LITTLE,
BUT I'VE ONLY EVER
SEEN HIM IN PICTURES
SHE SHOWED ME
FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
Killua: WAIT. SO WHO'S MITO?
Gon: SHE'S MY AUNT.
Killua: AH.
Gon: SHE SAID THAT MY DAD
TOOK THE HUNTER EXAM
WHEN HE WAS
ONLY 12 YEARS OLD, TOO.
HE PASSED HIS FIRST TRY
AND BECAME A HUNTER.
THAT'S WHEN HE DECIDED
TO LEAVE THE ISLAND.
SO I CAME HERE
IN ORDER TO FIND OUT
WHY HE CHOSE BEING A HUNTER
OVER STAYING AT HOME WITH ME.
Killua: HMM.
( gasps )
Applicant: THE EXIT!
Second applicant:
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
Third applicant: WE'RE FINALLY
GETTING OUT OF THIS DARK TUNNEL!
( monkey chitters )
Satotz: NOW THEN,
LET'S SEE HOW MANY APPLICANTS
HAVE MADE IT THIS FAR.
Both: GOAL!
( both laugh )
Gon: YEAH, I DID IT!
I FINISHED FIRST!
Killua: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I TOTALLY WON.
Gon: HUH? NO, I WON.
Killua: I WON!
Gon: I WAS FASTER THAN YOU,
SO YOU HAVE TO BUY ME DINNER!
Killua: NO WAY. I WAS FASTER,
SO YOU'RE BUYING ME DINNER.
Gon: NUH‐UH! I WAS FASTER!
HEY, WHICH ONE
OF US WAS FASTEST?
Satotz: YOU CROSSED
THE FINISH LINE SIMULTANEOUSLY.
Gon: OKAY, FINE.
GUESS I'LL HAVE
TO BUY YOU YOUR DINNER...
Killua: HUH?
Gon: BUT THEN YOU HAVE
TO BUY ME MY DINNER, OKAY?
Killua: I DON'T GET IT.
Gon: HEY, MR. SATOTZ,
IS THIS WHERE
THE SECOND PHASE BEGINS?
Satotz: NO, IT ISN'T.
WE HAVE QUITE A WAY TO GO.
Gon: AWW, MAN.
( applicants panting )
( Leorio laughing weakly )
( gasps )
Gon: HEY, KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: OH. HEY.
IS THIS OUR DESTINATION?
Gon: NOPE, NOT YET.
Kurapika: MM, I SEE.
LOOKS LIKE THE FOG IS LIFTING.
( Gon gasps ) REALLY?
WHOA.
♪♪♪
Satotz: THE MILSY WETLANDS,
ALSO KNOWN AS SWINDLERS SWAMP.
WE MUST CROSS IT
TO REACH PHASE TWO OF THE EXAM.
THIS PLACE IS HOME TO A VARIETY
OF TRULY BIZARRE ANIMALS,
MANY OF WHICH ARE
CRAFTY, VORACIOUS CREATURES
WHO DECEIVE
AND FEAST ON HUMAN PREY,
SO PLEASE, BE VERY CAREFUL.
IF YOU'RE DECEIVED,
YOU'LL SURELY DIE.
( applicants murmuring )
‐ ( whirring )
‐ ( applicants gasp )
Applicant #305: WAIT FOR ME!
AHH! NO!
Satotz: THESE WETLAND CREATURES
ARE NOT TO BE UNDERESTIMATED,
FOR THEY WILL USE EVERY TRICK
IN THE BOOK TO FOOL THEIR PREY.
( applicants gasp )
Satotz: THIS IS AN ECOSYSTEM
IN WHICH ALL CREATURES
HUNT BY THE ART OF DECEPTION,
AND THAT IS WHY IT IS ALSO
KNOWN AS SWINDLERS SWAMP.
NOW THEN,
PLEASE FOLLOW ME CLOSELY
SO YOU WON'T BE DECEIVED.
( Leorio scoffs )
IS HE MESSING WITH US?
IF WE KNOW
THEY'LL TRY TO DECEIVE US,
WHO'S GONNA FALL FOR IT?
Man: DON'T FALL FOR IT!
Leorio: LISTEN, DIDN'T I
JUST SAY THAT WE WON'T?
Man: DON'T LET THEM FOOL YOU!
( applicants gasp )
Man: HE'S LYING.
THAT MAN IS LYING TO YOU!
HE'S AN IMPOSTOR,
A TOTAL FRAUD!
I'M THE REAL EXAMINER!
YOU GOT IT?!
Leorio: IMPOSTOR?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
Hanzo: BUT THEN
WHO IS HE REALLY?
Man: I'LL PROVE IT.
LOOK AT THIS!
( applicants gasp )
Gon: OH, WOW!
HE LOOKS LIKE MR. SATOTZ!
Man: THIS IS A MAN‐FACED APE
FROM THE MILSY WETLANDS.
Leorio: A MAN‐FACED WHAT?
Man: THE MAN‐FACED APE LOVES
THE TASTE OF HUMAN FLESH,
BUT THEIR LIMBS
ARE REALLY LONG AND THIN,
SO THEY'RE ACTUALLY QUITE WEAK.
THAT'S WHY THEY DISGUISE
THEMSELVES AS HUMANS.
THEY TRICK US INTO FOLLOWING
THEM INTO THE WETLANDS,
WHERE THEY WORK TOGETHER
WITH OTHER CREATURES
TO KILL AND EAT US.
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS!
TO DECEIVE
THE ENTIRE HUNTER APPLICANT POOL
AND FEAST ON EVERY ONE OF YOU!
Leorio: BASTARD.
Hanzo: OH, YEAH?
WELL, THEN THAT
WOULD CERTAINLY EXPLAIN
WHY HE DOESN'T WALK
LIKE A NORMAL HUMAN.
( man gasps )
Leorio: WHAH?!
‐ ( applicants gasp )
‐ ( Hisoka chuckles )
I SEE. I SEE.
THAT SETTLES IT, THEN.
SO YOU ARE THE REAL ONE.
♪♪♪
( Hanzo thinking )
HOLD ON!
HE'S THE REAL EXAMINER?
( Man‐Faced Ape gasps )
( shrieking )
Hisoka: THE EXAMINERS
ARE HUNTERS.
EACH IS HAND‐PICKED
BY THE EXAM COMMITTEE
TO DO THIS JOB WITHOUT PAY.
ANYONE WHO HOLDS THE TITLE
WE'RE VYING FOR OURSELVES
COULD HAVE DEFLECTED
THAT ATTACK,
AND QUITE EASILY, I MIGHT ADD.
Satotz: I SHALL TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
THANK YOU.
STILL, SHOULD YOU
CHOOSE TO ATTACK ME AGAIN
FOR ANY REASON,
I WILL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO REPORT YOU
FOR ATTACKING AN EXAMINER
AND HAVE YOU
IMMEDIATELY DISQUALIFIED.
IS THAT CLEAR?
Hisoka: OF COURSE.
( birds squawking )
Leorio: NATURE CAN BE SO BRUTAL.
IT'S HARD TO WATCH.
Kurapika: SO HE WAS
A MAN‐FACED APE AS WELL.
Satotz: HE WAS TRYING
TO CONFUSE THE APPLICANTS
AND LURE SOME OF YOU AWAY.
THESE ATTEMPTS
ARE TO BE EXPECTED.
Killua: WE CAN'T
LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
Gon: RIGHT.
Satotz: PLEASE BE AWARE
THAT YOU WILL ENCOUNTER
SUCH DECEPTIONS
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
I MUST ASSUME
THAT A NUMBER OF YOU
WERE FOOLED INTO SUSPECTING
MY TRUE IDENTITY.
Leorio: OH, WELL, I, UH...
( Hanzo chuckles )
Satotz: UNDERSTAND? I WANT
TO MAKE IT ABUNDANTLY CLEAR
THAT IF ANY OF YOU
ARE TO LOSE SIGHT OF ME
ONCE WE ENTER THE FOG
OF THE MILSY WETLANDS,
YOU HAVE NO HOPE WHATSOEVER
OF REACHING THE SECOND PHASE
OF THE EXAM.
YOU'VE BEEN WARNED.
NOW LET'S BEGIN.
PLEASE FOLLOW ME.
♪♪♪
Leorio: OH, GREAT.
IT'S ANOTHER MARATHON.
Kurapika: EXCEPT THIS TIME,
WE'RE IN A SWAMP,
AND RUNNING ON WET GROUND
REQUIRES SIGNIFICANTLY
MORE ENERGY.
Narrator:
THE APPLICANTS HAVE FINALLY
LEFT THE LONG, DARK TUNNEL
AND STEPPED INTO THE LIGHT.
SO FAR, 36 CANDIDATES
HAVE WITHDRAWN FROM THE EXAM,
AND 368 REMAIN.
THEIR NEXT CHALLENGE
WILL BE THE MILSY WETLANDS,
WHICH IS ALSO KNOWN
AS SWINDLERS SWAMP.
THE EXCRUCIATING
HUNTER EXAM CONTINUES.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"HISOKA IS SNEAKY."
OKEY‐DOKEY!
♪♪♪