( beast roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Captain: SO...
I'LL MAKE SURE ALL THREE OF YOU
GET SAFELY DROPPED OFF
AT THE PORT
CLOSEST TO THE EXAM SITE.
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
Gon: ALL RIGHT!
( laughs )
( overlapping chatter )
Narrator: AFTER WINNING OVER
THE OLD CAPTAIN,
GON, KURAPIKA, AND LEORIO
ARRIVED AT DOLLE HARBOR,
WHERE THEIR ADVENTURES
WERE JUST BEGINNING.
Gon: THANKS A LOT, CAPTAIN.
THAT WAS REALLY FUN.
( Captain laughs )
I GOTTA ADMIT I HAD
A PRETTY GOOD TIME MYSELF.
OH, YEAH! LET ME GIVE YOU
A BIT OF ADVICE
AS A SMALL TOKEN
OF MY APPRECIATION.
Gon: ADVICE, SIR?
Captain: LOOK. DO YOU SEE
THAT BIG CEDAR TREE,
THE ONE UP ON THE TOP
OF THAT HILL?
Gon: UH‐HUH.
Captain: YOU'LL WANT
TO MAKE YOUR WAY THERE FIRST.
IT'S A SHORTCUT
TO THE EXAM SITE.
Gon: A SHORTCUT? GREAT!
SO JUST HEAD
FOR THAT TREE, HUH?
THANKS FOR THE TIP, CAPTAIN!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
Captain: GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
Gon: THANKS! HAVE A SAFE TRIP!
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF!
( Captain thinking )
YOU CAN REST EASY, GING.
YOUR BOY'S GROWN
INTO A FINE YOUNG MAN.
( man chuckles )
Leorio: HUH. THAT'S ODD.
Gon: WHAT IS?
Leorio: WELL, UH, ACCORDING
TO THIS NOTICE I RECEIVED,
THE EXAM IS SUPPOSED TO BE HELD
SOMEWHERE IN ZABAN CITY,
YOU SEE?
NOW WE'RE HERE,
AND THAT TREE IS THERE,
WHICH IS THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION
OF ZABAN.
Kurapika: COULD YOU
HAVE MISHEARD THE CAPTAIN?
Gon: I DON'T THINK SO.
HE TOLD ME I SHOULD GO
TOWARDS THAT CEDAR TREE.
Kurapika: I SEE.
Leorio: AND THIS STUPID NOTICE
ISN'T ANY HELP AT ALL.
IT SAYS THE EXAM'S
IN ZABAN CITY,
BUT IT DOESN'T
SAY WHERE, EXACTLY!
Kurapika: OUR TASK
IS TO FIND THE SITE
USING ONLY LIMITED INFORMATION.
THIS IS ANOTHER TEST
TO DETERMINE
IF WE'RE WORTHY OF THE EXAM.
Leorio: YEAH, I ALREADY
KNEW THAT, SMARTY‐PANTS,
SO GIVE IT A REST!
Gon: I THINK I'LL
CHECK IT OUT FOR MYSELF,
FIND OUT WHAT THE CAPTAIN
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
Leorio: WHOA, WHOA!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THE BUS TO ZABAN
IS GONNA LEAVE ANY SECOND.
WE NEED TO BE ON IT
WHEN IT DOES!
HEY!
JEEZ, THE KID'S
TOO TRUSTING FOR HIS OWN GOOD.
YOU CAN'T JUST TRUST EVERYONE
ALL THE TIME.
HUH?
KURAPIKA, COME BACK!
Kurapika: I'M INTRIGUED
BY THE CAPTAIN'S ADVICE,
BUT EVEN MORE SO
BY GON'S BEHAVIOR.
I'M CURIOUS
TO SEE WHAT HE'LL DO.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER.
SEE YOU.
IT WASN'T LONG,
BUT IT WAS NICE KNOWING YOU.
( scoffs ) ANOTHER FOLLOWER,
JUST LIKE THE REST OF 'EM.
NOT ME, THOUGH.
I'M GONNA TAKE THE BUS.
Man: SO IT WAS A TRAP?
Man #2: ALL I'M SAYIN'
IS THAT NONE OF THE BUSES
MADE IT TO ZABAN CITY.
( man #1 laughs )
ROOKIES ALWAYS FAIL THIS PART.
THEY BELIEVE
WHATEVER YOU TELL 'EM.
( laughs )
Leorio: HEY, HEY, HEY!
WAIT FOR ME!
IT'S JUST I KNEW YOU GUYS
WOULD BE LONELY WITHOUT ME.
PLUS, IT'S NO FUN
TRAVELING ALONE.
THAT'S WHY I FIGURED
I'D STICK WITH YOU TWO
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
( laughs )
( wind blowing )
( bird squawks )
Leorio: MAN,
THIS IS ONE CREEPY PLACE.
THERE ISN'T
A SINGLE SOUL ANYWHERE.
Gon: NO, THERE'S A BUNCH
OF PEOPLE HERE.
Leorio: WHAT?
( all gasp )
Leorio: WHAT'S UP
WITH THESE GUYS?
Woman: EXCITING.
Leorio: UH, EXCITING?
Leorio: "EXCITING."
( swallows )
Woman: TIME FOR THE EXCITING
MULTIPLE‐CHOICE QUIZ!
( playing fanfare )
( all murmuring )
( music ends )
Woman: LET ME TAKE A GUESS.
YOU BOYS ARE HEADED
FOR THE CEDAR ON THE HILL,
AREN'T YOU?
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO GET THERE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO PASS
THROUGH THIS TOWN FIRST.
YOU MUST PASS A QUIZ
COMPRISED OF A SINGLE QUESTION.
Leorio: WAIT A SECOND!
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?!
Woman: YOU'LL HAVE
FIVE SECONDS TO ANSWER.
IF YOU'RE CORRECT,
THEN YOU CAN MOVE ON.
IF NOT, YOU'RE DISQUALIFIED
FROM THIS YEAR'S EXAM.
Kurapika: OH, I SEE.
IT'S ANOTHER TRIAL WE HAVE
TO PASS BEFORE TAKING THE EXAM.
Leorio: SO THAT'S IT, HUH?
LUCKY I'M AN EXPERT IN QUIZZES.
WAIT! ONE QUESTION?!
Woman: YOUR ANSWER MUST BE
EITHER THE NUMBER ONE OR TWO.
ANY ANSWER THAT IS NOT
THE NUMBER ONE OR NUMBER TWO
WILL BE DEEMED INCORRECT.
Leorio: HOLD ON. ALL THREE OF US
HAVE TO SHARE THE SAME QUESTION?
SO IF KURAPIKA HERE
GETS IT WRONG,
IT MEANS
I GET DISQUALIFIED, TOO?
Kurapika: NOT VERY LIKELY.
ALTHOUGH,
IF THE ROLES WERE REVERSED,
IT WOULD BE
ALL BUT INEVITABLE.
Leorio: YOU WANNA REPEAT THAT?
Gon: IT'S OKAY! EVEN IF
ONLY ONE OF US KNOWS THE ANSWER,
ALL THREE OF US GET TO MOVE ON!
( laughs )
AND I'M REAL BAD AT QUIZZES.
‐ Leorio: TRUE.
‐ Kurapika: FAIR POINT.
Man: HEY, HEY.
HURRY IT UP,
OR I MIGHT ANSWER IT
BEFORE THE REST OF YOU
GET A CHANCE.
Leorio: SO WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
Gon: YOU DON'T KNOW? HE'S BEEN
FOLLOWING US PRETTY CLOSELY
EVER SINCE WE LEFT THE PORT.
( Leorio gasps ) REALLY?
Man: YEAH, SORRY, KID.
DIDN'T MEAN TO EAVESDROP,
BUT I COULDN'T HELP
BUT HEAR YOU GUYS TALKING.
Woman: WHAT WILL YOU DO?
Leorio: HE SEEMS
PRETTY EAGER TO ME.
SHOULD WE LET HIM
GO FIRST, GUYS,
SEE WHAT KIND OF QUESTION
WE CAN EXPECT FROM THEM?
Gon: SURE. I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
Kurapika: NO OBJECTIONS HERE.
Man: LET'S GET TO IT, THEN.
( thinking )
ONCE I ACE THIS QUIZ,
I'M GONNA LEAVE
A TRAIL OF TRAPS
FOR ANYONE
WHO TRIES TO FOLLOW ME.
Woman: NOW HERE
IS YOUR QUESTION.
‐ ( honks horn )
‐ ( bird squawks )
Woman: A GROUP OF EVIL VILLAINS
HAVE KIDNAPPED YOUR MOTHER
AND YOUR TRUE LOVE,
AND YOU CAN ONLY SAVE
ONE OF THEM.
CHOOSE ONE FOR YOUR MOTHER
OR TWO FOR YOUR TRUE LOVE.
WHICH DO YOU SAVE,
AND WHICH OF THEM DIES?
Leorio: HEY!
WHAT KIND OF QUIZ IS THIS?
( man chuckles )
( buzzer dings )
THE ANSWER'S NUMBER ONE.
Woman: OH?
AND WHAT'S YOUR REASON?
Man: IT'S YOUR MOM.
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU CAN REPLACE YOUR MOM.
BUT A LOVER,
YOU CAN ALWAYS FIND ANOTHER ONE.
Leorio: WHAT?
( bird squawks )
Woman: YOU MAY PASS.
Leorio: SERIOUSLY?
Man: LOOKS LIKE THE TRICK
IS TELLING THE OLD LADY
WHATEVER SHE WANTS TO HEAR.
ADIOS!
Leorio: HANG ON!
WHAT KIND OF CRAP IS THAT?!
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT WAS THE RIGHT ANSWER!
WE'RE JUST SUPPOSED TO SAY
WHAT WE THINK SHE WANTS TO HEAR?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
SAY SOMETHING!
( bird squawks )
( Leorio groans ) OKAY, I'VE HAD
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH OF THIS.
I'M GONNA FIND MY OWN WAY.
Woman: IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
REFUSE TO TAKE THE QUIZ
IF YOU WISH,
BUT KNOW YOU'LL BE DISQUALIFIED.
( Leorio growls )
THAT'S NUTS!
DIFFERENT PEOPLE WOULD
ANSWER THAT IN DIFFERENT WAYS!
THERE'S NO RIGHT ANSWER FOR THAT
QUESTION AND NEVER HAS BEEN!
( Kurapika gasps )
THERE'S NO RIGHT ANSWER.
I SEE.
Woman: OH?
Kurapika: LEORIO‐‐
Woman: THAT'S ENOUGH!
( thinking ) THE BOY WITH
THE CAT EYES HAS FIGURED IT OUT.
( aloud ) I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR ANOTHER WORD OUT OF YOU.
SAY ANYTHING BUT YOUR ANSWER,
AND YOU ARE DISQUALIFIED.
( Kurapika thinking )
YOU CAN DO THIS, LEORIO.
IT'S JUST A SIMPLE TRICK.
GON...
Woman: AND NOW
HERE IS YOUR QUESTION.
‐ ( honks horn )
‐ ( bird squawks )
Woman: YOU LEARN BOTH
YOUR SON AND YOUR DAUGHTER
HAVE BEEN KIDNAPPED.
YOU WILL ONLY BE ABLE
TO RESCUE ONE OF THEM.
CHOOSE ONE FOR YOUR SON
AND TWO FOR YOUR DAUGHTER.
WHICH OF THESE TWO
WILL YOU RESCUE?
( Leorio thinking )
SHE'S MESSING WITH US.
Woman: FIVE...
Leorio: GO AHEAD
AND COUNT DOWN...
‐ Woman: FOUR...
‐ Leorio: YOU OLD HAG.
( swings stick )
THREE...
TWO...
ONE.
ENNH! TIME IS UP!
( Leorio yells )
♪♪♪
OUT OF THE WAY, KURAPIKA!
THIS OLD HAG NEEDS
TO BE TAUGHT A LESSON,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
SHE GETS IT!
Kurapika: WOULD YOU
PLEASE CALM DOWN?
Leorio: HOW THE HELL
DO YOU EXPECT ME TO CALM DOWN?!
Kurapika: WE GOT IT RIGHT!
DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO JEOPARDIZE THAT?
WE DID?
Kurapika: WE'VE ALREADY GIVEN
THE CORRECT RESPONSE, SILENCE.
ANY OTHER ANSWER
WOULD HAVE BEEN INCORRECT.
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"SILENCE"?
Kurapika: JUST THAT.
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF, REMEMBER?
Leorio: HUH?
THERE'S NO RIGHT ANSWER FOR THAT
QUESTION AND NEVER HAS BEEN!
Kurapika: YOU WERE RIGHT.
THERE WAS NO CORRECT ANSWER
TO OUR QUESTION.
HOWEVER, WE HAD TO SAY
ONE OR TWO AS A RESPONSE,
AND SO OUR ONLY CHOICE
WAS TO RESPOND WITH SILENCE.
Leorio: WHAT ABOUT THAT GUY?
HE MADE IT THROUGH!
Kurapika: SHE NEVER TOLD HIM
HE WAS CORRECT.
ALL SHE SAID WAS,
"YOU MAY PASS."
WHICH MEANS THAT THIS IS
NOT THE PATH TO THE HUNTER EXAM.
RIGHT?
Woman: HMM.
THAT IS CORRECT.
THE REAL PATH
IS RIGHT OVER HERE.
FOLLOW THIS PATH FOR TWO HOURS,
AND YOU WILL REACH
THE LONE CEDAR TREE.
Leorio: OKAY.
I WAS NOT EXPECTING THIS.
Woman: THERE IS A COUPLE
THAT LIVE IN A SMALL CABIN
UNDER THAT TREE,
WHO WILL SERVE AS NAVIGATORS
ON YOUR JOURNEY.
THEY WILL GUIDE YOU
TO THE EXAM SITE,
IF YOU LIVE UP
TO THEIR EXPECTATIONS, THAT IS.
Leorio: I'M SORRY. I HOPE YOU'LL
FORGIVE ME FOR BEING RUDE.
Woman: DON'T BE. I DON'T MIND.
MEETING PEOPLE LIKE YOU
IS THE ONLY REASON I DO THIS JOB
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
DO YOUR BEST.
BECOME THE BEST HUNTER
YOU CAN BE.
Leorio: UH...
( chuckles )
SURE.
( Gon groans )
Leorio: HUH?
I'M STUCK.
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
THE RIGHT ANSWER.
( both laugh )
Leorio: YOU'VE BEEN
REALLY THINKING
OF AN ANSWER THIS WHOLE TIME?
YOU CAN STOP NOW.
Gon: HUH? BUT WHY?
Kurapika: BECAUSE THE QUIZ
IS ALREADY OVER.
Gon: I KNOW THAT, BUT WHAT IF‐‐
YOU KNOW, WELL, WHAT IF THAT
REALLY HAPPENS TO ME SOMEDAY,
IF TWO PEOPLE ARE IN TROUBLE AND
I CAN ONLY HELP ONE OF THEM?
THEN WHAT?
IT WOULDN'T BE RIGHT
TO PICK ONE OVER THE OTHER,
BUT LIKE IT OR NOT,
THAT'S A CHOICE
I MIGHT HAVE TO MAKE.
I JUST HOPE
THAT I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
( woman thinking )
THE BOY IS RIGHT, OF COURSE.
THAT IS INDEED
THE TRUE PURPOSE OF THIS TEST.
THE ABSTRACT MAY COME TO PASS,
AND A HUNTER MUST BE READY.
REALITY CAN BE CRUEL, AND IT
OFTEN STRIKES WITHOUT WARNING.
ONE MUST ALWAYS BE PREPARED
FOR THESE CROSSROADS IN LIFE.
♪♪♪
Kurapika: HMM?
( chuckles )
Leorio: MAN,
CAN'T SEE A THING.
"YOU'LL REACH THE TOP
IN TWO HOURS," SHE SAID.
WELL, IT WAS TWO HOURS
TWO HOURS AGO! ( scoffs )
ANOTHER
"BEWARE OF MAGICAL BEASTS" SIGN?
I'M STARTING TO THINK
WE'RE NEVER GONNA FIND
THE STUPID EXAM SITE.
GUYS! I'M SO HUNGRY!
‐ I NEED TO TAKE A DUMP!
‐ Gon: TRY TO KEEP UP, LEORIO!
Leorio: I GOTTA PEE, TOO!
HEY! HEY, GUYS!
‐ Kurapika: I THINK I SEE IT.
‐ Leorio: WAIT UP!
♪♪♪
( knocks )
HEY! ANYBODY HOME?
Gon: I GUESS NOT.
Leorio: COMING IN!
( all gasp )
‐ ( beast laughs )
‐ ( woman groans )
‐ Leorio: MAGICAL BEAST!
‐ Gon: A WHAT?
Kurapika: IT APPEARS
TO BE A KIRIKO.
IT CAN TAKE ON HUMAN FORM.
‐ ( Kiriko laughs )
‐ Kurapika: THEY'RE
EXTREMELY INTELLIGENT.
Gon: HE'S GOT A WOMAN.
Leorio: AND THE GUY ON THE FLOOR
LOOKS LIKE
HE NEEDS A DOCTOR BAD.
Man: PLEASE HELP.
SAVE HER!
YOU HAVE TO SAVE MY WIFE!
Kurapika: LEORIO,
SEE TO HIS INJURIES.
Leorio: RIGHT! I'M ON IT!
( Kurapika thinking )
EVEN IN PITCH DARKNESS,
HE CAN STILL SEE AND KEEP PACE
WITH SUCH A FAINT SHADOW.
IMPRESSIVE.
Gon: HEY, KIRIKO,
LET THE LADY GO!
( Kiriko chuckles ) WHY DON'T
YOU TRY TO TAKE HER FROM ME?
( Gon gasps )
WHOA!
YOU HEAR THAT? IT CAN TALK.
THAT'S AMAZING!
Kurapika: THE KIRIKO
IS A MAGICAL BEAST
CAPABLE OF HUMAN SPEECH.
Gon: REALLY?
WELL, THAT OUGHT TO MAKE THIS
A LOT EASIER.
HEY! COME HERE, YOU DUMB KIRIKO!
Kiriko: WHAT?
( thinking )
THIS KID IS FAST.
Gon: KURAPIKA!
Kurapika:
DAMN, THAT WAS RECKLESS.
Kiriko: STUPID KID.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY!
Gon: HEY! WAIT UP!
Kurapika: ARE YOU HURT, MISS?
ARE YOU FEELING PAIN
ANYWHERE AT ALL?
Woman: I'M FINE, BUT WHAT ABOUT
MY HUSBAND? IS HE ALL RIGHT?
Kurapika: NOT TO WORRY.
OUR FRIEND
IS TAKING GOOD CARE OF HIM.
Woman: THEN, PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO TAKE ME TO HIM, I BEG YOU!
( Kurapika gasps )
( thinking )
THOSE TATTOOS.
( woman gasps )
Kurapika: WAIT, YOU'RE NOT‐‐
Leorio: KURAPIKA!
YOU OKAY?
Kurapika: LEORIO.
Leorio: GUESS YOU ARE.
WHAT A RELIEF.
Kurapika: HOW IS THE MAN
YOU WERE CARING FOR?
Leorio: GOOD! I THINK
HE'LL PULL THROUGH FINE.
LUCKY FOR HIM THE WOUND
WASN'T AS DEEP AS IT LOOKED.
I GAVE HIM SOME PAINKILLERS,
SO HE'S SLEEPING IT OFF
BACK AT THE CABIN.
Kurapika: I SEE.
( Kiriko chuckles )
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
HOW COULD YOU TELL
THAT I WAS AN IMPOSTOR?
Kurapika: TO BE HONEST, I DIDN'T
ACTUALLY THINK YOU WERE.
YOU SEE, LEORIO MADE A PROMISE
THAT HE'D TAKE CARE
OF THAT INJURED MAN.
WHEN I SAW HIM, I ASSUMED
HE HAD LEFT THE MAN ALL ALONE,
AND WITH THE MAGICAL BEAST
STILL ON THE LOOSE,
I ATTACKED HIM
FOR ABANDONING HIS OBLIGATION,
NOTHING MORE.
( Kiriko laughs )
AND, YOU, TELL ME RIGHT NOW,
WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT IS IT YOU WANT FROM US?
( woman chuckles )
( leaves rustle )
Gon: WAIT!
♪♪♪
( Kiriko laughs )
YOU'RE PRETTY FAST FOR A KID,
YOU KNOW!
YOU REALLY HIT ME.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT FROM YOU.
THAT'S QUITE AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
IT COMES WITH A HIGHER PRICE
THAN YOU BARGAINED FOR!
KIRI! KIRI! KIRI! KIRI!
Gon: SO WHO ARE YOU?
( Kiriko gasps )
Gon: YOU'RE NOT THE ONE
I WAS CHASING, ARE YOU,
THE ONE THAT I HIT?
UM, ARE YOU A FRIEND OF HIS?
Kiriko: HOLD ON.
HOW CAN YOU TELL
THAT I'M NOT THE SAME ONE
FROM BEFORE?
Gon: HUH? OH, WELL,
YOU LOOK TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
YOUR VOICE IS DIFFERENT, TOO.
IT'S HIGHER AND KINDA THINNER.
( Kiriko laughing )
Gon: HMM?
Gon: WHAT'S UP?
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
IS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
Kiriko: HEY!
HEY, HONEY, COME HERE!
YOU'RE GONNA GET
A KICK OUT OF THIS!
( chuckles )
Kiriko #1:
HOW MANY YEARS HAS IT BEEN
SINCE ANYONE WAS ABLE
TO TELL THE TWO OF US APART?
HEH. I'M SO HAPPY!
Leorio: CAN YOU TELL 'EM APART?
SERIOUSLY.
Kurapika: NO. NO, NOT AT ALL.
Gon: DON'T YOU SEE?
THE KIRIKO THAT KURAPIKA AND I
HIT IS ACTUALLY THE HUSBAND.
Both: AND WHICH ONE
IS THAT, EXACTLY?
Father: ALLOW US
TO INTRODUCE OURSELVES.
WE ARE THE NAVIGATORS.
OUR FAMILY PROVIDES SUPPORT
FOR THE HUNTER EXAM.
Woman: I'M THEIR DAUGHTER.
Man: I'M THEIR SON.
Leorio: MAN, GREAT JOB.
YOU SURE HAD US FOOLED.
Father: THE EXAM SITE
MOVES AROUND.
KEEPS IT INTERESTING.
BUT THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
THEY RELOCATE IT
EVERY YEAR. UNDERSTAND?
Mother: THEY HIRE
NAVIGATORS LIKE US TO HELP
BY GUIDING WORTHY APPLICANTS
TO THE EXAMINATION SITE.
Gon: OH! SO THAT'S HOW IT WORKS!
Daughter: BUT DON'T GET
THE WRONG IDEA.
WE DON'T HELP EVERY CANDIDATE.
Son: FIRST, WE TEST THEM
TO SEE IF THEY'RE EVEN
QUALIFIED TO TAKE THE EXAM,
MAKE SURE
THEY HAVE WHAT IT TAKES.
Daughter: MR. KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: YES.
Daughter: WE MADE CERTAIN
THAT WE ONLY GAVE YOU
THE MOST VAGUE OF HINTS,
BUT YOU WERE STILL ABLE
TO PICK UP ON THEM
AND DETERMINE THAT WE WEREN'T
ACTUALLY A MARRIED COUPLE.
YOU ONLY CAUGHT A GLIMPSE
OF MY TATTOOS,
BUT YOU KNEW
THAT IN THIS REGION,
THESE TATTOOS ARE ONLY WORN
BY WOMEN WHO'VE TAKEN
A VOW OF CHASTITY.
MR. KURAPIKA DEMONSTRATED THAT
HE'S INCREDIBLY KNOWLEDGEABLE.
THEREFORE, HE PASSES.
( Kurapika sighs )
Gon: WAY TO GO, KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: THANKS.
Son: MR. LEORIO.
Leorio: YES?
Son: YOU, SIR,
UNFORTUNATELY NEVER REALIZED
THAT I WASN'T
WHO I CLAIMED TO BE.
( Leorio gasps )
Son: HOWEVER,
YOU DRESSED MY WOUNDS
FASTER AND MORE THOROUGHLY
THAN ANY DOCTOR.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
YOU DEMONSTRATED
ADMIRABLE EMPATHY AND KINDNESS
BY CONTINUING TO REASSURE ME
THAT MY WIFE WOULD BE OKAY.
Leorio: KNOCK IT OFF, OKAY?
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
Son: IT'S CLEAR TO ME
THAT YOUR COMPASSION
MAKES YOU WORTHY
OF TAKING THE HUNTER EXAM,
AND SO YOU PASS.
Leorio: WAIT! SERIOUSLY?!
( groans )
Gon: YOU DID IT!
( both chuckle )
Father: AND FINALLY MR. GON.
Gon: YES!
Father: YOUR SUPERHUMAN
PHYSICAL ABILITY
AND YOUR POWERS OF OBSERVATION
DEFY LOGIC.
YOU, TOO, ARE WORTHY
TO TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM,
SO YOU PASS.
( all chuckling )
Father: ALL RIGHT!
WE'LL NOW TAKE YOU
STRAIGHT TO THE SITE
OF THE EXAM!
Gon: OH, WOW!
ISN'T IT INCREDIBLE
THAT WE ALL PASSED?
Kurapika: I WOULDN'T
CELEBRATE JUST YET.
WE'VE MERELY EARNED
THE RIGHT TO TAKE THE EXAM.
Leorio: IT'S PROGRESS!
I'D SAY THAT CALLS
FOR A LITTLE CELEBRATION.
Kurapika: HONESTLY,
HAVE SOME FORESIGHT.
Leorio: MUST YOU BE
SUCH A SMART‐ASS ALL THE TIME?
‐ Mother: HEY!
‐ Father: STOP SQUIRMING!
IF YOU FALL,
IT'S YOUR FAULT!
( Gon laughs )
Narrator: AND SO
GON AND HIS FRIENDS
ENJOY A BRIEF JOURNEY
THROUGH THE SKY.
HOWEVER, EVEN AFTER ALL THIS,
THEY HAVE YET TO REACH
THE STARTING LINE.
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"RIVALS IN SURVIVAL."
I'M GONNA DO MY BEST!
♪♪♪