( somber chorus vocalizing )
( Killua gasps )
Hisoka: GUESS I'LL PLAY DUMB.
Killua: THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SEEMS TO LIKE GON,
SO HE MIGHT HELP US.
( Gon gasps ) HEY!
Killua: YOU IDIOT.
( Hisoka sighs )
Gon: OH, YEAH. OOPS.
Nobunaga: WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW SOMEONE HERE?
Killua: UH, NO.
HEY! IT'S THAT GIRL WE MET!
Phinks: IS THAT TRUE, SHIZUKU?
YOU KNOW THESE GUYS?
Shizuku: NO, I SURE DON'T.
Feitan: OH, I REMEMBER NOW.
THE KID WHO ARM WRESTLES.
Shizuku: REFRESH MY MEMORY.
Franklin: THAT KID,
YOU LOST TO HIM
IN AN ARM‐WRESTLING CONTEST
TWO DAYS AGO.
Shizuku: I DID? HE BEAT ME?
THAT'S A LIE!
I'M NOT THE STRONGEST,
BUT I WOULDN'T LOSE TO A KID.
Franklin: WELL, IT'S BECAUSE
YOU WERE USING YOUR RIGHT HAND.
Shizuku: I DID? BUT WHY?
I'M LEFT‐HANDED.
Feitan: DON'T BOTHER.
ONCE SHE HAS
FORGOTTEN SOMETHING,
IT IS GONE FOR GOOD.
Franklin: RIGHT. NEVER MIND.
GUESS I WAS MISTAKEN.
Shizuku: THOUGHT SO.
Nobunaga: HOLD ON.
IS THAT RIGHT?
‐ YOU REALLY BEAT SHIZUKU?
‐ Gon: YEAH.
Killua: I NEVER
WOULD HAVE IMAGINED
THAT SHE WAS
A PHANTOM TROUPE MEMBER.
Nobunaga: OKAY.
THEN SHOW ME WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Nobunaga: ONE MORE TIME.
( Gon grunts )
READY?
GO.
( Gon grunting )
Nobunaga: ALL RIGHT,
ONE MORE TIME.
READY?
‐ GO.
‐ ( Gon grunting )
Nobunaga: SO, HOW DO I STACK UP
AGAINST ALL THE OTHER SPIDERS?
BE HONEST.
Franklin: PROBABLY SEVENTH
OR EIGHTH, I'D GUESS.
Machi: WELL,
YOU AREN'T THE WEAKEST,
BUT NOT THE STRONGEST EITHER.
RIGHT. THE STRONGEST MEMBER
OF THE TROUPE
WAS THIS GUY CALLED UVOGIN,
BUT IT'S STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE THE CHAIN USER KILLED HIM.
Killua: WE TOLD YOU!
WE HAVE NO CLUE WHO THAT IS!
Nobunaga: HEY, KID!
SPEAK WITHOUT
MY PERMISSION AGAIN,
AND I'LL KILL YOU.
NOW ONE MORE TIME.
READY?
GO.
UVOGIN WAS AN ENHANCER.
HE WAS SIMPLE‐MINDED,
STRAIGHTFORWARD,
AND HE LOVED A GOOD FIGHT,
AND PUNCTUAL,
A REAL STICKLER ABOUT TIME.
WHENEVER FRANKLIN OR I
WERE LATE,
HE'D ALWAYS START SOMETHING.
HE BEAT THE CRAP OUT OF ME
MORE THAN ONCE, I CAN TELL YA!
I'VE KNOWN HIM SINCE
BEFORE THE TROUPE WAS FOUNDED.
I KNOW HIM BETTER THAN ANYONE.
HE WOULD NEVER‐‐
I MEAN NEVER LOSE
IN A FAIR FIGHT.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
NOT UNLESS HE WAS CAUGHT
IN SOME DIRTY TRAP!
I'LL MAKE HIS KILLER PAY.
I'LL FIND HIM,
NO MATTER WHO I HAVE TO KILL.
THE CHAIN USER HOLDS
SOME KIND OF GRUDGE AGAINST US,
A STRONG ONE.
THE MAFIA'S NOSTRADE FAMILY
HIRED HIM RECENTLY.
Killua: A GRUDGE
AGAINST THE TROUPE.
A RECENT HIRE? ( gasps )
Nobunaga: YOU MAY
NOT KNOW HIM PERSONALLY,
BUT MAYBE YOU HEARD RUMORS,
SO THINK HARD, ALL RIGHT?
YOU'D BETTER
NOT HOLD ANYTHING BACK.
Gon: I DON'T KNOW HIM,
BUT EVEN IF I DID,
I WOULD STILL
NEVER GIVE HIM UP TO YOU!
I THOUGHT YOU ALL WERE A BUNCH
OF COLD‐BLOODED MONSTERS,
BUT I SEE YOU CAN SHED TEARS
FOR YOUR FRIENDS...
SO YOU'RE CAPABLE OF EMPATHY,
BUT YOU'VE KILLED‐‐
YOU'VE KILLED SO MANY PEOPLE!
WHY COULDN'T YOU FEEL THAT
FOR THEM?!
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
( grunts )
Feitan: CAREFUL.
YOU'RE TOO COCKY.
( Gon groans )
Killua: GON!
♪
Hisoka: MOVE, AND I'LL CUT YOU.
Feitan: ANSWER THE QUESTION.
DO YOU KNOW
WHO THE CHAIN USER IS?
Gon: I TOLD YOU!
I'M NOT TELLING YOU ANYTHING,
SO GET OFF OF ME!
Feitan: HMM.
Nobunaga: FEITAN.
STOP IT.
Feitan: STOP WHAT?
Nobunaga: STOP DOING
WHAT YOU'RE JUST ABOUT TO DO.
Feitan: OH? YOU THINK
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO?
Nobunaga: YOU'RE GOING
TO BREAK HIS ARM, AREN'T YOU?
Feitan: I'D START WITH A FINGER,
PEEL OFF A NAIL.
Nobunaga: DOESN'T MATTER.
I TOLD YOU TO STOP IT.
Feitan: YOU'RE GIVING ME ORDERS?
I DON'T HAVE TO OBEY
Franklin:
HEY, QUIT IT, NOBUNAGA.
Machi: WHAT, HAVE YOU
ALREADY FORGOTTEN THE RULES?
Shizuku: THERE'S
NO PHYSICAL FIGHTING
BETWEEN THE TROUPE MEMBERS.
Nobunaga: I KNOW. I KNOW.
DISPUTES ARE DECIDED
BY A COIN TOSS.
Feitan: TAILS.
Nobunaga: THEN I'M HEADS.
IT'S HEADS, SO LET HIM GO.
Shizuku: WELL,
WHAT DO WE DO WITH THEM?
THEY HAVEN'T TOLD US ANYTHING
ABOUT THE CHAIN USER.
Franklin: IF THEY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, THEN JUST LET 'EM GO.
AM I RIGHT, PAKUNODA?
Pakunoda: I CHECKED
ON THE TRIP HERE.
IT'S TRUE.
THEY REALLY DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
‐ Killua: HUH?
‐ Machi: YOU SURE?
Pakunoda: I AM.
THEY HAVE NO MEMORIES
OF THE CHAIN USER WHATSOEVER.
Nobunaga: LOOKS LIKE YOUR HUNCH
WAS A LITTLE OFF
THIS TIME, HUH?
Machi: THAT'S BIZARRE.
OH, WELL. IF PAKUNODA SAYS SO,
IT MUST BE TRUE.
♪
( Gon growls )
HEY, GON, DID THEY DO ANYTHING
TO YOU ON THE WAY HERE?
Gon: NOT REALLY.
JUST ASKED ME SOME QUESTIONS.
Killua: THOUGHT SO.
( thinking ) SO SHE EXAMINED US
WITHOUT KNOWING.
WHAT WAS IT? AND HOW?
IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY ALL HAVE A LOT OF FAITH
IN THAT PAKUNODA WOMAN'S
JUDGMENT.
HER SKILL MUST BE
MORE ACCURATE THAN INSTINCT.
Pakunoda: THEY HAVE NO MEMORIES
OF THE CHAIN USER WHATSOEVER.
Killua: MEMORIES?
Pakunoda: HOW ABOUT YOU?
HAVE ANY GUESSES?
Killua: THE POWER
TO SCAN SOMEONE'S MEMORY,
BY WHAT, TOUCHING THEM?
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
WE'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
WHEN SHE SCANNED US BEFORE,
I HAD NO IDEA
WHO THE CHAIN USER WAS,
BUT NOW I HAVE
AN IMAGE IN MY HEAD.
IF SHE CHECKS ME AGAIN...
Franklin: THEY DON'T KNOW
THE CHAIN USER,
SO CAN'T WE
JUST LET THEM GO NOW?
Shalnark: YEAH.
I REALLY DON'T SEE THE POINT
IN KEEPING THEM HERE.
Phinks: NO.
WE CAN'T BE SURE
THEY'RE COMPLETELY UNRELATED.
IT'S POSSIBLE
THEY'RE BEING USED.
THE CHAIN USER IS DISCREET.
HE USUALLY KEEPS
HIS CHAINS HIDDEN.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
MAYBE THEY DON'T REALIZE
HE'S WHO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WE SHOULDN'T RELEASE THEM,
NOT UNTIL THEY TELL US
WHO THEY'RE WORKING FOR.
Shalnark: IF THEY ARE
WORKING FOR SOMEONE,
THEN IT ISN'T THE CHAIN USER,
BECAUSE HE PREFERS TO OPERATE
ALL BY HIMSELF.
Machi: SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU AGREE WITH NOBUNAGA?
Shalnark: WE CAN GET
WHATEVER INFORMATION WE NEED
FROM THE NOSTRADE FAMILY.
WE DON'T REALLY NEED
THESE KIDS FOR THAT.
AFTER ALL, WE KNOW
THE CHAIN USER IS A MEMBER.
Franklin: THAT'S RIGHT. WE DO.
Shalnark: OUR ONLY TARGET
RIGHT NOW IS THE CHAIN USER,
SO WE CAN PRETTY MUCH IGNORE
EVERYBODY ELSE.
Feitan: THERE YOU GO.
YOU ARE LUCKY.
( Gon grunts )
Nobunaga: NOT JUST YET.
♪
I'M NOT LETTING THE KID GO.
YOU WANNA JOIN THE SPIDERS?
TEAM UP WITH ME.
Gon: NO. I WOULD RATHER DIE
THAN TEAM UP WITH YOU GUYS,
SO IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN!
( Nobunaga laughs )
HE REALLY HATES US, DOESN'T HE?
WHAT ARE YOU?
YOU'RE AN ENHANCER, RIGHT?
Gon: YEAH, AND WHAT IF I AM?
Nobunaga: I THOUGHT
YOU'D SAY THAT.
( laughs )
HEY, WE'RE KEEPING THEM HERE
UNTIL THE BOSS GETS BACK.
I'M NOMINATING HIM.
Phinks: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Feitan: THE BOSS
WILL NEVER AGREE TO THAT.
Machi: FINE, WHATEVER,
BUT YOU'VE GOTTA BABY‐SIT 'EM.
IT'S ON YOU IF THEY ESCAPE.
Shizuku: REALLY?
HE REMINDS YOU OF UVO?
Franklin: YEAH.
HE WEARS ALL HIS EMOTIONS
RIGHT ON HIS SLEEVE,
AND WHEN HE'S MAD,
HE FORGETS
ABOUT THE CONSEQUENCES.
BUT WHAT'S THE MOST LIKE UVO IS
HE'S AT HIS ABSOLUTE STRONGEST
WHEN HE'S FIGHTING
FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
HE LIKED TO FIGHT ALONE,
BUT UVO WAS NEVER MORE POWERFUL
THAN WHEN HE WOULD GO OFF
AND TEAM UP WITH NOBUNAGA
TO FIGHT AN ENTIRE HORDE.
HE NEVER ADMITTED IT,
BUT I THINK UVO PREFERRED HAVING
SOMEONE THERE TO PROTECT.
Shizuku: HE WAS STRONGER WHEN
SOMEONE WAS HOLDING HIM BACK?
Franklin: I GUESS
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
Feitan: SHE DOES NOT
MINCE WORDS, DOES SHE?
Phinks: ON THE OTHER HAND,
NOBUNAGA'S SKILLS
ARE EXCELLENT FOR DUELING.
YOU MIGHT EVEN SAY THAT THEY'RE
ONLY EFFECTIVE ONE‐ON‐ONE.
Franklin: WHENEVER THOSE TWO
HAD TO FIGHT TOGETHER,
THEY WOULD ALWAYS COMPLAIN,
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE
THEY BOTH ENJOYED IT.
Shalnark: OKAY.
ENOUGH REMINISCING.
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
HERE'S A FULL LIST
OF THE NOSTRADE FAMILY MEMBERS.
I GOT IT STRAIGHT FROM
THE OFFICIAL HUNTER WEBSITE.
THESE FIVE
ARE ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT.
THEY SERVE
AS FULL‐TIME BODYGUARDS
FOR THE BOSS'S DAUGHTER,
NOT TO MENTION THE FACT
THAT THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO CAPTURED UVO.
BUT UVO WAS CERTAIN
THAT THE CHAIN USER
WASN'T ON THIS LIST,
AND SINCE WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE,
WE'RE GOING TO NEED TO FIND
SOMEONE WHO DOES.
Phinks: HEY,
THAT'S THE GUY I KILLED,
THE ONE ON THE TOP LEFT.
YOU CAN CROSS HIM OFF.
Shalnark: ALL RIGHT, PAIR UP,
AND SEARCH THE AREA,
AND KEEP A SHARP EYE OUT
FOR ANY OF THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE ON THIS LIST.
WE'LL ALL MEET BACK HERE
AT 10 P. M.
GOT IT? LET'S MOVE.
Machi: HEY, HOLD ON!
NOBUNAGA'S STAYING HERE, RIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT ME?
Shalnark: YOU CAN JUST TEAM UP
WITH WHOEVER IS LEFT.
( Hisoka chuckles )
( Machi sighs )
Gon: OW.
Killua: THAT WAS STUPID OF ME.
IF I'D MADE A MOVE,
HISOKA WOULD HAVE KILLED ME
WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT.
THAT MURDEROUS AURA.
I WAS PARALYZED.
IF THEY'D THREATENED
TO KILL GON,
WOULD I HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO STOP THEM?
WOULD I HAVE EVEN
BEEN ABLE TO MOVE?
Illumi: YOU CAN'T DO IT,
CAN YOU?
BECAUSE DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
YOU'RE MORE WORRIED
ABOUT WHETHER YOU CAN DEFEAT ME
THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
Killua: YOU'RE WRONG.
Illumi: REMEMBER THE LESSON
I DRILLED INTO YOU?
NEVER GO UP
AGAINST A SUPERIOR OPPONENT.
Killua: NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
♪
Nobunaga: HEH. PRETTY SCARY.
IF LOOKS COULD KILL, HUH?
I SHOULD WARN YOU,
STEP INTO RANGE,
AND I'LL CUT YOU DOWN.
Gon: KILLUA!
♪
( Killua gasping )
( Nobunaga exhales )
Killua: I DON'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST HIM.
I'VE GOTTA THINK
OF A WAY TO ESCAPE.
Gon: NO WINDOWS...
AND ONLY ONE EXIT.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GET HIM
TO MOVE AWAY FROM THE DOOR?
( wind blowing )
HEY, I WONDER
IF LEORIO IS OKAY.
I REALLY HOPE HE WAS ABLE
TO GET AHOLD OF MR. ZEPILE.
KILLUA? YOU OKAY?
Killua: YEAH.
Gon: LET'S SEE. MR. ZEPILE
TAUGHT US CAUTERIZATION,
AUTOPSY, AND SOMETHING ELSE.
REMEMBER WHAT IT WAS?
Killua: I FORGET.
Gon: WAS IT OSMOSIS, MAYBE?
I DON'T THINK IT WAS,
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW.
‐ Killua: GON.
‐ Gon: HMM?
Killua: I'LL BE THE DECOY.
WAIT FOR IT. THEN TRY TO ESCAPE.
Gon: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
Nobunaga: LOOK, SERIOUSLY,
FORGET ALL ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE GOOD ENOUGH TO RECOGNIZE
THE DIFFERENCE IN OUR ABILITIES.
YOU WON'T CATCH ME OFF GUARD.
Killua: I KNOW THAT ALREADY.
THIS ROOM HAS ONE EXIT
AND NOWHERE TO HIDE.
HE CAN SEE
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING.
HE CAN EVEN KEEP AN EYE ON US
WITHOUT EVER CREATING
AN OPENING.
HE'S PROBABLY AN IAIDO MASTER,
AND WITH HIS SHODACHI,
HIS RANGE IS TWICE MINE.
ONE STEP TOO CLOSE,
AND I'M DEAD MEAT.
BUT THAT'S
WHAT GIVES IT MEANING.
Illumi:
YOU CAN'T DO IT, CAN YOU?
Killua: SHUT UP, ALL RIGHT?!
THE ONLY WAY I'LL FIND OUT
IS IF I TRY!
Gon: KILLUA, WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING ABOUT DOING?
Killua: I'LL STOP HIS SHODACHI,
EVEN IF IT KILLS ME.
WHEN I DO, YOU RUN AWAY.
Nobunaga: HUH?
Killua: WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT FOR, HUH?!
‐ Gon: STOP BEING SO SELFISH!
‐ Killua: HUH?!
Gon: DON'T TALK ABOUT DYING
LIKE IT'S NO BIG DEAL!
Killua: WHY NOT?! YOU DID!
YOU SAID THE SAME THING EARLIER!
Gon: I'M ALLOWED TO,
BUT YOU'RE NOT! DO YOU HEAR ME?!
( Killua gasps )
( Nobunaga laughs )
REASON NEVER WORKS
ON AN ENHANCER.
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW THAT, KID.
Killua: WE CAN'T ESCAPE
UNLESS WE'RE PREPARED TO DIE,
YOU STUPID LITTLE JERK!
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING!
SO TELL ME,
WHO'S THE SELFISH ONE NOW?!
Gon: NO! I DON'T KNOW!
'CAUSE I'M STUPID!
( Nobunaga laughs )
YOU TWO KIDS ARE HILARIOUS.
YOU KNOW THAT?
LISTEN, I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
JUST BEHAVE YOURSELVES.
I KNOW YOU GUYS MEAN BUSINESS,
ALL RIGHT?
DON'T THROW YOUR LIVES AWAY.
SIT TIGHT, AND WAIT
UNTIL THE BOSS GETS BACK,
AND IF YOU
DON'T STRIKE HIS FANCY,
YOU GET TO LEAVE
FREE AND CLEAR,
BUT TRY TO ESCAPE,
AND I'LL KILL YOU.
MAKE ME DRAW MY SWORD
FROM ITS SCABBARD,
AND YOU WON'T SURVIVE
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
( Gon gasps )
I REMEMBER NOW!
THE OTHER ONE IS OSTOMY!
CAUTERIZATION, AUTOPSY,
AND THE LAST ONE'S OSTOMY!
♪
( Killua gasps )
Gon: DO YOU REMEMBER NOW?
Killua: YEAH! I JUST WISH
I'D THOUGHT OF IT SOONER!
Gon: RIGHT? I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE BOTH FORGOT
SOMETHING SO SIMPLE!
Nobunaga: WHAT?
Gon: NOW THAT WE'VE
FIGURED THAT OUT...
Killua: LET'S GO.
Nobunaga: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
I'M NOT NEARLY SKILLED
OR MERCIFUL ENOUGH
TO TEMPER MY STRENGTH
TO FACE YOU.
♪
YOU FOOLS!
Gon: IF THE EXIT IS BLOCKED...
Killua: YOU'VE JUST
GOTTA MAKE YOUR OWN!
Nobunaga: THE WALL.
HMM. WHICH ONE DO I CHASE?
WE'RE ON THE FIFTH FLOOR.
THE CAT‐EYED KID'S
ALREADY BY THE STAIRS,
SO THE BLACK‐HAIRED KID.
THERE. NOW HE DOESN'T
HAVE ANYWHERE TO RUN.
‐ ( crash )
‐ ( scoffs )
WHAT AM I THINKING?
THEY CAN KEEP BREAKING
THROUGH WALLS TO ESCAPE!
( crash )
THE CAT‐EYED KID IS BELOW.
I'LL STAY
ON THE BLACK‐HAIRED ONE.
WHERE IS HE?
THE WALLS ARE INTACT.
SO'S THE DOOR.
Gon: KILLUA, ARE YOU THERE?
‐ ( running footsteps )
‐ ( Nobunaga gasps )
Killua: YEAH! I'M HERE!
( Nobunaga gasps ) THAT'S IT!
THEN THAT MUST MEAN
THE LAST HOLE WAS A DECOY.
HE BUSTED THE WALL,
THEN DOUBLED BACK
AND HID IN THE NEXT ROOM
SO I'D PASS HIM.
Gon: WE CAN BEAT HIM,
THE TWO OF US!
Nobunaga:
HIS PRESENCE DISAPPEARED.
ZETSU?
DOES THIS IDIOT
REALLY WANT TO FIGHT ME?
AN ADVANCED APPLICATION
OF TEN AND REN...
EN!
AURA ENVELOPS THE BODY
IN A LAYER
A FEW MILLIMETERS
TO A COUPLE CENTIMETERS THICK,
BUT WITH EN, YOU CAN EXTEND IT
AS FAR AS NECESSARY.
YOU CAN SENSE ANYONE
WHO ENTERS YOUR EN.
INSIDE IT, YOU CAN EVEN COUNT
THE LEAVES AS THEY FALL.
YOU CAN CONCEAL YOUR PRESENCE
BEFORE YOUR APPROACH,
NEVER MAKING A SOUND,
BUT ENTER MY EN,
AND MY SWORD FLIES.
COME. I'M READY.
♪
Killua: THAT IDIOT.
Gon: MAN, I REALLY WANTED
TO BEAT THAT GUY UP.
Killua: YEAH,
FAT CHANCE OF THAT.
HE'D KILL YOU TWICE
BEFORE YOU TRIED.
Gon: YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
Killua: WE ONLY KNOW
THE BASICS OF NEN.
WE WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
( Gon giggles )
Killua: WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Gon: YOU'RE BACK
TO BEING YOUR OLD SELF AGAIN.
IT'S MY JOB TO BE RECKLESS,
AND IT'S YOUR JOB TO STAY COOL
AND KEEP ME IN LINE!
( Killua scoffs )
Gon: GLAD I CAN
COUNT ON YOU, PAL!
Killua: YOU'RE BEING SELFISH.
Gon: WELL? WHAT DO WE DO NEXT?
Killua: DEPENDS ON WHAT
WE WANNA DO, I GUESS.
Gon: OKAY.
I WANNA KICK THEIR BUTTS.
Killua: FIGURED.
WELL, THAT'S NOT TOO DIFFERENT
FROM THE ORIGINAL PLAN,
BUT BOTH OF US'LL NEED
TO IMPROVE OUR NEN
IF THAT'S WHAT WE
DECIDE WE'RE GONNA DO.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
WE MIGHT GET AS STRONG
AS WE'LL NEED TO,
AND THAT'S NEN.
AND THE FASTEST WAY
IS THROUGH KURAPIKA.
WE NEED TO GO ASK HIM.
Gon: HUH? WHY?
Killua: BECAUSE HE'S
THE CHAIN USER
WHO DEFEATED THEIR FRIEND
AND GOT US INTO THIS MESS.
Gon: WHAT?
Killua: WAIT. YOU HADN'T
FIGURED THAT OUT YET?
Gon: YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S KURAPIKA?
Killua: I'M PRETTY SURE IT IS,
AND IF I'M RIGHT,
WE STILL HAVE A CHANCE.
YOU AND I BOTH
STARTED LEARNING NEN
AT AROUND THE SAME TIME
KURAPIKA DID.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO NOW
IS LEARN THE UNIQUE ABILITIES
THAT FIT OUR TALENTS,
BUT WHAT'S EVEN MORE IMPORTANT,
WE'VE GOT TO GAIN
THE STRENGTH WE'LL NEED
TO FACE THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Gon: AND YOU
REALLY THINK KURAPIKA'S
THE KEY TO FINDING
THE ANSWERS WE'RE LOOKING FOR?
Killua: YEAH.
♪
Narrator: MEANWHILE,
DEEP IN THE TROUBLED HEART
OF YORKNEW CITY,
A FEARSOME STORM
HAS BEGUN TO BREW.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'LL INTRODUCE FRANKLIN.
HE'S AN EMITTER
AND A PHANTOM TROUPE MEMBER.
Killua: HIS DOUBLE MACHINE GUN
ATTACK SHOOTS NEN BULLETS.
Gon: USE YOUR FINGERS AS GUNS
FOR AN EXTRA PUNCH.
( Killua gasps )
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"A BRUTAL BATTLEFIELD."
‐ OUT.
‐ Killua: OUT?
Gon: OUTFIELD.
Both: INFIELD!