( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Leorio: GUESS I'LL LET GO, THEN.
Majitani: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA! HOLD ON!
DON'T LET GO!
I'M AWAKE! I'M AWAKE!
Leroute: EVEN SO, YOU HAVE
ONLY 20 HOURS REMAINING.
Leorio: I KNOW, BUT AT LEAST NOW
WE'RE IN A BETTER POSITION
WITH A TWO‐ONE LEAD.
NOW...
LET'S KEEP THIS BALL ROLLING.
THE CHOICE IS YOURS,
SO WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
♪♪♪
Narrator: IN THE FIVE‐ON‐FIVE
BATTLE WITH THE PRISONERS,
GON AND FRIENDS LEAD TWO‐TO‐ONE.
THEY'RE ONE WIN AWAY
FROM VICTORY.
ROUND FOUR IS A SERIES OF BETS
WITH TIME AS THE CURRENCY.
WHAT WILL THEY BET ON NEXT?
Leorio: WELL, LET'S HEAR IT.
WHAT'S THE NEXT WAGER
GONNA BE, HUH?
OR DID YOU LOSE YOUR NERVE WHEN
I SAW THROUGH YOUR LITTLE SCAM?
( Leroute chuckles )
VERY WELL.
Woman: WOW!
( Leorio gasps )
DAMN.
SHE'S REALLY CUTE.
( chuckling )
Killua: WHAT A PERVERT.
I HEAR HIS HEARTBEAT FROM HERE.
Kurapika: I DON'T LIKE
WHERE THIS IS HEADING.
Leroute: ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLACE BETS
ON WHETHER I'M A MAN OR A WOMAN?
( Leorio gasps )
Leroute: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
THAT ISN'T A PROBLEM, IS IT?
Leorio: UH, NO!
( thinking )
SHE IS DEFINITELY A WOMAN.
OR MAYBE SHE'S A CROSS‐DRESSER?
NO WAY. SHE'S GOTTA BE A WOMAN.
FINE, I ACCEPT.
BUT WHAT IF I BET YOU'RE A MAN?
HOW EXACTLY ARE YOU
GONNA PROVE YOU'RE NOT?
Leroute: OH, RIGHT.
I PROMISE TO LET YOU EXAMINE
EVERY SQUARE INCH OF MY BODY.
NOW, WILL THAT SATISFY YOU?
( Leorio gasps )
HER BODY?
( cackles )
Kurapika: HE'S ALREADY CHOSEN.
HE'LL BET SHE'S A MAN.
Killua: YEAH.
Gon: HUH? WHY?
Leorio: I'VE MADE UP MY MIND,
AND I'LL WAGER 10 HOURS
THAT YOU'RE ACTUALLY A MAN!
( Leroute scoffs )
Kurapika: I KNEW IT.
Killua: DIRTY, STINKIN' OLD MAN.
Gon: BUT HOW DID YOU KNOW?
( Leorio thinking )
THIS WAY, EVEN IF I'M WRONG
AND SHE IS A WOMAN, I STILL
GET TO CHECK OUT HER BODY!
EITHER WAY,
TALK ABOUT A WIN‐WIN SITUATION.
ACTUALLY, I HOPE I'M WRONG.
Killua: DO YOU GET IT NOW?
Gon: YEAH, I DO.
Leorio: OKAY, REVEAL THE ANSWER!
Leroute: THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'M REALLY A WOMAN.
( Leorio gasps )
OH, YOU ARE, HUH?
Leroute: WELL,
WANT TO CHECK FOR YOURSELF?
Leorio: WELL,
DON'T MIND IF I DO!
I MEAN, JUST TO BE FAIR,
OF COURSE.
♪♪♪
( laughing )
( thinking )
I REGRET NOTHING.
( Killua groans )
Kurapika: IT IS PHYSICALLY
PAINFUL TO WATCH THIS.
Tonpa: HE'S GONNA LOSE.
Gon: EH?
Tonpa: NO QUESTION.
SHE CAN ALREADY SEE
RIGHT THROUGH HIS STRATEGY.
HE'S BETTING SAFE. IT'S OBVIOUS.
HEDGING HIS BETS
TO MINIMIZE THE DAMAGE.
HE'S THE KIND OF GAMBLER
WHO TRIES TO AVOID LOSING
INSTEAD OF TRYING TO WIN.
THAT KIND OF BETTING
NEVER TAKES HOME THE PRIZE.
( Leorio chuckling )
Tonpa: SORRY TO SAY IT, BOYS,
BUT LEORIO JUST DOESN'T
HAVE WHAT IT TAKES.
( Leroute thinking )
I THOUGHT SO.
HIS GAMBLING STYLE
IS NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IF HE KEEPS PLAYING THAT WAY,
HE DOESN'T HAVE A PRAYER.
( chuckles )
WELL?
YOUR TURN TO PICK
WHAT WE BET ON NEXT.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANNA WAGER?
( Leorio gasps )
( thinking )
THIS IS NO TIME TO CELEBRATE.
I'VE ONLY GOT 10 HOURS
LEFT TO BET WITH.
Kurapika: LEORIO HAS
NO ROOM FOR ERROR.
LOSING THE NEXT BET WOULD TIE
THE SCORE UP AT TWO‐TO‐TWO,
AND THEN WE LOSE 50 HOURS,
LEAVING VERY LITTLE TIME
TO CLEAR THE TOWER.
( Gon groans )
LEORIO.
Leorio: 'KAY, WHAT TO BET ON.
I CAN'T AFFORD TO LOSE,
BUT I CAN'T THINK
OF A SUREFIRE WIN.
( gasps ) HEY, I GOT IT!
WE'LL BET ON WHETHER
I'M REALLY A MAN
OR JUST A WOMAN IN DISGUISE.
NO, THAT'S NEVER GONNA WORK.
GOTTA THINK OF SOMETHING ELSE.
Killua: KEEP IT TO YOURSELF,
OLD MAN.
THINKING OUT LOUD
ISN'T HOW YOU PLAN A STRATEGY.
Gon: I KNOW.
LEORIO!
‐ Leorio: HUH?
‐ Gon: HOW 'BOUT YOU BET
ON WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'RE A TEENAGER?
Leorio: GIMME A BREAK, GON!
THERE'S NO WAY I LOOK THAT OLD,
AND YOU ALL KNOW IT!
I'M CLEARLY A TEENAGER.
Leroute: HE'S A TEENAGER?
( thinking )
WOW, HE LOOKS LIKE AN OLD MAN.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT!
I KNOW WHAT WE'RE BETTING ON!
LET'S BET ON WHO'LL WIN
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS!
( Leroute giggles )
WHY NOT?
Kurapika: IS HE SERIOUS?
WHY DID HE HAVE TO PICK
SUCH A DIFFICULT WAGER?
Gon: WAIT. WHAT'S SO HARD
ABOUT ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS?
( Leorio chuckles )
( thinking )
JUST SO HAPPENS
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS
IS MY SPECIALTY.
IN FACT, I JUST PLAYED
A TOURNAMENT
IN THE SHOPPING DISTRICT,
AND I WON A GOURMET VACATION.
Leroute: LET'S SEE.
SO FOR MY WAGER,
I'VE GOT 80 HOURS
THAT SAY I'LL WIN, OKAY?
Leorio: DID‐‐
DID YOU JUST SAY 80?
Leorio: THAT'S NOT
A PROBLEM, IS IT?
I'M FREE TO BET
HOWEVER MUCH I WANT.
( Leorio gasps )
I GUESS THERE'S
NO RULE AGAINST IT.
Leroute: PERFECT.
AND IF YOU LOSE,
I CAN ONLY TAKE 10 FROM YOU,
SINCE THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE LEFT,
SO DON'T WORRY.
( Leorio thinking ) SHE DOESN'T
NEED TO BET 80 HOURS.
10 IS PLENTY.
I MEAN, WHAT IF SHE LOSES?
IS SHE THAT CONFIDENT IN HER
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS SKILLS?
( Leroute thinking) AS EXPECTED,
HE'S STARTING TO STRESS OUT!
( giggles )
I CAN READ HIM
LIKE AN OPEN BOOK.
Kurapika: WHILE THE RULES OF
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS ARE SIMPLE,
THE GAME ITSELF
CAN BE INCREDIBLY COMPLEX.
FROM THE PERSPECTIVE
OF PROBABILITY,
YOU ONLY STAND
A ONE‐IN‐THREE CHANCE
OF LOSING ANY GIVEN ROUND.
BUT IF YOUR OPPONENT
CAN PREDICT YOUR REASONING
AND CONTROL YOUR REACTIONS,
YOUR CHANCE OF LOSING
INCREASES DRAMATICALLY.
Killua: IN SHORT,
THIS IS A GAME OF WITS,
AND LEORIO IS PRETTY LACKING
IN THAT DEPARTMENT.
Gon: I SEE.
Leorio: OKAY, I'M READY!
( Leroute chuckles )
Leorio: HEY, WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Leroute: IT'S JUST I CAN ALREADY
TELL WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO USE.
I'M SOMETHING OF A MIND READER,
YOU SEE.
Leorio: THAT IS A LIE!
YOU CAN BLUFF ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IT'LL TAKE A LOT MORE
THAN THAT TO SCARE ME!
Leroute: YOU'LL BELIEVE IT SOON.
( giggles )
( thinking )
JUST LIKE I PLANNED.
ONE BLATANT LIE,
AND HE'S LOSING IT.
( Leorio thinking )
CAN SHE REALLY READ MINDS?
NO, SHE'S LYING.
SHE'S GOTTA BE.
BUT WHAT IF SHE ISN'T?
Kurapika: LEORIO WILL USE ROCK.
Gon: WHAT?
Leroute: YOU READY?
Leorio: GAH!
Leroute: AND ROCK, PAPER...
Both: SCISSORS!
Leorio: WHEW.
Gon: YOU WERE RIGHT.
GOOD GUESS, KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: LEORIO WAS NERVOUS,
LEADING HIM TO AVOID ANY ACTIONS
THAT INVOLVED OPENING UP.
SHE'S GOOD.
SHE'S DOING EVERYTHING SHE CAN
TO MAKE HIM UNCOMFORTABLE
AND LESS LIKELY TO USE PAPER.
Killua: SO SHE STICKS TO ROCK,
ENSURING EITHER A WIN OR A DRAW.
Kurapika: LIKE I SAID,
ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS
IS ACTUALLY A MIND GAME.
Gon: NOW I SEE.
Leorio: EH?
HANG ON.
WE BOTH USED ROCK,
SO THAT WAS A DRAW, WASN'T IT?
Leroute: SO WHAT IF IT WAS?
Leorio: AHA! I KNEW IT!
YOU WERE LYING ABOUT
BEING ABLE TO READ MY MIND!
IF YOU WERE REALLY A PSYCHIC,
THEN YOU WOULD HAVE
BEATEN ME, RIGHT?
( Leroute giggles )
Leorio: WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?
Leroute: I GAVE YOU
THAT TIE ON PURPOSE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
Leorio: QUIT LYING!
Leroute: HAVE YOU
FORGOTTEN ALREADY?
WE'RE TRYING TO STALL YOU HERE
FOR AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
IF I REALLY WANTED TO,
I COULD FORCE A SERIES OF DRAWS
THAT WOULD LAST INDEFINITELY.
BUT WHY?
I'M SURE THAT WOULDN'T BE
HALF AS FUN AS TOYING WITH YOU.
BUT I'LL END IT AFTER THIS.
WELL? WHAT'LL YOU USE NEXT?
COME ON. THINK HARD.
( laughs )
Leorio: DAMN IT! ( groans )
( Leroute thinking )
YES, THAT'S IT.
WORRY. FRET.
Kurapika: WORRYING, FRETTING.
WHENEVER SOMEONE'S CONFIDENCE
IS SHATTERED,
THEY BEGIN TO CRAVE REASSURANCE.
SEE? THAT'S OBVIOUSLY
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO LEORIO.
HE'LL USE THE SAME PLAY
OR SOMETHING STRONGER
TO REGAIN HIS CONFIDENCE.
Killua: I SEE WHAT SHE'S DOING.
SHE'S TRYING TO GET LEORIO
TO CHOOSE EITHER ROCK OR PAPER.
Kurapika: CORRECT. USING PAPER
MEANS SHE'S CERTAIN NOT TO LOSE.
Gon: THEN LEORIO'S
GOTTA STAY ONE STEP AHEAD!
Kurapika: INDEED.
AND IF HE WERE CALMER,
HE MIGHT ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO.
Gon: LEORIO!
Leorio: NOW WHAT?!
Gon: LISTEN! IF YOU WANT TO WIN,
YOU GOTTA PLAY SCISSORS!
Leorio: SCISSORS? WHAT?
( Leroute giggles )
GO AHEAD. TRY.
( Leorio thinking ) BUT IF I DO,
SHE'S JUST GONNA USE ROCK.
NO. SHE'LL GO A STEP FURTHER
AND CHOOSE PAPER.
UNLESS SHE GOES EVEN FURTHER
AND PICKS SCISSORS.
OR SHE MIGHT JUMP AHEAD
AND GO STRAIGHT TO ROCK.
( screams )
WHAT IS HAPPENING?!
‐ Leroute: HERE WE GO!
‐ ( Leorio groans )
Leroute: HERE COMES THE DRAW!
( Leroute laughs )
I WIN! YAAAAY!
( Leorio gasping )
( Leroute laughs )
Gon: AMAZING.
THIS GAME'S REALLY HARD.
Killua: AND NOW
THE SCORE'S TWO‐TWO.
Kurapika: EVEN WORSE,
WE HAVE FAR LESS TIME
NOW THAT WE'VE LOST
THE 50 HOURS HE GAMBLED WITH.
Leorio: SORRY. I THOUGHT
I WAS A ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS PRO.
( Tonpa scoffs )
PRETTY PATHETIC SHOWING.
Leorio: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
YEAH, I GUESS
I CAN'T ARGUE WITH YOU THERE.
Leroute: OKAY, SO HOW MUCH TIME
DO THEY HAVE LEFT?
HOW DID I DO?
( Lippo chuckles )
59 HOURS, 45 MINUTES.
Bendot: NOT BAD.
BY MY CALCULATIONS, THAT MEANS
THEY'VE NOW GOT FEWER THAN
10 HOURS TO REACH THE BOTTOM.
Prisoner: IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW MUCH TIME THEY HAVE.
( all gasp )
Prisoner: IT DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE MY OPPONENT
IS ABOUT TO DIE.
♪♪♪
Leorio: HMM.
( chuckles )
Kurapika: SO THE FINAL ROUND
IS UPON US.
Killua: I GUESS
THAT MEANS I'M UP.
Leorio: HUH? WAIT, KILLUA?!
Killua: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Leorio: DAMN, THIS SUCKS!
I REALLY
NEEDED TO WIN MY ROUND.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
Killua: GON, YOUR BUDDY HERE
IS PISSING ME OFF.
Gon: TAKE IT EASY.
Killua:
DON'T THROW IN THE TOWEL.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THE NEXT CONTEST IS YET.
BUT IF IT'S SOMETHING
LIKE DOING MATH IN YOUR HEAD,
I'M TOTALLY SURRENDERING.
Leorio: HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT!
IF THE NEXT OPPONENT'S
A WEAKLING,
WE MIGHT STILL HAVE A CHANCE!
Bendot: THAT KID'S
THEIR LAST MEMBER.
I DIDN'T THINK
HE'D DRAW THE SHORT STRAW.
Leroute: THAT POOR THING.
HE'S STILL SO YOUNG.
Lippo: I DID EVERYTHING I COULD
TO AVOID USING HIM.
HOWEVER THE HUNTER EXAM
ISN'T THE TIME OR THE PLACE
FOR SHOWING MERCY.
IF HE DIES, WELL, THAT'S FATE.
REMOVING HIS HANDCUFFS.
( prisoners gasping )
( Majitani scoffs )
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS SCARED OF?
Bendot: STOP, YOU IDIOT!
Majitani: HE DOESN'T LOOK
THAT TERRIFYING TO ME.
THAT'S ALL ANCIENT HISTOR‐‐
( prisoners gasp )
( Leorio gasps )
IT'S THAT GUY.
Gon: YOU KNOW HIM?
Leorio: WE SHOULD
JUST TAKE THE LOSS.
KILLUA,
YOU CAN'T FIGHT THIS GUY!
Killua: WHY NOT?
Leorio: JOHNESS THE DISSECTOR,
THE WORST MASS MURDERER
IN ZABAN'S HISTORY.
HE CHOSE HIS VICTIMS AT RANDOM.
IT WAS ALL OVER THE NEWS.
146 PEOPLE,
MEN, WOMEN, YOUNG, OLD,
ALL SLAUGHTERED.
EACH OF THE VICTIMS
HAD ONE THING IN COMMON.
HE MURDERED EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF THEM WITH HIS BARE HANDS.
HIS GRIP WAS INFAMOUS.
THE RAW POWER
IN HIS FINGERS ALONE,
IT WAS UNREAL.
Johness: IT'S BEEN AGES SINCE
I LAST TOUCHED HUMAN FLESH.
Leorio:
HE'S A COMPLETE PSYCHOPATH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT HIM.
THERE'S ALWAYS NEXT YEAR, RIGHT?
HEY! KILLUA!
KILLUA!
WHAT THE HELL?
WASN'T HE LISTENING
TO A WORD I JUST SAID?
Kurapika: LET HIM GO, LEORIO.
HE MIGHT HAVE A PLAN
WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
♪♪♪
Killua: HOW DO YOU
WANNA DO THIS?
Johness: DO THIS?
YOU HAVE THE WRONG IDEA.
SEE, YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE
ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF A ONE‐SIDED MASSACRE.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE EXAM
OR REDUCING MY SENTENCE.
ALL I WANT
IS TO HEAR YOU SCREAM.
Killua: REALLY? FINE.
WE'LL JUST KEEP FIGHTING
UNTIL ONE OF US DIES.
Johness: HUH.
THAT'S RIGHT,
A BATTLE TO THE DEATH.
SOON I'LL TEAR YOUR BODY APART
WITH JUST MY BARE HANDS.
YOU GOT IT?
( heart beats )
( all gasp )
( heart beating )
( Johness gasping )
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY AM I SO COLD?
( heart beating )
THAT'S MINE.
( gasps )
IT BELONGS TO ME.
GIVE IT BACK.
GIVE IT TO ME.
Killua: SO THAT'S
THREE WINS FOR US.
WE MOVE ON, RIGHT?
Bendot: THAT'S RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU GUYS WIN.
Killua: BY THE WAY, YOU MUST BE
ITCHING FOR SOME ACTION.
YOU DIDN'T GET TO FIGHT.
HOW 'BOUT IT? WANNA TAKE ME ON?
Bendot: THANKS, BUT NO, THANKS.
Killua: SUIT YOURSELF.
Leorio: WHOA.
WHO IS THIS KID, ANYWAY?
Gon: THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW.
Leorio: WAIT. KNOW WHAT?
Gon: KILLUA'S FAMILY,
HE SAYS THEY'RE
A BUNCH OF ELITE ASSASSINS.
Leorio: EH?
DID YOU SAY ELITE ASSASSINS?
Killua: I'M BACK.
( Leorio yelps )
Killua: WHAT?
Leorio: OH! JUST...
GOOD WORK OUT THERE.
♪♪♪
Lippo: PLEASE CROSS THE BRIDGE.
ON THE OTHER SIDE,
YOU'LL FIND A SMALL ROOM.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'LL BE SPENDING
THE 50 HOURS YOU GAMBLED AWAY.
Killua: WELL? COME ON.
‐ Gon: MM‐HMM.
‐ Leorio: ALL RIGHT. SURE.
Announcer: GITTARACKUR,
APPLICANT 301,
IS THE SECOND TO PASS.
TIME ELAPSED,
12 HOURS AND 2 MINUTES.
Gittarackur: SOMETHING TOLD ME
YOU'D ALREADY PASSED
THE FINISH LINE.
‐ ( door opens )
‐ ( man panting )
‐ ALL RIGHT!
‐ Announcer: HANZO...
‐ Hanzo: I'M THE FIRST ONE...
‐ Announcer: APPLICANT 294...
Hanzo: TO FINISH! WHAT THE?
Announcer:
...12 HOURS, 3 MINUTES.
Hanzo: OHH! I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
I CAME IN THIRD PLACE.
Leorio: AH, COME ON.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'VE JUST GOTTA
SIT AROUND HERE FOR 50 HOURS.
( scoffs )
‐ Kurapika: KILLUA...
‐ Killua: HUH?
Kurapika: CAN YOU TELL ME
HOW THAT TECHNIQUE WORKS?
Killua: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
TECHNIQUE?
Kurapika: THE ONE THAT YOU USED
TO INSTANTLY REMOVE HIS HEART.
Killua: OH, THAT ONE.
WELL, IT WASN'T
A TECHNIQUE, REALLY.
I JUST RIPPED IT OUT.
Kurapika: THAT'S ALL?
Killua: TO BE HONEST,
I DID MANIPULATE MY BODY SOME.
MADE IT A LOT EASIER.
Leorio: WHOA! YOUR NAILS!
Gon: OH, WOW!
Killua: MASS MURDERERS TALK BIG,
BUT THEY'RE STILL JUST AMATEURS.
I USED TO BE A PROFESSIONAL.
BUT MY OLD MAN
WOULD HAVE DONE A LOT BETTER.
WHEN HE TAKES A HEART,
THERE'S NOT EVEN
A DROP OF BLOOD.
( Leorio chuckles )
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
THANKS, KID.
( Kurapika thinking )
AT LEAST HE'S ON OUR SIDE.
Killua: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WE'VE GOT MORE THAN TWO DAYS.
Gon: SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
Killua: GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
FIRST, LET'S SEARCH THE ROOM
AND SEE IF THERE'S
ANYTHING TO PLAY WITH.
Gon: OKAY!
Leorio: KIDS,
NOT A CARE IN THE WORLD, HUH?
Tonpa: TIME TO TAKE A LOAD OFF.
Narrator: GON'S TEAM OF FIVE
PASSED THE TRIAL
WITH THREE WINS AND TWO LOSSES,
BUT NOW MUST SPEND
THEIR 50‐HOUR PENALTY HERE.
UNFORTUNATELY
THEY'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
( timer beeps )
♪♪♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"FINAL TEST OF RESOLVE."
YOU HAVE TO THINK LIKE A FISH.
Killua: SERIOUSLY?
Gon: YEP.
♪♪♪