Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS OFF
YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( aura whooshing )
( Zushi gasps )
MASTER?
Wing: MASTER...
IT WAS NEVER
MY INTENTION, BUT...
HAVE I‐‐
HAVE I AWOKEN
A TERRIBLE MONSTER?
♪
Narrator: ONE MONTH HAS PASSED
SINCE GON WAS INJURED
IN HIS FIGHT WITH GIDO.
IN HEAVENS ARENA,
ALL EYES ARE FOCUSED
ON A CERTAIN UPCOMING MATCH.
( Gon grunting )
Killua: HEY, GON!
I GOT SOMETHING‐‐( gasps )
Gon: OH, KILLUA! WHAT'S UP?
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT GOING OUT TO LOOK FOR YOU.
Killua: WHOA!
YOU'RE BETTER ALREADY?
Gon: YEAH!
CHECK IT OUT! I'M ALL GOOD!
Killua: YEAH, OKAY. I GET IT.
THOSE INJURIES SHOULD HAVE
KEPT HIM OUT OF COMMISSION
FOR FOUR MONTHS,
BUT HE RECOVERED IN ONE!
WHAT IS YOUR BODY
MADE OF, ANYWAY?
Gon: I REALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO ANSWER THAT.
‐ Killua: YOU'RE SUCH A WEIRDO.
‐ ( Gon groans )
SO WEREN'T YOU GONNA
SAY SOMETHING EARLIER?
Killua: OH. THAT'S RIGHT.
Gon: TICKETS, HUH?
BUT THESE AREN'T
JUST ANY TICKETS.
THEY'RE FOR HISOKA'S FIGHT.
( Gon gasps )
♪
Killua:
AS A 200th‐FLOOR‐LEVEL FIGHTER,
I GOT DIBS ON TICKETS.
HISOKA'S MATCH IS REAL POPULAR.
I EVEN SAW SCALPERS.
Gon: MM.
Killua: SO I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO GATHER UP INFORMATION.
TURNS OUT
HISOKA'S THE REAL DEAL.
HE HAS AN EIGHT‐AND‐THREE RECORD
WITH SIX K. O. s,
ALL OF WHICH ENDED IN DEATH.
Gon: YEAH, BUT HE'S
LOST THREE MATCHES.
Killua: HIS THREE LOSSES
WERE FORFEITS.
Gon: FORFEITS? REALLY?
Killua: WELL, HE REACHED
THE REGISTRATION DEADLINE,
SO HE SIGNED UP FOR A FIGHT,
THEN DIDN'T SHOW.
Gon: OKAY. WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Killua: THAT WHEN HISOKA
DOES COMPETE, HE NEVER LOSES.
Gon: MM. GUESS SO.
Killua: AND OUT
OF ALL THE TIMES HE'S FOUGHT,
HE'S ONLY GIVEN UP
A TOTAL OF FOUR POINTS.
ONE OF 'EM WAS A KNOCKDOWN,
AND THREE WERE CLEAN HITS,
WHICH MEANS
HE'S GOTTA BE AS STRONG
AS ANY OF THE FLOOR MASTERS.
Gon: WOW.
THAT'S PRETTY INTIMIDATING.
( chuckling )
Killua: DAMN IT.
YOU SURE DON'T LOOK
VERY INTIMIDATED TO ME.
SO HIS OPPONENT
IS SOME GUY NAMED KASTRO.
TWO YEARS AGO, HE MANAGED TO GET
THE ONLY KNOCKDOWN EVER
AGAINST HISOKA.
OF THE FOUR POINTS
HISOKA HAS EVER GIVEN UP
TO ANOTHER FIGHTER,
THIS KASTRO GUY IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THREE OF 'EM.
Gon: THREE POINTS
AGAINST HISOKA?
Killua: GUESS YOU COULD SAY
THEY'VE GOT HISTORY.
THEY BOTH REGISTERED
FOR THE SAME DAY
SO THEY COULD FIGHT EACH OTHER.
Gon: HUH.
Killua: THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
YOU'LL GET TO ANALYZE
HISOKA'S FIGHTING STYLE.
MAYBE HE'LL EVEN GO ALL‐OUT.
Gon: UH...
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS OKAY?
I MADE THAT PROMISE
TO MR. WING.
Wing: I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO PARTICIPATE
IN ANY MATCHES FOR TWO MONTHS,
NOR WILL I ALLOW THE STUDY OF
OR TRAINING IN THE USE OF NEN.
Killua: ARE YOU KIDDING?
OF COURSE IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA BE
WATCHING A MATCH.
( both gasp )
Wing: NOT OKAY.
VIEWING A MATCH COUNTS
AS STUDYING THE USE OF NEN.
Gon: UH, MR. WING.
Killua: COME ON.
DON'T SCARE US LIKE THAT.
( Wing gasps )
GON...
HAS YOUR ARM HEALED UP ALREADY?
Gon: UH, YES, SIR.
IT'S ALL BETTER NOW
Wing: WHAT INCREDIBLE
REGENERATION.
Killua: CAN'T HE WATCH THE MATCH
SINCE HE RECOVERED
AND EVERYTHING?
Wing: OH, NO. WHEN I TOLD GON
HE HAD TO WAIT TWO MONTHS,
I MEANT TWO MONTHS.
( Killua sighs )
Wing: NOW, GON,
YOU STILL HAVE ANOTHER MONTH.
YOU ARE TO CONTINUE
TO PRACTICE TEN
AND RECOVER FROM YOUR INJURIES.
Gon: UM, RIGHT, MR. WING.
I UNDERSTAND.
Wing: WELL, THAT'S ALL, THEN.
Zushi: OSU! TAKE CARE!
Killua: OKAY. WELL, THAT'S IT.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO WATCH A RECORDING.
I'LL GO SEE IT IN PERSON.
( Gon grunts )
Wing: THEY'VE KEPT
THEIR PROMISE EVERY DAY
AND HAVE ONLY PERFORMED TEN.
I CAN TELL FROM THE FAINT AURA
THAT CONSTANTLY SURROUNDS THEM
UNDER NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES.
THEIR AURA FLOWS LIKE A GREAT,
BUT TRANQUIL RIVER.
Zushi: MASTER WING?
Wing: EH?
Zushi: OH, NEVER MIND.
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY, SIR.
Wing: THIS WON'T DO.
IT SEEMS I'M THE ONE
WHO'S LOSING MY CALM.
♪
Cocco: HELLO!
I'M YOUR ANNOUNCER, COCCO!
TODAY IN HEAVENS ARENA,
WE HAVE KASTRO VERSUS HISOKA,
THE MATCH YOU'VE ALL
BEEN WAITING FOR!
JUST TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS CROWD, FOLKS!
ISN'T IT AMAZING?
THE MATCH WON'T GET STARTED
FOR ANOTHER HOUR,
BUT THE ARENA IS
ALREADY PACKED!
Wing: THIS IS A PROMISE THREAD,
ITS PURPOSE, TO REMIND YOU
OF THE PROMISE YOU MADE.
( Gon groans )
♪
Cocco: HISOKA TOOK HOME THE WIN
WHEN THEY FACED EACH OTHER
TWO YEARS AGO.
THE AUDIENCE HERE
IS OBVIOUSLY FIRED UP
TO SEE
THIS FATED REMATCH UNFOLD,
AS KASTRO LOOKS TO TAKE
HIS LONG‐AWAITED REVENGE!
HIS RECORD IS EIGHT WINS
AND THREE LOSSES,
BUT ONLY BECAUSE
HE FAILED TO SHOW.
HISOKA THE MAGICIAN
IS THE GRIM REAPER
WHO'S PRONE TO TAKING DAYS OFF.
WITH NINE WINS
AFTER HIS LOSS TO HISOKA,
FOR A NINE‐ONE RECORD,
ONLY ONE AWAY FROM CHALLENGING
THE FLOOR MASTERS, IS KASTRO!
HE'S VOWED TO GET PAYBACK,
BUT WILL HE SUCCEED?!
GET READY FOR AN EPIC BATTLE
BETWEEN THE TWO FIGHTERS CLOSEST
TO REACHING THE FLOOR MASTERS!
Killua: WOW. I FIGURED
HE'D BE ALL BIG AND MUSCLEY.
Cocco: NEXT UP, WE HAVE
AN INTERVIEW WITH KASTRO
FROM A FEW DAYS AGO.
Kastro: I WOULDN'T FIGHT
IF I DIDN'T EXPECT TO WIN.
YOU'LL SEE
THAT IN THE LAST TWO YEARS,
I'VE BECOME A DIFFERENT PERSON.
Killua: HUH. SOUNDS CONFIDENT.
LET'S SEE IF HE'S
GOT WHAT IT TAKES
TO BACK THAT CONFIDENCE UP.
♪
Worker: EH?
HUH?
EH? HUH?
WHAT THE...
( Killua gasps )
THERE HE IS.
Kastro: MAY I HELP YOU?
Killua: WHAT?
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HE WAS SITTING
ON THAT COUCH JUST A SECOND AGO.
WHEN DID HE MOVE?
DID HE OPEN THE DOOR
AND SLIP AROUND BEHIND ME,
ALL WITHOUT ME NOTICING?
NO! THERE'S NO WAY.
I NEVER TOOK MY EYES
OFF THE DOOR
UNTIL AFTER I HEARD HIM TALK.
HE NEVER HAD THE CHANCE.
SO HOW?
OH! WELL, I‐‐
I WAS JUST HOPING
FOR AN AUTOGRAPH.
Kastro: FROM ME?
WELL, THAT IS QUITE AN HONOR...
KILLUA.
( Killua gasps )
Kastro: I TRY TO KEEP TABS
ON ALL MY RIVALS
ON THE 200th FLOOR.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ISN'T GON WITH YOU TODAY?
Killua: WOW, I GUESS YOU
REALLY DO KNOW EVERYTHING, HUH?
Kastro: SO, ARE YOU HERE
TO SCOUT OUT OPPONENTS?
Killua: NO, NOT REALLY.
I JUST WANTED TO GET A LOOK
AT YOU UP CLOSE IS ALL.
WELL, THEN, NOW THAT YOU HAVE,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
Killua: YOU'RE
PRETTY DAMN IMPRESSIVE.
Kastro: THANK YOU.
AND YOUR ZETSU WAS QUITE
IMPRESSIVE AS WELL, KILLUA.
HOWEVER, YOU MADE A MISTAKE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN WISER
TO CONCEAL YOUR PRESENCE HERE.
AURA OF YOUR CALIBER
SUDDENLY DISAPPEARING
WOULD BE ENOUGH
TO GIVE ANYONE PAUSE.
Killua: SO YOU'VE
BEEN KEEPING TABS ON ME
EVER SINCE
I GOT ONTO THIS FLOOR?
Kastro: PRETTY MUCH.
Killua: WELL,
THEN I WANT TO KNOW.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT JUST NOW?
Kastro: UNFORTUNATELY
I CANNOT TELL YOU THAT.
AFTER ALL, I MIGHT HAVE
TO FIGHT YOU ONE OF THESE DAYS.
Killua: DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T REALLY PLAN
ON FIGHTING HERE ANYMORE.
Kastro: IS THAT SO?
BECAUSE THAT ISN'T
WHAT YOUR AURA SAYS.
( laughs )
OH, I'M ONLY JOKING.
I'LL SHOW YOU MY ANSWER
IN THE MATCH.
I'LL BE WAITING
AT THE BATTLE OLYMPIA.
I'M CERTAIN YOU CAN GET THERE.
Killua: I SAID
I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT, OKAY?!
( scoffs )
♪
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: IT'S FINALLY TIME!
THE LONG‐AWAITED REMATCH
BETWEEN HISOKA AND KASTRO
HAS ARRIVED!
I'M GRATEFUL, HISOKA.
IF NOT FOR YOUR INITIATION,
CHANCES ARE THAT I NEVER
WOULD HAVE GOTTEN THIS STRONG.
( Hisoka chuckles )
WHO DID YOU SAY GOT STRONG?
Kastro: JUST SO YOU'RE AWARE,
IN THE NINE MATCHES THAT I'VE
HAD SINCE MY LOSS TO YOU,
I'VE NEVER ONCE USED
MY FULL POWER.
EVERY ONE OF THEM WAS
A WARM‐UP TO DEFEATING YOU.
Referee: BEGIN!
Kastro: HERE I COME!
( growls )
( Hisoka grunts )
( Killua gasps )
Cocco: THAT WAS A CLEAN HIT!
KASTRO HAS LANDED
THE FIRST STRIKE OF THE MATCH!
Hisoka: HMM.
Killua: WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
Kastro: GET SERIOUS, HISOKA.
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: KASTRO HAS LANDED
THE FIRST STRIKE!
HISOKA HAS SURRENDERED
THE FIRST POINT
AFTER FAILING TO EVADE
KASTRO'S LIGHT‐SPEED CHOP!
Killua: WAS THAT
AN OPTICAL ILLUSION?
Kastro: I'M NOT THE PERSON
I WAS TWO YEARS AGO.
I WON'T GO SO EASILY NEXT TIME.
Hisoka: I THINK I'LL DECIDE
WHEN I GET SERIOUS,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
Kastro: THEN SO BE IT,
BUT I STRONGLY RECOMMEND
THAT YOU DECIDE QUICKLY.
♪
Hisoka: EH? ( grunts )
( crowd gasps )
( Killua gasps )
AGAIN? I WAS SURE
HE DODGED THAT ONE, TOO.
Kastro: ARE YOU
JUST GOING TO RUN,
OR ARE YOU GOING TO FIGHT ME?
( Hisoka groans )
THAT'S A CLEAN HIT
AND A KNOCKDOWN!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: WHAT A SURPRISE, FOLKS.
I CAN HARDLY BELIEVE IT!
KASTRO HAS BEEN KNOCKING
HIS OPPONENT AROUND
LIKE A RAG DOLL!
THE SCORE IS NOW FOUR‐ZERO,
BUT WHAT DID I JUST SEE?
WAS THAT MY IMAGINATION?
Kastro: SO YOU STILL
WON'T CHANGE YOUR MIND?
IS IT REALLY PREFERABLE TO YOU
TO DIE IN IGNORANCE?
SEEMS SO.
Referee: C‐CAN YOU STILL FIGHT?
( Hisoka chuckles )
( referee gasps )
♪
Hisoka: AM I SEEING THINGS?
BECAUSE IT LOOKED TO ME
LIKE YOU JUST VANISHED.
Cocco: THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS!
HE VANISHED!
THAT'S WHAT I SAW, TOO!
Hisoka: NO. VANISHED IS CLOSE,
BUT IT'S NOT QUITE
THE RIGHT WORD.
YOU WERE RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME
PREPARING TO DEAL A KICK,
AND THEN SUDDENLY,
YOU WERE BEHIND ME.
I'D HAVE TO SAY
THAT COMES THE CLOSEST
TO DESCRIBING WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT SOMETHING
STILL FEELS WRONG,
OUT OF PLACE. YES.
I CAN'T HELP BUT FEEL
AS IF I'M MISSING
SOMETHING VERY BASIC HERE.
Kastro: THIS IS FUTILE.
YOU CAN'T SOLVE ANYTHING IF YOU
KEEP RUNNING AWAY FROM ME.
IN ANY CASE, I'M DONE WAITING.
I'LL TAKE YOUR ARM
WITH MY NEXT STRIKE.
IF YOU INSIST
ON REMAINING POMPOUS,
BE MY GUEST.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT YOU WEREN'T MEANT
FOR ANYTHING MORE.
( exhaling )
♪
Man: THAT'S THE TIGER BITE FIST!
Man #2: KASTRO'S
GETTING SERIOUS!
Killua: TIGER BITE FIST?
MASTERS CAN RIP
WHOLE TREES IN HALF
WITH THEIR HANDS
USING THAT TECHNIQUE.
MEANWHILE, HISOKA STILL HASN'T
FIGURED OUT KASTRO'S ABILITY.
THEN AGAIN, NEITHER HAVE I.
AT THIS RATE,
HISOKA'S DEAD MEAT!
Kastro: HERE I COME!
( Killua gasps )
‐ ( Kastro gasps )
‐ Hisoka: TAKE IT ALREADY.
Kastro: HAH! IS THIS A TRAP
OR JUST FOOLISH COMPLACENCY?
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER,
YOUR ARM IS MINE!
THIS ONE, THAT IS.
‐ Man #3: WHAT THE...
‐ Man #4: HISOKA'S ARM IS...
Cocco: HISOKA'S RIGHT ARM
HAS BEEN COMPLETELY SEVERED!
( crowd gasping, screaming )
Kastro: IF YOU STILL THINK
YOU CAN GET YOUR WAY,
YOU ARE SORELY MISTAKEN.
Hisoka: THIS IS ALL
WITHIN EXPECTATIONS.
Kastro: THE HELL, IT IS!
Cocco: WOW.
HAVE WE EVER SEEN HISOKA
IN SUCH A PERILOUS SITUATION
BEFORE, FOLKS?
HE'S TAKEN ON
SOME SERIOUS DAMAGE.
( Hisoka chuckles )
YES, I SEE.
NOW I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOUR ABILITY IS.
YOU CAN CREATE A DOUBLE, RIGHT?
Kastro: VERY IMPRESSIVE.
YOU FINALLY GOT IT.
Killua: A DOUBLE?
WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
♪
( crowd gasping )
Killua: SO IT WASN'T
AN OPTICAL ILLUSION AFTER ALL.
WHEN KASTRO ATTACKED,
IT LOOKED LIKE THERE WAS
ANOTHER KASTRO
SUPERIMPOSED ON TOP OF HIM!
Cocco: WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS GOING ON HERE?!
AM I SEEING THINGS, OR HAS
KASTRO REALLY SPLIT IN TWO?
DID HE JUST CLONE HIMSELF?
KASTRO WENT FROM DISAPPEARING
TO MULTIPLYING!
DID HE HAVE A TWIN ALL ALONG?
Hisoka: I WONDER IF THIS IS
WHAT THEY CALL A DOPPELGANGER.
Kastros: INDEED IT IS.
Zushi: DID HE SAY,
"A DOPPELGANGER"?
Wing: YES.
Zushi: BUT, MASTER,
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT.
IT REFERS TO A DOUBLE,
OR IN OTHER WORDS,
AN ADDITIONAL YOU.
WHEN YOU SPOT SOMEONE
WHO CLOSELY RESEMBLES YOU,
THAT IS CALLED A DOPPELGANGER.
Zushi: I'M SORRY, MASTER.
I STILL DON'T GET IT.
Wing: WHENEVER YOU
ENCOUNTER YOUR DOPPELGANGER,
YOU BEGIN TO EXPERIENCE
HEADACHES AND FATIGUE,
BOTH OF WHICH CONTINUE
UNTIL YOUR DOUBLE VANISHES.
SOME PEOPLE BELIEVE
THAT THE DOUBLE
ACTUALLY SIPHONS ENERGY
AWAY FROM THE ORIGINAL,
PROMPTING
THESE PHYSICAL REACTIONS.
Zushi: BUT KASTRO ISN'T
SUFFERING AT ALL RIGHT NOW.
HE'S WAY TOO STRONG FOR THAT.
Wing: THAT'S ONLY
A STORY, ZUSHI.
IT'S CLEAR HE MASTERED THIS
THROUGH INTENSE TRAINING.
Hisoka: I DID AS YOU ADVISED
AND OBSERVED YOU
WITHOUT TRYING TO EVADE.
AND IT TURNS OUT
"VANISHED" WAS THE RIGHT WORD
FOR WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN DOING ALL ALONG.
BUT THEN, WHY COULDN'T I
SHAKE THE FEELING
THAT THERE WAS
SOMETHING MISSING BEFORE?
YOU VANISHED, YES,
BUT I STILL FELT
YOUR PRESENCE BY MY SIDE.
IN FACT,
JUST BEFORE YOU VANISHED,
I FELT EVEN MORE OF YOU.
BEFORE YOU DISAPPEAR,
YOU DUPLICATE YOURSELF.
( Kastros chuckle )
I'M IMPRESSED THAT YOU
MANAGED TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
USING NEN, I WAS ABLE TO
SUCCESSFULLY CREATE A DOUBLE.
AND WHILE MY DOUBLE
GOES ON THE ATTACK FOR ME,
I LURK SAFELY IN THE SHADOWS.
AS SOON AS YOU REACT...
( one only ) I RELEASE MY DOUBLE
AND ATTACK MYSELF.
Killua: SO THAT'S WHY
HE WEARS THOSE CLOTHES.
THE FLUTTERING HELPS
CREATE BLIND SPOTS.
THAT'D BE HARD
TO FIGURE OUT DURING COMBAT,
EVEN FOR A SKILLED NEN USER.
♪
Kastro: YOU SEE...
MY DOUBLE IS NO MERE ILLUSION.
IT'S REAL, JUST AS REAL
AS I AM UNTIL I MAKE IT VANISH.
YOU MUST KNOW THIS.
YOU FELT IT
STRIKE AGAINST YOU.
TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO FACE
TWO OF ME AT ONCE!
NOW BEHOLD THE CULMINATION
OF MY MASTERY OF NEN,
THE TRUE TIGER BITE FIST!
( Hisoka chuckles )
Cocco: INCREDIBLE!
WE HAVE AN UPSET IN THE MAKING!
HISOKA WON TWO YEARS AGO,
BUT NOW HE'S IN BIG TROUBLE!
IS KASTRO ABOUT TO AVENGE
HIS ONLY PREVIOUS DEFEAT?!
Kastro: AND NOW I WILL SEVER
YOUR LEFT ARM, IF ONLY TO SEE
IF YOU CAN MAINTAIN
YOUR APPEARANCE OF DISINTEREST.
( Hisoka chuckles )
WELL, LET'S FIND OUT.
( slurps )
MAYBE I FEEL
MORE UP TO IT NOW.
♪
Narrator: KASTRO, THE FEARSOME
USER OF CONJURED DOUBLES,
AND HISOKA, THE MAGICIAN,
THE END OF THEIR BATTLE
WILL BE AS INCREDIBLE
AS THE MATCH ITSELF,
THOUGH GON KNOWS
NOTHING OF THIS YET.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE
INTRODUCING RIEHLVELT,
WHO USES ACCUMULATED AURA
TO MOVE HIS WHEELCHAIR AROUND.
Killua: AND HE FIGHTS
WITH TWO WHIPS.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THERE'S PROBABLY A SECRET THERE.
Gon: WHIP, WHIP.
♪
NEXT TIME, "A SURPRISING WIN."
Killua: HEY, GON.
IF YOU COULD CLONE YOURSELF,
‐ WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
‐ Gon: PLAY ROCK‐PAPER‐SCISSORS!
Killua: WOULDN'T YOU
JUST TIE EVERY TIME?