( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( waves crashing )
( seabirds calling )
♪
Mito: "DEAR AUNT MITO
AND GRANDMA, HOW ARE YOU?
"I'M DOING GREAT, AS USUAL.
"THE HUNTER EXAM
IS FINALLY OVER NOW,
AND TURNS OUT
I ACTUALLY PASSED."
( laughs )
"BUT WHILE I PASSED
AND EVERYTHING,
I CAN'T SAY THAT I'M
ALL THAT HAPPY ABOUT IT..."
Gon: ...'CAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE FINAL PHASE.
Hanzo: I SEE
YOU'RE NOT GETTING IT,
SO I'LL TRY AGAIN.
DIE, AND YOU'LL NEVER
GET ANOTHER CHANCE.
IF I KILL YOU
RIGHT HERE AND NOW,
I ONLY NEED TO COME BACK AND
TAKE THE EXAM AGAIN NEXT YEAR.
WE ARE NOT ON EQUAL FOOTING!
IS YOUR PRIDE
TRULY ALL THAT YOU CARE ABOUT?!
EVEN MORE THAN YOUR LIFE?!
IS IT WORTH DYING FOR?!
Gon: I'M GONNA GO SEE MY DAD.
‐ ( Kurapika and Leorio gasp )
‐ Gon: SEE, MY DAD IS A HUNTER,
SO I'M GONNA BECOME A HUNTER
EXACTLY LIKE HE IS,
AND THEN I'LL
BE ABLE TO MEET HIM.
I KNOW I'LL FIND HIM SOMEDAY...
BUT I FEEL LIKE
IF I SURRENDER NOW,
I'M NEVER GONNA FIND HIM...
♪
SO I WON'T GIVE UP.
Hanzo: SURRENDER,
OR YOU WILL DIE.
( thinking ) SO LOGIC
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
FINE. YOU WIN. I GIVE UP, OKAY?
Gon: NO FAIR!
WE BOTH HAVE TO COME UP
WITH SOME WAY
THAT WE CAN HAVE A PROPER MATCH!
Hanzo: MORON!
Gon: I KIND OF GOT KNOCKED OUT,
SO I DON'T REALLY
REMEMBER ANYTHING AFTER THAT,
BUT MR. SATOTZ TOLD ME
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
Masta: BEGIN!
Illumi: IT'S BEEN A WHILE, KIL.
( rattles )
( Killua gasping )
BIG BROTHER.
( somber chorus singing )
Illumi: YOU'RE NOT CUT OUT
TO BE A HUNTER.
( Killua gasps )
Illumi: YOU WERE BORN
FOR ONE PURPOSE,
TO BE AN ASSASSIN.
WHAT DO YOU IMAGINE
THAT YOU WOULD ACCOMPLISH
BY BECOMING A HUNTER?
Killua: IT'S TRUE. I DON'T
REALLY WANT TO BE A HUNTER.
BUT EVERYONE WANTS SOMETHING,
EVEN ME.
Illumi: YOU DON'T.
Killua: WRONG!
THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I REALLY WANT!
Illumi: HMM.
ENLIGHTEN ME.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?
Killua: I...
WANT TO BE...
FRIENDS WITH GON.
I‐I'M JUST SO SICK
OF KILLING PEOPLE.
I WANT TO BE FRIENDS WITH GON,
JUST HAVE FUN.
Illumi: IMPOSSIBLE.
( Killua gasps )
Illumi: YOU ARE INCAPABLE
OF FRIENDSHIP.
BECAUSE YOU ARE,
BY NATURE, A MURDERER.
MOVE ONE MORE INCH, AND I'LL
ASSUME THE FIGHT HAS BEGUN.
THE SAME GOES FOR IF OUR BODIES
COME IN CONTACT WITH EACH OTHER.
THE FIGHT STARTS.
IF YOU DECIDE
THAT YOU WON'T FIGHT ME,
YOUR DEAR GON
WILL CERTAINLY DIE.
( Killua gasping )
YOU WIN, ILLUMI.
I ADMIT DEFEAT.
Gon: I THINK THAT'S
WHEN KILLUA HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
♪
( door bangs open )
APOLOGIZE TO KILLUA!
Illumi: SORRY? BUT WHAT FOR?
Gon: YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU DID WRONG?
( Hunters gasp )
Gon: DON'T EVEN
BOTHER APOLOGIZING.
JUST TAKE ME TO SEE KILLUA.
Illumi: AND WHAT WILL YOU DO?
Gon: IT'S OBVIOUS.
I'LL BRING HIM BACK.
AND AFTER THAT,
KURAPIKA, LEORIO, AND I
MADE OUR WAY
TO KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
THAT'S WHERE KILLUA LIVES!
Zebro: THIS GATE IS OFFICIALLY
KNOWN AS THE TESTING GATE,
BECAUSE ANYONE WHO'S
NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO OPEN IT...
HUHH!
...IS CONSIDERED UNWORTHY
OF ENTERING THE ZOLDYCK ESTATE.
( grunts )
( all gasp )
Zebro: LISTEN TO ME, GON.
YOU THREE CAN TRY
TO OPEN THE DOOR TOGETHER.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH TEAMWORK.
( both gasp )
Zebro: AND WITH
A LITTLE BIT OF TRAINING,
IT SHOULD BE POSSIBLE.
( Kurapika and Leorio grunt )
Leorio: LET'S DO THIS, KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: WELL? LET'S PUSH.
Leorio: HERE GOES.
Kurapika: READY.
Leorio: GET SET.
Gon: GO!
( all grunting )
( Gon gasps )
OW.
( both panting )
Gon: IT OPENED.
Leorio: HELL, YEAH!
Kurapika: WE REALLY DID IT, GON!
Gon: UH‐HUH!
♪
Canary: PLEASE LEAVE NOW.
YOU'RE TRESPASSING
ON PRIVATE PROPERTY.
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO PASS
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
TAKE ONE STEP PAST IT,
AND I WILL REMOVE YOU
BY FORCE IF NECESSARY.
Gon: WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I JUST CAME HERE
TO SEE MY FRIEND.
THE ONLY REASON I'M HERE
IS TO SEE KILLUA!
SO WHY ARE YOU MAKING ME
GO THROUGH ALL OF THIS?!
( birds squawking )
I CAN TELL
YOU'RE DIFFERENT FROM MIKE.
YOU MAY BE TRYING
TO COVER UP YOUR FEELINGS,
BUT YOU STILL HAVE A HEART.
WHEN I MENTIONED KILLUA'S NAME,
YOUR EYES SOFTENED
JUST FOR A MOMENT.
( Canary shudders )
PLEASE...
( crying )
HELP HIM.
HELP MASTER KI‐‐
( all gasp )
Mrs. Zoldyck:
AND YOU MUST BE GON.
ILLUMI TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
KILLUA IS AWARE THAT YOU'VE BEEN
ON THE PREMISES
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
Gon: WHY CAN'T KILLUA
COME TO SEE US? WHERE IS HE?
Mrs. Zoldyck:
IN SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
Leorio: WAIT. WHAT?
‐ ( whir )
‐ Mrs. Zoldyck: AND THEN,
BECAUSE HE REGRETTED
WHAT HE HAD DONE,
OUR KILLUA RETURNED TO US
AND ENTERED SOLITARY CONFINEMENT
VOLUNTARILY.
Canary: I WILL...
TAKE YOU
TO THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
THERE'S A PHONE THAT CONNECTS
DIRECTLY TO THE MANSION.
IF MASTER ZENO ANSWERS IT,
YOU MIGHT‐‐
Gotoh: SO WHICH HAND?
I'VE KNOWN MASTER KILLUA
HIS ENTIRE LIFE,
AND I CARE FOR HIM
AS I WOULD MY OWN SON.
IN ALL HONESTY, I DESPISE YOU
FOR ATTEMPTING TO TAKE HIM AWAY.
( all gasp )
♪
Gotoh: IF YOU ANSWER
INCORRECTLY, YOU ARE OUT.
SHOULD YOU ALL BE DISQUALIFIED,
WHICH IS QUITE POSSIBLE,
THEN I SHALL TELL MASTER KILLUA
THAT YOU LEFT
AND THAT HE WILL NEVER
SEE ANY OF YOU AGAIN.
‐ HERE WE GO.
‐ Gon: WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
Gotoh: WHAT IS IT?
IF YOU'RE TRYING TO BUY TIME,
I WILL KILL ONE OF YOU.
( Kurapika thinking ) HE CUT
HIMSELF TO REDUCE THE SWELLING.
Gon: THERE. MUCH BETTER.
I CAN SEE NOW.
OKAY, I'M READY!
( Kurapika and Leorio gasp )
Gotoh: NOW,
WHICH ONE OF US HAS IT?
( Gon chuckles )
THAT GUY, RIGHT BEHIND ME.
‐ ( applause )
‐ SPLENDID. WELL DONE.
Killua: GOTOH! IS GON HERE YET?
‐ Gon: KILLUA!
‐ Killua: YOU WERE ALREADY HERE?
GON!
AND THIS GUY, UM...
KURAPIKA?
Kurapika: YOU REMEMBERED.
Killua: REOLIO!
Leorio: IT'S LEORIO!
Killua: IT'S BEEN SO LONG,
BUT YOU MADE IT.
WOW. YOUR FACE IS A MESS.
( Gon laughs )
BACK AT YA!
( boys laugh )
Gon: AND JUST LIKE THAT,
WE MANAGED TO RESCUE KILLUA.
♪
Mito: "I KNOW THAT I
SHOULD BE HAPPY RIGHT NOW,
"BUT I STILL HAVE
SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS
THAT I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF,
AUNT MITO."
♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED
IN THE FOURTH PHASE OF THE EXAM.
♪
Lippo: TO BEGIN WITH,
I WILL NEED EACH OF YOU
TO DRAW LOTS NOW.
( applicants murmur )
Geretta: REALLY?
Pokkle: DRAW LOTS FOR WHAT?
WHAT'LL THAT DECIDE?
( Lippo chuckles )
WHO YOU HUNT AND WHO HUNTS YOU.
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
COLLECTING THE I. D. BADGE
OF YOUR SPECIFIED TARGET
WILL EARN YOU THREE POINTS.
UNDERSTAND?
YOUR OWN BADGE
IS ALSO WORTH THREE POINTS,
AND ALL THE OTHER BADGES
ARE WORTH ONE POINT.
IN ORDER TO MOVE ON
TO THE FINAL PHASE,
YOU WILL HAVE TO COLLECT
SIX POINTS,
SO DURING YOUR TIME
THERE ON ZEVIL ISLAND,
GATHER ENOUGH BADGES
TO COLLECT SIX POINTS,
OR FAIL THE EXAM.
ONLY THOSE WHO DO
WILL CLEAR THE FOURTH PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
Killua: SO, UH, WHO DID YOU GET?
YOU WANNA SHOW OUR NUMBERS
AT THE SAME TIME?
Gon: OKAY.
Both: READY, AND...
( Killua gasps )
NUMBER 44 IS...
( Hisoka slurps )
Gon: REALLY?
IF I HAD TO FIGHT
WITH HISOKA ONE‐ON‐ONE,
I WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM,
BUT IF ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS JUST STEAL HIS BADGE,
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK I MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE A REAL SHOT.
Killua: YEAH.
Gon: THE WAY IT IS NOW,
WELL, AT LEAST
I'VE GOT A CHANCE.
AND TO BE HONEST,
IT DOES SCARE ME A LITTLE BIT,
BUT I THINK IT'S WORTH IT.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
NOW!
( bird chirps )
I DID IT!
I FIGURED IT OUT!
I'VE JUST GOTTA GO
FOR THE TARGET
THE MOMENT
IT GOES FOR ITS PREY!
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: THERE.
I'VE ONLY GOT ABOUT A MINUTE
OR SO BEFORE HISOKA SPOTS HIM.
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
THEIR PATHS ARE GONNA CROSS.
GOT IT!
GOTTA HURRY.
HISOKA WILL ATTACK
THE SECOND HE NOTICES THAT GUY.
IF I WANNA STEAL HIS BADGE,
THIS IS IT.
IT'S THE LAST CHANCE
I'M GONNA GET.
♪
( panting )
( singing in Japanese )
I HAVE TO STAY HIDDEN.
I CAN'T LET HIM SENSE ME.
FOCUS.
♪
HERE HE COMES.
Agon: HISOKA. DAMN IT.
BRING IT ON!
♪
( Hisoka screeches )
‐ ( gasps )
‐ ( Gon grunts )
♪
Gon: I DID IT.
I TOOK HISOKA'S BADGE FROM HIM.
( gasping )
Geretta: ABOUT 7,000.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT NUMBER REPRESENTS?
THAT IS THE NUMBER OF CHANCES
I HAD TO KILL YOU.
( Gon gasping )
Geretta: IT'S ALSO
ABOUT THE NUMBER OF TIMES
THAT YOU CAST YOUR FISHING ROD
WHILE YOU WERE TRAINING.
IN THE FUTURE,
REMEMBER TO WATCH YOUR BACK.
SO LONG.
Gon: DAMN IT.
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: YOU SURPRISE ME.
YOU HID YOUR PRESENCE FROM ME
WHILE YOU WERE WAITING
FOR YOUR CHANCE TO STRIKE,
BIDING YOUR TIME
UNTIL THE VERY MOMENT
THAT I ATTACKED SOMEONE ELSE.
DID YOU LEARN HOW TO CONCEAL
YOURSELF ALL ON YOUR OWN?
MARVELOUS.
YOU'RE LIKE A WILD ANIMAL.
AND YOUR TIMING
WAS JUST IMPECCABLE.
YOU WERE ABLE TO CONCEAL
YOUR BLOODLUST
BY CLEVERLY HIDING IT
BEHIND MINE
SO THAT I WOULDN'T NOTICE.
MASTERFULLY DONE.
Gon: WAIT.
IF YOU'RE NOT TAKING YOUR BADGE,
THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
Hisoka: TO SAY CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU OWE ME ONE NOW.
YOU CAN PAY ME BACK
WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
SO LONG.
( Gon grunting )
I DON'T OWE YOU OR ANYBODY.
HERE. TAKE IT BACK.
( Hisoka chuckles )
I REFUSE.
I'VE DECIDED
TO LET YOU LIVE FOR NOW,
AND I PLAN
TO LET YOU CONTINUE LIVING
FOR AS LONG AS IT SUITS ME,
UNTIL SOMEDAY YOU BECOME
TRULY WORTHY OF KILLING.
♪
I WILL TAKE IT BACK,
BUT ONLY WHEN YOU CAN PUNCH ME
IN THE FACE LIKE THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU JUST HOLD ON TO IT FOR ME.
( laughs )
Gon: IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I EVER FELT THAT FRUSTRATED.
THAT'S WHY
I NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO PAY HISOKA BACK.
I DON'T WANT TO COME BACK
TO WHALE ISLAND
FEELING LIKE I DO.
Mito: "THAT'S WHY I'LL BE GOING
TO HEAVENS ARENA WITH KILLUA.
"IT'S TIME FOR ME TO START
MY TRAINING AS A HUNTER.
"SO PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELVES.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU BOTH
WHEN I GET BACK. GON FREECSS."
I DIDN'T EXPECT HIM HOME
ANYTIME SOON.
HE REALLY IS YOUR SON,
ISN'T HE?
( laughs )
WHEREVER YOU ARE,
I HOPE YOU'RE
WATCHING OVER HIM, GING.
( singing in Japanese )
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"ARRIVAL AT THE ARENA."
OFF WE GO! GON, GON!
Killua: WHAT, AGAIN?