♪
Kurapika: THEY'RE COMING.
THEY'RE DEFINITELY COMING.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: SEPTEMBER FIRST,
THE DAY GON, KILLUA,
KURAPIKA, AND LEORIO
HAVE CHOSEN TO REUNITE
IN YORKNEW CITY,
AND IT IS ON THIS MORNING
THAT GON AND KILLUA
VISIT THE BUSTLING
YORKNEW MARKETPLACE.
( overlapping chatter )
Gon: WOW,
LOOK AT ALL THE PEOPLE!
Killua: THE WHOLE PURPOSE
OF THIS MARKET
IS TO SWINDLE THE VISITORS
WHO HAVE COME FOR THE AUCTION.
Gon: WAIT. SO THIS
ISN'T THE AUCTION VENUE?
Killua: NO, OF COURSE IT ISN'T.
YORKNEW'S DREAM AUCTION
IS HELD ONCE A YEAR
IN THE WORLD'S
LARGEST AUCTION HOUSE.
THEY SAY THAT TENS OF TRILLIONS
OF JENNY EXCHANGE HANDS
DURING ONLY 10 DAYS
OF OFFICIAL BIDDING.
Gon: TENS OF TRILLIONS? REALLY?
Killua: YEAH. SOMETHING
THAT SELLS FOR 10,000 TODAY
COULD GO FOR
A HUNDRED MILLION TOMORROW.
BAM, INSTANT FORTUNE.
IT'S WHERE DREAMS COME TRUE.
Gon: WOW.
Killua: WELL, ANYWAY,
THAT'S A BIG PART OF THE REASON
WHY SO MUCH
OF THE UNDERWORLD AUCTIONING
HAPPENS AT THE SAME TIME.
Gon: THAT'S AWESOME!
Killua: SO, HEY,
YOU THINK KURAPIKA
AND LEORIO ARE GONNA SHOW?
Gon: THEY PROMISED
THEY'D MEET US HERE TODAY,
SO I'M SURE THEY WILL.
Killua: RIGHT. THEY MIGHT
TRY TO CONTACT US, SO...
GON! YOU'VE REALLY
GOTTA GET A PHONE.
EVERY HUNTER NEEDS ONE.
Gonna: YEAH. I KNOW.
Vendor: HEY, WELCOME!
THIS IS ONE
THE HOTTEST NEW MODELS.
IT'S ULTRA‐THIN AND
NO BIGGER THAN A CREDIT CARD.
PLUS IT HAS G. P. S., WHICH IS
GREAT FOR FINDING PEOPLE.
‐ Leorio: DON'T BOTHER.
‐ Gon: HMM?
Leorio: THE RANGE IS TERRIBLE,
AND IT'S NOT EVEN WATERPROOF.
THE ONLY THING IT'S GOOD FOR
IS MAKING PHONE CALLS.
Gon: LEORIO!
Leorio: HEY!
INSTEAD, I WOULD RECOMMEND...
THIS BEATLE‐ZERO‐SEVEN.
IT'S PRETTY HEAVY AND EXPENSIVE,
BUT IT CAN TRANSLATE
OVER 200 LANGUAGES
FROM PLACES
ALL AROUND THE GLOBE.
Killua: WAIT. REALLY?
HEY, GET THIS ONE,
‐ AND I'LL GET ONE, TOO.
‐ Gon: YEAH!
Leorio:
TWO OF THESE BEAUTIES, PLEASE.
Vendor: YES, SIR.
THAT'LL BE 400,000.
Leorio: FOUR HUNDRED‐‐
THAT'S HIGHWAY ROBBERY!
Gon: THANKS, LEORIO.
Leorio: SURE,
BUT 110,580 JENNY APIECE?
AND THAT'S A FAIR PRICE
FOR A NEW MODEL IN THIS MARKET.
Killua: STILL, YOU OVERDID IT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
GET APPLAUSE
FOR BUYING A CELLPHONE BEFORE.
‐ ( applause )
‐ ( whistles a tune )
Gon: BUT YOU REALLY SAVED US.
Leorio: THAT WAS JUST A TASTE
OF WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF.
THE REAL DEALS
DON'T REALLY START ROLLING
UNTIL AFTER THE SELLER
ASKS YOU TO LEAVE.
( laughs )
Gon: HE DOESN'T REALLY STRIKE ME
AS THE AUCTION‐GOING TYPE.
Killua: NO KIDDING.
Leorio: SO HOW YOU COMING ALONG?
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Leorio: YOU'VE BOTH
BEEN TRAINING
AND GETTING STRONGER,
HAVEN'T YOU?
( Killua snickers )
Leorio: WHAT?!
YOU GAVE THE BADGE
BACK TO HISOKA
AT HEAVENS ARENA?!
NOT TO MENTION
YOU WERE GOOD ENOUGH
TO REACH THE 200th FLOOR.
JUST HOW STRONG HAVE YOU GOTTEN?
Gon: HEY,
DID YOU LEARN NEN, LEORIO?
Leorio: EH?
YOU BETTER BELIEVE I DID.
‐ Gon: THAT'S AWESOME.
‐ Killua: SERIOUSLY?
Leorio: WHY THE HELL
WOULD I LIE ABOUT THAT?
IT'S BUILDING UP
A SHROUD OF AURA,
MAKING YOUR OWN LIFE FORCE
EVEN STRONGER.
( Killua groans )
Gon: THAT'S TEN, ACTUALLY,
ONE OF THE FOUR MAJOR PRINCIPLES
FOR LEARNING NEN.
Leorio: WHAT?! ARE YOU
SAYING THERE'S MORE TO IT?
Killua: I FIGURED IT'D BE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
Leorio: "GREED ISLAND"?
WHAT'S THAT?
Killua: A LEGENDARY GAME.
Gon: WE'RE TRYING
TO GET A COPY AT THE AUCTION.
Leorio: BUT WHY WOULD YOU
EVEN WANT ONE?
Gon: I THINK THE GAME
MIGHT HAVE A CLUE IN IT
THAT'LL HELP ME FIND MY DAD.
Leorio: HUH? A CLUE
HIDDEN IN SOME VIDEO GAME?
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
Gon: IT'S KIND OF A LONG STORY.
Killua: ANYWAY,
THE PROBLEM'S THE COST.
Leorio: HOW MUCH IS IT?
Killua: THE LOWEST
STARTING BID...
IS 8.9 BILLION.
Leorio: DID YOU SAY BILLION?!
AND HOW MUCH DO YOU HAVE?
( Gon chuckles )
AFTER SOME BAD INVESTMENTS,
WE'RE DOWN TO FIVE MILLION.
Leorio: OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN UP.
THIS EVENT IS BEING HELD
AT SOUTHERNBEES,
THE WORLD'S
FINEST AUCTION HOUSE,
SO THAT MUCH MONEY
WON'T EVEN COVER THE ENTRY FEE.
Gon: BUT THE ACQUISITION RANK
FOR THE GAME
WAS LISTED AS "EASY"
ON THE HUNTER WEBSITE.
Leorio: REALLY?
Gon: BECAUSE TO GET
YOUR HANDS ON A COPY,
ALL YOU NEED IS MONEY.
Leorio: HEH!
IT'S LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
MONEY MAKES
THE WORLD GO ROUND!
‐ Killua: WELL...
‐ Leorio: HMM?
ALL THAT REALLY MEANS
IS THAT REAL TREASURE
JUST CAN'T BE PURCHASED.
IF YOU CAN'T GET ONE
AND PRETTY EASILY, TOO,
YOU'RE NOT MUCH OF A HUNTER,
RIGHT, YOU GUYS?
( both groan )
Leorio: HEH! I DON'T NEED YOU
TO TELL ME THAT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST,
WE NEED SOME SEED MONEY,
SOMETHING TO GET
THE BALL ROLLING.
LET'S SEARCH FOR WAYS WE
CAN MAKE FAST CASH IN YORKNEW.
Gon: YEAH!
Killua: SIMPLE AND STUPID.
HE MUST BE AN ENHANCER, TOO.
‐ ( clatter )
‐ Milluki: DAMN IT!
WHAT'S WRONG?!
I CREATED A COMPLETE DUPLICATE
OF THE PROGRAM.
SO WHY AREN'T ANY EVENTS
BEING TRIGGERED?!
♪
DID KIL TRICK ME?
NO. NO, THERE'S NO WAY!
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE SKILLS
TO FORGE A GAME,
AND HE'S DEFINITELY NOT STUPID
ENOUGH TO DOUBLE‐CROSS ME.
SO EITHER HE WAS TRICKED, TOO,
OR THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
I HAVE TO KNOW.
I'LL FIND OUT ITS SECRET,
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
NO MATTER WHAT THE COST.
I'VE GOT 12.7 BILLION LEFT,
AND I'M GONNA NEED
AT LEAST TWICE THAT AMOUNT
TO GUARANTEE A WINNING BID.
( rotors whirring )
DAD, I WANT TO MAKE A DEAL.
LEND ME 15 BILLION,
AND I'LL KILL 15 PEOPLE.
GOT IT. BYE.
Computer: AUTOPILOT ENGAGED
TO LINGON AIRPORT.
Melody: I THINK
I WAS ABOUT 10 YEARS OLD
THE LAST TIME I LEFT THE HOUSE.
Leorio: HUH? SWAP?
Gon: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Computer: SWAP MEET‐‐
A GATHERING FOR THE AUCTION
AND BARTER OF OBJECTS.
SEE ALSO, CONDITIONAL AUCTION.
Leorio: CONDITIONAL AUCTION?
Computer: CONDITIONAL AUCTION‐‐
AN EXCHANGE
IN WHICH THE SELLER SPECIFIES
A NONMONETARY CONDITION
AND HANDS THE ITEM OVER
TO THE FIRST BUYER
WHO SATISFIES THAT CONDITION.
Gon: CONDITIONS, HUH?
Killua: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Leorio: ALL RIGHT.
I THINK I GET IT.
SO THERE'S ANOTHER KIND
OF AUCTIONING.
( chuckles )
Dalzollene: AT 9:00 TONIGHT,
THE MUMMY OF PRINCESS CORCO
WILL BE SOLD OFF
AT THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
IVLENKOV, TOCINO, AND BAISE,
YOU'LL BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE BIDDING.
Basho: ARE THREE PEOPLE
GONNA BE ENOUGH?
Dalzollene: BUYERS CAN
ONLY ENTER IN GROUPS OF THREE.
WEAPONS, COMMUNICATION
AND RECORDING DEVICES
ARE ALL STRICTLY FORBIDDEN.
THE MAFIA THAT RUNS
THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION
ALSO HANDLES SECURITY,
SO THERE'S RARELY ANY TROUBLE.
ALL IT TAKES IS
ONE MISCALCULATED MOVE,
AND THEN EVERY MAFIA MEMBER
IN THE WORLD BECOMES YOUR ENEMY.
THIS AUCTION IS BUILT
ON A FOUNDATION OF TRUST,
AND THAT'S THE REASON
YOU WON'T SEE ANY
SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS ON‐SITE.
THE ONE UNSPOKEN RULE
IS THAT ANY GRUDGES
ARE TO BE CHECKED AT THE DOOR.
AND SO IF ANYTHING DOES HAPPEN,
YOUR WORD
IS OF UTMOST IMPORTANCE.
THERE ARE NO COURTS HERE,
BUT IT WILL HOLD THE SAME WEIGHT
AS SWORN TESTIMONY.
IT'S CRUCIAL THAT EACH ONE OF
YOU MAKES A GLOWING IMPRESSION.
DON'T CAUSE MINOR DISTURBANCES
FOR ANY REASON.
SPEAK TO NO ONE
OUTSIDE OF THIS GROUP.
Basho: AND THE REST OF US?
Dalzollene: BASHO AND LINSSEN
WILL BE COVERING
THE REAR ENTRANCE.
KURAPIKA AND MELODY
WILL TAKE THE FRONT ENTRANCE.
SQUALA AND I
WILL GUARD THE GIRL.
AND SO THE MISSION
WILL NOW BEGIN.
♪
Leorio: STEP RIGHT UP, FOLKS!
LET'S HAVE A LITTLE
CONDITIONAL AUCTIONING FUN!
HERE'S WHAT'S UP FOR BID,
A DIAMOND WORTH THREE MILLION,
BOUGHT TODAY WITH
A CERTIFICATE OF AUTHENTICITY!
ARM WRESTLING
DECIDES THE WINNER!
FIRST PERSON TO BEAT THIS BOY
WALKS OFF WITH THE DIAMOND!
ENTRY FEE IS 10,000!
ALL RIGHT.
THE AUCTION STARTS NOW!
Man: I WANT IN ON THAT!
‐ Man #2: ME, TOO!
‐ Man #3: SAME HERE!
‐ ( overlapping chatter )
‐ Leorio: NO PUSHING, PEOPLE!
FORM A LINE!
ADJUST YOUR STRENGTH
TO MATCH THAT OF YOUR OPPONENT,
AND PRETEND TO STRUGGLE
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
OKAY, YOU'RE UP FIRST!
THE ENTRY FEE IN ADVANCE,
PLEASE.
Man #1: HERE YOU GO, 10,000.
Leorio: THANK YOU, SIR.
NOW STEP RIGHT UP.
ALL RIGHT, CLASP HANDS.
JUST DO WHAT I TOLD YOU.
( Gon groans )
Leorio: AND REMEMBER,
YOU GET ONE ROUND.
READY.
GO!
♪
( Gon grunting )
Leorio: UH‐OH! CAN HE DO IT?
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
DON'T GIVE UP NOW!
( Gon yells )
( man #1 groans )
( hand thumps )
Leorio: OHH!
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE!
Man #1: AH, DAMN IT!
I LOST TO A LITTLE KID.
Leorio: AND WHO WILL BE
OUR NEXT CONTENDER?
READY.
AND GO!
( crowd cheering )
Killua: I GET IT.
♪
SO THIS
IS CONDITIONAL AUCTIONING.
BUT TO REACH 8.9 BILLION,
WE'LL NEED 889,999 WINS.
‐ ( hand thumps )
‐ Man #4: OH, DAMN.
Leorio: ANOTHER LOSER.
SO WHO'S UP NEXT?
( hand thumps )
YOU LOSE!
( overlapping chatter )
Man #5: HE'S BEATEN 150 PEOPLE.
Man #6: HE'S GOTTA BE
RUNNING OUT OF STEAM.
Man #7: HE LOOKS TIRED,
AND HE'S SWEATING BULLETS.
Man #8: DON'T LOSE
BEFORE I GET MY TURN!
Gon: I FEEL BAD
FOR TRICKING EVERYBODY,
MAKING SO MUCH MONEY
THIS EASILY.
I'M BREAKING OUT IN A COLD SWEAT
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
Leorio: OKAY! SO WHO'S UP NEXT?
UH...
LOOK AT THAT! WE HAVE
OUR FIRST FEMALE CHALLENGER!
Man #9: ALL RIGHT!
GET HIM, GIRL!
Man #10: AND TRY TO TAKE IT EASY
ON THE LITTLE LADY, MUSCLE BOY!
Leorio: SO TELL US
WHERE YOU'RE FROM.
ALL BUSINESS, I SEE.
Shizuku: I LOOK FORWARD
TO OUR MATCH.
Gon: OH. YEAH, SAME HERE.
( gasps )
Leorio: READY, AND...
GO!
( both grunting )
( hand thumps )
Leorio: OH, SO CLOSE!
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME!
Man #11:
YEAH, GOOD EFFORT, GIRL!
Shizuku: THANK YOU
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY.
Gon: OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
ANYTIME.
( Shizuku sighs ) WHAT A PITY.
Killua: WAS THAT FULL POWER?
Gon: YEAH.
I WONDER WHO SHE IS.
Killua: WORLD CHAMPION
ARM WRESTLER, MAYBE?
Franklin: WELL?
Shizuku: I LOST. HE'S TOUGH.
Feitan: THAT LITTLE BRAT?
Shizuku: I SORT OF WANTED
THAT DIAMOND.
Franklin: THEN YOU SHOULD
HAVE USED YOUR LEFT HAND.
Feitan: YES, WHY DIDN'T YOU
USE YOUR STRONGER ARM?
Shizuku: OH, BECAUSE HE EXTENDED
HIS RIGHT HAND FIRST.
I THINK I'D LIKE
TO CHALLENGE HIM AGAIN.
Feitan: THERE IS NO TIME.
WE HAVE A JOB TO DO.
Franklin: HE'S RIGHT.
BESIDES, BUYING AND BIDDING'S
NOT OUR STYLE.
WE'RE THIEVES, REMEMBER?
Feitan: IF WE WANT SOMETHING,
WE TAKE IT.
‐ ( crashing )
‐ Neon: NO WAY!
I'M GOING!
( sobbing )
Dalzollene: HEAR THAT, SIR?!
I'M AT A LOSS HERE!
( gas whooshing )
( somber chorus humming )
( chorus continues )
( chorus vocalizing )
( debris tinkling )
Dalzollene: YES, SIR.
HER TANTRUM‐‐
HER CRYING EXHAUSTED HER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'S FAST ASLEEP NOW, SIR.
BUT THERE'S SIMPLY NO TELLING
WHAT WE'RE ALL IN FOR
WHEN SHE FINALLY WAKES UP AGAIN.
I VOW TO OBTAIN
THE ITEMS SHE WANTS,
BUT SHE'S SET ON PARTICIPATING
IN THE BIDDING HERSELF.
SHE'S BOUND TO BE DISAPPOINTED
WHEN SHE WAKES UP
TO FIND THAT SHE MISSED
HER ONLY CHANCE AT DOING SO.
Nostrade: VERY WELL. I'LL ADJUST
MY SCHEDULE AND HEAD OVER.
FOR NOW, FOCUS ON GETTING
THE MUMMY OF THAT PRINCESS
SO WE CAN IMPROVE
HER MOOD AGAIN.
Dalzollene: UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
‐ ( beep )
‐ ( sighs )
( dialing )
Dalzollene: WELL,
HOW ARE THINGS WITH YOU?
Melody: ALL CLEAR.
Kurapika: THERE'S NOTHING
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
YES, SIR.
WE'LL CALL YOU
IF ANYTHING NEW HAPPENS.
Melody: THEY'RE BEING
QUITE THOROUGH, AREN'T THEY?
NO ONE IS ALLOWED WITHIN
500 METERS OF THE AUCTION HOUSE
EXCEPT FOR APPROVED
MAFIA SECURITY PERSONNEL.
Kurapika:
IF THEY DIDN'T DO THAT,
THE PERIMETER WOULD BE
CRAWLING WITH THUGS,
WHICH WOULD PRACTICALLY
BE AN ANNOUNCEMENT
THAT SINISTER DEEDS
ARE TAKING PLACE.
Melody: GUESS SO.
Kurapika: I WONDER...
WILL THE PHANTOM TROUPE
REALLY SHOW UP?
( Melody gasps )
( wind blowing )
THAT'S THE SAME SOUND
I HEARD EARLIER.
Kurapika: HMM?
Melody: JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I HAPPENED TO SEE YOU AS YOU
WERE LEAVING THE HUNTER AGENCY.
( chains jangle )
I HEARD IT
WHEN YOU WALKED PAST ME.
YOUR HEART PLAYED
A MELODY OF WRATH.
MIND IF I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
Kurapika: GO AHEAD.
Melody: SCARLET EYES.
( Kurapika gasps )
Melody: EXACTLY...
WHAT DO THEY MEAN TO YOU?
( siren passing )
Kurapika: WHY DO YOU ASK?
Melody: THERE'S NO REASON
IN PARTICULAR.
JUST CURIOUS.
WHEN YOU SAW
THE IMAGE ON THE DATA CARD,
YOUR HEARTBEAT WAS EVEN
MORE FEARSOME THAN IT WAS THEN.
IT PLAYED A MELODY
OF BOUNDLESS FURY.
Kurapika: I GUESS
THERE'S NO POINT IN LYING.
I AM A MEMBER OF THE KURTA CLAN.
OUR EYES ARE NORMALLY BROWN,
BUT THEY BURN A BRIGHT CRIMSON
WHEN WE'RE AGITATED,
SO I WEAR BLACK CONTACT LENSES
TO ESCAPE DETECTION.
I SEEK THE EYES THAT WERE
STOLEN FROM MY BRETHREN,
AND WHATEVER IT TAKES, I WILL
RETURN THEIR EYES TO THEM.
Melody: HMM.
Kurapika: WILL YOU
TELL DALZOLLENE ABOUT ME?
Melody: NO, I WON'T,
BECAUSE YOU'D KILL ME IF I DID.
Kurapika:
YOU'RE VERY PERCEPTIVE.
Melody: A HEARTBEAT'S
ALWAYS HONEST.
WHEN YOU FIRST BEGAN CONFESSING
AND TOLD ME YOUR TRUE NATURE,
YOUR HEARTBEAT WAS AS CALM
AS IT WAS ICY,
THE HEARTBEAT OF ONE WHO IS
PREPARED TO KILL IF NEED BE.
YOUR HEART SAYS
YOU HOLD NO GRUDGES,
BUT THAT I WAS FAIR GAME
IF I TALKED.
Kurapika:
WHY DID YOU TAKE THIS JOB?
Melody: WHY WOULD YOU ASK?
YOU KNOW THAT I'LL
PROBABLY LIE TO YOU.
Kurapika: YOUR EYES
WILL TELL ME IF YOU DO.
( Melody sighs )
I'M ALSO A PRO HUNTER,
A MUSIC HUNTER, I SUPPOSE.
I SEEK A CERTAIN SHEET MUSIC.
Kurapika: YOU AREN'T LYING,
BUT YOU LEFT OUT
CRUCIAL DETAILS.
( Melody chuckles )
LET'S SAY YOU'RE RIGHT
AND LEAVE IT AT THAT.
( flute playing )
IT'S THE SONATA OF DARKNESS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M AFTER.
IT IS SAID TO BE COMPOSED
BY THE DEVIL HIMSELF.
THERE ARE SOLO PARTS
FOR THE PIANO, VIOLIN,
FLUTE, AND HARP.
IF A HUMAN PLAYS
OR EVEN LISTENS TO THE PIECE,
THEY WILL BE HORRIBLY CURSED.
Kurapika: ISN'T THAT
JUST AN URBAN LEGEND?
I DOUBT THAT ANYTHING LIKE THAT
COULD TRULY EXIST.
( gasps )
Melody: THE ONLY SOLO I HEARD
WAS THE FLUTE SOLO.
ONE MOVEMENT TURNED ME
INTO WHAT YOU SEE NOW.
MY FRIEND WHO PLAYED IT DIED,
AND HER WHOLE BODY
TURNED TO THIS.
JUST A SINGLE MOVEMENT FROM
SOMEONE WHO HAD GIVEN WARNINGS
NEVER TO PLAY IT
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES.
THAT DAY,
WE WERE DRUNK AND GIDDY.
MY BODY WAS DESTROYED, BUT I
GAINED THIS ABILITY IN RETURN.
I WISH TO RESTORE MY BODY
TO THE WAY IT WAS.
I'M WILLING TO DO ANYTHING.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE
TO SUFFER THE SAME FATE AS ME.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO FIND
THE SCORE AND DESTROY IT.
YOU ASKED ME
WHY I TOOK THIS JOB.
THE ANSWER IS I WAS HOPING
ONE DEVIL WOULD KNOW ANOTHER.
( sighs )
MM? LOOKS LIKE IT'S TIME.
THE UNDERWORLD AUCTION
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
Pakunoda: IT'S ALMOST TIME.
Hisoka: IT IS.
♪
Narrator: THE PHANTOM TROUPE
PREPARES TO BARE ITS FANGS,
AND SOON KURAPIKA,
NOW A BODYGUARD
FOR THE NOSTRADE FAMILY,
MUST DECIDE
ON HOW TO DEAL WITH THEM.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING BASHO.
Killua: HE WRITES A LOT
OF HAIKU, HIS HOMELAND'S POETRY.
Gon: LET ME DO ONE!
"THIS SEGMENT IS A TEST
OF HEART AND SOUL."
Killua: YOU'RE WAY OFF.
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"A SHOCKING TRAGEDY."
SHOCKING!
Killua: SHOCKING?
Both: IT'S A SHOCKER!