( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Satotz: GON!
Gon: WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
Satotz: YOU MUST LIE DOWN.
YOU NEED TO REST.
( footsteps )
♪
Narrator:
AFTER LEARNING THE REASON
FOR KILLUA'S DISQUALIFICATION,
GON WAS FURIOUS
WITH GITTARACKUR.
OR RATHER WITH KILLUA'S
OLDER BROTHER, ILLUMI.
Gon: APOLOGIZE TO KILLUA!
Illumi: SORRY? BUT WHAT FOR?
Gon: YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU DID WRONG?
Illumi: NOPE.
♪
Gon: YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED
TO BE HIS BIG BROTHER.
Illumi: I DIDN'T KNOW
I HAD TO QUALIFY.
( hunters gasp )
Gon: FRIENDS
DON'T HAVE TO, EITHER.
HE GETS TO CHOOSE!
( Illumi thinking )
THIS BOY...
Gon: DON'T EVEN
BOTHER APOLOGIZING.
JUST TAKE ME TO SEE KILLUA.
Illumi: AND WHAT WILL YOU DO?
Gon: IT'S OBVIOUS.
I'LL BRING HIM BACK.
Illumi: FROM THE SOUND OF IT,
YOU MUST THINK
I KIDNAPPED MY LITTLE BROTHER,
BUT HE WALKED OUT OF HERE
OF HIS OWN FREE WILL.
Gon: HE LEFT,
BUT NOT BY FREE WILL.
YOU GUYS WERE MANIPULATING HIM.
THAT'S THE SAME THING
AS KIDNAPPING.
Netero: WE WERE JUST DISCUSSING
THAT VERY SUBJECT, GON.
IN FACT, KURAPIKA AND LEORIO
HAVE BOTH LODGED COMPLAINTS.
THE COMMITTEE HAS BEEN REVIEWING
THE FAIRNESS
OF KILLUA'S DISQUALIFICATION.
Kurapika: YOU SAW IT YOURSELF.
BOTH DURING AND SINCE HIS MATCH
WITH THE MAN CALLED GITTARACKUR,
KILLUA BEHAVED STRANGELY.
I BELIEVE
THAT THERE IS ONLY ONE REASON
THAT KILLUA COMMITTED MURDER.
HE WAS HYPNOTIZED.
IT'S GENERALLY
CONSIDERED IMPOSSIBLE
TO USE HYPNOSIS TO DIRECT
SOMEONE TO DO SUCH A THING.
HOWEVER,
ASSASSINS RAISED KILLUA,
AND MURDER WAS COMMONPLACE,
SO IT'S NATURAL
THAT HE WOULD LACK
THE PROPER ETHICAL RESTRAINT.
Leorio: IT'S WORTH NOTING
THAT THE ATTACK HAPPENED
DURING MY MATCH WITH BODORO,
SO IT'S POSSIBLE
KILLUA INTENDED TO AID MY CAUSE,
WHICH MEANS IF YOU'RE
GOING TO DISQUALIFY ANYONE,
IT SHOULD BE ME.
Kurapika: WHATEVER THE CASE,
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT KILLUA
WAS NOT IN FULL CONTROL
OF HIS ACTIONS AT THE TIME,
AND THUS HE SHOULD NOT
HAVE BEEN DISQUALIFIED.
Netero: THAT IS NOTHING MORE
THAN SPECULATION.
THERE'S NO CONCRETE PROOF.
FROM WHAT WE SAW,
THERE WERE NO CLEAR INDICATIONS
HE WAS ORDERED
TO COMMIT MURDER.
AND REGARDING THE HYPNOTISM,
I WOULD HAVE TO QUESTION
THAT CLAIM, AS WELL.
I WILL AGREE
THAT THE INCIDENT OCCURRED
ONCE THE BATTLE BETWEEN LEORIO
AND BODORO HAD GOTTEN UNDER WAY.
AT THAT POINT, BOTH FIGHTERS
WERE EVENLY MATCHED,
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED.
WHILE BODORO
CERTAINLY HAD MORE EXPERIENCE,
IT WAS CLEAR THAT LEORIO
HAD THE DEFINITE EDGE
WHEN IT CAME
TO RAW ABILITY IN COMBAT.
GIVEN THAT IT WAS A FAIR FIGHT,
THERE WAS NO NEED
FOR KILLUA TO INTERFERE.
Pokkle: AND SPEAKING
OF WEIRD THINGS HAPPENING...
Kurapika: HMM?
Pokkle: WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT
WHEN YOU FOUGHT WITH HISOKA?
( Kurapika gasps )
Pokkle: MIND TELLING US
WHAT IT WAS HE SAID TO YOU?
NEITHER OF YOU LOOKED TIRED,
BUT HISOKA WHISPERED SOMETHING
TO YOU, THEN SURRENDERED.
WEIRD, RIGHT?
I'D UNDERSTAND
IF HE WHISPERED SOMETHING
AND YOU SURRENDERED,
LIKE WITH HANZO AND ME
OR BODORO AND HISOKA.
WE WERE
UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE.
INSTEAD, THE OPPOSITE HAPPENED,
WHICH MAKES ME WONDER
IF THE TWO OF YOU
STRUCK SOME SORT OF BARGAIN.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THINGS
THAT DON'T MAKE SENSE,
THEN YOUR VICTORY
WOULD FIT THE BILL PERFECTLY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO HIDE, RIGHT?
SO WHAT DID HE SAY?
ENLIGHTEN US.
Kurapika: I HAVE
NO SUCH OBLIGATION.
Pokkle: MAYBE YOU DON'T,
BUT I THINK YOU OWE IT TO US.
Kurapika: I DON'T.
YOU MAY FIND MY VICTORY SUSPECT,
BUT I WOULD SAY THE SAME
OF VICTORY BY DEFAULT.
( Pokkle growls )
WHAT?!
( growls )
( Kurapika grunts )
Gon: THIS IS POINTLESS.
‐ Illumi: HMM?
‐ Hanzo: COME ON.
LET'S JUST GET THIS OVER WITH
SO WE CAN ALL GO HOME.
Leorio: LOOK HERE, PAL!
Gon: THIS IS
COMPLETELY POINTLESS!
WHY ARGUE ABOUT WHETHER
SOMEBODY SHOULD'VE PASSED?
IF YOU'RE NOT SATISFIED
THAT YOU MADE IT,
YOU CAN KEEP WORKING
UNTIL YOU ARE.
IF KILLUA WANTS
TO RETAKE THE HUNTER EXAM,
THEN I KNOW HE'LL PASS.
HE DIDN'T THIS TIME,
AND IT IS WHAT IT IS.
BUT STILL, IF YOU'VE BEEN
FORCING KILLUA TO MURDER PEOPLE
AGAINST HIS WILL
THIS WHOLE TIME...
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
Illumi: NEVER FORGIVE ME?
SO WHAT WILL YOU DO?
Gon: I WON'T DO ANYTHING,
BUT AFTER I GO RESCUE KILLUA,
I'LL NEVER
LET YOU SEE HIM AGAIN.
Illumi: HMM.
( Netero clears throat )
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
LET'S CONTINUE.
GON'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
IT'S UP TO EACH OF YOU
TO DECIDE WHETHER
YOU'RE WORTHY OF YOUR LICENSE.
NOW, YOU'RE PERFECTLY WELCOME
TO COMPLAIN ABOUT THE RESULTS
AS MUCH AS YOU LIKE,
BUT OUR MINDS ARE MADE UP.
KILLUA HAS BEEN DISQUALIFIED
FROM THIS YEAR'S HUNTER EXAM,
WHILE THE REST OF YOU
HAVE PASSED.
Beans: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I SHALL CONTINUE
WITH THE ORIENTATION.
NOW, THE CARDS
THAT WE'VE PASSED OUT
ARE YOUR HUNTER LICENSES.
♪
THIS CARD
WILL ALLOW YOU TO ENTER
90% OF THE COUNTRIES
THAT LIMIT IMMIGRATION,
AS WELL AS GRANT YOU ACCESS
TO 75% OF RESTRICTED AREAS
IN THE WORLD.
Hanzo: AMAZING.
Beans: YOU MAY USE 95%
OF PUBLIC FACILITIES
AT ABSOLUTELY NO COST,
AND BANKS WILL TREAT YOU AS IF
YOU WERE A TOP‐RATED COMPANY.
YOU CAN SELL IT FOR ENOUGH MONEY
TO LAST SEVEN LIFETIMES,
OR YOU CAN KEEP IT FOR
A LIFE OF GUARANTEED COMFORT.
( Pokkle swallows )
Beans: PLEASE BE VERY CAREFUL.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT IT
TO BE MISPLACED OR STOLEN.
YOU WON'T GET A REPLACEMENT.
ACCORDING TO OUR ESTIMATES,
AS MANY AS ONE IN FIVE HUNTERS
SOMEHOW MANAGE
TO LOSE THEIR CARD
WITHIN A YEAR OF RECEIVING IT.
YOUR VERY FIRST CHALLENGE
AS A LICENSED HUNTER
IS TO PROTECT YOUR CARD
AT ALL COSTS.
FROM HERE ON OUT,
IT'S YOUR SHOW.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELVES,
AND KEEP WORKING
TO MAKE YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE.
Netero: WELL,
THEN WE CAN NOW CERTIFY
ALL SEVEN APPLICANTS PRESENT
AS LICENSED HUNTERS.
( fanfare playing )
♪
( chuckles )
Gon: GITTARACKUR.
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
WHERE KILLUA IS.
Illumi: YOU'RE REALLY
GOING AFTER HIM?
I THINK THAT'S A BAD IDEA.
Gon: WHO CARES WHAT YOU THINK?!
KILLUA IS MY FRIEND.
I'LL GET HIM BACK, I SWEAR.
Illumi: AND DO THEY
FEEL THE SAME WAY?
Leorio: YOU BET WE DO.
Kurapika: HMM.
( Gon chuckles )
Leorio: HMM.
( Illumi sighs )
FINE, THEN.
I DOUBT YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO GET THERE ANYWAY.
I'M SURE KIL
JUST WENT BACK HOME.
Gon: WHERE'S THAT?
Illumi: ON KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
YOU CAN FIND OUR FAMILY'S HOUSE
AT THE SUMMIT.
Leorio: KUKUROO MOUNTAIN?
Gon: WE GOT IT. THANKS A LOT.
Hisoka: WAS THAT WISE,
GIVING UP YOUR BASE
OF OPERATIONS LIKE THAT?
Illumi: SURE. IT ISN'T A SECRET.
THE LOCALS
ALL KNOW WHERE WE LIVE.
OUR WORLDS
ARE DRASTICALLY DIFFERENT,
A FACT THAT I'M SURE
THEY'LL ALL COME TO REALIZE
ONCE THEY ARRIVE.
Hisoka: HMM.
Illumi: OH. THIS?
YEAH. IT'S BROKEN.
Hisoka: HMM.
Illumi: HE IS INTERESTING.
I CAN UNDERSTAND
YOUR CONCERN FOR HIS FUTURE.
( no audible dialogue )
Hisoka: UH‐HUH.
Illumi: HOWEVER, THAT MAKES HIM
ALL THE MORE DANGEROUS.
I'D LIKE TO DEAL
WITH THAT AS SOON AS‐‐
( aloud )
HMM?
Hisoka: GON IS MINE.
DO NOT FORGET THAT.
LEAVE HIM BE,
OR SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES.
Illumi: I'M AWARE OF THAT.
I HAVEN'T KNOWN YOU LONG,
BUT I KNOW YOUR TASTES.
SO, HISOKA, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
Hisoka: WAIT PATIENTLY. HEH.
( shudders )
UNTIL THE FRUIT BECOMES
RIPE ENOUGH FOR ME TO PLUCK.
Leorio: KUKUROO MOUNTAIN, HUH?
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS, KURAPIKA?
HEY! KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: HUH?
OH. WHAT'S THAT?
Leorio: PAY ATTENTION.
ILLUMI MENTIONED
KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE IT IS?
Kurapika: NO,
I'M AFRAID I DON'T.
BUT WE CAN JUST GO
LOOK IT UP ONLINE.
All: HMM?
Hanzo: HEY!
Gon: OH! HEY, HANZO!
Hanzo: I'M HEADING HOME.
WE ALL WENT THROUGH A LOT
IN A SHORT TIME,
BUT I HAD A LOT OF FUN.
Gon: YEAH, ME, TOO.
Hanzo: IF YOU EVER VISIT
MY COUNTRY, JUST LET ME KNOW.
I'LL GIVE YOU A REAL TOUR,
NO TOURIST TRAPS.
LATER.
Gon: BYE! SEE YA!
Kurapika: UH...
♪
THAT CERTAINLY IS
ONE BIG SELF‐ASSURED NINJA.
‐ Pokkle: HEY.
‐ All: HMM?
Pokkle: I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT
GETTING SO WORKED UP BACK THERE.
Kurapika: PLEASE.
I WAS NO BETTER.
I HOPE YOU'LL FORGIVE ME.
Pokkle: NO. I ONLY GOT MAD
'CAUSE, DEEP DOWN,
I KNEW YOU WERE RIGHT.
I WAS JUST TAKING OUT
MY FRUSTRATION
AT WINNING BY DEFAULT.
BUT I'M OVER THAT.
I PASSED, SO I MIGHT AS WELL
MAKE THE BEST OF IT, RIGHT?
THE QUESTION IS
WHAT AM I GONNA DO NEXT?
Kurapika: YES. YOU'RE RIGHT.
Pokkle: I DECIDED
THAT I'LL TRAVEL THE WORLD,
DISCOVER NEW SPECIES,
AND AS A LICENSED
EXOTIC GAME HUNTER,
LEARN EVERYTHING I CAN.
Kurapika: EXOTIC GAME HUNTER?
Gon: OH, HEY! WHAT'S THAT THING?
Pokkle: WHAT, THIS?
YOU USE IT TO FIND
ALL KINDS OF INFORMATION.
THERE ANYTHING YOU WANT TO KNOW?
I CAN LOOK IT UP FOR YOU.
Gon: HMM.
OH, THERE IS!
THINK YOU CAN LOOK UP A HUNTER
NAMED GING, GING FREECSS.
Pokkle: SURE.
HOLD ON JUST A SECOND.
♪
Menchi: WHAT'S SATOTZ DOING?
Pokkle: I'M CURIOUS.
SO WHO IS THIS GING GUY, ANYWAY?
Gon: HUH?
Pokkle: 'CAUSE EVERYTHING
THAT'S RELATED TO HIM
IS BEHIND
A TIGHT SECURITY SYSTEM.
YOU NEED A WHOLE BUNCH OF CODES
TO ACCESS IT.
I THINK HE MUST HAVE FRIENDS
ON THE NATIONAL LEVEL.
( Gon gasps )
REALLY?
FORGET IT, THEN.
Leorio: DID YOU HEAR THAT?
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR DAD
IS SOMEONE REALLY SPECIAL.
( Gon chuckles )
Pokkle: OKAY.
LET ME KNOW
IF ANYTHING COMES UP.
THIS IS MY E‐MAIL ADDRESS.
SEE YOU AROUND.
Gon: BYE, POKKLE!
‐ ( Leorio gasps )
‐ Gon: EH?
Leorio: WE SHOULD HAVE ASKED HIM
TO LOOK UP KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
Gon: YEAH. I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
Kurapika: WELL,
WE ARE ALL HUNTERS NOW.
CHAIRMAN NETERO
MADE THAT MUCH CLEAR.
AND IT'S PROBABLY
NOT THE BEST IDEA
TO LET OTHER HUNTERS
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
BETTER TO LOOK IT UP OURSELVES.
( both chuckle )
Satotz: GON.
Gon: MR. SATOTZ!
Satotz: IT APPEARS
THAT YOU FORGOT SOMETHING.
Gon: OH! THAT'S RIGHT.
THANKS A LOT!
Satotz: ALSO DO YOU
HAVE A BRIEF MOMENT?
Kurapika: WE'LL BE WAITING
FOR YOU IN THE LOBBY.
Gon: OKAY.
Satotz: FORGIVE ME.
I COULDN'T HELP BUT OVERHEAR
YOUR CONVERSATION.
AS IT HAPPENS,
I SPECIALIZE IN ANCIENT RUINS,
RESTORATION AND PRESERVATION.
AT FIRST, I WAS FIXATED
ON THE GLORY OF NEW DISCOVERIES,
BUT AFTER WATCHING
A CERTAIN HUNTER,
I BECAME
QUITE ASHAMED OF MYSELF.
( water drips )
THE HUNTER OF WHICH I SPEAK
WOULD DISCOVER RUINS,
THEN SPEND HIS OWN MONEY
TO COMPLETELY RESTORE THEM.
HE TOOK STEPS
TO PRESERVE THE SITES
FOR FUTURE GENERATIONS,
ENSURING THAT PEOPLE
FROM EVERY WALK OF LIFE
WOULD BE ABLE TO ENJOY THEM.
HIS DEDICATION WAS IMPRESSIVE,
I'D SAY MORE IMPRESSIVE
THAN THE RUINS THEMSELVES.
HIS WORK
WAS DOCUMENTED IN MANUALS,
MANUALS WHICH ARE NOW USED
IN RESTORATIONS
THROUGHOUT THE WORLD.
THE NAME OF THIS HUNTER, GON,
IS NONE OTHER
THAN GING FREECSS,
THE MAN WHOM YOU WERE
JUST ASKING ABOUT.
( Gon gasps )
Satotz: I WANTED
SO DESPERATELY TO MEET HIM,
I DID A BIT
OF INVESTIGATING MYSELF.
HOWEVER, THE MAN IS AN ENIGMA,
AND I WAS NEVER ABLE TO UNEARTH
A SINGLE THING ABOUT HIM.
Gon: REALLY? THAT FIGURES.
Satotz: MY GOAL IS TO BECOME
A HUNTER JUST LIKE HIM,
AND MY DREAM IS TO THANK HIM
IN PERSON ONE DAY.
Gon: MM.
Satotz: HMM.
THAT'S ALL I HAD TO SAY.
MY APOLOGIES
FOR INTERRUPTING YOU.
Gon: IT'S FINE.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING,
MR. SATOTZ.
‐ WELL, BYE!
‐ Satotz: OH!
AND, GON...
Gon: HMM?
Satotz: IT'S NOTHING.
JUST TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
Gon: YEAH. ( laughs )
YOU DO THE SAME.
GOOD‐BYE!
♪
Leorio: FIRST LET'S LOOK UP
KUKUROO MOUNTAIN.
Kurapika: RIGHT.
THERE.
HERE IT IS.
"KUKUROO MOUNTAIN,
"IN THE DENTORA REGION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA,
IS 3,722 METERS HIGH."
Leorio: REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA?
NEVER HEARD OF THE PLACE.
SO WHERE IS IT?
Kurapika: HOLD ON.
I'LL BRING UP A MAP.
THIS IS THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA.
IT APPEARS TO BE
A STABLE COUNTRY,
SO WE SHOULD BE FINE.
THIS COUNTRY'S OPEN TO TOURISTS.
Gon: THAT'S WHERE KILLUA IS?
Kurapika: IT'LL TAKE THREE DAYS
TO REACH BY AIRSHIP.
WHEN DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD LEAVE?
Gon: TODAY! RIGHT NOW!
Leorio: ALL RIGHT! I'M WITH GON.
Kurapika: GOT IT.
I'LL ORDER THE TICKETS THEN.
♪
( traffic honking )
Leorio: WHAT'S GOING ON?
FEELS LIKE WE'VE BEEN
STUCK HERE FOREVER.
Kurapika: THIS IS BAD.
AT THIS RATE,
WE'LL BE LATE FOR OUR FLIGHT.
Leorio: HEY, POPS, DO SOMETHING!
Driver: NOTHING I CAN DO
ABOUT TRAFFIC,
AND IT'S THE ONLY ROAD.
Gon: IN THAT CASE...
♪
Both: HMM?
Gon: YAY!
( running footsteps )
Leorio: HEY, GON! DO YOU REALIZE
HOW FAR AWAY THE AIRPORT IS?
Gon: SURE! BUT I WANT
TO GO RESCUE KILLUA,
AND I DIDN'T WANT TO WAIT AROUND
ANOTHER SECOND!
( Kurapika chuckles )
Leorio: FINE. YOU WIN.
RUNNING LIKE THIS KIND OF
REMINDS ME OF THE HUNTER EXAM.
Gon: I KNOW, RIGHT?
BUT THIS IS
A HECK OF A LOT EASIER
THAN THE HUNTER EXAM WAS. HEH.
Leorio: OH, YEAH.
GOT THAT RIGHT.
Gon: ALL RIGHT.
RACE YOU GUYS TO THE AIRPORT!
READY. SET.
GO!
Narrator: GON AND HIS FRIENDS
SET OFF
FOR THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA.
THEIR DESTINATION
IS KUKUROO MOUNTAIN,
WHERE THEY HOPE TO FIND
KILLUA'S HOME.
( footsteps )
Menchi: SATOTZ.
Satotz: OH, MENCHI AND BUHARA.
Menchi: IS IT JUST ME,
OR WAS THAT A REALLY CLOSE CALL?
( Satotz chuckles )
YOU SAW THAT, DID YOU?
THE BOY'S A MYSTERY.
I FEEL MOST COMPELLED
TO HELP HIM.
I ALMOST NEARLY
LET IT SLIP THAT...
THE REAL HUNTER EXAM
ISN'T OVER JUST YET.
( wind blowing )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"A DANGEROUS WATCHDOG."
‐ DOGGIE, GO FETCH!
‐ Leorio: THAT'S IT!
‐ Gon: DOGGIE, ROLL OVER!
‐ Leorio: OH, YEAH!