Leorio: YEAH. IT LOOKS REAL,
AND THERE'S A VIDEO
ATTACHED TO IT.
WE'VE GOT TWO TARGETS,
A MAN AND A WOMAN.
I'LL HEAD OUT RIGHT NOW,
SO YOU JUST MEET ME THERE.
Gon: GOT IT.
COME ON. LET'S GO!
Killua: OKAY.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: FOLLOWING A TIP
ABOUT THE PHANTOM TROUPE,
GON AND HIS FRIENDS MOVE OUT.
ONCE THERE, THEY ENCOUNTER
MACHI AND NOBUNAGA,
BUT THE PAIR IS NOT SIMPLY
WAITING AROUND TO BE CAUGHT.
Nobunaga: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DID UVO REALLY
GET HIMSELF KILLED?
Machi: PROBABLY, YEAH.
Nobunaga: UVO MAY HAVE
BEEN A BRUTE,
BUT HE WASN'T STUPID.
Machi: I CERTAINLY
CAN'T DISAGREE WITH YOU THERE.
Nobunaga: IT DIDN'T MATTER
HOW TOUGH HIS OPPONENT WAS.
HE ALWAYS HAD THE WITS
AND EXPERIENCE TO PREVAIL.
‐ ( cell phone rings )
‐ ( man gasps )
Woman: YEAH. HELLO?
Leorio: I'M THE GUY
WHO POSTED THE AD.
Woman: WELL, YOU'RE LATE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
Leorio: PLEASE STOP
LOOKING AROUND.
WE CAN SEE YOU, SO DON'T WORRY.
IS THAT THEM, THE COUPLE
RIGHT BEHIND YOUR BOYFRIEND?
I'M WIRING THE MONEY
TO YOUR ACCOUNT.
CONFIRM RECEIPT.
( beeping )
( man gasps ) REALLY?
( woman gasps )
LET'S GO. COME ON.
Machi: BUT UVO
DIDN'T COME BACK THIS TIME.
HAS HE EVER BEEN THIS LATE
WITHOUT LETTING US KNOW BEFORE?
Nobunaga: YOU HEARD
WHAT HE SAID, DIDN'T YOU?
HE WASN'T COMING BACK
'TIL HE SETTLED THE SCORE
WITH THE CHAIN USER.
Machi: YEAH, I HEARD.
THAT'S WHY I SAID, "PROBABLY."
I DIDN'T SAY
THAT I WAS SURE HE WAS DEAD.
Nobunaga: THAT YOUR HUNCH?
Machi: JUST A HUNCH.
Nobunaga: WELL, YOUR HUNCHES
ARE RIGHT MORE OFTEN THAN NOT.
Leorio: OKAY.
WE SHOULD DECIDE OUR NEXT MOVE.
SO HOW SHOULD WE GO ABOUT
CAPTURING THESE TWO?
Killua: WE DON'T.
‐ Leorio: HMM?
‐ Gon: HUH?
Killua: LOOK, THEY'RE WAY
OUT OF OUR LEAGUE.
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
Leorio: OH, COME ON!
WE WON'T KNOW UNTIL WE TRY,
AND BESIDES, WHY DIDN'T
YOU MENTION THIS BEFORE?!
Killua: STOP YELLING.
THEY'LL NOTICE US.
BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
I KNEW IT AS SOON AS I SAW THEM.
A WHILE BACK, MY DAD
KILLED A SPIDER FOR A JOB.
‐ ( Gon gasps )
‐ Leorio: WHAT?
Killua: HE DOESN'T
COMPLAIN MUCH,
BUT HE SAID THE JOB
WASN'T WORTH THE PRICE,
AND THAT IS THE HIGHEST
COMPLIMENT HE GIVES A TARGET.
HE EVEN GOT ALL OF US TOGETHER
AND TOLD US
WE SHOULD STEER CLEAR
OF THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
BUT THAT WAS YEARS AGO,
SO I THOUGHT
WE MIGHT STAND A CHANCE.
Leorio: THEY CAN'T BE
THAT STRONG, CAN THEY?
Killua: JUST IMAGINE IF
THE PEOPLE SITTING AT THAT TABLE
WERE BOTH HISOKAS.
♪
Leorio: I GUESS IT'S SAFE TO SAY
THAT'S A LOT MORE
THAN WE CAN HANDLE.
Killua: OKAY. SO WHAT DO
YOU THINK THEY'RE DOING HERE?
Leorio: THEY'RE DATING.
IT'S A DATE. RIGHT?
Gon: WAIT. IS IT, REALLY?
Killua: NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THEY NOTICED
THAT OTHER COUPLE BEHIND THEM.
I CAN TELL THEY'RE
PAYING CLOSE ATTENTION
TO THEIR SURROUNDINGS.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
JUST BEING CAUTIOUS
SINCE THE MAFIA'S AFTER THEM,
BUT IF THAT WAS THE CASE,
THEY WOULDN'T BE SITTING
IN A PUBLIC AREA LIKE THAT.
INSTEAD, THEY ACT LIKE THEY
DON'T HAVE A CARE IN THE WORLD.
♪
THEY'RE WAITING
FOR SOMEONE TO FIND THEM,
ACTING AS BAIT, AND TRYING
TO DRAW OUT THEIR PREY.
Nobunaga: WE'RE BEING OBSERVED.
Machi: AND THEY'RE NOT AMATEURS.
Nobunaga: YEAH.
I CAN'T TELL WHERE THEY ARE.
THEY'RE WATCHING US.
Machi: IS IT THE CHAIN USER?
Nobunaga: NO IDEA, BUT IF IT IS,
THE BOSS GAVE US FREE REIGN
TO DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
Machi: I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I GOT
THE DISTINCT IMPRESSION
HE WANTS US TO RECRUIT HIM.
Nobunaga: MACHI...
THE BOSS SAID TO FIND HIM
AND BRING HIM BACK.
THOSE WERE OUR ONLY ORDERS.
COME ON. YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
ALL ABOUT THE UNSPOKEN RULE,
HAVE YOU?
"ALIVE OR DEAD
AND BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY"?
YOU'RE WELCOME
TO INTERPRET THE BOSS'S ORDERS
ANY WAY YOU SEE FIT,
BUT YOU CAN'T FORCE ME
INTO AGREEING WITH YOU.
Machi: DON'T PUT WORDS
IN MY MOUTH, ALL RIGHT?
BESIDES, YOU'RE THE ONE
FORCING THE ISSUE.
♪
( all gasp )
Killua: THE ATMOSPHERE
HAS CHANGED.
Gon: I'M GETTING A BAD FEELING.
Leorio: DO YOU THINK
THEY NOTICED US?
Killua: NOT YET.
WE'RE STILL IN THE CLEAR.
Leorio: YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
REMEMBER, I CAN'T USE ZETSU
TO MASK MY PRESENCE
LIKE THE TWO OF YOU.
Killua: ZETSU WOULD
ATTRACT ATTENTION,
SO WE CAN'T USE IT HERE.
THEY CAN SENSE NEN,
BUT THEY AREN'T TRYING.
THEY'RE LOOKING
AT PEOPLE IN THE AREA,
TRYING TO FIND ANYONE
WHO ACTS SUSPICIOUS.
BE CAREFUL.
AND WIPE THOSE LOOKS
OFF YOUR FACES.
JUST ACT NATURAL.
( both chuckle )
Killua: YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET IT.
Nobunaga: LET'S DECIDE
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
ARE WE GOING TO TAKE HIM DEAD
OR TRY TO BRING HIM IN ALIVE?
Machi: OH, ALL RIGHT.
Nobunaga: HEADS.
Machi: TAILS, THEN.
♪
‐ Chrollo: HER?
‐ Shalnark: YEAH.
SHE'S NOSTRADE'S DAUGHTER.
HER NAME'S NEON.
ACCORDING TO THE INFORMATION
ON THE HUNTER WEBSITE,
THE CHAIN USER WE'RE LOOKING FOR
IS ONE OF HER BODYGUARDS.
AS FOR THE REST
OF HER BODYGUARDS,
WE HAVE PICTURES AND NAMES
FOR THESE FIVE HERE.
Chrollo: THIS GIRL,
SHE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR NOSTRADE'S SUCCESS?
Shalnark: MOST LIKELY.
THE INFO'S
ON THE HUNTER WEBSITE,
SO IT SHOULD BE ACCURATE.
Nostrade: I SEE.
SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
GETTING A NEW ROOM
WAS A SMART MOVE.
THE PHANTOM TROUPE
IS USING THE HUNTER WEBSITE.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
NEON WOULDN'T BE SAFE RIGHT NOW
WITHOUT YOUR QUICK THINKING.
THANK YOU.
NOW, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
WE NEED TO TRANSPORT MY DAUGHTER
HOME URGENTLY.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU, NEON?
Neon: IT SOUNDS LIKE
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WITH THE AUCTION CANCELED,
I DON'T SEE ANY POINT
IN BEING HERE,
AND THAT MAKES ME SAD, BECAUSE I
REALLY WANTED TO GO TO THAT.
Nostrade: THEY'LL HOLD ANOTHER
AUCTION NEXT YEAR, PUMPKIN,
SO DON'T BE SAD. AND I PROMISE
I'LL RECOVER THE ITEMS
YOU WANTED FROM THOSE BANDITS
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO.
Neon: REALLY?
Nostrade: OF COURSE, MY DEAR.
I PROMISE.
AND HAVE I EVER IN YOUR LIFE
BROKEN A PROMISE TO YOU?
Neon: WELL, YEAH,
MORE THAN YOU'VE KEPT.
( Nostrade laughs )
ALL RIGHT, YOU GOT ME.
YOUR NAMES ARE MELODY
AND BASHO, YES?
Both: YES.
Nostrade: YOU TWO TAKE NEON
BACK TO THE MANSION IMMEDIATELY.
BE SAFE. I WANT YOU BOTH
WEARING SIMPLE DISGUISES.
( bodyguards grunt )
Nostrade: NOW, NEON,
GO BACK TO YOUR ROOM,
AND PACK UP YOUR THINGS.
Neon: OKAY.
Nostrade: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
♪
THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION
WILL BE RESUMING TONIGHT.
( bodyguards gasp )
Nostrade: THE TIME AND PLACE
HAVEN'T CHANGED.
THE COMMUNITY MUST DEMONSTRATE
THAT THEY WILL NOT BE
INTIMIDATED BY ANYONE.
THE TEN DONS
HAVE VOWED TO RECOVER
ALL OF THE STOLEN MERCHANDISE.
Kurapika: BUT, SIR...
AS I MENTIONED EARLIER,
THE MAN WE CAPTURED
GAVE UP INFORMATION.
HE CLAIMED THAT A SHADOW BEAST
TOOK EVERYTHING
BEFORE THEY EVEN ARRIVED.
Nostrade: YES,
THAT MUCH IS TRUE.
HOWEVER, ALL OF
THE SHADOW BEASTS ARE DEAD.
( both gasp )
Nostrade: NINE BODIES
HAVE BEEN RECOVERED.
THE FINAL MEMBER, THE OWL,
WAS THE ONE IN CHARGE
OF TRANSPORTING THE MERCHANDISE.
HE WAS PROBABLY CAPTURED
BY THE TROUPE.
THE TEN DONS UNDERSTAND
HOW FRIGHTENING NEN CAN BE.
IF A TROUPE MEMBER
CAN COMPEL A CONFESSION,
THEY WON'T NEED
TO RESORT TO TORTURE.
WE THINK
THE MERCHANDISE THE OWL TOOK
HAS FALLEN
INTO THE TROUPE'S HANDS...
SO AS I WAS JUST SAYING,
WITH ALL
THE SHADOW BEASTS DESTROYED,
THE TEN DONS WILL HIRE PROS
TO HANDLE THE TROUPE.
Kurapika: SIR?
♪
Kurapika: THE MAFIA USES MURDER
AS A TOOL OF INTIMIDATION,
BUT IT'S NOT OUR AREA
OF EXPERTISE.
CONSIDERING THE NATURE
OF OUR OPPONENTS,
IT WOULD BE WISE FOR US
TO LEAVE IT TO THE EXPERTS.
WE'LL HAVE THEM
CRUSH THE TROUPE ON OUR BEHALF
WHILE AVOIDING
FURTHER LOSSES OURSELVES.
HOWEVER, IT'S A CHANCE FOR US
TO BUILD OUR REPUTATION.
WE CAN'T ALLOW THE ASSASSINS
TO TAKE ALL THE CREDIT,
AND SO, KURAPIKA, I WANT YOU
TO JOIN THE ASSASSIN TEAM.
Chrollo: TAKE CARE
OF THE CHAIN USER FOR ME.
Shalnark: WILL DO.
Killua: THEY'RE ON THE MOVE.
NOW WHAT?
LIKE I SAID,
WE CAN'T BEAT THEM IN A FIGHT.
Leorio: WE'LL FIGURE OUT A WAY.
FAILURE'S NOT REALLY AN OPTION.
Gon: HE'S RIGHT. WE CAN'T
LEAVE EMPTY‐HANDED, NOT NOW.
( Killua grunts )
OKAY, FINE.
BUT LISTEN.
GON AND I WILL TRACK THEM,
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
WE CAN'T LET THEM SPOT US,
WHICH MEANS WE'LL
HAVE TO USE ZETSU. GOT IT?
♪
Leorio: WOW.
I CAN SEE THEM STANDING HERE,
BUT I CAN'T SENSE THEM.
Leorio: HEY, GON,
PROMISE ME TWO THINGS.
IF THEY SEE US, WE GIVE UP
IMMEDIATELY AND RETREAT,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED,
SAME IF I SAY FURTHER PURSUIT
IS IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ANY OTHER REASON. OKAY?
Gon: OKAY.
Killua: THE SIGNAL TO ABORT
WILL BE ONE RING.
MAKE SURE
YOUR PHONE IS ON VIBRATE.
IF THEY SPLIT UP,
WE FOLLOW THE WOMAN.
LEORIO, CALL ZEPILE, AND KEEP
AN EYE ON THE AUCTION FOR US.
Leorio: NO PROBLEM.
Killua: I'M GUESSING YOU'VE
NEVER TRACKED ANYONE BEFORE.
Gon: OH, UH, YEAH, KINDA.
I TRACKED HISOKA
DURING THE EXAM.
Killua: REALLY?
AND HE DIDN'T NOTICE YOU?
Gon: NO. I SHADOWED HIM
PRETTY MUCH THE WHOLE DAY.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT!
NOT TOO SHABBY!
Gon: THAT HURT!
WHAT DID YOU HIT ME FOR?
Killua: HUH? OH, NO REASON.
WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE A PROBLEM, THEN.
JUST BE SURE TO STAY OUT
OF THEIR FIELD OF VISION,
NO MATTER WHAT.
OKAY, READY TO GO?
‐ Leorio: YEAH!
‐ Gon: YEAH!
♪
Killua: THE TARGETS
HAVE PASSED THE PLAZA
AND GONE DOWN A SIDE STREET.
( Gon on phone )
ROGER THAT.
DO YOU THINK
THEY KNOW WE'RE HERE?
Killua: IT'S FINE.
WE'RE USING ZETSU,
SO THEY WON'T,
UNLESS SOMETHING GOES WRONG.
BUT THEY'RE EXPECTING SOMEONE
TO FOLLOW THEM, SO BE CAREFUL.
Gon: OKAY. YOU, TOO, KILLUA.
( Killua sighs ) HE'S REALLY
TELLING ME TO BE CAREFUL?
I'M THE ONE ON HIGH ALERT,
LOOKING FOR CHANGES
IN THEIR BEHAVIOR.
GOOD. THEY HAVEN'T NOTICED US.
WHEN THEY REALIZE WE'RE HERE,
THEY'RE BOUND TO REACT SOMEHOW.
THEY CAN TRY TO HIDE IT,
BUT THEIR FACES OR GESTURES
WILL GIVE 'EM AWAY.
( no audible dialogue )
I'VE BEEN PLAYING
LIFE‐OR‐DEATH
GAMES OF SHADOW
EVER SINCE I WAS THREE.
I WON'T LOSE SIGHT OF THEM.
I CAN'T.
Machi: ARE WE BEING FOLLOWED?
Nobunaga: YES, MOST LIKELY.
IT'S A PRETTY GOOD BET, ANYWAY.
GUESS THEY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
I DON'T SENSE A DAMN THING.
Machi: THEY MUST BE
QUITE SKILLED.
( footsteps pattering )
Killua: DAMN.
THEY'RE MOVING TOWARD
A DESERTED PART OF THE CITY.
MAYBE THEY FIGURED OUT
THEY'RE BEING FOLLOWED.
SO COULD THIS BE A TRAP?
NO. THEY DON'T KNOW
OUR EXACT LOCATIONS.
UNLESS THEY DON'T KNOW
THEY'RE BEING FOLLOWED
AND THEY'RE HEADING
BACK TO THEIR HIDEOUT.
THAT'D BE A HUGE WIN FOR US.
SO A TRAP OR THEIR HIDEOUT,
WHICH IS IT?
IF IT'S A TRAP, WE BAIL.
HIDEOUT,
WE KEEP FOLLOWING THEM.
THERE'S NOTHING UNNATURAL
IN THEIR BEHAVIOR.
WE KEEP GOING.
( wind blowing )
Machi: OUR STALKER
ISN'T TAKING THE BAIT.
Nobunaga: WHICH MEANS THAT IT'S
PROBABLY NOT THE CHAIN USER.
Machi: WHY'S THAT?
Nobunaga: I CAN SENSE
MULTIPLE PEOPLE TAILING US,
BUT THE CHAIN USER
PROBABLY WORKS ALONE.
Machi: THINK SO?
Nobunaga: YEAH,
HE WORKS AS A BODYGUARD
FOR THE NOSTRADE FAMILY, RIGHT?
YET HE MANAGED TO DEFEAT UVO
COMPLETELY ON HIS OWN,
AND THAT'S NO EASY TASK.
BUT THE MAFIA
HASN'T TAKEN ANY ACTION,
WHICH SUPPORTS MY THEORY.
IF THEY WERE RESPONSIBLE,
THEY'D BE USING UVO
TO THREATEN US,
WHETHER HE WAS DEAD OR ALIVE.
HEH. NOT TO MENTION THE NEWS
WOULD PROBABLY BE
ALL OVER THE WEB BY NOW.
SINCE IT'S NOT, THE CHAIN USER
PROBABLY DEFEATED UVO ALONE,
WITHOUT EVER REPORTING IT
TO THE MAFIA.
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE WITH TIES
TO THE MAFIA WORK ALONE?
PROBABLY A PERSONAL GRUDGE.
Machi: "PROBABLY," HUH?
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THAT A LOT.
Nobunaga: OH, SHUT UP.
IF HE WENT OUT SEEKING REVENGE
WITHOUT MAFIA BACKUP,
I DOUBT THAT HE'D BE
TEAMING UP WITH SOMEONE ELSE,
THUS THE CHAIN USER WORKS ALONE.
THE GROUP FOLLOWING US
IS TOTALLY UNRELATED.
Machi: IMPRESSIVE
HOW FULL OF HOLES YOUR LOGIC IS.
Nobunaga: OKAY, FINE, THEN.
LET'S HEAR WHAT YOU THINK.
Machi: ALL RIGHT,
IF YOU REALLY MUST KNOW,
I SUSPECT THAT THERE'S A LINK
BETWEEN THESE GUYS
AND THE CHAIN USER.
Nobunaga: HUNCH AGAIN?
Machi: IT IS.
Nobunaga:
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
PEOPLE WHO RELY
ON THEIR GUT FEELINGS
REALLY SHOULDN'T CRITICIZE
SOMEONE ELSE'S LOGIC.
Gon: SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Killua: THEY'RE WAITING
FOR SOMEONE
OR TRYING TO DRAW US OUT,
ONE OR THE OTHER.
Gon: YEAH, BUT DO YOU THINK
THEY KNOW WE'RE FOLLOWING THEM?
Killua: RIGHT NOW, IT'S 50/50.
BUT THEY DEFINITELY
DON'T KNOW OUR LOCATION.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE
TRYING TO LURE US OUT.
THEY WANT US TO SHOW OURSELVES.
Gon: WHAT DO WE DO?
Killua: THEY MIGHT BE
WAITING FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
HOLD YOUR POSITION.
( cell phone ringing below )
GON, I'M HANGING UP.
PAY CLOSE ATTENTION,
AND IF THEY REACT AT ALL,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE A RUN FOR IT,
AND DON'T STOP.
THE NEXT TIME I RING,
IT MEANS WE BAIL. GOT IT?
Gon: YEAH, I GOT IT.
( Phinks on phone )
IT'S PHINKS.
Nobunaga: OH, WHAT'S UP, PHINKS?
Phinks: JUST WANTED TO SEE
HOW YOU'RE DOING.
Nobunaga: WE WERE
BEING FOLLOWED FOR A WHILE,
BUT THEY HAVEN'T
MADE THEIR MOVE,
AND WE CAN'T LOCATE THEM,
SO THIS'LL TAKE SOME TIME.
Phinks: OH, YEAH?
THEN HOW ABOUT A HINT?
Nobunaga: WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
♪
( both gasp )
( Killua grunts )
Phinks: A DIVERSION?
Killua: GOT HIM!
HE BLOCKED IT EASILY
WITH HIS LEFT HAND
( grunting )
( Phinks whistles )
‐ Nobunaga: HEY.
‐ ( Killua gasps )
Nobunaga: HELLO, PHINKS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I SWEAR I WAS TOLD THAT YOU
WERE HEADING OUT WITH THE BOSS.
Killua: THIS IS
THE FOURTH FLOOR.
Phinks: WELL, LIKE THEY SAY,
"DECEIVE YOUR ALLIES
TO DECEIVE YOUR ENEMIES."
( Nobunaga laughs )
LOOKS LIKE THE BOSS
GOT ME GOOD AGAIN.
ZETSU MASTERS
ALL OVER THE PLACE?
GUESS I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
Killua: THEY TAILED US
WHILE WE TAILED THEM,
AND OUR TARGETS DIDN'T KNOW?
THEY TRICKED US.
Nobunaga: SO, KIDDO,
I'VE GOT A COUPLE
OF QUESTIONS FOR YOU.
( Gon gasps )
Pakunoda: DO YOU KNOW
THE CHAIN USER?
AND THINK BEFORE YOU ANSWER.
( Gon gasps )
Machi: HE'S A NEN USER
WHO FIGHTS WITH CHAINS.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIND HIM.
IS HE THE ONE
WHO ASKED YOU TO FOLLOW US?
WAS THIS HIS IDEA?
Gon: I DON'T KNOW HIM.
WE FOLLOWED YOU TWO
FOR OUR OWN REASONS
AND NOT ANYBODY ELSE'S.
I JUST NEED A SPLIT SECOND,
AN OPENING TO GET AWAY.
Machi: YOUR THOUGHTS?
Pakunoda: I JUST CAN'T TELL.
IF HE'S LYING,
HE'S CERTAINLY GOOD AT IT.
WHY DON'T I CHECK?
Nobunaga: QUESTION ONE, WHY WERE
YOU FOLLOWING US? BE CONCISE.
Killua: A BAD LIE
WILL MAKE THINGS WORSE.
BECAUSE THE MAFIA HAS PUT OUT
A HUGE BOUNTY ON YOUR HEADS.
WEBSITES ARE OFFERING
A LOT OF MONEY
JUST FOR INFORMATION
ON YOUR WHEREABOUTS.
Nobunaga: QUESTION TWO,
WHO TAUGHT YOU TO TRACK PEOPLE?
Killua: I GUESS MAINLY I USED
A NEN ABILITY TO HIDE MYSELF
CALLED ZETSU.
SEE, I WANT TO BE A PRO HUNTER.
Nobunaga: WHO TAUGHT YOU
TO DO THAT?
Killua: IT WAS
A SHINGEN‐RYU MASTER.
Nobunaga: AND THREE,
DO YOU KNOW A NEN USER
WHO FIGHTS WITH CHAINS?
Killua: FIGHTS WITH CHAINS?
Nobunaga: HE'D BE
A CONJURER OR MANIPULATOR.
Phinks: WE WANT TO KNOW
IF YOUR MASTER
HAS CHAINS HANGING
FROM HIS RIGHT ARM.
OR IS IT YOU? YOU SHOULD
COME CLEAN RIGHT NOW IF IT IS.
Killua: I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
MY MASTER IS AN ENHANCER,
AND HE JUST TAUGHT ME THE FOUR
BASIC EXERCISES, NOTHING MORE.
Nobunaga: WELL, THAT'S A PITY.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW,
WE GOT NOTHIN'.
IT'S TIME FOR THE LAST QUESTION.
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO CHOICES,
BUT THINK CAREFULLY
BEFORE YOU ANSWER.
DO YOU WANT TO DIE NOW OR LATER?
IT'S UP TO YOU.
Phinks: YOU HAVE THREE SECONDS.
( Killua gasps )
( cell phone buzzing )
Machi: IT'S NO USE.
DON'T TRY ANY ANYTHING.
Pakunoda: YES.
UNDERSTOOD. ON OUR WAY.
LITTLE BOY, THAT FRIEND OF YOURS
SURRENDERED QUIETLY.
( Gon gasps )
Pakunoda: I'LL ASK AGAIN.
DO YOU KNOW THE CHAIN USER?
Gon: I ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT
BEFORE. I DON'T.
Pakunoda: I SEE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, BOY?
DO YOU HAVE ANY GUESSES?
( tires skid )
( car doors open )
( car doors close )
Pakunoda:
WELCOME TO OUR HIDEOUT.
( both gasp )
♪
Narrator: GON AND KILLUA
FIND THEMSELVES STANDING
INSIDE THE HIDEOUT
OF THE DREADED PHANTOM TROUPE,
GRIPPED BY THE ANTICIPATION
OF WHAT'S TO COME.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'RE INTRODUCING MACHI.
SHE'S PHANTOM TROUPE,
AND SHE'S A TRANSMUTER.
Killua: SHE CAN TURN HER AURA
INTO NEN THREADS.
Gon: HER BIG TECHNIQUE
IS NEN STITCHES.
SHE CAN PUT YOUR BODY
BACK TOGETHER.
Both: JUST LIKE THIS!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"ALLY AND SWORD."
GOTCHA!
( Killua buzzes
like an insect )
Gon: HEY, LOOK! I CAUGHT IT!
Killua: THAT'S ONE
OF MILLUKI'S MINI‐BOMBS.
Both: KA‐BOOM!