Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS OFF
YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( crowd cheering )
Hisoka: OHH.
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
IT'S REALLY TURNING ME ON.
♪
Narrator: GON WAS
FINALLY ABLE TO LAND
A SOLID PUNCH TO HISOKA'S FACE,
BUT WILL HE BE ABLE
TO WIN THE MATCH?
Referee: CRITICAL HIT FOR GON!
TWO POINTS!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: AMAZING!
GON MANAGED TO LAND
A CRITICAL HIT!
HE'S COME BACK FROM A DEFICIT
TO TAKE A TWO‐ONE LEAD.
GON IS ON TOP!
BUT WAIT A SECOND.
HISOKA LOOKS JUST FINE.
IN FACT, IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HE
TOOK ON VERY MUCH DAMAGE AT ALL.
THE REFEREE'S CALL
MIGHT BE OPEN TO QUESTION.
Man: THE REFEREE
IS PERFECTLY ENTITLED
TO AWARD POINTS
HOWEVER HE PLEASES.
Cocco: HUH?!
Man: AS YOU'RE AWARE,
SOME AWARD POINTS
BASED ON DAMAGE DONE,
WHILE OTHERS BASE THEIR SCORES
ON STRATEGY AND TECHNIQUE.
MY PERSONAL OPINION IS THAT
IN THIS CASE THE REFEREE
WAS REWARDING THE FIGHTER
FOR USING THE STONE BLOCK
IN HIS ATTACK.
Cocco: OH, IS THAT SO?
AND WHO ARE YOU?
Gon: OKAY.
( crowd cheering )
( overlapping chatter )
Cocco: OH! LOOK AT THAT!
HISOKA HAS MOVED FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE THE FIGHT STARTED.
AND IS THAT A HINT
OF A SMILE I SEE?
CAN THIS MEAN THAT HE'S
FINALLY GETTING SERIOUS?
♪
WHOA!
OHH.
♪
WHOA!
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
I HAVE NO IDEA!
Hisoka: ONE QUESTION.
HOW MUCH HAVE YOU
LEARNED ABOUT NEN?
Gon: I KNOW ALL THE BASICS.
Hisoka: AH. THAT MEANS
YOU'RE AN ENHANCER.
( Gon gasps ) BUT HOW
THE HELL DID YOU KNOW THAT?
( Hisoka laughs )
YOU'RE SO ADORABLE
AND NOT VERY GOOD
AT KEEPING SECRETS, ARE YOU?
( Gon groans )
SHUT YOUR BIG MOUTH!
JUST TELL ME HOW YOU KNEW!
IT'S PERSONALITY ANALYSIS
BASED ON AURA TYPE.
IT'S NOT AN EXACT SCIENCE,
MUCH LIKE PERSONALITY PROFILES
BASED ONLY ON BLOOD TYPE.
ENHANCERS ARE SIMPLE
AND DETERMINED!
Killua: HE'S RIGHT.
Zushi: HE'S RIGHT.
Hisoka: OH, AND I AM
A TRANSMUTER, BY THE WAY,
BOTH WHIMSICAL AND A LIAR.
Gon: HE'S RIGHT.
Killua: HE'S RIGHT.
Hisoka: MM.
EMITTERS ARE SHORT‐TEMPERED.
SPECIALISTS
TEND TO BE INDEPENDENT.
CONJURERS ARE HIGH‐STRUNG
AND NERVOUS.
MANIPULATORS ARE ARGUMENTATIVE.
WE'RE QUITE COMPATIBLE,
YOU AND I.
OUR OPPOSING PERSONALITIES
ATTRACT.
WE COULD BECOME GREAT FRIENDS.
BUT I'D BE CAREFUL
IF I WERE YOU,
AS TRANSMUTERS
ARE KNOWN TO BE FICKLE.
WHAT WAS ONCE TREASURED
CAN EASILY BECOME TRASH.
♪
SO...
I REALLY HOPE
YOU DON'T DISAPPOINT ME, GON.
♪
( crowd roars )
‐ Killua: HE'S FAST!
‐ ( Gon gasps )
( crowd gasps )
Cocco: THAT WAS
ONE POWERFUL KICK!
HE SENT THAT STONE TILE FLYING
ALL THE WAY TO THE ENTRANCE!
( Gon gasps )
Cocco:
LOOK AT THAT SPEED, FOLKS!
HISOKA IS SHOWING
HIS TRUE POWER!
Referee: CRITICAL HIT, HISOKA,
BRINGING THE SCORE TO THREE‐TWO!
Cocco: HIS NONSTOP
FLURRY OF ATTACKS
HAS BEEN SCORED A CRITICAL HIT,
AND HISOKA REGAINS THE LEAD.
( Gon panting )
Cocco: GON LOOKS CONFUSED
AND IS BACKING OFF.
CAN'T HE FIGHT BACK?
Zushi: AMAZING. TOO AMAZING.
Hisoka: WHAT'S WRONG?
COME ON. ATTACK ME.
Gon: DON'T WANNA. I'M THINKING!
I CAN BARELY FOLLOW HIM
WITH MY EYES,
AND THE REST OF MY BODY
JUST CAN'T KEEP UP.
AT THIS RATE,
HE'LL BEAT THE CRAP OUT OF ME.
Hisoka: HMM. VERY WELL.
IF YOU WON'T COME WILLINGLY,
I SUPPOSE
I'LL HAVE TO FORCE YOU.
♪
Killua: YOU'VE GOTTA USE GYO!
Gon: DAMN IT!
Hisoka: DO YOU EVEN
HAVE THE SLIGHTEST IDEA
WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN?
( Gon grunting )
( yells )
Cocco: WHOA! LOOK AT THAT!
GON IS BEING DRAWN
TOWARD HISOKA!
( tears splash )
( gagging )
Hisoka: THIS IS MY ELASTIC LOVE,
BETTER KNOWN AS BUNGEE GUM.
IT CAN EXPAND
AS WELL AS CONTRACT,
ATTACH AND DETACH AS I DESIRE.
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: YOU WILL
NEVER ESCAPE ME NOW.
( crowd cheering )
♪
Referee: CRITICAL HIT
AND KNOCKDOWN!
THREE POINTS AWARDED TO HISOKA!
SIX TO TWO!
( Gon gasping )
Cocco: HISOKA CLOBBERS GON
WITH A STRONG RIGHT,
AND GON IS DOWN!
Wing: HIS AURA TURNS
INTO A RUBBERY SUBSTANCE
THAT ATTACHES TO OTHER OBJECTS.
Gon: BUNGEE GUM.
Killua: ONLY HISOKA
CAN ATTACH AND DETACH IT.
Hisoka: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STAND UP, GON.
Gon: DAMN IT.
Cocco: IT'S SIX TO TWO!
HISOKA HAS WIDENED HIS LEAD
EVEN MORE!
IS HE ABOUT TO CLAIM
YET ANOTHER VICTORY
IN HIS UNDEFEATED STREAK?
‐ Man #2: HEY! GET UP, KID!
‐ Man #3: COME ON, REF!
YOU'RE TOTALLY FAVORING HISOKA!
Man #4: YOU CAN DO IT, GON!
Referee: CAN YOU FIGHT?
Gon: OF COURSE.
( gasps )
Cocco: OH!
GON IS BACK ON HIS FEET!
BUT YOU CAN TELL HE'S REALLY
TAKEN A BEATING OUT THERE!
Hisoka: NOW HERE'S
A QUESTION FOR YOU,
AND IF YOU ANSWER IT CORRECTLY,
I'LL GIVE YOU A FREE HIT.
Gon: YOU WILL?
Hisoka: AT WHAT POINT
DURING THIS MATCH
DID I ATTACH MY BUNGEE GUM
TO YOUR CHEEK?
Gon: WHEN DID HE ATTACH IT?
Hisoka: ONE, WHEN I ELBOWED YOU?
TWO, WHEN I LANDED A CLEAN HIT?
THREE, WHEN I LANDED
THE CRITICAL HIT?
Gon: WHEN WAS IT?
NUMBER THREE! IT WAS WHEN
YOU HIT ME WITH BOTH HANDS!
Hisoka: WRONG!
THE ANSWER IS FOUR.
IT WAS ACTUALLY
WHEN I WAS GIVING YOU
MY AURA PERSONALITY ANALYSIS.
Gon: NO FAIR!
DAMN! IF ONLY I HAD BEEN USING
GYO FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
( Hisoka chuckles )
AH, YES. ONE WORD OF CAUTION.
HAD YOU BEEN USING GYO,
THEN DURING
MY AURA PERSONALITY ANALYSIS,
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO SEE
EXACTLY WHAT MY AURA
WAS DOING THE ENTIRE TIME
AND AVOIDED IT QUITE EASILY.
BUT WHAT ABOUT SITUATIONS
ONE, TWO, AND THREE?
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: HAVE YOU FIGURED IT OUT?
I COULD ALSO HAVE ATTACHED
MY BUNGEE GUM TO YOU
WHILE ATTACKING YOU DIRECTLY.
YOU ONLY NEED
TO CONCEAL YOUR AURA
WHEN YOU WISH TO CATCH
YOUR OPPONENT OFF GUARD.
NORMALLY YOU USE YOUR AURA
WHEN ATTACKING.
IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
IF YOUR OPPONENT
CAN SEE YOUR AURA
WHILE YOU'RE LANDING ATTACKS.
Gon: HE'S RIGHT.
IF I CAN'T DODGE HIS ATTACKS,
USING GYO TO SEE HIS AURA
WON'T DO ME ANY GOOD AT ALL.
Killua: THIS IS BAD.
HIS POWER'S WAY MORE DANGEROUS
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
Zushi: SO YOU'VE GOTTA DODGE
ALL OF HISOKA'S ATTACKS.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
THAT YOU'RE EVER GONNA KEEP HIM
FROM ATTACHING
BUNGEE GUM TO YOU.
BUT IF YOU'RE ABLE TO DEFEND...
Wing: DEFENSE
WOULDN'T BE EFFECTIVE.
HE CAN ATTACH HIS AURA
TO THE PART YOU BLOCK WITH.
( Zushi groans, sighs )
Gon: I CAN'T ESCAPE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Hisoka: THAT'S ENOUGH TALK
FOR THE TIME BEING.
NOW WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE BEGIN PREPARING FOR BATTLE?
RESUME.
♪
Gon: IF I CAN'T ESCAPE...
I'LL GO FORWARD!
♪
( Hisoka sighs )
GON. GON!
THAT'S GOOD.
YOU'RE SO VERY GOOD.
THOSE EYES.
THAT LOOK.
THAT SPIRIT.
( moaning )
I JUST CAN'T WAIT
TO BREAK YOU.
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: OH, BUT, NO, NOT YET.
‐ ( crowd roars )
‐ Cocco: WHOA!
Hisoka: MORE. MORE!
UNTIL IT'S ALMOST A SHAME
TO DESTROY YOU.
Cocco: OH! THAT'S GOTTA HURT!
Hisoka: UNTIL YOU'VE MATURED.
Cocco: LOOK AT HIM GO, FOLKS!
Hisoka: UNTIL YOU'VE REACHED
SOARING NEW HEIGHTS.
UHH!
PATIENCE.
Cocco: A VICIOUS ASSAULT!
( Hisoka moans )
( Gon groans )
Cocco: OH! NOT AGAIN!
HISOKA DRAWS GON RIGHT INTO
ANOTHER EPIC LEFT UPPERCUT!
Gon: GOOD! I BLOCKED THAT ONE.
I'M GETTING USED
TO HIS BUNGEE GUM
YANKING ME AROUND
ALL OVER THE PLACE,
BUT IT'S NOT OVER, NOT YET.
I'M SCARED,
BUT I CAN'T LET
MY FEAR TAKE OVER.
IF I DO, I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIGHT ANYONE ELSE AGAIN!
Referee BOTH CRITICAL HITS!
THAT'S TWO MORE POINTS!
PLUS A KNOCKDOWN
AWARDED TO HISOKA!
( Gon gasps )
Referee: THAT'S NINE POINTS
FOR HISOKA
AND FOUR POINTS FOR GON!
Gon: BUT HE NEVER
KNOCKED ME DOWN,
AND I EVEN BLOCKED HIS ATTACK!
Man #2: WHAT?
Man #3: SOMETHING'S UP
WITH THIS REF!
Man #4: GIVE ME A BREAK, REF!
GET YOUR EYES CHECKED!
Cocco: OKAY, WE HAVE YET
ANOTHER INTERESTING CALL.
THE CROWD'S NOT PLEASED
WITH THE REF'S DECISION,
AND THEY'RE REALLY
LETTING HIM HEAR IT.
Referee: FIGHT!
( Gon groans )
♪
IF HE GETS 10 POINTS, I LOSE.
I ONLY HAVE ONE POINT LEFT.
HE DOESN'T NEED A KNOCKDOWN.
IF JUST ONE MORE ATTACK
HITS ME, IT'S OVER.
( Hisoka chuckles )
YOU SHOULD BE
MORE VIGILANT, GON.
TAKE A LOOK OVER TO THE RIGHT.
♪
I'M SO SORRY. I SUPPOSE WHAT
I MEANT TO SAY WAS MY RIGHT.
Referee: AND THAT'S ANOTHER
KNOCKDOWN AND A CLEAN HIT!
TWO MORE POINTS AWARDED!
11 TO FOUR!
THE WINNER BY T. K. O. IS HISOKA!
Gon: HUH?
( crowd cheering )
( Killua sighs )
Hisoka: WHILE YOU WERE BUSY
PLEADING YOUR CASE
TO THE REFEREE,
I SENT THE AURA ON MY LEFT HAND
TO THE STONE.
Referee: THAT'S NINE POINTS
FOR HISOKA
AND FOUR POINTS FOR GON!
Hisoka: WHEN I SAW MY OPENING,
I ACTIVATED THE BUNGEE GUM.
♪
( Gon gasps )
HUH? IS IT REALLY OVER?
Hisoka: YOU'VE MADE PROGRESS,
BUT YOU DO STILL
LACK EXPERIENCE.
IF WE HAD 10 MORE MATCHES,
I BELIEVE WE MIGHT ACTUALLY
HAVE A GOOD FIGHT.
OF COURSE,
THAT'S ASSUMING THOSE FIGHTS
TAKE PLACE HERE
IN HEAVENS ARENA.
THEREFORE I WILL NOT BE
FIGHTING YOU HERE AGAIN.
OUR NEXT FIGHT WILL BE
IN THE REAL WORLD,
WITHOUT RULES TO HINDER US,
WITH OUR LIVES ON THE LINE.
Gon: HE'S SO FAR BEYOND ME,
BUT HE'S NOT SO FAR OUT OF REACH
I CAN'T CATCH UP SOMEDAY.
I NEED MORE TRAINING IN NEN.
I'VE GOTTA FIND A POWER
THAT'S AS STRONG AS HISOKA'S!
Cocco: THIS VICTORY
MARKS 10 WINS FOR HISOKA
AND EARNS HIM THE RIGHT
TO CHALLENGE A FLOOR MASTER.
GON FOUGHT BRAVELY, AND WE
WISH HIM LUCK IN HIS NEXT MATCH.
WELL, THAT'S ALL FOR NOW, FOLKS.
THIS IS YOUR COMMENTATOR COCCO
SIGNING OFF.
Referee: A REFEREE
IS SUPPOSED TO BE IMPARTIAL,
BUT WITH THIS MATCHUP,
I THOUGHT IT WAS PRUDENT
TO TRY AND FINISH
THE FIGHT QUICKLY,
EVEN IF THAT MEANT THAT I
HAD TO LOWER MY STANDARDS.
Man #5: SO HE'S
A TECHNICAL JUDGE.
Man #6: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Man #5: SEE,
IF A REF THINKS A FIGHT
IS GONNA GET TOO DANGEROUS,
HE'LL AWARD POINTS LIKE CRAZY
TO TRY TO GET IT OVER WITH FAST.
‐ Man #6: OH, YEAH?
‐ Man #5: YEAH, IT'S SOMETHING
YOU GOTTA THINK ABOUT
WHEN YOU'RE PLACING A BET.
Man #7: OH, MAN! I WAS SURE
HISOKA WAS GONNA WIN 10‐NOTHIN'.
Wing: ABOUT YOUR FIGHT
WITH HISOKA,
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN TELL YOU.
YOU UNDERSTAND
BETTER THAN ANYONE,
HAVING FACED HIM YOURSELF.
‐ ( Gon laughs )
‐ Killua: "UNDERSTAND"?
Wing: WHAT HE LEARNED
DURING THAT FIGHT, OF COURSE.
Gon: RIGHT!
Killua: WHAT EXACTLY
DID YOU LEARN?
Gon: IT'S SECRET.
( Killua scoffs )
Wing: GON, KILLUA,
AS YOU CONTINUE ON YOUR PATHS,
IT WILL BECOME
EVER MORE IMPORTANT
TO MASTER
YOUR VERY OWN STYLES OF NEN.
‐ Gon: YES!
‐ Killua: YEAH.
Zushi: I'M REALLY GLAD I GOT
THE CHANCE TO MEET BOTH OF YOU.
I LOOK FORWARD TO TRAINING HARD
SO I CAN SURPASS YOU ONE DAY
Killua: YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN SURPASS US?
Zushi: I PROMISE YOU I WILL.
Killua: NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
Gon: CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU DO IT, ZUSHI.
Zushi: OSU! ( laughs )
Killua: WELL, LET'S GO.
Gon: 'KAY. BYE, MR. WING,
AND THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING!
Killua: YEAH. THANKS A LOT
FOR ALL YOUR HELP, WING.
Wing: YOU BOYS
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELVES.
Gon: BYE, ZUSHI! SEE YOU LATER!
Zushi: OSU! HEH.
♪
Killua: WELL, YOU FINALLY
ACCOMPLISHED YOUR GOAL,
‐ HUH, GON?
‐ Gon: YEP.
Killua: NO REASON FOR US
TO STICK AROUND ANYMORE THEN.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA TO DO NEXT?
Gon: I'M GOING BACK
TO WHALE ISLAND.
Killua: WHALE ISLAND?
Gon: YEAH. SINCE I WAS
ABLE TO PAY BACK HISOKA,
I WANT TO GO BACK HOME
AND FINALLY SHOW AUNT MITO
MY HUNTER'S LICENSE.
IT'S CRAZY. I HAVEN'T BEEN HOME
IN OVER SIX MONTHS.
Killua: I GUESS
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
‐ Gon: HUH?
‐ Killua: YEAH.
I REALLY WANT TO MEET AUNT MITO.
Gon: YOU DO?
THEN LET'S GO TOGETHER.
Killua: SURE.
I'LL JUST TAG ALONG.
Gon: BYE‐BYE, HEAVENS ARENA.
♪
Narrator: GON FULFILLED
HIS PROMISE TO PUNCH HISOKA
AND RETURN HIS BADGE TO HIM.
DESPITE LOSING THE FIGHT,
GON WAS SATISFIED THAT HE HAD
ACHIEVED HIS GOAL AT LONG LAST.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY, WE'RE INTRODUCING...
‐ Killua: GON!
‐ Gon: WHO, ME?
Killua: GON BECAME
MY VERY FIRST FRIEND
WHEN WE MET AT THE HUNTER EXAM.
HE'S FUN TO BE AROUND,
BECAUSE HIS EXPRESSIONS
ARE ALWAYS CHANGING,
AND YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT HE'S THINKING. ( chuckles )
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME, "GING AND GON."
HEY, WANNA COME
TO MY HOUSE, KILLUA?
Killua: I‐I'M NOT V‐VERY USEFUL,
B‐BUT T‐THANKS
FOR LETTING ME STAY OVER!
Gon: YOU'RE STUTTERING.