( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NOW!
♪
I DID IT!
I FIGURED IT OUT.
I'VE JUST GOTTA GO
FOR THE TARGET
THE MOMENT IT GOES FOR ITS PREY!
Narrator:
ZEVIL ISLAND, DAY TWO.
GON HAS MASTERED THE TECHNIQUE
THAT WILL BE INSTRUMENTAL
IN THE CAPTURE OF HIS TARGET.
( bird chirping )
( Gon winces )
OW! MY HANDS ARE ALL BLOODY.
WELL, I GUESS I HAVE BEEN
CASTING MY FISHING ROD
FOR TWO STRAIGHT DAYS.
STILL, ALL THAT PRACTICE
HAS REALLY PAID OFF.
NOW WHEN A BIRD
SWOOPS DOWN ON A FISH,
I CAN SNAG IT EVERY TIME.
IF I USE IT THE RIGHT WAY,
I'LL BE ABLE TO STEAL
HISOKA'S BADGE.
ALL THAT'S LEFT NOW
IS TO FIND HIM.
( groans )
( birds squawking )
BUT HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIND HISOKA, ANYWAY?
I GUESS
I'LL JUST HAVE TO WALK AROUND
AND TRUST MY INSTINCTS
TO GUIDE ME.
WHAT THE...
WHY ARE THEY ALL
GATHERING AROUND ME LIKE THAT?
♪
HMM.
I THINK THESE BUTTERFLIES
ARE ATTRACTED
TO THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
( walkie‐talkie beeps )
Man: HAVE YOU TAKEN
YOUR TARGET'S BADGE, HISOKA?
Hisoka: NO. NOT YET.
Gittarackur: YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO YOUR TARGET IS YET, DO YOU?
Hisoka: NO.
Gittarackur:
WANT ME TO TELL YOU?
Hisoka: NO. IT DOESN'T MATTER.
( blows )
I'LL JUST HUNT DOWN
THREE OTHERS.
♪
Gon: IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
HISOKA WAS INJURED
BACK AT THE TOWER.
IF THIS WORKS, THESE BUTTERFLIES
MIGHT LEAD ME RIGHT TO HIM.
IT'S THE GUY WHO GOT SHOT
WITH THE ARROW.
OH, WELL. BETTER LUCK NEXT YEAR.
♪
THERE HE IS.
( breathing deeply )
CALM DOWN.
( deep breath )
I'LL JUST HAVE TO WAIT...
UNTIL HE MAKES HIS MOVE.
Leorio: DAMN IT. WHERE THE HELL
IS EVERYBODY HIDING?
IT'S BEEN TWO DAYS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANYONE.
‐ ( bush rustles )
‐ ( gasps )
WHO'S THERE?!
Tonpa: WHOA, HOLD ON!
IT'S JUST ME, OKAY?
Leorio: TONPA.
SO I'M YOUR TARGET.
Tonpa: HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
JUST RELAX!
I PROMISE YOU'RE NOT MY TARGET,
ALL RIGHT?
Leorio: THEN PROVE IT.
Tonpa: RIGHT.
SEE?
Leorio: HMM.
Tonpa: WHEW.
I GUESS IT'S A GOOD THING
I DIDN'T THROW IT AWAY, HUH?
THERE'S NO POINT
IN GOING AFTER JUST ANYONE.
THAT'S A HUGE WASTE
OF TIME AND ENERGY.
( gasps )
W‐W‐WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
DON'T TELL ME.
I'M NOT YOUR TARGET, AM I?
Leorio:
UNFORTUNATELY YOU'RE NOT.
Tonpa: 246.
PONZU, HUH?
Leorio: UHH! WAIT. ARE YOU
SAYING YOU KNOW WHO THAT IS?
Tonpa: ARE YOU SAYING
YOU DIDN'T?
Leorio: UH, OH, WELL, SEE, UH,
I WOULDN'T PUT IT LIKE THAT.
I JUST DIDN'T HAVE THE CHANCE
TO FIGURE IT OUT YET.
( Tonpa chuckles )
DO YOU WANT ME TO FILL YOU IN?
Leorio: WHAT?
Tonpa: WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE,
THEIR WEAPONS,
THEIR SPECIAL ABILITIES,
AND THEIR WEAKNESSES?
I WILL,
BUT I HAVE ONE CONDITION.
( stomach gurgles )
Leorio: HMM?
Tonpa: I ATE SOME NUTS
THAT AREN'T REALLY
AGREEING WITH ME.
Leorio: NUTS, YOU SAY?
Tonpa: TO BE HONEST,
I CAN BARELY STAND RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU ARE PRE‐MED, AREN'T YOU?
DO YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE
ANY MEDICINE ON HAND?
‐ ( stomach gurgles )
‐ ( groans )
Leorio: WHOA!
DON'T CRAP YOUR PANTS.
ANTIDIARRHEALS AND PRETTY MUCH
ALL THE OTHER BASICS.
Tonpa: THAT'S GREAT.
THANK YOU.
Leorio: BUT FIRST, THE INFO.
Tonpa: FINE. IF YOU INSIST.
FOR STARTERS, PONZU'S A WOMAN.
Leorio: GO ON.
Tonpa: AS FAR AS I KNOW,
OUT OF THE 24 APPLICANTS
WHO ARE LEFT,
THERE ARE ONLY FIVE OF THEM
WHO USE SOME SORT
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
PONZU IS ONE OF 'EM.
Leorio: THAT'S HER.
Tonpa: SHE HAPPENS TO SPECIALIZE
IN ALL SORTS OF TOXINS,
SO YOU'LL WANT TO BE CAREFUL.
HOWEVER, HER STRATEGY'S SIMPLE.
SHE JUST LIES IN WAIT.
Leorio: SHE DOES?
Tonpa: SHE SETS A TRAP
AND WAITS PATIENTLY
FOR HER TARGET
TO WANDER INTO IT.
Leorio: I SEE.
Tonpa: AND YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE.
SHE'S NOT
ALL THAT DAUNTING HERSELF,
SO GET HER INTO AN ACTUAL FIGHT,
AND YOU'RE GUARANTEED TO WIN.
‐ ( stomach gurgles )
‐ ( winces )
STILL, IF YOU FIND HER,
WATCH YOUR STEP,
AND REMEMBER TO STAY DOWNWIND.
SHE KNOWS
SOMEONE'S TARGETING HER,
SO IT'S NOT LIKE YOU CAN RELY
ON THE ELEMENT OF SURPRISE.
( stomach gurgles )
YOW!
AND THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
NOW GIVE ME THAT MEDICINE!
Leorio: OKAY,
BUT I NEED YOU
TO TAKE A STEP BACK.
Tonpa: OHH! JUST HURRY!
I‐I CAN'T HOLD IT IN!
( Leorio gasps )
♪
DAMN IT!
( monkey chitters )
( Sommy laughs )
LOOKS LIKE I GOT YOUR BADGE.
HEH.
Tonpa: I KNEW YOU WERE
KEEPING IT IN YOUR BRIEFCASE.
Leorio: TONPA!
YOU'RE WORKING TOGETHER?
Tonpa: YOU BET,
AND I DIDN'T NEED YOUR MEDICINE.
I'VE GOT MY OWN.
AS YOU MIGHT HAVE GUESSED,
YOU REALLY WERE MY TARGET
THIS WHOLE TIME.
Leorio: BUT THE CARD
YOU JUST SHOWED ME...
Sommy: OH, THAT ONE'S MY TARGET.
AND THIS ONE IS TONPA'S.
WE TRADED
FOR THIS LITTLE DECEPTION.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU FELL FOR IT.
Tonpa: SO THERE YOU HAVE IT!
( laughs )
Leorio: DAMN YOU!
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS!
Tonpa: WHOOPS!
( laughs )
Sommy: TONPA, LET'S MEET
AT THE RENDEZVOUS POINT!
Tonpa: GOTCHA!
Leorio: STOP RIGHT THERE!
YOU'RE DEAD! YOU HEAR ME?
Tonpa: WHY ARE YOU CHASING ME?
I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO'S GOT YOUR BADGE!
Leorio: SHUT YOUR TRAP!
Tonpa: YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
YOU STILL DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU, ROOKIE?
THAT'S A SHAME.
Leorio: WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
Tonpa: IT'S NOT OUR FAULT
YOU GOT DUPED, BUDDY!
( Leorio screams )
Tonpa: BESIDES,
FORMING ALLIANCES
IS A GREAT WAY
TO PASS THE EXAM.
Kurapika:
I CAN ACCEPT THE LATTER,
BUT NEVER THE FORMER.
Tonpa: UNH!
Kurapika: DECEPTION IS
THE FAULT OF THE DECEIVER.
Leorio: KURAPIKA!
Kurapika: LEORIO,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TEAM UP?
♪
Leorio: HMM.
HEH HEH.
( brush rustling )
Tonpa: HUMPH.
♪
Leorio: HEY!
GIVE ME BACK MY DAMN BADGE!
( Sommy laughs )
IF YOU WANT IT,
YOU GOTTA CATCH ME!
EH?
HUH?
( Kurapika chuckles )
( monkey chitters )
( animals squeaking )
Leorio: OKAY, I GOT MY BADGE
BACK SAFE AND SOUND.
Kurapika: WE HAVE THE BADGES
FOR NUMBERS 16 AND 118, AS WELL.
Leorio: SO, HEY,
IT WAS PRETTY LUCKY
THAT TONPA WAS YOUR TARGET.
YOU SAVED ME BACK THERE.
Kurapika: PLEASE,
NO THANKS NECESSARY.
I DIDN'T WANT TONPA
TO REALIZE I WAS THERE,
WHICH IS WHY I HID WHILE YOU
WERE AMBUSHED FROM BEHIND.
Leorio: WHAT?
Kurapika: IN MY DEFENSE,
I HAD TO BE SURE YOU COULD
HANDLE AN ATTACK LIKE THAT.
OTHERWISE, WHAT USE WOULD
YOU BE TO ME AS A PARTNER?
YOU QUALIFIED, THOUGH BARELY.
Leorio: YOU ARE SO FULL OF IT.
EITHER WAY,
I ADMIT IT'S A LOT EASIER
WHEN YOU JOIN FORCES.
THE NEXT FOUR DAYS,
LET'S STICK TOGETHER.
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT.
Leorio: WELL, YOU GOT
YOUR TARGET'S BADGE,
SO THAT'S A GOOD START.
ADD IT TO YOUR OWN,
AND THAT'S A TOTAL
OF SIX POINTS.
Kurapika: THAT'S ASSUMING
HE DOESN'T TAKE IT BACK.
AND NUMBER 118's BADGE
IS ONLY WORTH ONE MORE POINT
FOR EITHER OF US.
Leorio: TRUE, BUT IT
MIGHT STILL COME IN HANDY.
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT,
WE NEED TO FIND YOUR TARGET.
NUMBER 246. PONZU, RIGHT?
Leorio: WE NEED TO STAY ALERT.
Kurapika:
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT?
Leorio: RIGHT. POINT TAKEN.
♪
( Killua sighs )
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING ME
SINCE WE STARTED.
IT'S PRETTY DAMN OBVIOUS.
YOU WANNA PLAY? COME ON OUT.
( wind blowing )
( sighs )
♪
Hisoka: WELL? SHOW YOURSELF.
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
Gon: DID HE NOTICE ME?
Hisoka: IF YOU WON'T COME OUT,
I SUPPOSE
I'LL HAVE TO COME TO YOU.
Gon: THIS IS IT.
IT'S ALL OR NOTHING.
HUH?
WHEN DID HE...
( Gon gulps )
Goz: I SEEK A BOUT WITH YOU.
Hisoka: YOU'LL DIE.
Goz: MM.
♪
Gon: NOW'S MY CHANCE.
Goz: HAH!
YAAH!
Gon: IT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
I'VE JUST GOTTA WAIT
'TIL HE GOES FOR THE KILL.
Goz: YAAH!
Gon: WHY?
WHY ISN'T HISOKA FIGHTING BACK?
( Goz panting )
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY WON'T YOU FIGHT?
Hisoka: I ONLY NEED TO EVADE,
AND YOU'LL DIE EVENTUALLY, YES?
( Goz gasps )
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: I CAN TELL
BY THE LARGE SWARM
OF HEMOTROPIC BUTTERFLIES
THAT YOUR WOUNDS
ARE QUITE SERIOUS.
( Goz gasping )
Hisoka: SOMEONE HAS ALREADY
WOUNDED YOU, CORRECT?
I UNDERSTAND WANTING
TO END YOUR LIFE
FIGHTING AS A WARRIOR.
Goz: IF THAT'S TRUE
AND YOU REALLY
DO UNDERSTAND, THEN WHY?
WHY DO YOU REFUSE TO FIGHT ME
AND GRANT ME
THE DEATH I DESIRE?
Hisoka: HMM.
BECAUSE I HAVE
NO INTEREST IN THE DEAD.
Goz: WAIT. WHAT?!
BUT I'M‐‐I'M NOT‐‐
Hisoka: DO YOU KNOW
HOW I KNOW YOU'RE DEAD?
YOUR EYES.
BYE‐BYE.
( Goz gasping )
( yelling )
( groans )
( Gon gasps )
Gittarackur: SORRY.
I WAS CARELESS, AND HE GOT AWAY.
Hisoka: DON'T LIE TO ME.
HE PROBABLY BEGGED YOU
TO GRANT HIM A LAST REQUEST,
AND YOU RELENTED. AM I RIGHT?
Gittarackur: WELL, I MAY HAVE
FELT SORRY FOR THE MAN.
HE WAS GOING TO DIE ANYWAY.
Hisoka: YOU REALLY
NEED TO STOP PITYING
THOSE WHO SERVE NO PURPOSE.
Gittarackur: BUT YOU'RE
GUILTY OF THAT YOURSELF.
YOU'VE WALKED AWAY FROM
OPPONENTS BEFORE FINISHING THEM.
Hisoka: I DO HAVE STANDARDS.
WHY WASTE TIME ON PEOPLE
WHO ARE UTTERLY USELESS?
I ONLY SPARE THOSE
WHOSE PREMATURE DEATHS
WOULD BE A WASTE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT HIS BADGE?
Gittarackur:
OH, I ALREADY TOOK IT.
I HAVE SIX POINTS NOW,
SO I DON'T REALLY NEED THIS ONE.
WANT IT?
Hisoka: WHOSE IS THIS?
Gittarackur: IT BELONGS TO
SOMEONE WHO TRIED TO SNIPE ME.
THAT PISSED ME OFF,
AND SO, WELL, I KILLED 'EM.
( rattles )
WELL...
( Gon gasps )
Hisoka: HMM.
THAT'S ALWAYS
SO MUCH FUN TO WATCH.
Gittarackur: IT DOES TAKE
ITS TOLL ON ME, YOU KNOW.
AH, THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
WELL, I'M GONNA SLEEP
UNTIL THE DEADLINE.
BEST OF LUCK.
♪
Leorio: IT GOT DARK
REALLY QUICK.
Kurapika: WE SHOULDN'T
LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
NIGHTFALL IS THE BEST TIME
FOR AN AMBUSH.
Leorio: I KNOW. I KNOW.
Hisoka: ONLY TWO POINTS
LEFT TO GO.
I GUESS
I'D BETTER START HUNTING.
Gon: THIS IS IT.
♪
( insects chirping )
Hisoka: HMM?
( Gon gasps )
♪
Hisoka: HMM.
LOOK WHO IT IS.
Narrator: HISOKA TARGETS
KURAPIKA AND LEORIO,
UNAWARE THAT GON
IS AFTER HIS BADGE.
FOUR DAYS REMAIN
BEFORE THE END
OF THE FOURTH PHASE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"DEFEAT AND DISGRACE."
LET'S SHAKE HANDS.
Hisoka: WITH A NICE FIRM GRIP.