( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Buhara: COME ON!
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
( Netero laughs )
OH, I AM QUITE SERIOUS.
THE WINNERS WILL PASS THE EXAM
AND EARN THE TITLE OF HUNTER.
♪
Narrator: THE NINE
REMAINING APPLICANTS,
GON, KILLUA, KURAPIKA,
LEORIO, POKKLE,
BODORO, GITARRACKUR,
HANZO, AND HISOKA,
HAVING PASSED THE FOURTH PHASE,
HEAD TO THE SITE
OF THE FINAL PHASE OF THE EXAM.
Netero: WELL, GENTLEMEN,
EVERYONE RESTED UP? GOOD.
NOW, THEN, THE HUNTER
EXAM COMMITTEE RUNS THIS HOTEL,
SO I WANT ALL OF YOU
TO MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME
UNTIL THE BATTLES
HAVE CONCLUDED.
FOR THE FINAL PHASE
OF THE HUNTER EXAM,
YOU'LL BE COMPETING
IN A ONE‐ON‐ONE TOURNAMENT.
Leorio: HOLD ON A SECOND.
SO ONLY THE LAST PERSON
STANDING PASSES?
Netero: NO.
YOU ONLY NEED ONE WIN
TO PASS THIS PHASE.
Gon: JUST ONE?
Leorio: WAIT.
SO IN THIS TOURNAMENT...
Netero: SEE, IT'S THE WINNERS
WHO WILL DROP AWAY
AND THE LOSERS WHO WILL ADVANCE
TO THE NEXT ROUND,
WHICH MEANS THE PERSON
WHO FINISHES AT THE TOP
WILL NOT PASS.
MAKE SENSE TO EVERYONE?
Hanzo: YOU'RE SAYING THAT ONLY
ONE PERSON WILL FAIL THE EXAM.
Netero: EXACTLY.
♪
HERE IS THE BRACKET
WE'VE PUT TOGETHER.
Hanzo: HMM.
Netero: IMPRESSIVE, YES?
YOU SEE, UNDER THIS FORMAT,
EVERY COMPETITOR
HAS AT LEAST TWO CHANCES
TO WIN A ROUND.
Pokkle: YEAH, BUT SOME PEOPLE
GET FIVE CHANCES TO WIN,
LIKE NUMBERS 294 AND 405.
Bodoro: COULDN'T YOU HAVE USED
A MORE BALANCED BRACKET?
Netero: HMM.
NOW, THAT'S A FAIR QUESTION.
THIS BRACKET
WAS CAREFULLY ASSEMBLED
BASED ON EACH
OF YOUR INDIVIDUAL PERFORMANCES
THROUGHOUT THE HUNTER EXAM.
TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
THOSE WHOSE PERFORMANCES
WERE RATED HIGHLY
WILL HAVE
THE MOST CHANCES TO WIN.
Killua: I'M NOT CONVINCED.
COULD YOU EXPLAIN EXACTLY
HOW YOU SCORED OUR PERFORMANCES?
Netero: HMM.
‐ NO!
‐ ( bell rings )
Killua: WHY NOT?!
( Netero laughs )
I CAN'T SAY, BECAUSE
YOUR SCORES ARE CLASSIFIED.
I CAN'T REVEAL
YOUR ACTUAL SCORES.
HOWEVER, I CAN EXPLAIN
THE CRITERIA WE USED.
WE START WITH THE BASICS.
THERE ARE THREE CATEGORIES.
THERE'S PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
MENTAL ACUITY,
AND LASTLY OVERALL IMPRESSION.
♪
WHEN JUDGING PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
WE RELY ON AN AGGREGATE
OF AGILITY, FLEXIBILITY,
ENDURANCE, AND PERCEPTION.
FOR MENTAL ACUITY, THE AGGREGATE
CONSISTS OF RESILIENCE,
ADAPTABILITY, JUDGMENT,
AND, OF COURSE, CREATIVITY.
BUT THESE ARE
ONLY REFERENCE POINTS.
AFTER ALL, EVERY LAST ONE OF YOU
WAS STRONG ENOUGH
IN MIND AND BODY
TO REACH THE FINAL PHASE.
WE'RE MOST CONCERNED
WITH YOUR OVERALL IMPRESSION.
THIS REFERS
TO ANY INTANGIBLE FACTORS
THAT DEFY BASIC CATEGORIZATION.
( chuckles )
THINK OF IT AS OUR WAY
OF ASSESSING
YOUR POTENTIAL AS A HUNTER.
WE ROUND OUT OUR ASSESSMENT
BY INCORPORATING
THE OPINIONS OF YOUR PEERS.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
Killua: BASED ON MY PERFORMANCE,
I SHOULD BE RANKED HIGHER.
DO I HAVE
LESS POTENTIAL THAN GON?
Netero: THE RULES OF THE BATTLE
ARE REALLY QUITE SIMPLE.
WEAPONS ARE ALLOWED,
CHEATING IS FORBIDDEN,
AND IF YOUR OPPONENT
ADMITS DEFEAT, YOU WIN.
HOWEVER,
IF YOU KILL YOUR OPPONENT,
YOU WILL BE DISQUALIFIED
WITHOUT HESITATION,
AND IF THAT HAPPENS,
THE EXAM ENDS,
AND THE REMAINING
APPLICANTS PASS. GOT IT?
Examiner: LET THE FINAL PHASE
OF THE EXAM BEGIN!
( joints crack )
THE FIRST MATCH,
HANZO VERSUS GON.
ENTER!
( fanfare playing )
♪
Masta: I'M MASTA.
I'LL BE SERVING
AS REFEREE FOR THE TOURNAMENT.
GOOD LUCK, BOTH OF YOU.
Hanzo: HEY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
‐ Masta: HUH?
‐ Hanzo: YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO WAS TAILING ME AROUND
DURING THE FOURTH PHASE.
Masta: YOU NOTICED THAT,
DID YOU?
Hanzo: NATURALLY. I ASSUME
THAT EACH OF THE EXAMINERS
WAS ASSIGNED
AN EXAMINEE TO FOLLOW.
WELL, I'M SURE I WASN'T
THE ONLY ONE WHO NOTICED.
Gon: I HAD NO IDEA.
Killua: OH,
I DEFINITELY NOTICED.
Kurapika: I NOTICED, BUT DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS WORTH MENTIONING.
Leorio: UH, YEAH.
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
Hanzo: I'M VERY GRATEFUL.
YOU RECOGNIZED MY TALENT,
AND MY RANK IMPROVED
AS A RESULT.
BUT NO SURPRISE THERE, REALLY.
Masta: SURE, BUT‐‐
Hanzo: NOW, MOVING ON.
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
Masta: WHAT IS IT?
Hanzo: WE CAN ONLY WIN
IF OUR OPPONENT SURRENDERS,
CORRECT?
KNOCKING THEM UNCONSCIOUS
DOESN'T COUNT.
NO T. K. O. s EITHER?
Masta: RIGHT.
THOSE ARE THE RULES.
Hanzo: HMM. I SEE.
WELL, THIS ONE
MIGHT PROVE DIFFICULT.
♪
Gon: HE LOOKS TOUGH,
BUT WE SHOULD BE PRETTY EVEN
IN STRENGTH AND SPEED.
I'VE JUST GOTTA
KEEP HIM ON THE MOVE
'TIL I SEE AN OPENING.
Masta: NOW, TIME TO START.
Leorio: ALL RIGHT, GON. GET HIM.
Kurapika: I WONDER
HOW HE'LL DO AGAINST HANZO.
Masta: BEGIN!
Gon: I'LL KEEP SOME DISTANCE.
( gasps )
Hanzo: YOU MUST THINK YOU'RE
PRETTY QUICK ON YOUR FEET,
DON'T YOU? I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
( Gon gasping )
Hanzo: NOT HALF‐BAD
FOR A LITTLE KID.
( Killua scoffs ) I COULD HAVE
DODGED THAT. NO PROBLEM.
Hanzo: NOW, IF THIS
WERE A REGULAR MATCH,
I'D ALREADY BE DECLARED
THE WINNER.
COME ON. PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
( Gon gasping )
Hanzo: YOU MUST FEEL AWFUL.
I HIT YOU HARD ENOUGH
TO BOUNCE YOUR BRAIN
AROUND YOUR SKULL.
YOU GET IT?
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
JUST GIVE UP,
AND SPARE YOURSELF THE TROUBLE.
Gon: NO WAY.
( coughs )
Hanzo: THINK HARD ABOUT IT.
SURRENDER NOW,
AND YOU'LL HAVE ANOTHER CHANCE,
BUT BEING STUBBORN
ISN'T GONNA GET YOU ANYWHERE,
SO JUST GIVE UP.
Gon: THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN!
( blow lands )
♪
Hanzo: SAY IT.
( Gon gasping )
( blow lands )
Leorio: GON! DON'T PUSH IT!
YOU STILL HAVE
OTHER FIGHTS, SO JUST‐‐
Kurapika: LEORIO!
IF YOU WERE IN GON'S POSITION,
WOULD YOU GIVE UP?
Leorio: HELL, NO, I WOULDN'T!
HE THINKS HE'S SO TOUGH.
Kurapika: GON FEELS THE SAME.
Leorio: COME ON! I KNOW THAT!
BUT IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
HE HAS MUCH OF A CHOICE.
Kurapika: MY POINT EXACTLY,
BUT I UNDERSTAND.
( blow lands )
( thinking )
SURRENDER, GON.
THIS IS SUICIDE.
( Gon gasping )
Menchi: THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
THE CHAIRMAN'S MEAN STREAK
IS REALLY IN A CLASS BY ITSELF.
Backup: WAIT. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Menchi: NO APPLICANT WHO'S
MADE IT ALL THE WAY TO HERE
IS GOING TO SIMPLY
GIVE UP A FIGHT THAT EASILY.
Buhara: THAT'S TRUE.
Menchi: THIS FIGHT
ISN'T JUST PECULIAR.
A SYSTEM LIKE THIS
IS COMPLETELY CRAZY.
THE KID'S IN REAL DANGER.
♪
Leorio: HMM.
HEH HEH.
♪
( blows landing )
( Leorio sputtering )
Pokkle: THREE WHOLE HOURS. DAMN.
Bodoro: LOOK.
HE CAN'T EVEN VOMIT ANYMORE.
Hanzo: NOW GET UP.
( Leorio growls )
ENOUGH ALREADY!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU,
YOU HEAR ME?
PICK ON SOMEONE YOUR OWN SIZE!
Hanzo: IF YOU CAN'T HANDLE IT,
YOU'D BETTER LEAVE.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET WORSE.
Leorio: WHAT THE HELL
DID YOU SAY?
Masta: THERE'LL BE
NO INTERFERENCE
IN A ONE‐ON‐ONE MATCH.
STAY BACK. IF YOU TRY
TO HELP HIM IN ANY WAY,
GON WILL BE
INSTANTLY DISQUALIFIED.
Gon: IT'S OKAY.
LEORIO...
THIS IS‐‐
THIS IS NOTHING, REALLY.
( gasping )
I CAN STILL FIGHT HIM.
Hanzo: I'LL BREAK YOUR ARM.
♪
I'M NOT KIDDING. NOW SAY IT.
SAY YOU SURRENDER.
Gon: NEVER!
( thump )
( gasping )
Pokkle: HE ACTUALLY BROKE IT.
Hanzo: THERE.
NOW YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO USE YOUR LEFT ARM ANYMORE.
( Leorio sputtering )
DON'T TRY TO STOP ME, KURAPIKA.
IF THAT BASTARD
DOES ANYTHING ELSE,
GON WILL FAIL THE EXAM,
'CAUSE I WON'T BE
ABLE TO STOP MYSELF.
Kurapika: ME?
YOU THINK I'LL STOP YOU?
DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S NO CHANCE OF THAT.
Hanzo: I'M SURE YOU'RE
IN TOO MUCH PAIN TO LISTEN,
BUT HEAR THIS.
I'M A DESCENDANT
OF A CLANDESTINE GROUP
CALLED THE SHINOBI.
♪
FROM THE DAY I WAS BORN,
I'VE BEEN SUBJECTED
TO INTENSIVE TRAINING
IN ORDER TO MASTER
THE SPECIAL ART OF NINPO.
FOR THE PAST 18 YEARS,
I'VE TIRELESSLY TRAINED MY BODY
AND HONED MY TECHNIQUE.
BY THE TIME I WAS YOUR AGE,
I HAD ALREADY KILLED.
( Killua scoffs )
NOT LIKE IT'S THAT BIG A DEAL.
Hanzo: AT THIS POINT IN TIME,
YOU HAVE NO HOPE
OF DEFEATING ME IN COMBAT.
I'M BEING NICE.
SO JUST ADMIT DEFEAT.
Gon: OW!
DAMN IT!
BETWEEN THE PAIN
AND YOU BLABBING,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT CLEARED MY HEAD UP MORE!
Leorio: HELL, YEAH!
ATTABOY!
NOW KICK HIM WHILE HE'S DOWN,
AND HE'S FINISHED!
Gon: IF YOU'RE 18, THEN YOU'RE
JUST SIX YEARS OLDER THAN ME.
BESIDES,
THIS ISN'T A BATTLE
TO SEE WHO'S STRONGER.
IT'S TO SEE WHO'S WILLING
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL FIRST.
Hanzo: I LET YOU KICK ME,
BECAUSE I WANTED TO.
Leorio: YOU'RE A LIAR!
Hanzo: YOU MUST BE CONFUSED.
THAT WAS NOT A WARNING.
IT WAS A DIRECT ORDER.
WAS IT TOO HARD
FOR YOU TO UNDERSTAND?
I'M QUITE HAPPY
TO BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU.
I'LL CUT OFF YOUR LEGS SO THAT
THEY CAN'T BE REATTACHED.
A PERMANENT INJURY
SHOULD OPEN UP YOUR EYES
TO THE CURRENT SITUATION,
BUT BEFORE WE MUST RESORT
TO SUCH THINGS,
I WANT TO HEAR YOU SURRENDER.
Gon: WELL, THAT'S A PROBLEM.
I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE MY LEGS CUT OFF,
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO SURRENDER, EITHER.
HOW 'BOUT WE FIND
A DIFFERENT WAY TO FIGHT?
Hanzo: WHAT THE HELL?!
HAVE YOU NOT
BEEN PAYING ATTENTION?!
Leorio: GUH!
( both laugh )
Bodoro: PARDON ME.
Hanzo: ARE YOU
REALLY MAKING DEMANDS?!
YOU MESSIN' WITH ME?!
I'M SERIOUSLY
ABOUT TO CUT YOUR LEGS OFF!
Gon: YOU DO WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT I WON'T GIVE UP!
BESIDES, IF YOU CUT MY LEGS OFF,
I'LL PROBABLY
JUST BLEED TO DEATH.
‐ Hanzo: WHAT?
‐ Gon: MR. MASTA,
HE'D BE DISQUALIFIED
FOR THAT, RIGHT?
Masta: UH, YES.
Gon: SEE? AND THAT'D BE BAD
FOR THE BOTH OF US,
SO LET'S THINK OF A BETTER WAY.
( Hanzo sputtering )
( Kurapika chuckles )
I THINK GON IS OKAY.
HE'S IN CONTROL NOW.
Leorio: HE'S JUST
SO DAMN STUBBORN.
Kurapika: BUT HE'S
ALSO CONVINCING
TO HANZO AND THE REST OF US.
IMPRESSIVE.
Killua: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
NOTHING'S CHANGED.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
GON'S GOTTEN ANY STRONGER.
HIS ARM IS STILL BROKEN
AND EVERYTHING.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MOOD IN HERE?
IT WAS SO TENSE A SECOND AGO.
WHY DID IT GET SO MUCH LIGHTER?
( Hanzo sputtering )
( groans )
( both gasp )
♪
Hanzo: I SEE
YOU'RE NOT GETTING IT,
SO I'LL TRY AGAIN.
DIE, AND YOU'LL NEVER
GET ANOTHER CHANCE.
IF I KILL YOU
RIGHT HERE AND NOW,
I ONLY NEED TO COME BACK AND
TAKE THE EXAM AGAIN NEXT YEAR.
WE ARE NOT ON EQUAL FOOTING!
( Killua thinking )
HE'S RIGHT, GON.
YOU MIGHT HAVE THE EDGE
WHEN IT COMES TO BRAINS,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
THE COMBAT SKILLS HE DOES.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU CAN MAKE UP FOR RIGHT NOW.
IN THE END,
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO ABILITY.
Hanzo: WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S JUST A STUPID SENTENCE.
THINK. GIVE UP,
AND YOU CAN STILL
TRY AGAIN NEXT YEAR.
IS YOUR PRIDE
TRULY ALL THAT YOU CARE ABOUT?!
EVEN MORE THAN YOUR LIFE?!
IS IT WORTH DYING FOR?!
Gon: I'M GONNA GO SEE MY DAD.
Hanzo: YOUR DAD?
Gon: SEE, MY DAD IS A HUNTER,
SO I'M GONNA BECOME A HUNTER
EXACTLY LIKE HE IS,
AND THEN I'LL BE
ABLE TO MEET HIM!
I KNOW I'LL FIND HIM SOMEDAY.
BUT I FEEL
LIKE IF I SURRENDER NOW,
I'M NEVER GONNA FIND HIM.
SO I WON'T GIVE UP.
Hanzo: SURRENDER,
OR YOU WILL DIE.
( thinking ) SO LOGIC
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
FINE YOU WIN. I GIVE UP, OKAY?
( all gasping )
Hanzo: I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO KILL YOU,
AND I JUST CAN'T THINK
OF ANOTHER WAY
TO FORCE YOU TO SURRENDER,
SO I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES
IN THE NEXT ROUND.
Gon: WELL, I CAN'T ACCEPT THAT.
NO FAIR!
WE BOTH HAVE TO COME UP
WITH SOME WAY
THAT WE CAN HAVE A PROPER MATCH!
( Hanzo sighs )
WHY AM I NOT SURPRISED?
YOU JUST SAID THAT YOU
WOULD NEVER SURRENDER,
SO WHAT THE HELL IS
THE POINT OF THAT, YOU IDIOT?!
Gon: THE POINT IS THAT I DON'T
WANT TO WIN LIKE THIS, OKAY?!
Hanzo: THEN WHAT
DO YOU SUGGEST?!
Gon: LET'S WORK TOGETHER
AND FIGURE IT OUT!
( Hanzo growls )
SO IN OTHER WORDS,
I'VE ALREADY GIVEN UP THE MATCH,
BUT YOU WANT ME
TO CONTINUE FIGHTING
AND TRY TO BEAT YOU AGAIN,
RIGHT?
BUT FIRST WE HAVE TO WORK
TOGETHER TO FIND A WAY
YOU CAN WIN SO YOU CAN
FEEL GOOD ABOUT YOUR VICTORY.
IS THAT RIGHT?
Gon: YEAH!
Hanzo: MORON!
HEY, REFEREE, I LOSE,
SO MOVE ON TO THE NEXT MATCH.
Masta: UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
Hanzo: BUT I'D LIKE
TO SAY SOMETHING FIRST.
WHENEVER HE WAKES UP,
HE'LL PROBABLY DECLINE
HIS ADVANCEMENT.
AND AS WE'VE ALL SEEN,
HE CAN BE INCREDIBLY STUBBORN.
ONLY ONE PERSON
FAILS THIS ROUND, RIGHT?
SO IF GON IS DISQUALIFIED,
WOULDN'T THAT RENDER
THE REST OF OUR UPCOMING FIGHTS
COMPLETELY MEANINGLESS?
Narrator:
WITH HANZO'S CONCESSION,
GON'S VICTORY HAS BEEN ASSURED.
THE FINAL PHASE
THAT WILL DETERMINE
THE SINGLE FAILING APPLICANT
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"BAFFLING TURN OF EVENTS."
( babbles )
Killua: THEY STUCK A NEEDLE
IN GON, TOO?