Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS
OFF YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( crowd cheering )
Gon: I'M REALLY SORRY,
MR. WING...
BUT I'M ITCHING
FOR A FIGHT RIGHT NOW!
♪
( crowd cheering )
Narrator: GON FACES HIS
FIRST MATCH ON THE 200th FLOOR,
BUT IS CAUGHT OFF GUARD
BY HIS OPPONENT'S
UNCONVENTIONAL ATTACK.
( Gido cackles )
( Gon gasps )
Cocco: AND ANOTHER TOP
HITS HIM FROM BEHIND!
IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S IN BIG TROUBLE NOW,
BECAUSE HE'S JUST BEEN
SURROUNDED BY THE DANCING TOPS!
( Gon gasps )
Referee: THAT'S A CLEAN HIT
AND KNOCKDOWN FOR TWO POINTS!
Cocco: GIDO'S UP
TO AN EARLY FOUR‐POINT LEAD!
Referee: CAN YOU FIGHT?
Gon: YOU BET!
THERE ARE TOO MANY TOPS
FOR ME TO BE ABLE
TO KEEP TRACK OF ALL OF 'EM.
DAMN IT.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Zushi: M‐MASTER...
IS HE USING NEN RIGHT NOW?
Win: YES.
THAT'S A FORM OF HATSU.
HE'S PROJECTING HIS AURA
INTO THE TOPS.
THAT IS WHAT ALLOWS THE TOPS
TO MOVE AROUND
WITH SIGNIFICANTLY
MORE STRENGTH AND SPEED
THAN WOULD NORMALLY BE POSSIBLE.
( Gido grunts )
Wing: SMALL OBJECTS REQUIRE
ONLY A SMALL AMOUNT OF AURA.
THE LARGER THE OBJECT,
THE MORE AURA IS NECESSARY.
AND I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF GIDO GAVE THE TOPS
EXTRA NEN FOR GOOD MEASURE.
THAT'S BECAUSE LETTING THE TOPS
SPIN ON THEIR OWN
WITHOUT THE BENEFIT
OF ADDITIONAL AURA
WOULDN'T PACK MUCH OF A PUNCH.
HE CAN DO THIS,
BECAUSE HE FEELS GREAT
PERSONAL AFFINITY WITH THEM.
NOTHING HAS MORE OF AN IMPACT
ON AN OBJECT'S RESPONSE
THAN STRONG
EMOTIONAL ATTACHMENT.
Gon: I CAN'T FOLLOW THEM
WITH MY EYES.
THE TOPS HAVE BEEN
CHARGED WITH NEN.
I HAVE TO SENSE THEIR PRESENCE.
YEAH. I FEEL IT.
( gasps )
MY TEN IS FADING!
( groans )
Cocco: ANOTHER DIRECT HIT!
GON IS COMPLETELY HELPLESS!
HE'S BEEN KNOCKED
CLEAR OUT OF THE RING!
THE SCORE IS NOW SIX‐ZERO.
HE'S DUG HIMSELF QUITE A HOLE.
Gon: IT'S NO USE.
IF I FOCUS ON SENSING THE TOPS,
I NEGLECT MY TEN,
AND IT SEEPS AWAY.
SO WHAT SHOULD I...
A TOP BOUNCED OUTSIDE THE RING,
BUT IT'S NOT ATTACKING ME.
Referee: WHAT'S WRONG? CAN YOU
CONTINUE ON WITH THE MATCH?
Gon: BE QUIET, OKAY?!
I'M TRYING TO THINK HERE!
Referee: IF YOU'RE
NOT BACK IN THE RING
BY THE COUNT OF 10,
YOU LOSE! ONE...
Gon: NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE NEN IN THIS TOP
DIDN'T FEEL MALICIOUS.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THE OTHERS?
THEY'RE JUST SPINNING
AROUND THE RING RANDOMLY
AND BUMPING INTO EACH OTHER.
MAYBE THE TOPS AREN'T
REALLY COMING AFTER ME AT ALL.
Referee: FOUR...
Gon: HOW COME YOU'RE
STANDING OUTSIDE OF THE RING?
Referee: BECAUSE IF I
STAYED UP THERE IN THE RING,
I'D PROBABLY END UP
GETTING HURT, TOO.
‐ AND FIVE...
‐ Gon: THAT'S IT!
IT'S JUST LIKE A GAME
OF SUMO TOPS!
Wing: IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO COMMAND REGULAR TOPS
TO MOVE WITH PRECISION.
IT'S MUCH MORE LIKELY
THAT GIDO COMMANDS THEM
TO STRIKE DOWN
ANYTHING IN THEIR WAY.
THEY SPIN AROUND THE RING,
STRIKING ANYTHING UNFORTUNATE
ENOUGH TO CROSS THEIR PATHS.
Referee: SEVEN...
Gon: IF THE TOPS
AREN'T AIMING FOR ME,
I DON'T HAVE
TO FEAR THEM SO MUCH.
I CAN IGNORE THEM
AND ATTACK GIDO DIRECTLY!
( Gon yells )
Gido: HAH! YOU MAY HAVE
FIGURED OUT MY TOPS,
BUT YOU STILL CAN'T
LAND AN ATTACK ON ME!
( Gon gasps )
Cocco: THERE IT IS,
GIDO'S SPECIAL TECHNIQUE,
COMBINING OFFENSE AND DEFENSE,
TORNADO TOP!
‐ ( Gon yells )
‐ Cocco: WHOA!
GON GETS HIT
WITH A VICIOUS COUNTER!
THREE POINTS!
THE JUDGE HAS AWARDED
A CRITICAL HIT AND KNOCKDOWN.
GIDO HAS NINE POINTS!
GON IS ON THE BRINK OF DEFEAT!
( Gido cackles )
I TURN INTO A TOP
TO PROTECT MYSELF
AND LET MY DANCING TOPS
HANDLE THE OFFENSE.
IT'S A CONSERVATIVE STRATEGY,
BUT IT'S EFFECTIVE
FOR RACKING UP THE POINTS.
Wing: THERE ARE A NUMBER
OF WAYS TO DEFEAT GIDO.
YOU CAN ATTACK HIM
UNTIL HE TIRES
AND HIS TEN BEGINS TO FADE,
OR YOU CAN USE HATSU
TO OVERPOWER HIS DEFENSE.
BOTH OF THOSE METHODS
WOULD REQUIRE
AN EXTREMELY LARGE AMOUNT
OF AURA.
BUT GON DOESN'T KNOW REN YET,
THE TECHNIQUE
FOR GENERATING AURA INSTANTLY.
LEARNING HOW TO CREATE
LARGE AMOUNTS OF AURA QUICKLY
AND HOW TO CHANNEL IT
INTO ATTACKS,
THAT REQUIRES ENDLESS TRAINING
AND COMBAT EXPERIENCE
IN ORDER TO LEARN.
GON HAS NEITHER.
HE'D NEED FIVE MORE YEARS
TO FIGHT GIDO.
I'M SURE THAT'S BEGINNING
TO DAWN ON HIM.
Gon: WHAT SHOULD I DO?
HOW AM I GONNA PROLONG
THIS MATCH?
IF HE SCORES ONE MORE POINT,
IT'S OVER.
BUT I WANT TO KEEP FIGHTING.
WHAT CAN I DO RIGHT NOW?
I GOT IT.
‐ ( Gido gasps )
‐ Killua: GON.
( Wing gasps )
♪
HE RELEASED HIS TEN?
THAT'S SO RECKLESS.
BUT HE DIDN'T JUST RELEASE IT.
THAT'S ZETSU,
THE TECHNIQUE
FOR CONCEALING YOUR PRESENCE.
ALL THE NODES ARE CLOSED,
AND THERE IS NO AURA.
EVEN THE NORMAL, FAINT LEAK
OF AURA IS CLOSED OFF,
LEAVING HIM NO DEFENSE
AGAINST NEN.
I DIDN'T TEACH HIM ZETSU.
DID HE LEARN IT BEFORE WE MET?
IF THAT'S THE CASE, HE WOULDN'T
KNOW THAT THIS IS ZETSU.
HE PROBABLY PICKED IT UP
NATURALLY ON HIS OWN,
JUST LIKE HOW BEASTS IN NATURE
LEARN IT TO HUNT THEIR PREY.
HE CERTAINLY
HAS INCREDIBLE POTENTIAL.
BUT WHY WOULD HE
USE IT NOW HERE?
Killua: YOU IDIOT!
WHAT IF YOU GET HIT
BY ANOTHER NEN ATTACK?!
WITHOUT PROTECTION,
THAT'D TOTALLY MESS YOU UP!
Gon: I KNOW THAT,
BUT IF I'M GONNA TRACK
THE TOPS' COMPLEX MOVEMENTS
WITH ONLY FEELINGS TO GO ON,
THEN I NEED TO FOCUS
ALL OF MY SENSES.
Wing: COULD IT BE THAT HE NEVER
INTENDED TO WIN THIS MATCH?
HE'S RISKING EVERYTHING.
HE'S RISKING
HIS OWN LIFE TO TRAIN?
( Gido laughs )
DO YOU HAVE A DEATH WISH, KID?
THEN HERE!
LET ME GIVE YOU WHAT YOU WANT!
♪
WHAT?!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: AMAZING!
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME GON
HAS MANAGED TO EVADE AN ATTACK!
Gon: I CAN FEEL THEM.
I KNOW WHERE THEY'RE HEADING.
THIS IS ALL I CAN DO RIGHT NOW,
JUST CONCENTRATE ON DODGING
MY OPPONENT'S ATTACKS.
( Gido sputters )
Gon: AT LEAST THIS WAY,
I CAN STILL FIGHT!
Killua: YOUR RIGHT RADIUS
AND YOUR ULNA WERE BOTH BROKEN,
A FRACTURED HUMERUS,
THREE BROKEN RIBS,
NOT TO MENTION
12 OTHER MINOR FRACTURES.
IT'LL TAKE FOUR MONTHS TO HEAL.
YOU MORON.
Gon: SORRY.
Killua: WELL,
AN APOLOGY ISN'T GONNA HELP!
DON'T YOU HAVE ANY BRAINS
IN THERE AT ALL?!
DIDN'T YOU SEE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ALL THE GUYS
WHO WENT THROUGH IT,
THE NEN INITIATION?!
ONE WRONG MOVE, AND YOU
WOULD HAVE ENDED UP LIKE THEM!
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A LOT WORSE,
SO YOU'RE LUCKY.
MAN, HOW COME
YOU THINK FOUR‐EYES
WAS TRAINING US
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
( Gon chuckles ) STILL...
I HAD A FEELING
THAT IT'D BE OKAY.
I MEAN, SURE, I TOOK A FEW HITS,
BUT HE MISSED MY VITAL SPOTS,
SO IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
( gasping )
‐ ( knock on door )
‐ Killua: COME IN.
♪
Killua: UH, FOUR‐EYES.
Gon: UH...
I'M SOR‐‐
Wing: APOLOGIZING TO ME
ISN'T GOING TO HELP!
WHAT ON EARTH
WERE YOU THINKING?!
DIDN'T YOU SEE THE ONES WHO WENT
THROUGH THE NEN INITIATION?
YOU COULD EASILY
HAVE ENDED UP JUST LIKE THEM!
Killua: YEAH. I JUST
TOLD HIM THE SAME THING.
( Wing sighs )
HONESTLY, I'M GLAD
IT WASN'T ANY WORSE.
Gon: I'M SORRY, MR. WING.
I REALLY AM.
Wing: I'M NOT
LETTING THIS SLIDE.
KILLUA, DO YOU KNOW WHEN GON
WILL BE COMPLETELY RECOVERED?
Killua: THE DOCTOR SAID
IT'D TAKE ABOUT TWO MONTHS.
Wing: I SEE.
Killua: HMM.
Gon: THANKS A LOT, KILLUA.
Wing: IN THAT CASE,
I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY MATCHES
FOR TWO MONTHS,
NOR WILL I ALLOW THE STUDY OF
OR TRAINING IN THE USE OF NEN.
IF YOU CHOOSE NOT TO ABIDE
BY THESE CONDITIONS,
THEN YOU WILL NEVER RECEIVE
INSTRUCTION FROM ME AGAIN.
UNDERSTAND?
Gon: YES, SIR.
I'LL DO AS YOU SAY.
Wing: YOUR LEFT HAND.
THIS IS A PROMISE THREAD,
ITS PURPOSE, TO REMIND YOU
OF THE PROMISE YOU MADE.
Gon: OKAY.
Wing: KILLUA, A WORD.
( door closes )
SO TELL ME,
WHAT IS THE TRUE GOAL THAT YOU
AND GON ARE PURSUING HERE?
Killua: WELL, WE DON'T
REALLY HAVE A GOAL.
BEFORE WE
RAN INTO YOU AND ZUSHI,
I JUST WANTED TO EARN
SOME QUICK CASH.
GON WANTS TO BEAT A GUY NAMED
HISOKA, SO HE'S HERE TO TRAIN,
AND THAT'S IT.
EVERYONE ON THE 200th FLOOR
JUST WANTS TO REACH
THE TOP FLOOR.
THE BATTLE OLYMPIA, RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M NOT TOO INTERESTED.
BUT GON, THOUGH,
WELL, I'M NOT SO SURE.
HE SAYS
HE DOESN'T CARE WHAT HAPPENS,
AS LONG AS HE GETS
TO FIGHT HISOKA.
BUT AFTER YESTERDAY'S MATCH,
I DON'T KNOW.
I GET THE FEELING
HE JUST ENJOYS THE THRILL.
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: HOW LONG
THIS BACK‐AND‐FORTH
IS GOING TO GO ON
IS ANYBODY'S GUESS!
THERE ARE NEARLY 50 TOPS
LITERALLY FLYING
AROUND THE RING!
IT'S A TERRIFYING WHIRLWIND
OF SPINNING TOPS,
BUT GON IS EVADING ALL OF THEM!
WITH ALL OF HIS TOPS
ALREADY IN PLAY,
GIDO CAN ONLY WATCH
WITH THE REST OF US!
( Killua gasps )
NO! NOT THAT WAY!
( Gon gasps )
OH, NO.
THERE'S NOWHERE TO RUN!
Wing: THAT SITUATION
COULD VERY WELL
HAVE COST HIM HIS LIFE,
AND HE WAS ENJOYING IT?
Killua: YEAH. AND I WOULD KNOW.
I'VE FELT THE SAME WAY
BEFORE MYSELF.
BUT AT LEAST
I PICK AND CHOOSE MY BATTLES.
ONCE HE'S IN THE ZONE, HE LOSES
SIGHT OF EVERYTHING ELSE.
UH, BUT HE'S NOT THE TYPE
TO BREAK THE SAME PROMISE TWICE,
SO DON'T WORRY.
Wing: OH, DEAR.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
Killua: IT'S TOO LATE.
WE ALREADY KNOW ALL THE FACTS,
GON AND ME BOTH.
IF YOU REGRET TEACHING US
AND WANNA BACK OUT,
WE'LL FIND SOMEBODY ELSE,
OR WE'LL SIMPLY
LEARN IT OURSELVES.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO FEEL RESPONSIBLE.
MY BROTHER CAN USE NEN.
HISOKA CAN, TOO.
SO GON AND I WERE BOUND
TO FIND OUT ABOUT IT EVENTUALLY.
Wing: I UNDERSTAND.
I INTEND TO FINISH
WHAT I STARTED.
THERE ARE SO MANY MORE THINGS
THAT I HAVE YET TO TEACH YOU.
ZUSHI IS WAITING IN MY ROOM.
YOU CAN TRAIN WITH HIM
IF YOU'D LIKE.
Killua: NAH. I'LL PASS.
I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE GON BEHIND.
IF HE CAN KEEP HIS PROMISE,
WE'LL TRAIN TOGETHER.
Wing: GIVE HIM
A MESSAGE FOR ME, THEN!
TELL HIM I WILL LET HIM PRACTICE
THE OTHER NEN, THE FLAME!
AND TELL HIM
TO WORK ON TEN DAILY!
( chorus vocalizing )
Killua: HEY, GON. ( gasps )
( chuckles )
( chorus continues )
Wing: MASTER...
IT WAS NEVER
MY INTENTION, BUT...
HAVE I‐‐
HAVE I AWOKEN
A TERRIBLE MONSTER?
Zushi: EH?
MASTER?
Kurapika: WHAT'S GOING ON?
Woman: YOU FOUND
THIS AGENCY ON YOUR OWN,
AND THAT TELLS ME
YOU'RE PRETTY SHARP.
EVEN SO...
I CAN'T INTRODUCE YOU
TO OUR VALUED CLIENTS.
AND IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF
YOUR TOTAL LACK OF EXPERIENCE.
SOME OF OUR CLIENTS
DON'T SEEM TO MIND THAT.
THE THING IS,
EXPERIENCE ISN'T ALL YOU LACK.
Kurapika: BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE I TOLD YOU, I ALREADY
HAVE A HUNTER'S LICENSE.
Woman: MAYBE,
BUT YOUR EXAM ISN'T OVER YET.
( Kurapika gasps )
Woman: IT'S OBVIOUS.
Kurapika: EXCUSE ME?
Woman: CAN YOU SEE ANYTHING?
Kurapika: HUH?
Woman: LIKE NEXT TO ME, I MEAN.
( aura sneers )
CAN'T SEE A THING, CAN YOU?
( Kurapika stammers )
Woman: YOU COME BACK
WHEN YOU CAN AND NOT BEFORE.
THAT'S THE MINIMUM
REQUIREMENT HERE.
♪
Kurapika: WHAT DOES SHE MEAN?
WHAT IS IT THAT I CAN'T SEE?
( thunder crashing )
♪
( thunder crashes )
( Kurapika gasps )
( grunts )
Man: YOU CAN'T SEE IT,
BUT YOU CAN SENSE IT, HUH?
Kurapika: WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
Man: THIS? ( laughs )
‐ I WAS JUST PLAYING AROUND.
‐ ( thunder crashes )
THIS MUST BE FATE,
US CROSSING PATHS. YOU THINK?
TRY TO THINK OF THIS
AS A LITTLE BIT OF
FRIENDLY ADVICE FROM A SENIOR.
( Kurapika gasps )
Man: YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
WHEN I STOLE THIS
OR WHEN I WALKED
RIGHT PAST YOU, EITHER.
YOU'RE TOTALLY CLUELESS.
Kurapika: BASTARD. GIVE ME
BACK MY LICENSE RIGHT NOW!
Man: DOES A NEWBIE
WHO KNOWS NOTHING OF NEN
HAVE A CHANCE OF BEATING ME?
Kurapika: NEN, HUH?
‐ ( man chuckles )
‐ ( thunder crashes )
WANNA GIVE IT A TRY?
( Kurapika panting )
Man: DO YOU GET IT NOW?
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
YOU STILL LACK.
HMM?
Kurapika: I‐‐I NEED‐‐
I NEED ENOUGH POWER
TO FIGHT ON MY OWN!
Man: COME WITH ME.
I'LL TEACH YOU.
THE REAL EXAM HAS JUST BEGUN.
♪
Narrator: GON'S HIDDEN POTENTIAL
IS BEGINNING TO AWAKEN,
AND KURAPIKA HAS ALSO
ENCOUNTERED A NEW POWER,
ONE THAT HE HOPES
WILL HELP PROPEL HIM FORWARD.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE INTRODUCING
THE HUNTER AGENCY.
THIS PLACE
HELPS PRO HUNTERS FIND WORK,
BUT IT WAS REALLY HARD
FOR KURAPIKA
TO FIND THE OFFICE
THAT HE VISITED.
Killua: GOTTA FIND THE AGENCY
BEFORE YOU QUALIFY
AS A PRO HUNTER.
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"DESTINY AND TENACITY."
Killua: I WONDER
WHO FOUR‐EYES IS, ANYWAY?
Gon: I WONDER
WHO THE FLOOR MASTERS ARE.
( Killua gasps )
Both: COULD IT BE?!