Kurapika: THIS COUNTRY'S
OPEN TO TOURISTS.
Gon: THAT'S WHERE KILLUA IS?
Kurapika: IT'LL TAKE THREE DAYS
TO REACH BY AIRSHIP.
WHEN DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD LEAVE?
Gon: TODAY! RIGHT NOW!
Leorio: ALL RIGHT! I'M WITH GON.
Kurapika: GOT IT.
I'LL ORDER THE TICKETS THEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Killua: I'M FROM
A FAMILY OF ASSASSINS,
SO, YEAH, THEY'RE ALL
IN THE BUSINESS OF MURDER.
AND MY ENTIRE FAMILY, THEY'VE
GOT REAL HIGH HOPES FOR ME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I CAN'T STAND IT.
WHO WANTS THEIR WHOLE LIFE
MAPPED OUT FOR 'EM?
Gon: KILLUA.
Leorio: SO WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THE LONG FACE, GON?
Kurapika: BY TOMORROW,
WE'LL BE IN PADOKEA.
YOU'LL SEE KILLUA SOON.
Gon: YUP!
WE'LL DEFINITELY
BRING KILLUA BACK WITH US.
♪
( train whooshes )
Narrator: GON, LEORIO,
AND KURAPIKA HAVE ARRIVED
IN THE DENTORA REGION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF PADOKEA,
WHICH KILLUA CALLS HOME.
Leorio: I CAN ALMOST SEE IT.
SO THAT'S WHERE
THE ASSASSINS' BASE IS?
LOOKS KINDA CREEPY, DOESN'T IT?
Kurapika: IT DOES.
ONCE WE ARRIVE,
WE SHOULD GATHER INFORMATION.
Leorio: OKAY.
Woman: KUKUROO MOUNTAIN?
YOU'LL WANT TO TAKE THE SCENIC
MOUNTAIN BUS TOUR OVER THERE.
IT ONLY RUNS ONCE A DAY,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE A GUIDE
TO SHOW YOU AROUND.
Guide: I'D LIKE
TO THANK ALL OF YOU
FOR CHOOSING LAMENTATION TOURS.
IT'S AN HONOR TO HAVE YOU HERE.
NOW GET READY,
BECAUSE WE'LL BE MAKING OUR WAY
UP TO KUKUROO MOUNTAIN,
HOME TO THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY
OF ASSASSINS.
Leorio: CHECK IT OUT.
Kurapika: HMM?
Leorio: NO WAY
THOSE GUYS ARE TOURISTS.
Kurapika: TRUE.
Guide: OKAY, EVERYONE.
IF YOU'LL ALL LOOK OUT
THE WINDOW TO YOUR RIGHT,
YOU'LL SEE KUKUROO MOUNTAIN,
WHERE THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY LIVES.
IT'S 3,722 METERS HIGH,
AND IT'S SURROUNDED BY FOREST.
THE ZOLDYCK ESTATE IS RUMORED
TO BE SOMEWHERE ON THE MOUNTAIN,
ALTHOUGH NO ONE'S
EVER ACTUALLY SEEN IT.
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY
CONSISTS OF 10 MEMBERS,
MOTHER AND FATHER,
FIVE SIBLINGS,
GRANDPARENTS,
AND GREAT‐GRANDFATHER,
ALL OF WHOM ARE ASSASSINS.
ALL RIGHT. NOW HOLD ON
WHILE WE GET
A LITTLE CLOSER TO THE MOUNTAIN.
♪
( tourists gasping, murmuring )
Leorio: WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
Guide: THIS IS THE FRONT GATE
OF THE ZOLDYCK ESTATE.
NO ONE WHO'S ENTERED
HAS EVER RETURNED ALIVE,
WHICH HAS EARNED THIS GATE
THE NICKNAME,
"THE DOOR TO HADES."
TO ENTER, YOU HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THE DOOR
BY THE SECURITY CHECKPOINT,
BUT BEYOND THAT
IS PRIVATE PROPERTY,
SO THIS IS AS FAR AS WE CAN GO.
Leorio: HOLD ON!
THIS IS THE FRONT GATE?
BUT THE MOUNTAIN IS
ALL THE WAY OVER THERE!
Guide: THAT'S RIGHT.
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY
OWNS KUKUROO MOUNTAIN,
EVERY INCH OF IT,
NOT TO MENTION
ALL OF THE SURROUNDING LAND.
Leorio: SO WHAT
YOU'RE TELLING ME
IS THIS IS THEIR FRONT YARD?
‐ Gon: MISS TOUR GUIDE?
‐ Guide: YES?
Gon: WHAT ARE WE
GONNA HAVE TO DO TO GET INSIDE?
Guide: HMM. OH, DEAR.
YOU WERE PAYING ATTENTION,
RIGHT?
Gon: YEAH. BUT YOU DIDN'T SAY‐‐
Guide: IF YOU GO INSIDE,
YOU'LL NEVER COME OUT AGAIN!
IT'S AN ASSASSINS' HIDEOUT.
‐ Swordsman: IT'S A SHAM.
‐ Guide: EH?
Man: A FAMILY OF ASSASSINS
NO ONE'S EVER SEEN?
Swordsman: IF WE CAN
JUST SNAP A PICTURE OF 'EM,
WE'RE GONNA GET A HUNDRED
MILLION IN REWARD MONEY.
Leorio: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
DAMN IT! I SHOULD'VE
TAKEN A PICTURE OF KILLUA!
( both groan )
Swordsman: THEY PROBABLY RELY
ON THE MYSTIQUE TO PROTECT 'EM.
I BET THE TRUTH IS
A WHOLE LOT LESS INTERESTING.
♪
( clank )
Guard: HUH?
( man roars, growls )
OPEN UP THE GATE.
( guard gasps )
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T!
THE MASTER OF THE HOUSE WOULD
NOT APPROVE OF SUCH A THING!
Swordsman:
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
WE KINDA FIGURED
WE'D KILL YOUR MASTER ANYWAY.
( guard sighs )
( groaning )
Gon: ARE YOU OKAY?
Guard: YES. I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
( lock clatters )
OH, DARN.
THE MASTER HATES IT
WHEN MIKE SNACKS BETWEEN MEALS.
Gon: WHAT?
( men scream )
( wind blowing )
( door creaks )
( both gasp )
( guide screams )
( tourists yelling, chattering )
Guide: AHH! GET INSIDE!
Guard: WELL, DAMN IT,
MIKE IS ONLY SUPPOSED TO EAT
AT DESIGNATED TIMES.
MIKE, DON'T BLAME
THOSE EXTRA POUNDS ON ME!
Kurapika: WHAT WAS THAT THING?
( Leorio grunts )
♪
Guide: HEY, YOU GUYS!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
TIME TO GET BACK ON THE BUS!
Gon: OH! GO AHEAD WITHOUT US,
'CAUSE WE'RE ALL STAYING HERE.
( guide gasps )
‐ ( cup clinks )
‐ Guard: I SEE.
SO YOU'RE YOUNG MASTER
KILLUA'S FRIENDS, ARE YOU?
HAPPY TO HEAR IT.
I'VE WORKED HERE
FOR THE PAST 20 YEARS,
AND TO THE BEST
OF MY RECOLLECTION,
YOU THREE ARE THE FIRST FRIENDS
WHO'VE EVER COME TO VISIT.
NOW, I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
BE TELLING YOU THIS,
SEEING AS HOW I WORK HERE,
BUT THIS PLACE IS PRETTY LONELY.
NO ONE EVER REALLY VISITS.
WELL, EXCEPT THOSE TYPES.
WE GET OUR FAIR SHARE OF THOSE.
HEH HEH.
BUT A FAMILY OF ASSASSINS
IS BOUND TO BE UNUSUAL.
GUESS THAT'S THE PRICE
THEY HAVE TO PAY.
AH, WELL. ANYWAYS,
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
Leorio: DON'T MENTION IT.
Guard: HOWEVER,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I'M GOING TO BE ABLE
TO LET ANY OF YOU INSIDE.
( all grunt )
Guard: YOU SAW IT EARLIER,
DIDN'T YOU,
HOW HUGE THE BEAST'S ARM WAS?
THAT ARM BELONGS TO MIKE.
IT'S THE ZOLDYCKS' WATCHDOG.
IT ONLY OBEYS THE FAMILY
AND ATTACKS EVERYONE ELSE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
IT'S STILL FOLLOWING THE ORDER
ITS MASTER GAVE IT 10 YEARS AGO
TO KILL EVERY SINGLE INTRUDER
WHO TRIES TO GET INSIDE.
Kurapika: HMM?
Guard: I GUESS HE ISN'T
FOLLOWING IT, TECHNICALLY,
BECAUSE HE KEEPS EATING THEM!
( laughs )
BUT LIKE I WAS SAYING,
I CAN'T LET YOU IN.
I WOULDN'T WANT FRIENDS
OF YOUNG MASTER KILLUA
BEING STRIPPED DOWN
TO THEIR SKELETONS.
( laughs )
Kurapika: QUESTION‐‐HOW IS IT
THAT YOU'RE SAFE HERE?
Guard: HMM?
Kurapika: IT'S JUST
YOU CAN GO INSIDE,
AND IF YOU WERE
NEVER ALLOWED TO GO IN,
IT'S UNLIKELY
THAT YOU WOULD BE GIVEN A KEY.
Guard: HMM.
THAT'S VERY PERCEPTIVE,
BUT THE FACT IS
YOU'RE ONLY ABOUT HALF RIGHT.
SEE, I DON'T NEED A KEY
TO GET INSIDE.
THIS KEY WAS SPECIALLY MADE
FOR INTRUDERS ONLY.
Leorio: THERE'S A KEY
FOR INTRUDERS?
Guard: ALMOST ALL OF THEM
GO RIGHT FOR THE FRONT GATE,
ABOUT 90%.
I COULDN'T BEGIN
TO TELL YOU WHY, THOUGH.
IF I DON'T OPEN THE GATE
FOR THEM,
EVERY TIME, WITHOUT FAIL,
THEY TRY TO BREAK IT DOWN.
THEY'RE REAL TROUBLEMAKERS,
THESE TYPES.
THAT'S WHY WE ADDED
A LOCKED DOOR TO ONE SIDE.
WORKS PRETTY WELL.
THEY JUST TAKE THE KEY
FROM THE POOR,
HELPLESS SECURITY GUARD,
AND THEN MIKE EATS THEM.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
( Kurapika thinking )
A LOCKED DOOR.
( aloud )
THAT'S IT!
Man: HUH?
AS YOU JUST REALIZED,
I'M NOT A SECURITY GUARD.
I'M JUST THE JANITOR
WHO CLEANS UP AFTER MIKE.
Kurapika: SO THE FRONT GATE
ISN'T ACTUALLY LOCKED AFTER ALL!
Janitor: EXACTLY.
Leorio: WHAT?!
♪
HMM.
HEH HEH.
♪
( grunting )
( panting )
( pants )
I'VE PUSHED AND PULLED,
BUT IT WON'T BUDGE.
ARE YOU SURE
THE GATE ISN'T LOCKED?
Janitor: I'M AFRAID
YOU'RE JUST NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
Leorio: SHUT UP! I WAS
GIVING IT EVERYTHING I'VE GOT!
‐ Gon: HUH?
‐ Kurapika: HMM?
Janitor: STEP BACK, AND WATCH.
THIS GATE IS OFFICIALLY KNOWN
AS THE TESTING GATE,
BECAUSE ANYONE WHO'S
NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO OPEN IT...
HUHH!
...IS CONSIDERED UNWORTHY
OF ENTERING THE ZOLDYCK ESTATE.
( grunts )
( all gasp )
( janitor groans )
( rumbling )
SO YOU CAN SEE THAT THE DOOR
CLOSES AUTOMATICALLY,
SO YOU'LL WANT TO SLIP INSIDE
AS SOON AS IT OPENS.
OH, AND YOU WON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT MIKE.
HE HAS STRICT ORDERS
NOT TO ATTACK ANYONE
WHO ENTERS
THROUGH THE TESTING GATE.
HOO!
THE OLDER I GET, THE TOUGHER
THIS SEEMS TO BECOME,
BUT THEY'LL FIRE ME
IF I CAN'T OPEN THE GATE,
SO I NEED TO STAY FIT.
AND I SHOULD MENTION
THE FIRST DOORS
WEIGH TWO TONS EACH.
Leorio: WHAT?!
YOU'RE REALLY
NOT SUPPOSED TO BE ABLE TO‐‐
WAIT. WHAT DID YOU SAY?
DID YOU SAY, "THE FIRST DOORS"?
Janitor: YEAH. TAKE A LOOK.
THERE ARE SEVEN DOORS IN ALL,
AND KEEP IN MIND THAT EACH SET
IS TWICE AS HEAVY
AS THE SET OF DOORS BEFORE IT.
Leorio: TWICE?!
Janitor: THE MORE FORCE
YOU PUT INTO IT,
THE MORE DOORS YOU OPEN.
GOTTA BE PRETTY STRONG
TO GET THROUGH ALL OF 'EM.
INCIDENTALLY, WHEN YOUNG MASTER
KILLUA RETURNED TO THE ESTATE,
HE OPENED THREE OF THEM
JUST LIKE THAT.
Gon: THREE? THAT'S LIKE...
12 TONS!
Kurapika: IT'S 16 TONS, GON.
( Gon laughs )
Janitor: STARTING TO GET IT NOW?
THIS IS WHAT IT TAKES
JUST TO GET THROUGH THE DOOR.
THEY LIVE
IN A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT WORLD.
( Gon sighs ) I DON'T LIKE THIS.
‐ MAY I BORROW THE KEY?
‐ Janitor: HMM?
Gon: I DIDN'T COME ALL THIS WAY
TO BE TESTED.
I CAME SO I COULD SEE MY FRIEND.
THINK OF ME AS AN INTRUDER.
SO PLEASE
LET ME BORROW THE KEY.
THEN I'LL GO IN THERE
THROUGH THE INTRUDER'S DOOR.
Kurapika: GON!
Leorio: HEY, UH...
Gon: LEND IT TO ME, OR DON'T,
BUT I'M GETTING IN.
I'LL CLIMB THE WALL
IF I HAVE TO.
Leorio: DON'T BE STUPID, GON!
DIDN'T YOU SEE
THAT TERRIFYING MONSTER?
ITS FOREARM WAS BIGGER
THAN YOUR WHOLE BODY TIMES TWO.
Gon: I TOLD YOU
I DON'T LIKE THIS!
( Leorio gasps )
Gon: WHY TEST YOUR FRIENDS?
IT'S CRAZY!
THERE'S NO WAY I'M EVER
GOING THROUGH THAT DOOR.
Janitor: YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN FORCE YOUR WAY IN,
THINK AGAIN.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY IMPOSSIBLE.
MIKE WOULD DEFINITELY KILL YOU.
Kurapika: I HAVE
TO AGREE WITH YOU.
WE HAVE THE TIME, SO LET'S FIND
A WAY TO USE THE FIRST DOOR.
( Gon grunts )
Leorio: NO USE. HE WON'T CHANGE
HIS MIND WHEN HE'S LIKE THIS.
Kurapika: YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
Janitor: I'M SORRY TO SAY THIS,
BUT I CAN'T
LET YOU HAVE THE KEY.
I WON'T FEED YOUNG MASTER
KILLUA'S FRIENDS TO MIKE.
I CAN'T DO IT.
GUESS I DON'T HAVE IT IN ME.
BUT WOULD YOU WAIT HERE
FOR A MINUTE, PLEASE?
( telephone line ringing )
HELLO. THIS IS ZEBRO.
SORRY TO CALL.
IT'S JUST THAT THREE
OF YOUNG MASTER KILLUA'S FRIENDS
ARE HERE,
AND THEY WOULD
VERY MUCH LIKE TO SEE HIM.
YES.
YES, I'M SORRY.
OH, OF COURSE.
YES, I UNDERSTAND. YES, YES.
I'M SO VERY SORRY
TO DISTURB YOU.
YEAH. I FIGURED
I WOULD GET YELLED AT.
Gon: YOU CALLED
UP TO THE HOUSE FOR US?
Zebro: NO. I WAS SPEAKING WITH
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY'S BUTLER.
ALL COMMUNICATION
WITH THE MANSION
HAS TO GO THROUGH
THE BUTLER FIRST.
IT'S NOT EASY TO REACH
THE FAMILY MEMBERS DIRECTLY.
Gon: COULD YOU GET HIM
ON THE PHONE AGAIN?
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO HIM
THIS TIME.
Zebro: WELL, I SUPPOSE I CAN,
BUT I GUARANTEE THAT
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO ENJOY IT.
( dials )
( line rings )
Butler: YOU'VE REACHED
THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
Gon: MY NAME'S GON,
AND I'M ONE OF KILLUA'S FRIENDS
THAT CAME TO VISIT.
IS KILLUA THERE?
CAN I SPEAK TO HIM?
Butler: MASTER KILLUA
DOES NOT HAVE FRIENDS.
( hangs up )
( line beeps )
‐ Kurapika: UH...
‐ Leorio: HUH?
( line ringing )
Butler: YOU'VE REACHED
THE BUTLERS' QUARTERS.
Gon: HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT, HUH?!
PUT KILLUA ON THE PHONE NOW!
( both gasp )
Butler: I BELIEVE
YOU SAID YOUR NAME IS GON?
Gon: YEAH.
Butler: LET US PRETEND
THAT MASTER KILLUA
DOES HAVE A FRIEND NAMED GON.
THERE IS NO PROOF
THAT YOU ARE HIM.
Gon: PUT HIM ON THE PHONE.
HE'LL RECOGNIZE ME.
Butler: BY YOUR VOICE?
THAT IS NO GUARANTEE.
( Gon over phone )
PUT HIM ON THE PHONE.
HE'LL RECOGNIZE ME.
Butler: THAT WAS
A SIMPLE RECORDING,
BUT THERE ARE MANY OTHER WAYS
TO MIMIC SOMEONE'S VOICE.
NEXT, YOU'LL SAY
HE'D RECOGNIZE YOU BY SIGHT.
THERE AREN'T AS MANY METHODS
BY WHICH YOU COULD PERFECTLY
REPLICATE SOMEONE'S APPEARANCE,
BUT IT ISN'T IMPOSSIBLE.
OR PERHAPS YOU ARE GON,
BUT SOMEONE HAS COERCED YOU
TO APPROACH MASTER KILLUA
FOR SOME SINISTER MOTIVE.
AS LONG AS THAT THREAT EXISTS,
I CANNOT LET YOU MEET WITH HIM.
THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY ARE
IN THE ASSASSINATION BUSINESS.
THEY HAVE THEIR ENEMIES,
OF COURSE,
AND IT IS
A BUTLER'S RESPONSIBILITY
TO GUARD THEM
FROM THOSE ENEMIES.
APOLOGIES.
YOU WILL HAVE TO LEAVE.
( hangs up )
( line beeps )
Leorio: HEY, WAIT!
GON!
( Gon grunts )
Leorio: HE'S REALLY PISSED,
ISN'T HE?
Kurapika: I THINK HE'S
GOING TO CLIMB OVER THE WALL.
Leorio: HE WHAT?!
♪
HEY, GON, KNOCK IT OFF!
Gon: IT'S OKAY.
YOU TWO CAN WAIT HERE.
I'M GOING IN ALONE.
Leorio: I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT!
‐ Gon: I'LL BE FINE.
‐ Leorio: NO, YOU WON'T!
Kurapika: LOOK, BOTH OF YOU
NEED TO CALM DOWN.
Leorio: I'M PERFECTLY CALM.
NOW COME ON! GET DOWN!
Kurapika: HE'S RIGHT.
DON'T BE STUPID.
Zebro: HERE, GON.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE KEY.
YOU CAN GO THROUGH
THE DOOR, ALL RIGHT?
Leorio:
JUST WAIT A SECOND, POPS!
WE CAN CONVINCE HIM
TO STOP THIS!
Zebro: OH, REALLY? BECAUSE HE
STRIKES ME AS THE STUBBORN TYPE.
TO MAKE AMENDS, I'VE DECIDED TO
ACCOMPANY YOU THROUGH THE DOOR.
Gon: HUH?
Zebro: MIKE KNOWS ME
WELL ENOUGH TO RECOGNIZE ME,
AND IT'S POSSIBLE
HE MIGHT NOT ATTACK
IF HE SEES I'M WITH YOU,
THOUGH I'M ALMOST 100% CERTAIN
THAT HE'LL JUST KILL US ALL.
Gon: I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT.
I DON'T WANNA CAUSE
ANY TROUBLE FOR YOU.
Zebro: TOO LATE. I'M COMING.
THERE'D BE TROUBLE
EVEN IF I STAYED.
IF I SENT YOUNG MASTER KILLUA'S
FRIENDS TO THEIR DEATHS,
I'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO LOOK HIM IN THE EYE AGAIN.
IF YOU DIE, WELL,
THEN I'LL DIE ALONGSIDE YOU.
Gon: I UNDERSTAND, SIR.
I GUESS I DIDN'T STOP
TO THINK ABOUT YOUR SITUATION.
SORRY.
( Kurapika chuckles )
( Leorio sighs )
( Zebro thinking )
HE'S A GOOD KID,
READY AND WILLING
TO PUT ASIDE HIS OWN ANGER
FOR THE SAKE OF ANOTHER.
HE BELIEVES IN HIS OWN STRENGTH,
AND HE BELIEVES IN HIS FRIENDS
JUST AS MUCH.
HE HAS SUCH A STRONG HEART.
IN FACT, IT'S LIKELY THAT MIKE
WON'T FRIGHTEN HIM AT ALL.
( aloud ) YOU LIKE ANIMALS,
DON'T YOU, GON?
Gon: HUH? YEAH.
Zebro: I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT.
AND DID YOU GROW UP
PLAYING IN THE COUNTRYSIDE?
Gon: YEAH.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
Zebro: ALL RIGHT.
IN JUST A MOMENT,
I'M GOING TO OPEN
THE TESTING GATE AGAIN.
I WANT YOU TO SEE MIKE
WITH YOUR OWN EYES.
♪
( gate rumbles )
Leorio: HEY, ARE YOU SURE THAT
IT'S OKAY FOR US TO COME IN?
Zebro: OF COURSE.
YOU ENTERED
THROUGH THE TESTING GATE,
SO YOU'LL BE FINE.
MIKE!
COME HERE!
( echo )
COME HERE! COME HERE!
...HERE! ...HERE! ...HERE!
( Mike growling )
( rumble )
( growling, rumbling continue )
( Gon gasps )
( Mike growls )
( Gon shuddering )
Zebro: SO, GON,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS A HUNTING BEAST,
A HIGHLY TRAINED ONE AT THAT.
IT'S LIKE NO ANIMAL YOU'VE
EVER ENCOUNTERED IN THE WILD,
NO, NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
YOU BELIEVED
YOU COULD COMMUNICATE WITH HIM
UNTIL YOU LOOKED
IN HIS EYES, RIGHT?
AS WE SPEAK, MIKE IS
MEMORIZING THE APPEARANCES
AND SCENTS OF THESE NEW HUMANS.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING ELSE
ON HIS MIND AT THE MOMENT.
HE'S JUST LIKE A MACHINE.
SO, GON,
DO YOU THINK
YOU COULD FIGHT HIM?
Gon: MM‐MM.
I'D BE TOO SCARED.
I DON'T EVER WANT TO FIGHT HIM.
( Zebro chuckles )
( thinking )
HE'S AN HONEST LAD, TOO.
( aloud ) WELL, HOW LONG
WILL YOU BE STAYING HERE?
Gon: UNTIL WE SEE KILLUA,
AND WE'RE NOT LEAVING
A SECOND BEFORE.
( Zebro chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, THEN. FOLLOW ME.
♪
Narrator: FIRST THE TESTING GATE
AND NOW MIKE,
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM,
GON HAS SEEN FOR HIMSELF
THAT THE ZOLDYCK FAMILY
TRULY LIVE
IN A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT WORLD.
HOWEVER, GON HAD MADE
A PROMISE TO HIMSELF
THAT NO MATTER WHAT DIFFICULTIES
LAY ON THE PATH AHEAD OF HIM,
IN THE END, HE WOULD SEE KILLUA.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"THE GUARD'S DUTY.
FIVE TIMES FIVE IS 25.
Killua: SO YOU KNOW
HOW TO DO MATH?
Both: FIVE TIMES FIVE IS 25!