( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: LEORIO!
( Leorio gasping )
♪
Narrator: GON AND HIS GROUP
HAVE BEEN TRAPPED BY VIPERS,
WHICH NOW BLOCK THEIR EXIT,
BUT THE VIPERS' MASTER,
BOURBON, IS DEAD.
Kurapika: ARE YOU TELLING US
THAT THE PERSON
WHO SET THIS TRAP IS NOW DEAD?
BUT HOW?
‐ Ponzu: WELL, I KILLED HIM.
‐ ( both gasp )
Ponzu: BUT MY METHODS
ARE A TRADE SECRET.
Kurapika: HEY, GON, TAKE LEORIO.
Ponzu: IT'S NO USE.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU
WON'T BE ABLE TO SEARCH HIM.
THE SNAKES ARE TRAINED,
AND IF YOU EVEN TRY TO TOUCH HIM
OR YOU TRY
TO LEAVE THE CAVE AND ESCAPE,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM
WILL ATTACK YOU.
Kurapika: SO YOU
FOUGHT POISON WITH POISON.
JUDGING BY HIS WOUNDS, YOU MUST
HAVE USED NEUROTOXIC BEES,
SO IT'S LIKELY THAT HE DIED
OF ANAPHYLACTIC SHOCK.
Gon: "ANAPHYLACTIC"?
WHAT IS THAT?
Kurapika: HMM.
WHEN A BEE STINGS A HUMAN,
CERTAIN ANTIBODIES ARE PRODUCED
IN AN ATTEMPT TO COUNTER
THE EFFECTS OF THE BEE'S VENOM,
BUT IF THAT PERSON IS STUNG
AGAIN BY THE SAME KIND OF BEE,
THEY WILL EXPERIENCE
AN ALLERGIC REACTION.
AN EXTREME ALLERGIC REACTION
IS KNOWN AS ANAPHYLACTIC SHOCK.
DEPENDING ON THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
IT CAN BE FATAL.
Ponzu: THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU GOT ME.
Gon: SO YOU
KILLED HIM WITH BEES?
Ponzu: BOURBON WAS
WHO I DREW AS MY TARGET.
♪
ONCE I'D CONFIRMED
HE WAS INSIDE THE CAVE,
I SPRAYED SLEEPING GAS
INTO THE ENTRANCE,
THEN WAITED
UNTIL IT WAS SAFE TO GO IN.
WHEN I FOUND HIM, BOURBON WAS
COMPLETELY PASSED OUT,
BUT HE HAD ALREADY
SET UP HIS TRAPS.
‐ ( snakes hissing )
‐ ( Ponzu screams )
AND UNFORTUNATELY FOR ME,
THERE WERE SNAKES
IN THE BACK OF THE CAVE
HIDING IN CREVICES.
I GUESS THE SLEEPING GAS
DIDN'T REACH THEM.
I WAS ABLE
TO JUMP OUT OF THE WAY
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME,
SO I DIDN'T GET BITTEN
BY THEM OR ANYTHING.
BUT THAT'S WHAT TRIGGERED
MY OWN DEFENSES TO ACTIVATE.
Kurapika: THAT'S WHERE YOU
KEEP ALL YOUR BEES?
Ponzu: IF I SCREAM, COLLAPSE,
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
THESE LITTLE GUYS
WILL ATTACK ANYONE NEARBY.
I WASN'T EXPECTING HIM
TO DIE, THOUGH.
HOW COULD I HAVE KNOWN
HE WAS ALLERGIC TO BEES?
AND THE SNAKES
KEPT ME FROM HELPING HIM.
WELL, NOT LIKE
I COULD'VE DONE ANYTHING.
YOU CAN COME BACK NOW.
THE PROBLEM IS THE PERSON WHO
SET THE TRAP IN THE FIRST PLACE
DIED WITHOUT EVER HAVING
THE CHANCE TO DEACTIVATE IT,
AND WE CAN'T EXACTLY DISARM IT
OR ASK HIM FOR HELP.
WE'RE TRAPPED
WITH NO HOPE FOR ESCAPE.
( Leorio groans )
Gon: LEORIO.
( Ponzu sighs )
SO IT'S HOPELESS. I GAVE UP.
WE'RE STUCK UNTIL THE EXAM
COMMITTEE COMES AND SAVES US.
Kurapika: THE EXAM COMMITTEE?
ARE YOU SAYING THEY'LL
RESCUE US FROM THIS CAVE?
Ponzu: YOU DIDN'T KNOW?
EACH OF OUR NUMBER BADGES
CONTAIN TRANSMITTERS.
THE EXAMINERS KNOW
WHERE ALL THE APPLICANTS
ARE LOCATED AT ALL TIMES,
AND IF SOMEONE HASN'T RETURNED
BY THE DEADLINE,
THEY GO OUT AND LOOK FOR THEM.
HOWEVER, IF IT'S LOST OR STOLEN,
THEN YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
LUCKILY, THERE'S ONLY
ONE MORE DAY LEFT.
BEST TO JUST GIVE UP
FOR THIS YEAR AND WAIT FOR HELP.
Kurapika: WE CAN'T DO THAT.
LEORIO'S CONDITION IS WORSENING.
HE NEEDS TO GET TO A DOCTOR.
Ponzu: THE EXAMINERS
AREN'T GOING TO BUDGE
'TIL IT'S PAST THE DEADLINE.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE YOUR BADGE,
YOU'LL BE LEFT FOR DEAD.
THIS IS HIS FAULT, REALLY.
I TRIED TO WARN HIM.
Leorio: KURAPIKA, GON,
DON'T COME IN HERE!
( snakes hissing )
( Leorio yelling )
Ponzu: ALL YOU
CAN DO FOR HIM IS PRAY
THAT HE CAN MANAGE TO HANG ON
UNTIL HELP CAN ARRIVE.
Kurapika:
NO, THERE'S ANOTHER WAY,
ONE WITH A GOOD CHANCE
OF SUCCESS,
BUT IF HE ISN'T CARRYING ANY,
WE'LL HAVE
ANOTHER FATALITY ON OUR HANDS.
Gon: KURAPIKA.
TAKE CARE OF LEORIO.
Kurapika: BUT, GON‐‐
Gon: IT'S THERE. DON'T WORRY.
Kurapika: GON.
GON! HEY!
Ponzu: ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR A WORD
I JUST SAID?
( snakes hissing )
‐ ( Ponzu yells )
‐ ( snakes hissing )
Kurapika: OH, NO!
Ponzu: HE‐‐HE'S OUT OF HIS MIND.
( Gon gasping )
FOUND IT!
♪
KURAPIKA! CATCH!
Kurapika: GON!
Gon: HURRY.
GIVE IT TO LEORIO.
♪
Kurapika: THERE. YOU READY, GON?
Gon: YEAH.
Ponzu: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HE JUMPED INTO A NEST OF SNAKES
LOOKING FOR AN ANTIDOTE
HE WASN'T SURE WAS THERE.
Kurapika: TRUE, BUT THE ODDS
WERE IN HIS FAVOR.
IF YOU POISON SOMEONE,
YOU CAN'T BARGAIN
UNLESS YOU HAVE THE ANTIDOTE.
Ponzu: YEAH, BUT IT WAS
STILL PRETTY RISKY.
Kurapika: THAT SAID,
DOING WHAT GON JUST DID
TOOK AN INCREDIBLE AMOUNT
OF COURAGE.
HE'S STABILIZING.
HE SHOULD BE ALL RIGHT.
Ponzu: YOU MUST BE
REALLY GOOD FRIENDS.
( Gon groans )
HEY, DO YOU HAVE ANY
OF YOUR SLEEPING GAS LEFT OVER?
Ponzu: I DO.
Gon: WILL YOU TRADE IT FOR THIS?
( Ponzu gasps )
THAT'S BOURBON'S BADGE!
Gon: AND IF YOU HAD IT,
IT WOULD GIVE YOU
THE SIX POINTS YOU NEED.
Ponzu: YEAH. THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT, UH, WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO WITH IT,
THE SLEEPING GAS?
Gon: USE IT. WE'LL PUT
ALL THE SNAKES TO SLEEP.
THEN WE CAN ESCAPE.
Ponzu: RELEASING IT IN HERE
WOULD BE MUCH MORE EFFECTIVE
THAN WHEN I USED IT
AT THE ENTRANCE.
WITHIN FIVE MINUTES,
THE CAVE WILL FILL WITH GAS,
KNOCKING ALL THE SNAKES
OUT COLD.
THAT'S FIVE WHOLE MINUTES,
WHICH IS WAY LONGER THAN ANYONE
CAN HOLD THEIR BREATH.
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE POINT
IN TRYING IF WE'RE ALL
JUST GOING TO PUT OURSELVES
TO SLEEP IN THE PROCESS?
‐ Gon: 9 MINUTES AND 44 SECONDS.
‐ Ponzu: WHAT?
Gon: MY RECORD
FOR HOLDING MY BREATH. HEH.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
I'LL CARRY YOU OUT OF HERE.
Ponzu: WHY SHOULD I TRUST YOU?
YOU'RE JUST GONNA LEAVE ME HERE
AND ESCAPE BY YOURSELF.
Kurapika: YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YOU SAW WHAT HE DID.
GON BRAVED A NEST OF
VENOMOUS SNAKES TO SAVE LEORIO.
Gon: TRUST ME.
I'LL GET YOU OUT.
I PROMISE I WILL.
( Ponzu sighs )
IT'S READY TO GO.
Gon: WAIT FOR MY SIGNAL.
THEN RELEASE THE GAS.
Ponzu: READY AND WAITING.
( Gon breathes deeply )
( deep inhale )
( Ponzu grunts )
( grunts )
( exhales )
( sighs )
( Gon thinking )
199, 200,
201, 202, 203,
204, 205, 206...
( exhales )
ALL RIGHT!
♪
WELL, I'LL LEAVE
BOURBON'S BADGE HERE WITH YOU
SO THE COMMITTEE CAN FIND YOU.
YOURS GOES TO LEORIO.
THAT WAY, HE'LL HAVE
HIS SIX POINTS, AND HE CAN PASS.
CONSIDER IT
A SMALL FEE FOR SAVING YOU.
SORRY 'BOUT THAT! NNN!
( ship's horn blows )
Khara on loudspeaker:
PHASE FOUR OF THE HUNTER EXAM
IS NOW OFFICIALLY OVER.
ALL REMAINING APPLICANTS,
PLEASE RETURN
TO THE STARTING POINT AT ONCE.
YOU WILL BE GIVEN ONE ADDITIONAL
HOUR TO MAKE YOUR WAY BACK.
IF YOU STILL HAVEN'T RETURNED
BY THE TIME THAT HOUR IS UP,
YOU WILL FAIL THE EXAM.
FURTHERMORE, EXCHANGING BADGES
AT THE STARTING POINT
IS PROHIBITED.
ANY ATTEMPT TO DO SO WILL RESULT
IN IMMEDIATE DISQUALIFICATION.
♪
Gon: HMM?
( laughs )
( fanfare playing )
Khara: NOW WE
WILL CHECK THE BADGES
OF EVERYONE PRESENT HERE.
NUMBER 44, MR. HISOKA.
NUMBER 53, MR. POKKLE.
NUMBER 99, MR. KILLUA.
NUMBER 301, MR. GITTARACKUR.
NUMBER 191, MR. BODORO.
NUMBER 294, MR. HANZO.
SO ONLY SIX APPLICANTS
HAVE PASSED?
OH, WAIT!
♪
( Hanzo gasps )
Killua: GON!
Khara: THREE MORE.
YOU'RE CERTAINLY
CUTTING IT CLOSE, AREN'T YOU?
Gon: KILLUA.
Hisoka: HMM.
Khara: NOW THE LAST THREE.
THEY ARE...
NUMBER 404, MR. KURAPIKA,
NUMBER 403, MR. LEORIO,
AND NUMBER 405, MR. GON.
SO THESE NINE APPLICANTS
HAVE PASSED
THE FOURTH PHASE OF THE EXAM!
( Netero laughs )
SIX OF THE NINE THAT HAVE PASSED
ARE ROOKIES?
MARVELOUS! MARVELOUS!
Buhara: HAS THAT
EVER HAPPENED BEFORE?
Netero: AH, WELL,
THERE HAS BEEN A TREND LATELY.
WE'LL SOMETIMES GO
SEVERAL YEARS IN A ROW
WITHOUT A SINGLE ROOKIE
WORTHY OF QUALIFYING,
AND THEN WE'LL SUDDENLY HAVE
A WHOLE BUNCH
OF PROMISING NEWBIES APPLY.
THIS MAKES FOUR TIMES
SINCE I BECAME CHAIRMAN.
Satotz: BY THE WAY, SIR,
WHAT WILL WE BE DOING
FOR THE FINAL PHASE?
Buhara: OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVEN'T TOLD US
WHAT YOU HAVE PLANNED YET.
Netero: AH, YES.
WELL, ABOUT THAT,
THEY'LL BE PARTICIPATING
IN A RATHER PECULIAR FIGHT.
Satotz: HMM?
A PECULIAR FIGHT, YOU SAY?
Netero: GATHER THE NINE
REMAINING APPLICANTS.
I'D LIKE TO SPEAK
WITH EACH OF THEM ALONE.
Leorio: DAMN IT,
I'M SO PATHETIC.
THE WHOLE FOURTH PHASE,
I RELIED ON YOU TWO
TO DO EVERYTHING FOR ME.
I PROMISE
I'LL RETURN THE FAVOR.
SO, UH,
WELL, THANKS, YOU GUYS.
( Gon chuckles )
Beans on P. A.:
ATTENTION, ALL APPLICANTS.
THE CHAIRMAN WISHES
TO INTERVIEW YOU.
Leorio: REALLY?
Beans: WHEN YOU HEAR
YOUR NUMBER,
COME TO THE RECEPTION ROOM
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
WE'LL START WITH NUMBER 44,
MR. HISOKA.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION.
Netero: PLEASE,
MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE.
Hisoka: DON'T TELL ME
THAT THIS IS THE FINAL PHASE.
Netero: NOT THE TEST ITSELF,
YOU UNDERSTAND.
I JUST HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS,
MOSTLY TO SATISFY
MY OWN CURIOSITY.
( Hisoka chuckles )
Netero: TO START WITH, WHY DO
YOU WANT TO BECOME A HUNTER?
Hisoka: TO BE FRANK,
I DON'T, BUT...
Netero: GO ON.
Hisoka: A HUNTER LICENSE
CAN BE INCREDIBLY USEFUL.
Netero: OH? AND HOW SO?
Hisoka: FOR EXAMPLE,
HUNTERS CAN OFTEN KILL
WITHOUT ANY FEAR OF PROSECUTION.
Netero: I UNDERSTAND.
MOVING ON TO THE NEXT QUESTION.
OUT OF THE OTHER
EIGHT APPLICANTS,
WHICH ONE ARE YOU
KEEPING A CLOSE EYE ON?
♪
Hisoka: NUMBER 99.
Netero: OH.
Hisoka: 405 ALSO CAUGHT MY EYE,
BUT NOT LIKE 99.
I WOULD LOVE
TO CHALLENGE HIM ONE DAY.
( chuckles )
Netero: WELL, ONE LAST QUESTION,
AND WE'RE DONE.
WHICH OF THE OTHER EIGHT
REMAINING APPLICANTS
WOULD YOU LEAST WANT TO FIGHT?
Hisoka: THAT WOULD BE
NUMBER 405,
THOUGH 99's A CLOSE SECOND.
Netero: AH.
Hisoka: THE TIME
SIMPLY ISN'T RIGHT.
AS FOR NOW,
I'D HAVE TO SAY NUMBER 405.
Netero: HMM. UNDERSTOOD.
Hisoka: HOWEVER, THE ONE I WOULD
MOST LIKE TO FIGHT RIGHT NOW
WOULD HAVE TO BE YOU.
Netero: WELL,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT'LL BE ALL.
Hisoka: THAT IS ONE SLY OLD MAN.
HE LEFT HIMSELF SO OPEN
THAT I LOST MY EDGE.
♪
Pokkle: I'M KEEPING
AN EYE FOCUSED ON NUMBER 404.
HE'S THE MOST WELL‐ROUNDED
APPLICANT.
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT WITH 44,
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
I COULD BEAT HIM.
Killua: WELL, GON.
WE'RE THE SAME AGE.
WHO I DON'T WANNA FIGHT, THOUGH,
IS NUMBER 53.
I DON'T THINK IT'D BE
VERY FUN AT ALL.
Bodoro: I'M KEEPING
A WATCHFUL EYE ON NUMBER 44.
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE HIM.
NUMBERS 405 AND 99
ARE OUT, HOWEVER.
I SIMPLY
WILL NOT FIGHT CHILDREN.
( Gittarackur rattles )
NUMBER 99
AND NUMBER 44.
Gon: WHO AM I KEEPING AN EYE ON?
HISOKA, NUMBER 44.
HE'S ON MY MIND THE MOST,
ANYWAY.
( sighs )
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
I COULD EVER PICK NUMBER 99,
NUMBER 403, OR NUMBER 404.
Hanzo: IT HAS TO BE 44.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY
THE MOST DANGEROUS APPLICANT.
THE ONE I'D LEAST WANT TO MEET
IN COMBAT IS ALSO 44.
Kurapika: I'M WATCHING 405
PURELY FOR POSITIVE REASONS,
44 FOR NEGATIVE REASONS.
I WILL FIGHT ANYONE
IF THERE'S A REASON.
OTHERWISE, I'D RATHER
NOT FIGHT AT ALL.
Leorio: NUMBER 405.
I OWE HIM,
AND I SURE HOPE HE PASSES.
THAT'S WHY HE'S THE ONE
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
Netero: HMM, I SEE.
THIS IS MORE LOPSIDED
THAN I EXPECTED.
Kurapika: GON.
SO WE MADE IT
TO THE FINAL PHASE.
( Kurapika gasps )
Netero: THAT'LL DO IT.
♪
SORRY TO KEEP YOU ALL WAITING.
I'VE DRAWN UP THE BRACKETS.
‐ Menchi: HUH?
‐ Satotz: WHAT'S THIS?
Lippo: HUH?
Buhara: BUT‐‐BUT, CHAIRMAN!
COME ON! YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
( Netero laughs )
OH, I AM QUITE SERIOUS.
Satotz: THAT LOOK.
HE'S SERIOUS INDEED.
Menchi: THAT'S A SERIOUS LOOK?
YOU SURE?
Netero: THE WINNERS
WILL PASS THE EXAM
AND EARN THE TITLE OF HUNTER.
Kurapika: GON...
Gon: HMM?
Kurapika: DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
IN THE FOURTH PHASE?
SINCE WE MET UP,
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING STRANGELY,
AND I'M GETTING CONCERNED.
EVER SINCE WE LEFT ZEVIL ISLAND,
YOU'VE SEEMED RATHER QUIET.
Gon: MY TARGET WAS HISOKA.
( Kurapika gasps )
Gon: I WAITED
FOR THE PERFECT CHANCE
AND STOLE HIS BADGE...
BUT SOMEONE ELSE
WAS FOLLOWING ME,
AND HE GOT ME
WITH A POISON DART.
( no audible dialogue )
AFTER THAT, HISOKA SHOWED UP
AND TOOK HIS BADGE
FROM THE GUY WHO TOOK IT FROM ME
AND THEN LEFT IT.
HE SAID I OWED HIM NOW.
Kurapika: HE REALLY SAID THAT?
Gon: I SAID I DIDN'T NEED IT,
AND HE SENT ME FLYING.
Hisoka: I WILL TAKE IT BACK,
BUT ONLY WHEN YOU CAN PUNCH ME
IN THE FACE LIKE THAT.
Gon: I WAS JUST
SO MAD AT MYSELF.
I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
I WAS HELPLESS AGAINST HIM.
( crying )
♪
AND WHEN HE LEFT,
I GOT SO MISERABLE AND LONELY.
IT WAS JUST AWFUL.
I GUESS IT HURT TO REALIZE
THAT I WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO CHALLENGE HIM.
THAT'S WHY
I WANTED SOME COMPANY.
I WANTED TO FIND SOMEBODY
I COULD HELP, I GUESS.
THAT'S WHEN I DECIDED TO LOOK
FOR THE TWO OF YOU.
Kurapika: GON...
WITHOUT YOUR ASSISTANCE,
LEORIO AND I NEVER
WOULD HAVE MADE IT THIS FAR.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
Gon: I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
THANK YOU, TOO.
Narrator: GON AND HIS FRIENDS
HAVE GROWN CLOSER,
AND THE NINE
REMAINING APPLICANTS
ARE ABOUT TO ENTER
THE EXAM'S FINAL PHASE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"CAN'T WIN AND CAN'T LOSE."
Killua: THEN HOW DO I WIN?
Gon: GIVE IT ALL YOU'VE GOT!