( chorus vocalizing )
Narrator: NEN ABILITIES
FALL INTO THE FOLLOWING
SIX DISTINCT CATEGORIES.
ENHANCERS ARE ABLE
TO STRENGTHEN AND REINFORCE
THE NATURAL PROPERTIES
OF ANY OBJECT THEY ENCOUNTER.
TRANSMUTERS CAN MANIPULATE
AND CHANGE
THE QUALITY OF AURA AT WILL.
SIMILAR TO TRANSMUTERS,
CONJURERS HAVE THE ABILITY
TO MATERIALIZE AN OBJECT
OUT OF AURA.
EMITTERS CAN PROPEL THEIR AURA,
SHOOTING OR
PROJECTING IT FORWARD.
MANIPULATORS CAN USE THEIR AURA
TO CONTROL OBJECTS
OR LIVING THINGS.
SPECIALISTS POSSESS
RARE ABILITIES
WHICH DO NOT FIT WITHIN
THE OTHER FIVE CATEGORIES.
ONE MUST DETERMINE WHICH
CATEGORY THEIR AURA FALLS INTO.
THIS IS THE FIRST STEP
TO BECOMING A SKILLED NEN USER.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: AUNT MITO!
SO LONG! I'M GONNA GO
FIND GING! I PROMISE!
Woman: BYE!
Gon: AND AFTER I MEET HIM,
I'M GONNA COME BACK
TO THE ISLAND, OKAY?
‐ Woman: GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
‐ Man: SAFE TRIP.
Gon: BYE! TAKE CARE!
I'LL MISS YOU!
( overlapping chatter )
( waves crash )
Narrator: MEANWHILE,
AS GON AND KILLUA
DEPART FROM WHALE ISLAND,
KURAPIKA IS PREPARING
TO BEGIN A JOURNEY OF HIS OWN.
Kurapika: SO YOU REMEMBER ME?
Agent: WELL, YEAH.
WE DON'T GET
MANY VISITORS HERE.
IN FACT, EVER SINCE
YOU WERE HERE LAST,
THERE'S ONLY BEEN
ONE OTHER PERSON.
THIS PLACE IS A WHOLE LOT HARDER
TO FIND THAN YOU THINK.
♪
YOU FOUND THIS AGENCY
ON YOUR OWN,
AND THAT TELLS ME
YOU'RE PRETTY SHARP.
EVEN SO...
I CAN'T INTRODUCE YOU
TO OUR VALUED CLIENTS.
AND IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF
YOUR TOTAL LACK OF EXPERIENCE.
SOME OF OUR CLIENTS
DON'T SEEM TO MIND THAT.
THE THING IS,
EXPERIENCE ISN'T ALL YOU LACK.
Kurapika: BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE I TOLD YOU, I ALREADY
HAVE A HUNTER'S LICENSE.
Agent: MAYBE,
BUT YOUR EXAM ISN'T OVER YET.
( Kurapika gasps )
Agent: IT'S OBVIOUS.
Kurapika: EXCUSE ME?
( aura sneers )
Agent: YOU CAN'T SEE ANYTHING,
CAN YOU?
( Kurapika stammers )
Agent: YOU COME BACK
WHEN YOU CAN.
( wind blows )
( Kurapika exhales )
( gasps )
Man: YOU CAN'T SEE IT,
BUT YOU CAN SENSE IT, HUH?
Kurapika: WHY DID YOU DO THAT?!
Man: THIS? ( chuckles )
I WAS JUST PLAYING AROUND.
( thunder crashes )
THIS MUST BE FATE,
US CROSSING PATHS. YOU THINK?
TRY TO THINK OF THIS
AS A LITTLE BIT OF
FRIENDLY ADVICE FROM A SENIOR.
( Kurapika gasps )
Man: YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
WHEN I STOLE THIS
OR WHEN I WALKED
RIGHT PAST YOU, EITHER.
YOU'RE TOTALLY CLUELESS.
Kurapika: BASTARD. GIVE ME
BACK MY LICENSE RIGHT NOW!
Man: DOES A NEWBIE
WHO KNOWS NOTHING OF NEN
HAVE A CHANCE OF BEATING ME?
Kurapika: NEN, HUH?
‐ ( man chuckles )
‐ ( thunder crashes )
WANNA GIVE IT A TRY?
( Kurapika panting )
Man: DO YOU GET IT NOW?
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
YOU STILL LACK.
COME WITH ME.
I'LL TEACH YOU.
THE REAL EXAM HAS JUST BEGUN.
( birds chirping )
TODAY WE'RE GONNA DETERMINE
WHICH CATEGORY
YOUR AURA FALLS UNDER.
( Kurapika exhales )
Teacher: THERE'S SOMETHING
FORMING IN THE WATER,
SO YOU'RE A CONJURER.
IT'S CLEAR.
Kurapika: A CONJURER?
Teacher: A TYPE WHOSE SPECIALTY
IS MANIFESTING THEIR AURA.
Kurapika: I SEE. I WAS HOPING
I WOULD BE AN ENHANCER.
Teacher: UNFORTUNATELY YOU CAN'T
CHANGE WHAT YOU'RE BORN WITH.
BUT IT ISN'T HOPELESS.
YOU CAN STILL LEARN
ENHANCEMENT TECHNIQUES.
AND THAT WOULD MAKE AN EXCELLENT
TOPIC FOR US TO GO OVER TODAY.
( wings flutter )
NOW LET'S SAY
YOU HAVE THE APTITUDE
TO ACHIEVE 100% MASTERY
OF CONJURATION ABILITIES.
AT THE MOST, THIS IS HOW MUCH
YOU COULD MASTER THE OTHERS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW FAST OF A LEARNER YOU ARE.
YOU CAN NEVER COMPLETELY MASTER
A DIFFERENT CATEGORY.
THE FURTHER A CATEGORY IS FROM
YOUR OWN, THE LESS YOU ACQUIRE.
Kurapika: WHY IS
SPECIALIST AT ZERO?
Teacher: SPECIALIST IS
A UNIQUE CATEGORY,
AND THEIR ABILITIES
AREN'T THE KIND
YOU CAN SIMPLY TEACH YOURSELF.
THEY'RE VERY DISTINCT ABILITIES,
EITHER INHERITED
OR ACQUIRED NATURALLY,
A PRODUCT OF YOUR ENVIRONMENT.
SO WHY THIS POSITION?
BECAUSE THE ADJACENT CATEGORIES,
CONJURER AND MANIPULATOR,
HAVE THE GREATEST CHANCE OF
BECOMING SPECIALISTS LATER ON.
IN THAT RESPECT, YOU STILL
HAVE A CHANCE, IN A WAY.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID?
♪
( Kurapika panting )
‐ Teacher: HMM?
‐ Kurapika: I‐‐I NEED‐‐
I NEED ENOUGH POWER
TO FIGHT ON MY OWN!
Teacher: YOU MIGHT ASSUME THAT
THE FASTEST MEANS TO YOUR GOAL
WOULD BE THROUGH
ENHANCEMENT ABILITIES,
AND YOU'D BE RIGHT.
ENHANCERS ARE ABLE TO REINFORCE
OFFENSE, DEFENSE, AND HEALING
MOST EFFICIENTLY.
BUT SINCE YOU'RE A CONJURER,
YOU CAN ONLY LEARN ENHANCER
ABILITIES UP TO HALF POTENCY.
IF YOU TRY
TO EXCEED YOUR LIMITS,
IT WILL CAUSE YOU
INCREDIBLE STRAIN,
AND THAT CAN WEAKEN YOU.
( snap )
IT COULD EVEN BE FATAL.
CONSISTENT POWER
IS THE ONLY WAY TO STAY ON TOP.
Kurapika: IF I WERE CONSISTENT
IN MY ABILITIES AS A CONJURER,
DO YOU THINK THAT IT
WOULD HELP ME IN A BATTLE
IF I WERE PITTED
AGAINST A MASTER ENHANCER?
Teacher: HMM.
IN SHORT,
IT WOULD BE DIFFICULT.
WHEN CLOSELY COMPARED
TO AN ENHANCER'S
OFFENSE AND DEFENSE,
FAR MORE OFTEN THAN NOT,
CONJURERS ARE SIMPLY
NOT AS EVENLY BALANCED.
BUT THAT SAID, YOU COULD
ACTUALLY BE QUITE FORMIDABLE
IF YOU FIND YOUR GROOVE.
‐ HERE'S A QUIZ.
‐ Kurapika: EH?
Teacher: CAN YOU
CONJURE A SWORD
THAT'S ABLE
TO CUT THROUGH ANYTHING?
‐ Kurapika: YOU CAN'T.
‐ Teacher: WHY NOT?
Kurapika: BECAUSE IT EXCEEDS
THE BOUNDS OF HUMAN CAPACITY.
Teacher: THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THERE ARE THINGS
YOU CAN NEVER CONJURE,
EVEN WITH 100% MASTERY.
♪
OF COURSE, YOU COULD CONJURE
A SWORD THAT'S
VERY SHARP AND STURDY,
BUT IT WOULD MAKE
A LOT MORE SENSE
TO JUST GO OUT AND BUY ONE.
YOU WOULDN'T NEED
EXTRA TRAINING.
YOU CAN MAKE THE SWORD APPEAR
AND DISAPPEAR USING NEN,
BUT CONJURED WEAPONS
JUST AREN'T AS EFFECTIVE.
THE PHYSICAL VERSIONS
ARE BETTER.
UNFORTUNATELY YOU CAN'T CONJURE
ANYTHING THAT'S SUPERNATURAL.
SO CONSIDER IT CAREFULLY,
AND CHOOSE
WHAT YOU WISH TO CONJURE.
NO MISTAKES ALLOWED.
CONJURING SOMETHING AT WILL
TAKES A LOT OF CONCENTRATION,
NOT TO MENTION
TRAINING AND TIME,
AND THAT'S JUST
WHAT IT TAKES FOR ONE THING.
♪
Agent: WHAT A SURPRISE.
Kurapika: HUH?
Agent: I DON'T KNOW MANY PEOPLE
WHO LEARNED NEN
IN ONLY SIX MONTHS.
SO WHAT KIND OF EMPLOYER
DO YOU WANT?
Hisoka: I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING
INTERESTING ABOUT SPIDERS.
♪
MEET ME IN YORKNEW CITY
ON SEPTEMBER FIRST.
Kurapika: I WOULD PREFER
TO FIND AN EMPLOYER
WITH STRONG TIES
TO THE YORKNEW AUCTION.
THE JOB IS IRRELEVANT.
Agent: THE YORKNEW CITY AUCTION.
EMPLOYERS WHO HAVE
A LOT OF INFLUENCE
GENERALLY POST
THE DIFFICULT JOBS.
I DOUBT THEY'RE LOOKING TO HIRE
A HUNTER WITH ZERO EXPERIENCE.
I SEE THREE,
THREE EMPLOYERS WHO'LL DECIDE
BASED ON THE INTERVIEW
AND NOT ON YOUR RECORD,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE ALL THREE
ARE LOOKING FOR BODYGUARDS.
I'LL READ. YOU CHOOSE, 'KAY?
THE FIRST IS A HANDGUN BUFF.
HE'S AFTER
THE MISETTE LIMITED EDITION
BULL SNAKE MODEL S‐55,
NUMBER 001.
THE SECOND IS
A COLLECTOR OF FINE CHINA.
THIS ONE IS SEEKING
RODO MEMORIAL PLATES
FROM 1655 TO 1657.
AND THE THIRD
IS A FLESH COLLECTOR...
( Kurapika gasps )
SEEKING A HIDE WITH A FULL
BODY TATTOO OF A RISING DRAGON,
THE HEAD OF A CHILD
WITH JELLY SYNDROME,
AND A FEW OTHERS.
THAT SURE IS QUITE A HOBBY.
ALL RIGHT. TAKE YOUR PICK.
HUH?
♪
Teacher: CHAINS?
Kurapika: YES. WHEN YOU
SAID I WAS A CONJURER,
THAT WAS THE FIRST THING
THAT CAME TO MIND.
Teacher: INTERESTING,
BUT WHY CHAINS?
Kurapika: IT'S BECAUSE
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
AT LARGE IN THE WORLD
RIGHT NOW
WHO NEED TO BE CHAINED TO HELL.
Teacher: OH, IS THAT SO?
BECAUSE I CAN'T SHAKE
THE NAGGING SUSPICION
THAT YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'LL BE CHAINED DOWN.
Kurapika: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW?
Teacher: WAIT A SECOND!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M YOUR TEACHER! DO AS I SAY!
I'M NOT DONE TALKING TO YOU!
HOLD ON, DAMN IT!
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
ORDINARY CHAINS ARE POINTLESS!
THEY'RE INFERIOR!
AND CONJURING SOME KIND
OF UNBREAKABLE CHAIN
IS COMPLETELY IMPOSSIBLE!
♪
Kurapika: ON SEPTEMBER FIRST,
YORKNEW CITY WILL HOST
THE WORLD'S GREATEST AUCTION.
THAT'S WHERE THE SPIDER,
THE PHANTOM TROUPE WILL APPEAR.
( chains jangle )
( woman gasps )
THAT HEARTBEAT,
IT PLAYS
A HORRIBLE MELODY OF RAGE.
Agent: SO YOU WANT ME
TO FIND YOU AN EMPLOYER
WITH CONNECTIONS
TO THE YORKNEW AUCTION?
DID I GET THAT RIGHT?
Hunter: THAT'S RIGHT.
Agent: LIKE THE LAST GUY
WHO WALKED IN.
Hunter: HUH?
Agent: SAME REQUEST TWICE TODAY.
AMUSING, IS ALL.
Hunter: THE BOY I JUST PASSED?
Agent: DO YOU KNOW HIM?
Hunter: UH, NO, I DON'T.
( chains jangle )
HE'S INTERESTED
IN THE AUCTION, TOO?
BUT THEN...
WHY IS HIS HEARTBEAT
SO FULL OF RAGE?
♪
( car door closes )
( man gasps )
( whimpers )
Man #2: EATING WITH
A TWERP LIKE THAT
WILL ONLY MAKE
YOUR FOOD TASTE WORSE.
Man #3: WHY DON'T YOU
LET US TAKE YOU OUT INSTEAD?
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE BEST NIGHT
OF YOUR LIFE, SWEETHEART.
Woman: THIS ISN'T A DATE,
UNFORTUNATELY.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A JOB.
Man #3: A JOB? REALLY?
Woman: THIS IS
ACTUALLY MY EMPLOYER.
HE'S HIRED ME AS HIS BODYGUARD.
Man #2: BODYGUARD?
Man #3: YOU'VE GOTTA BE JOKING.
A BABE LIKE YOU, A BODYGUARD?
( men laugh )
Man #2: I'D BE HAPPY
TO LET YOU GUARD MY BODY.
( slurps )
Woman: I DON'T GUARD UGLY MEN,
BUT THANKS, ANYWAY.
Man #2: WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?!
SHUT YOUR‐‐
( laughs )
( woman, echoing )
INSTANT LOVER.
EVERY SINGLE PERSON THAT I KISS
BECOMES MY WILLING SLAVE.
( man #2 panting )
WHAT'S YOUR COMMAND, MISTRESS?
I LIVE TO SERVE YOU.
Woman: BEAT THEM UP FOR ME.
Man #2: YES, MA'AM! MY PLEASURE!
( men stammer )
( man #2 laughs )
‐ ( blows landing )
‐ ( men grunting )
( employer whimpers )
( screams )
( woman sighs ) HE RAN AWAY.
AH, WELL. GUESS I'LL NEED
ANOTHER EMPLOYER.
WHAT A PAIN.
♪
Man: A SPLENDID MOON.
Guard: THERE HE IS!
Guard #2: WE'VE GOT YOU NOW!
Guard #3: HAND OVER
THE CORPSE SAMPLES YOU STOLE,
NICE AND EASY!
Thief: HMM? DON'T INTERRUPT,
NOT MY WORK
AND NOT THIS SPLENDID MOON.
( guard #2 groans )
THAT'S ENOUGH!
PUT YOUR HANDS UP!
Thief: I WAS ON THE VERGE
OF ANOTHER MASTERFUL POEM,
BUT YOU SPOILED THE MOMENT,
YOU IMBECILES!
♪
( blows landing )
"SPLENDID FULL MOON AND PURSUERS
AS CLUMSY AS A BABOON..."
( growls ) THAT SUCKS.
Man: YES, I KNOW, ELIZA.
WELL, IF THIS JOB
WORKS OUT, I‐‐
YEAH. THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
I'LL HANDLE IT. RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU
AND THE DOGS.
REALLY WON'T BE A PROBLEM,
SO DON'T WORRY, ELIZA.
BEAR WITH ME
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
YEAH. IT'LL BE FINE.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
♪
( chains jangle )
( doorbell chimes )
Kurapika: I WAS SENT
BY THE EMPLOYMENT AGENCY!
MY NAME IS KURAPIKA!
( dog growling )
Butler: WELCOME. WE'RE HAPPY
THAT YOU COULD JOIN US.
IF YOU'D BE SO KIND
AS TO WAIT HERE.
♪
Butler: THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
IT SEEMS EVERYONE HAS ARRIVED,
SO WE WILL NOW BEGIN GOING OVER
THE DETAILS OF THE CONTRACT.
Employer: I'LL START
BY GOING OVER THE REQUIREMENTS.
I WON'T ASK WHETHER OR NOT
YOU HAVE A LICENSE.
MY ONLY CONCERN IS WHETHER YOU
CAN OBTAIN THE ITEMS WE SEEK.
THE AUCTION, AS YOU ALL KNOW,
WILL BEGIN IN ONE MONTH.
BEFORE THAT TIME, FIND ONE ITEM
FROM THE LIST PROVIDED,
AND THEN BRING IT
SAFELY BACK HERE.
Butler: HERE YOU GO.
THESE ARE THE DATA CARDS
YOU'RE ASSIGNED.
♪
( beep )
( Kurapika gasps )
♪
( gasping )
Poet: WHAT? SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE PALE.
AH. THE EYEBALLS
OF A KURTA, HUH?
"DIFFICULTY LEVEL 'A.'
"PRESERVE THE POSTMORTEM
SCARLET HUE AFTER DEATH.
COMPLETE SET
WITH HEAD PREFERRED."
YEAH, I'VE HEARD ABOUT THAT.
THEIR EYES TURN RED
WHENEVER THEY'RE EXCITED.
‐ YOU SEE, THE KURTA‐‐
‐ Kurapika: SHUT UP.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
Poet: HMM. HUMPH.
Employer: I'LL SAY IT AGAIN.
ALL THAT'S REQUIRED
IS ONE ITEM
FROM THE LIST YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN.
IF YOU'RE SUCCESSFUL,
YOU'LL BE HIRED
AND BEGIN YOUR TRAINING
IN SECURITY AND ACQUISITIONS.
WELL, THEN,
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU.
Kurapika: I WILL PASS THIS TEST.
FIRST I MUST INGRATIATE MYSELF
AND WIN THEIR TRUST.
IN ALL LIKELIHOOD,
THE MAN WE SAW
WAS NOT THE ACTUAL CLIENT,
THUS ILLUSTRATING THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN THE CLIENT AND MYSELF.
IT'S CRITICAL THAT I GET
AS CLOSE TO THEM AS POSSIBLE
UNTIL THEY EVENTUALLY
LET THEIR GUARD DOWN
AND SHARE THEIR SECRETS.
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
THAT COLLECTORS ALWAYS DESIRE.
THE FIRST IS ANY ITEM
OF EXTREME RARITY.
THE SECOND IS COLLEAGUES
TO WHOM THEY CAN BRAG
ABOUT THEIR COLLECTION.
HE MUST HAVE CONNECTIONS
TO OTHER FLESH COLLECTORS,
THOSE WHO SHARE
THEIR DISGUSTING ACQUISITIONS,
A NETWORK OF SCUM.
I WILL INFILTRATE THEIR RANKS
AND ERADICATE THEM ALL.
( lock rattles )
Poet: HEY, IT WON'T OPEN.
( screen whirs )
Employer: I FORGOT
TO MENTION ONE THING.
THE MINIMUM REQUIREMENT
FOR THE POSITION IS STRENGTH,
ENOUGH STRENGTH
TO GET OUT OF THIS MANSION...
WITH YOUR LIVES.
( woman gasps )
♪
Narrator: KURAPIKA
PURSUES HIS QUEST
TO AVENGE HIS BRETHREN
AND PUNISH THE PHANTOM TROUPE,
AND RIGHT NOW HE IS PREPARING
TO ENTER A NEW BATTLEFIELD.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE INTRODUCING
MIZUKEN, KURAPIKA'S TEACHER.
Killua: AND HE'S
AN EMITTER TYPE.
Gon: I GUESS NEN USERS
ARE FATED TO MEET NEN TEACHERS.
Killua: IT HAPPENED TO US.
Both: MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE
MET EACH OTHER. IT'S FATE!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"NEN USERS UNITE?"
Killua: HEY, GON, LET'S GO BREAK
SOME OF MILLUKI'S FIGURINES.
Gon: COUNT ME IN
AS YOUR ACCOMPLICE.