Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS OFF
YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Killua: GON, YOU AND ME,
WE'VE GOTTA LEARN
ALL THAT WE CAN ABOUT NEN.
( Gon chuckles )
YEAH!
♪
Narrator: AFTER TWO MONTHS,
DURING WHICH GON WAS FORBIDDEN
TO PRACTICE NEN,
WING SUMMONED GON AND KILLUA
TO HIS ROOM FOR A MEETING.
Wing: GON, KILLUA,
STARTING TODAY, YOU WILL BE
TRAINING ALONGSIDE ZUSHI.
AND, GON, SPLENDID WORK.
I'M HAPPY TO SEE
THAT YOU KEPT YOUR PROMISE.
IT'S BECAUSE
OF YOUR PROMISE THREAD.
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF TIMES
THAT I GOT REALLY CLOSE
TO GIVING IN,
BUT THEN I'D LOOK AT THE THREAD,
AND I COULD FEEL MYSELF
GETTING CALMER.
Wing: BECAUSE I IMBUED IT
WITH NEN TO HELP YOU.
Gon: WAIT. REALLY?
Wing: NO. I WAS KIDDING.
( Gon groans )
Killua: HOLD ON.
HOW CAN YOU TELL
GON'S BEEN KEEPING HIS PROMISE?
AS FAR AS YOU KNOW,
HE WAS SECRETLY CHEATING
THIS WHOLE TIME.
( Gon groans )
Wing: BECAUSE THE PROMISE THREAD
IS COMPLETELY INTACT.
GON, I KNOW IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
BUT WOULD YOU SHOW ME YOUR TEN?
Gon: YOU SURE?
Wing: YES.
Killua: OH, MAN.
DO I EVEN REMEMBER HOW?
Gon: IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
I WONDER IF I
CAN STILL PULL IT OFF.
Wing: WHAT DO YOU THINK, ZUSHI?
Zushi: IT‐‐IT'S AMAZING.
HIS AURA IS FLOWING
COMPLETELY AROUND HIM, SIR!
IT'S SOFT AND TRANQUIL,
BUT IT'S‐‐IT'S SO POWERFUL, TOO!
Gon: THAT'S IT! WHAT A RELIEF.
MAN, I WAS WORRIED
I HAD FORGOTTEN HOW TO DO IT!
Wing: ONCE YOU'VE
LEARNED THE TECHNIQUE,
IT CAN'T BE FORGOTTEN.
HOWEVER, IN ORDER
TO BECOME A TRUE MASTER,
YOU WILL HAVE
TO PRACTICE DILIGENTLY.
Gon: BUT IT FELT A LOT EASIER
THAN IT DID BEFORE,
AND I HAVEN'T PRACTICED TEN
IN A REAL LONG TIME.
Wing: I CAN EXPLAIN.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
TRAINING YOUR SPIRIT EVERY DAY.
NOW PLEASE LOOK
AT YOUR LEFT HAND.
Gon: HUH?
( gasps )
IT BROKE!
Wing: I TIED THE THREAD
TO YOUR FINGER WITH MY OWN NEN,
SO IF YOU
HAD BROKEN YOUR PROMISE,
THE THREAD
WOULD HAVE BROKEN AS WELL.
Killua: YOU CAN
DO STUFF LIKE THAT?
QUESTION, MR. WING‐‐
YOU SAW HISOKA
AND KASTRO'S MATCH?
Wing: YES, I DID.
Killua: SO WHAT
WAS HISOKA'S ABILITY?
DO YOU THINK WE COULD DO THAT,
SEND OUR LIMBS FLYING
ALL OVER THE PLACE?
Wing: HMM.
THAT'S A DIFFICULT QUESTION.
GON, HAVE YOU SEEN
A RECORDING OF THE FIGHT?
Gon: NO. NOT YET, SIR. EH?
Wing: THEN I'LL EXPLAIN
WHILE WE WATCH.
( crowd cheering )
Wing: THERE.
SEE THE STRANDS OF AURA
EXTENDING OUT
FROM HIS LEFT HAND?
Gon: STRANDS OF AURA?
Wing: YES. DO YOU SEE THEM?
( boys groan )
Gon: NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
Killua: I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
Zushi: ME NEITHER, SIR.
( Gon grunts )
ARE THERE REALLY STRANDS OF AURA
COMING OUT OF HIS LEFT HAND?
ARE YOU SURE?
Wing: I AM. SEE,
HISOKA IS USING A TECHNIQUE
THAT MAKES HIS AURA EXCEEDINGLY
DIFFICULT TO PERCEIVE.
IT'S A HIGH‐LEVEL APPLICATION
OF ZETSU, KNOWN AS "IN."
IT RENDERS EVEN POWERFUL AURA
INVISIBLE TO YOUR OPPONENT.
AND TO COUNTER THIS,
YOU MUST FOCUS ALL YOUR REN
IN BOTH OF YOUR EYES
UTILIZING A TECHNIQUE
KNOWN AS GYO.
THE METHOD GON USED IN HIS FIGHT
WITH GIDO MIGHT ALSO BE USEFUL,
BUT YOU CAN'T COUNTERATTACK,
SO YOU'D ULTIMATELY
GET YOURSELF KILLED.
Gon: RIGHT.
Wing: MY ASSIGNMENT
FOR THE TWO OF YOU
IS TO PRACTICE REN UNTIL YOU
CAN SEE THROUGH HISOKA'S IN.
Zushi: BUT, MASTER,
WHAT ABOUT ME?
WHAT KIND OF TRAINING
SHOULD I DO?
Wing: ZUSHI, YOU SHOULD
ALREADY BE JUST STRONG ENOUGH
TO SEE PAST HISOKA'S IN.
Zushi: YOU THINK SO?
Wing: IF YOU WOULD,
PLEASE SHOW THEM YOUR REN.
Zushi: UH...
( grunts )
O‐OSU!
( chorus vocalizing )
( inhales )
( grunts )
REN!
( Gon and Killua gasp )
Gon: IT'S SO STRONG.
IT'S JUST AS BIG AS OURS,
BUT THE AURA
IS SO MUCH MORE DENSE.
Wing: NOW FOCUS THAT AURA
INTO YOUR EYES.
Zushi: OSU!
( grunting )
AND GYO!
Wing: GOOD. SO TELL ME,
CAN YOU SEE THE AURA
RUSHING FROM HIS BODY?
Zushi: EH...
YES.
Wing: THERE ARE
INDIVIDUAL STRANDS OF AURA.
HOW MANY OF THEM DO YOU SEE?
Zushi: 12.
WAIT. NO.
I THINK I COUNT 13, SIR.
Wing: NOT QUITE,
BUT YOU ARE VERY CLOSE INDEED.
( Zushi groans )
( panting )
I REALLY COULD SEE THEM.
Wing: YOU'RE REALLY MAKING
EXCELLENT PROGRESS, ZUSHI.
Zushi: OSU! THANK YOU!
I'M TRYING, MASTER.
Wing: BY CHANNELING EVERY OUNCE
OF YOUR POWER THROUGH GYO,
YOU ACHIEVED A LEVEL WHERE YOU
COULD SEE THROUGH HISOKA'S IN.
BUT WITH ENOUGH TRAINING,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO USE GYO
EVEN WHILE YOU'RE FIGHTING.
♪
NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
FIRST, PRACTICE USING REN,
AND MASTER THE APPLICATION
KNOWN AS GYO.
THEN, AND ONLY THEN,
WILL YOU DISCOVER THE TRUE
NATURE OF HISOKA'S ABILITY.
YOU ASKED IF YOU WOULD EVER BE
ABLE TO USE THAT SAME ABILITY,
AND MY ANSWER IS YES,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, NO.
( both gasp )
Wing: REGARDLESS
OF WHAT HIS POWER IS,
SO LONG AS IT USES NEN,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO LEARN IT,
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE
THAT NEN ABILITIES
DEPEND ON THE INDIVIDUAL,
BECAUSE OF COURSE
WE EACH POSSESS
DIFFERENT SPECIALTIES
AND PREFERENCES,
WHICH MEANS THAT NEN
DIFFERS FOR EACH PERSON.
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT MASTERING NEN,
YOU SHOULDN'T MERELY COPY
THE ABILITIES OF OTHERS.
YOU NEED TO FIRST IDENTIFY
YOUR OWN PARTICULAR STRENGTHS.
Killua: STRENGTHS, HUH?
Wing: YOU'RE STILL GROWING,
SO YOU HAVEN'T SETTLED
ON ONE FORM YET.
MY ADVICE IS TO ENRICH YOURSELF
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
THAT IS THE PURPOSE
OF YOUR TRAINING.
TRAIN WITH ALL OF YOUR MIGHT.
PLAY JUST AS HARD,
AND ENJOY LIFE.
Boys: OSU!
Wing: I BELIEVE THE LAST DAY
OF KILLUA'S WINDOW TO COMPETE
IS JUNE NINTH.
AND, GON,
YOURS IS THE TENTH, CORRECT?
BOTH OF YOU SHOULD REGISTER
TO FIGHT ON YOUR FINAL DAY.
IN THE MEANTIME, YOU'LL TRAIN.
YOU MUST BOTH LEARN GYO
BEFORE YOU ENTER BATTLE.
Boys: OSU!
Gon: HEY, ZUSHI,
YOUR REN WAS IMPRESSIVE.
YOU GOT WAY AHEAD OF US
WHILE I WAS STUCK RECUPERATING.
Zushi: NO. I'VE STILL
GOT A LONG WAY TO GO.
Gon: HEY, WHY DON'T
WE PRACTICE A LITTLE?
IT SHOULD BE FUN.
Killua: OKAY. THEN LET'S
GO UP TO YOUR ROOM, GON.
Gon: MM‐HMM.
( gasps )
ZUSHI, KILLUA...
Zushi: I FEEL IT.
Killua: WE'VE GOT COMPANY, GUYS.
( elevator bell dings )
♪
YOU DON'T GIVE UP, DO YOU?
THAT ISN'T THE WAY
TO MAKE FRIENDS.
Man: NOW THAT'LL BE
ENOUGH OF THAT.
JUST TELL US WHEN
YOU'RE GOING TO FIGHT,
BECAUSE I'M DYING
TO BE YOUR OPPONENT. HEH.
( Killua scoffs )
I GUESS THESE GUYS
SPECIALIZE IN HUNTING NEWBIES.
THIS IS WHAT THEY DO,
GET WINS BEATING US UP.
Man: WE'RE GETTING
DESPERATE HERE.
SEE, OUR DEADLINE
IS APPROACHING.
COME ON. WE WANNA FIGHT. HEH.
I'LL EVEN DEMONSTRATE MY POWER
FOR YOU RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
HOW ABOUT THAT? HEH.
‐ ( Zushi gasps )
‐ Gon: OKAY.
I'M GOING TO BE FIGHTING
ON JUNE THE TENTH.
Killua: HEY! GON!
Man: THAT WON'T WORK FOR ME.
I'M SORRY TO TELL YOU,
BUT MY DEADLINE IS MAY 29th.
FIGHT ON THAT DAY.
Killua: WHO CARES ABOUT
YOUR STUPID DEADLINE, YOU IDIOT?
LET'S GET GOING.
Man: GON, MY FRIEND...
YOU AND I WILL FIGHT.
I GUARANTEE IT. HEH.
IT'S A PROMISE.
Killua: COME ON. IGNORE HIM.
Riehlvelt:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
Man: I'M GOING
TO FORCE HIM TO FIGHT ME.
HEH HEH.
Killua: VISUALIZE ENERGY
BUILDING UP IN YOUR BODY.
FEEL THE POWER FROM EACH
AND EVERY CELL GATHERING,
GROWING AND GROWING.
THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
FORCE THAT POWER OUT!
( boys sigh )
Gon: I'M GETTING THE HANG OF IT.
Killua: THE TIMING TO GET TEN
TO CONTAIN THAT AURA
WAS A LITTLE BIT TRICKY.
Zushi: WAIT. A LITTLE?!
HOW ARE THEY
PICKING IT UP SO FAST?
Gon: BUT ZUSHI'S AURA
IS STRONGER.
WE'RE NOT EVEN CLOSE
TO MATCHING HIM YET.
Killua: GUESS WE
OUGHT TO TRAIN MORE.
Zushi: UH, N‐NO! THAT'S ENOUGH.
LEARNING WHEN TO REST
IS A BIG PART OF TRAINING.
WHY DON'T WE
JUST CALL IT A DAY?
Killua: REALLY? 'CAUSE I CA‐‐
Zushi: I TOLD YOU NO!
IF THEY SURPASS ME
IN HALF A DAY,
I'LL LOSE ALL MY MOTIVATION.
Killua: WHAT'S THE DEAL?
Gon: OH, IT'S FINE.
SO MORE TOMORROW?
Killua: WORKS FOR ME.
Zushi: I'LL SEE YOU
AGAIN TOMORROW.
Gon: TAKE IT EASY.
Killua: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
( overlapping chatter )
( elevator bell dings )
Man: HEH.
( sighs )
( Zushi gasping )
I CAN'T‐‐I CAN'T MOVE!
I CAN'T TALK OR BREATHE EITHER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Riehlvelt: OOPS.
Man: IT'S YOUR TURN.
Gido: ALL RIGHT.
Man: HEH HEH.
‐ Killua: KNOCK IT OFF.
‐ ( man gasps )
Killua: I FIGURED
YOU MIGHT BE UP TO SOMETHING.
BUT FORGET THE DIRTY TRICKS.
YOU WANT A FIGHT, FINE.
WHICH DAY DO YOU WANT?
OH, AND DON'T WORRY.
I'LL LET YOU WIN, OKAY?
WAIT. HOW ABOUT
I GIVE ALL OF YOU A WIN?
GOOD ENOUGH?
Man: ONCE I GET
MY WIN AGAINST YOU,
YOUR FRIEND GON
WILL BE MY NEXT VICTIM.
Killua: IF YOU WANNA FIGHT GON,
YOU'LL HAVE TO WORK
AROUND HIS SCHEDULE.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
HE'LL BE HAPPY TO.
IN FACT, I CAN GUARANTEE IT.
Man: HEH HEH HEH HEH.
OKAY.
IF THE TWO OF YOU
ARE WILLING TO FIGHT,
IT'LL SAVE US THE TROUBLE
OF USING TACTICS LIKE THIS ONE.
Riehlvelt: WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE ALL REGISTER TOGETHER?
ONCE THAT'S DONE,
WE'LL RETURN THE BOY UNHARMED.
Killua: YEAH, SURE. OKAY.
BUT THIS IS ABSOLUTELY
THE VERY LAST TIME.
YOU GOT THAT?
( pen scratching )
THERE. MAY 29th.
DONE. YOU HAPPY NOW?
Man: YES.
WE'LL RETURN YOUR FRIEND HERE.
Killua: AND UP WE GO.
OH. I'LL SAY IT AGAIN.
IT'S THE LAST TIME.
AND IF YOU BREAK YOUR PROMISE‐‐
( groans ) WHATEVER.
FORGET IT.
Riehlvelt: WHAT? I'M CURIOUS.
Man: WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
IF WE BREAK OUR PROMISE?
Killua: THERE'S NO POINT
IN TELLING YOU NOW.
JUST KEEP YOUR END
OF THE DEAL, OKAY?
Man: HEH HEH.
( rings )
Gido: HELLO? IS THIS GON?
♪
I DON'T THINK I HAVE
TO TELL YOU WHAT THIS MEANS.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T TELL ANYONE
AND YOU FOLLOW MY INSTRUCTIONS
TO THE LETTER,
THE THREE OF YOU
WILL BE ABLE TO TRAIN TOMORROW
JUST LIKE YOU PLANNED.
( Gon gasps )
ZUSHI.
( peg leg thumping )
Man: SO HOW DID IT GO WITH GON?
Gido: PERFECTLY.
HE'S REGISTERED FOR THE 30th.
Man: HEH HEH.
THAT MAKES TWO VICTORIES.
TOO EASY.
HEH HEH HEH.
Killua: NOT KILLING PEOPLE IS
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
AH, MAN.
HONEST LIVING IS TOUGH.
( overlapping chatter )
Scalper: STEP RIGHT UP!
GET YOUR TICKETS HERE!
THESE ARE HOT OFF THE PRESSES,
LADIES AND GENTS!
GON VERSUS SADASO!
( Killua gasps )
Scalper: WE'VE GOT KILLUA
VERSUS SADASO, TOO!
BETTER BUY 'EM NOW,
OR YOU'RE GONNA REGRET IT!
Killua: HEY, POPS.
Scalper: 'SUP, KID?
Killua: THAT SADASO GUY
HAS JUST ONE ARM?
Scalper: THAT'S RIGHT.
THE ONE‐ARMED FIGHTER
WITH A FACE LIKE A MASK.
IF HE GRABS YOU
WITH HIS INVISIBLE LEFT ARM,
YOU'RE DONE.
SEE, THEY CALL HIM
THE NEWBIE HUNTER, AND‐‐
♪
Killua: THAT SON OF A...
( door closes )
Gon: KILLUA? HEY.
Killua: GON.
THIS IS WHERE YOU'VE BEEN?
Gon: UH, YEAH.
Wing: KILLUA, I HEAR THAT YOU
HELPED ZUSHI HOME LAST NIGHT.
THANK YOU.
Killua: ARE YOU
FEELING ALL RIGHT?
Zushi: YEAH. I'M FINE.
I WAS PROBABLY JUST TIRED.
THAT'S ALL.
I'M SORRY TO WORRY YOU.
Killua: OH. HEY, MR. WING,
DO YOU THINK THAT WE
CAN WATCH THAT VIDEO AGAIN?
'CAUSE I FIGURED OUT
HOW TO USE GYO.
‐ Wing: EH?
‐ Gon: AHH!
Zushi: HUH? REALLY?
♪
( somber chorus singing )
Killua: 15 THREADS, RIGHT?
13 FOR THE CARDS,
ONE MORE FOR THE SCARF,
AND ONE WELL‐HIDDEN ONE
FOR THE ARM HE TOSSED.
AND THEN...
KEEP GOING.
HISOKA'S AURA,
IT ALMOST LOOKS LIKE...
IT'S EXPANDING AND CONTRACTING.
OR DOES IT ATTRACT CERTAIN
OBJECTS LIKE A MAGNET DOES?
HOW ELSE WOULD HIS ARM
REATTACH ITSELF?
NOT TO MENTION FLYING OFF
AND TARGETING KASTRO'S JAW?
MY MONEY IS ON THE FORMER.
I THINK HIS AURA
MUST BE STRETCHY,
LIKE RUBBER OR SOMETHING.
AND IF IT IS,
THEN THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
MOST OF HIS MAGIC TRICKS.
( Killua exhales )
( Zushi gasps )
HE'S ON A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT LEVEL.
Wing: YOU PASS.
THAT'S VERY GOOD.
ALTHOUGH, I AM
A LITTLE SURPRISED.
I CERTAINLY NEVER
EXPECTED BOTH OF YOU
TO ACTUALLY LEARN GYO OVERNIGHT.
‐ ( Killua gasps ) BOTH OF US?
‐ Gon: YEP,
BUT I STILL COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT HISOKA'S ABILITY WAS.
‐ ( Zushi sighs )
‐ Wing: SO, KILLUA,
I'M SURE NOW THAT YOU'VE
FINISHED YOUR ASSIGNMENT,
YOU'LL BE WANTING
TO FIGHT SOON, CORRECT?
Gon: IT'S OKAY. I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BEAT YOU TO THE PUNCH.
I GUESS I JUST GOT AN ITCH
TO FIGHT. THAT'S ALL.
Killua: YEAH. I UNDERSTAND.
THEY MUST HAVE
THREATENED YOU, HUH, GON?
ACTUALLY, I'VE ALREADY
CHOSEN MY DAY TO FIGHT.
I SIGNED UP FOR MAY 29th.
Gon: I'M FIGHTING ON MAY 30th.
Wing: ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I GUESS I UNDERESTIMATED
YOUR PROGRESS.
IT'S QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
BETWEEN NOW
AND YOUR SCHEDULED FIGHTS,
PRACTICE BOTH TEN AND REN,
AND IN ADDITION
TO YOUR TRAINING,
GET PLENTY OF REST AND SLEEP.
Killua and Gon: OSU!
♪
‐ Gon: KILLUA...
‐ Killua: HMM?
Gon: THOSE GUYS THREATENED YOU,
TOO, DIDN'T THEY?
THAT MAKES ME SO MAD.
Killua: YEAH. BUT STILL,
MY BIGGEST CONCERN
WAS GETTING WING'S PERMISSION.
Gon: I GUESS MY BIGGEST CONCERN
IS THAT THEY'LL DO
THE SAME THING TO ZUSHI AGAIN.
Killua: IT'S OKAY.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY.
♪
Sadaso: TODAY, I'LL BEAT
KILLUA FOR MY SIXTH WIN.
TOMORROW, I'LL BEAT GON
FOR MY SEVENTH WIN.
AFTER THAT, ALL I'LL NEED TO DO
IS FIND THREE MORE SUCKERS.
HEH HEH HEH.
THEN I'LL BE A FLOOR MASTER.
WITH THE KIND OF FAME
AND FORTUNE THAT'LL GET ME,
I'LL BE SET
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
( gasps )
Killua: YOU MOVE, YOU DIE.
YOU USE NEN, AND YOU DIE.
MAKE A SOUND, AND YOU DIE.
IF YOU UNDERSTAND,
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
DO YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU BREAK YOUR PROMISES?
IF YOU DO, OPEN YOUR EYES,
LOOK AT ME IN THE MIRROR,
AND LISTEN CAREFULLY.
DON'T EVER SHOW YOUR DIRTY FACE
IN FRONT OF US AGAIN.
YOU'LL KEEP THIS PROMISE.
♪
Referee: SADASO'S TIME IS UP!
KILLUA WINS BY DEFAULT!
‐ ( crowd groaning )
‐ Man: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
‐ Man #2: WHAT IS THIS?!
‐ Man #3: BOO!
Narrator:
KILLUA OPENS THE BATTLE
AGAINST THE PERSISTENT TRIO
WITH A TECHNICAL VICTORY.
THANKS TO THEIR
UNIQUE NATURAL TALENTS,
THE REAL BATTLE AT HEAVENS ARENA
IS ONLY JUST BEGINNING
FOR GON AND KILLUA,
WHO ARE LEARNING NEN
AT INCREDIBLE SPEED.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY
WE'LL BE INTRODUCING SADASO!
HE WENT THROUGH
THE TRADITIONAL INITIATION
WITH GIDO AND RIEHLVELT.
Killua: ONE ARM'S INVISIBLE,
'CAUSE IT'S MADE OF NEN.
Gon: THAT'S RIGHT!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"POWER TO AVENGE."
POWER?
Killua: AVENGE?