Uvogin: YOU TELL THE BOSS...
I'M NOT LEAVING.
I CAN'T GO BACK
UNTIL I SETTLE THE SCORE
WITH THAT DAMN CHAIN USER!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( chorus singing
in foreign language )
Narrator: HISOKA, WHO JOINED UP
WITH THE PHANTOM TROUPE
FOR A CHANCE TO FIGHT
THEIR LEADER CHROLLO,
HAS PROPOSED
A PARTNERSHIP WITH KURAPIKA,
WHO IS SEEKING REVENGE
ON THE GROUP.
Hisoka: WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO DO?
WILL YOU WORK WITH ME,
OR WOULD YOU RATHER FIGHT ALONE?
( cell phone rings )
( ring )
‐ GO AHEAD.
‐ ( ring )
( ring )
Kurapika: YES, IT'S ME.
Melody: TERRIBLE NEWS.
THE BIG MAN WE CAPTURED
HAS ESCAPED.
Kurapika: ESCAPED?
ALL ON HIS OWN?
Melody: NO.
SOME PHANTOM TROUPE MEMBERS
DISGUISED THEMSELVES AS MAFIA
HENCHMEN AND CAME FOR HIM.
Kurapika: AND OUR LEADER?
Melody: NOT SURE. WE HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO REACH HIM.
( Kurapika gasps )
Melody: WE'RE MOVING TO PLAN B.
GET BACK HERE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
Kurapika: UNDERSTOOD.
HISOKA,
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
WHERE CAN I FIND
THE SCARLET EYES?
Hisoka: UNFORTUNATELY
THAT HAPPENED BEFORE I JOINED.
THE BOSS SELLS EVERY ITEM
AFTER REVELING IN THE SPOILS
FOR A BIT.
I ASSUME THE SCARLET EYES
WERE NO EXCEPTION,
AND THAT'S ALL I CAN TELL YOU
ON THE MATTER.
BUT KEEP THIS IN MIND,
A SPIDER WILL KEEP GOING
UNTIL YOU CRUSH ITS HEAD.
I SUGGESTED WE FORM AN ALLIANCE,
BUT NOT THAT WE
FIGHT SIDE BY SIDE,
MERELY THE GIVE AND TAKE
OF CERTAIN INFORMATION.
AND IF IT CEASES TO BENEFIT US,
THERE IS NO FURTHER OBLIGATION
TO COOPERATE.
SIMPLE ENOUGH?
♪
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
Kurapika: I'LL BE BACK HERE
AT THE SAME TIME TOMORROW.
Basho: SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
Squala: OUR LEADER'S
PROBABLY DEAD ALREADY,
AND WE STILL HAVEN'T
COMPLETED THE MISSION.
Melody: WE SHOULD REPORT THIS
TO THE BOSS, DON'T YOU THINK?
Basho: THAT LITTLE GIRL
IS OUR BOSS IN NAME ONLY.
Squala: YEAH, IT WAS
SOMEBODY ELSE WHO HIRED US.
Melody: EH?
Squala: LIGHT NOSTRADE,
HER FATHER.
OUR ORDERS
COME DIRECTLY FROM HIM.
THE LEADER
JUST RELAYED THEM TO US,
AND HE WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNEW HOW TO CONTACT HIM.
Kurapika: WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE HAVE TO REPORT THIS
TO THE BOSS.
BOSS.
( Neon sighs )
EH?
HOLD ON. WHAT TIME IS IT?
Kurapika: IT'S 2:00
IN THE MORNING.
Neon: HUH? OH, NO!
WHAT ABOUT THE AUCTION?!
Kurapika: IT'S BEEN CALLED OFF.
Neon: HUH? COMPLETELY?
WHY? WHAT FOR?
Kurapika: THERE WAS
A GANG OF THIEVES
WHO ATTACKED THE AUCTION HALL.
Neon: HUH?
Kurapika: BAISE,
IVLENKOV, AND TOCINO
LOST THEIR LIVES
IN THE INCIDENT.
Neon: HUH?!
Squala: WE CAN'T REACH
THE LEADER,
SO HE MIGHT ALSO BE...
Neon: NO WAY. BUT WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT THE MUMMY?
( both gasp )
Neon: WAS IT REALLY STOLEN?
I WANTED IT SO MUCH.
( Squala clears throat )
Kurapika: SEEMS THE MAFIA
MOVED THE MERCHANDISE
TO A SAFE LOCATION.
( Neon giggles ) THAT'S GREAT!
WHEN'S THE NEXT ONE?
THERE'S ANOTHER AUCTION SOON,
RIGHT?
Kurapika: WE DON'T KNOW YET.
Neon: YOU DON'T? BUT WHY NOT?
Kurapika:
IN ANY CASE, THE LEADER
HANDLED ALL COMMUNICATION
WITH YOUR FATHER,
SO I'M AFRAID
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
AND WE CAN'T ACT
UNTIL WE RECEIVE HIS ORDERS.
Neon: DON'T ASK ME.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
BUT HERE. JUST ASK DADDY.
I'VE GOT HIS NUMBER
SAVED HERE IN MY PHONE.
Kurapika: SQUALA,
YOU MAKE THE CALL.
Squala: EH, WHY DO I HAVE TO?
Kurapika:
YOU'RE THE MOST EXPERIENCED,
AND WE NEED A NEW LEADER,
SO IT SHOULD BE YOU
Squala: OH, NO! THAT'S
COMPLETELY OUT OF THE QUESTION.
I'M JUST NOT LEADER MATERIAL.
Melody: THEN PERHAPS WE SHOULD
PUT IT TO A VOTE TO BE FAIR.
WE NEED TO MAKE THE CALL
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE,
AND MY VOTE'S FOR KURAPIKA.
HE'S THE ONE
WHO CAPTURED THE BANDIT,
AND HE'S SHOWN
EXCELLENT JUDGMENT.
I BELIEVE HE WOULD MAKE
THE MOST EFFECTIVE LEADER.
Basho: WORKS FOR ME.
I VOTE FOR KURAPIKA, TOO.
Squala: THAT'S THAT.
SO YOU MAKE THE CALL.
Kurapika: VERY WELL.
THEN AS INTERIM LEADER,
I'LL CALL MR. NOSTRADE,
BUT ONLY UNTIL WE CAN CONFIRM
WHAT'S REALLY BECOME
OF DALZOLLENE.
FURTHER CHOICES WILL BE MADE
BY MR. NOSTRADE.
♪
I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS
TO HAPPEN SO SOON.
IT WOULD BE INAPPROPRIATE
FOR ME TO CALL,
SO WOULD YOU PLEASE PROVIDE
AN INTRODUCTION?
Neon: OKAY.
( dials )
HERE. I'M PUTTING HIM ON NOW.
Kurapika: HELLO.
Nostrade: IS IT TRUE
THAT DALZOLLENE HAS BEEN KILLED?
Kurapika: YES, SIR.
Nostrade:
THAT'S QUITE HARD TO BELIEVE.
HE IS A NEN USER.
HE'S TRAINED
TO WITHSTAND 10 GUNSHOTS
WITHOUT SUSTAINING
ANY INJURIES.
Kurapika: HE WAS
KILLED BY OUTLAWS
KNOWN AS THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
Nostrade: WAIT. THE SPIDERS?
Kurapika: I HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SEE THEM IN ACTION.
ONE OF THEM
STOPPED A BAZOOKA ROUND
WITH HIS BARE HAND.
MY NAME IS KURAPIKA,
AND I'M THE INTERIM LEADER.
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL ME HOW YOU
WOULD LIKE US TO PROCEED?
Nostrade: OF COURSE. BUT FIRST
I WANT TO HEAR WHAT YOU THINK.
Kurapika:
I BELIEVE YOUR DAUGHTER
SHOULD LEAVE YORKNEW CITY
IMMEDIATELY, SIR.
I'M NOT CONFIDENT
THAT WE CAN PROTECT HER
IN THE EVENT
OF UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES.
Nostrade: I AGREE
WITH YOUR ASSESSMENT,
BUT MY DAUGHTER
HAS A SAY AS WELL.
I WANT TO RESPECT HER WISHES
WHENEVER POSSIBLE.
Kurapika: HER SAFETY'S
MY TOP PRIORITY.
Nostrade: HMM.
UNDERSTOOD.
I'M ON MY WAY THERE RIGHT NOW,
SO I SHOULD ARRIVE
SOMETIME TOMORROW EVENING.
I PROMISE I'LL DO MY BEST
TO PERSUADE NEON.
YOU WILL BE THE NEW LEADER,
KURAPIKA.
HERE IS YOUR FIRST ORDER.
KEEP AN EYE ON NEON
UNTIL I GET THERE.
Kurapika: YES, SIR. I WILL.
YOUR FATHER WANTS YOU TO KNOW
HE'LL BE HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
Neon: REALLY? THAT'S PERFECT!
WHEN HE LANDS, I'LL GET HIM
TO TAKE ME SHOPPING!
Kurapika: UNTIL THEN,
HE MADE IT QUITE CLEAR
THAT HE'D LIKE YOU
TO STAY IN YOUR ROOM.
Neon: AWW!
I WANTED TO SEE THE CASINO.
Kurapika: YOU STAY HERE
WITH THE BOSS.
Squala: WHAT?! YEAH, I GOT IT.
Kurapika: I'LL BE DOWNSTAIRS.
( drinking )
( sighs )
Shalnark: THIS IS IT!
IT SAYS HERE
THAT A DUMMY CORPORATION
FOR THE NOSTRADE FAMILY
OWNS THAT BUILDING YOU WERE IN.
Uvogin: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN TRACK DOWN
A LIST OF ALL
THE BUILDINGS IN THIS AREA
THE NOSTRADE FAMILY OWN?
Shalnark: SURE CAN.
I CAN ALSO SEE IF ANYONE
HAS CHECKED IN TO A HOTEL
USING THE NOSTRADE NAME LATELY.
( door closes )
( footsteps thumping )
Franklin: OKAY,
I BROUGHT SOME MORE BEER.
Uvogin: HEY, THANKS A LOT!
Franklin: HERE YOU GO.
Shalnark: KNOW WHAT YOU NEED,
UVO? A HUNTER'S LICENSE.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE THE MONEY,
YOU CAN DIG UP ALL KINDS
OF INFORMATION FROM THEIR SITE.
Uvogin: UNLIKE YOU GUYS,
I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA OF MONEY.
IF I WANT SOMETHING, I TAKE IT.
Shalnark: WELL SAID.
YOU'RE AN EXEMPLARY BANDIT.
‐ HERE.
‐ Uvogin: HUH?
Shalnark: THEY OWN TWO OTHER
BUILDINGS IN YORKNEW CITY,
AND THERE ARE THREE HOTELS
WHERE MEMBERS ARE STAYING.
ALL RIGHT. THIS SEARCH
SHOULDN'T TAKE TOO LONG. THERE.
Uvogin: THANKS, BUDDY.
I OWE YOU ONE.
Shalnark: WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
( Uvogin chuckles )
WELL, I'M OFF.
Franklin: WHAT ABOUT THE BEER?
Uvogin: YOU GUYS CAN FINISH IT.
Franklin: MAKE SURE
YOU DISPOSE OF THE BODY,
AND TRY TO MAKE IT QUICK.
Uvogin: YEAH.
LATER.
Shalnark: HEY, UVO!
Uvogin: HUH?
Shalnark: DON'T GET
CARELESS OUT THERE.
Uvogin: NO PROB.
♪
FAMILY MEMBERS.
SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD PLACE TO START.
Kurapika: LOOK AT THIS.
Squala: WHAT'S THAT?
A LIST OF THE BUILDINGS
THE NOSTRADES OWN?
Melody: AND A LIST
OF FAMILY MEMBERS.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THIS WAS OUT THERE.
Kurapika: THIS WEBSITE CAN ONLY
BE ACCESSED BY PRO HUNTERS.
WITH THIS INFORMATION,
THEY CAN FIND
THE LOCATION OF THIS ROOM
WITHOUT ANY TROUBLE AT ALL.
Squala: THERE'S A WEBSITE
JUST FOR PRO HUNTERS?
Melody: THAT MEANS
IF ONE OF OUR ENEMIES
IS A PRO HUNTER, TOO...
Kurapika: WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WE NEED TO MOVE THE BOSS
TO A DIFFERENT ROOM RIGHT AWAY
Melody: WE DO?
IN THE SAME HOTEL?
Kurapika: IT'S FASTER
AND CLEANER THAT WAY.
BUT DO NOT USE ALIASES!
WE'LL HAVE MELODY OR BASHO
BOOK THE ROOM.
AND DON'T LET ANYONE LEAVE,
ESPECIALLY THE BOSS.
Squala: YOU GOT IT.
Kurapika: DON'T CHECK OUT
OF THIS ONE, EITHER.
Melody: HOLD ON. WHAT ABOUT YOU?
Kurapika: I'LL STAY HERE.
( Squala gasps )
Melody: KURAPIKA,
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF...
♪
( man groans ) I DON'T THINK
HE'S A FAMILY MEMBER.
HE'S A BODYGUARD
FOR THE BOSS'S DAUGHTER.
Uvogin: HIS DAUGHTER?
Man: YEAH. SHE'S A FREAK
WHO GETS HER KICKS
OUT OF COLLECTING BODY PARTS,
EYEBALLS, ORGANS, GUTS.
OH, AND SHE'S A FORTUNETELLER.
SHE'S REALLY ACCURATE, TOO.
Uvogin: THAT SO?
Man: YEAH! SHE'S GOT A LONG LIST
OF CLIENTS IN THE MAFIA.
SOME OF THE COMMUNITY ELDERS
PRACTICALLY WORSHIP HER.
( laughs )
( Uvogin sighs )
Man: I MEAN, IT MAKES SENSE.
OUR BOSS USED
HIS DAUGHTER'S POWER
TO MAKE HIS ENTIRE FORTUNE.
LOOK, CUT ME SOME SLACK,
ALL RIGHT?
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING I KNOW,
SO JUST LET ME‐‐
Uvogin: SOMEONE WHO CAN
SEE THE FUTURE.
SO SHE KNEW THIS ATTACK
WAS GONNA HAPPEN?
THE BOSS WAS RIGHT.
THERE WEREN'T ANY TRAITORS
AMONG US AFTER ALL.
Leorio: AS IT STANDS,
WE HAVE A DIAMOND
WORTH 3 MILLION JENNY
AND 2.4 MILLION
IN LEFTOVER CASH,
NOT TO MENTION THE 2.75
WE MADE ARM WRESTLING.
ALL TOLD, THAT'S A TOTAL
OF AROUND 8 MILLION.
WE NEED AT LEAST 9 BILLION.
THAT'S THE MINIMUM OPENING BID
FOR "GREED ISLAND,"
SO IF WE DON'T HAVE THAT,
THERE'S REALLY NO POINT.
I DON'T SEE
HOW WE'RE GONNA GET THERE,
NOT THROUGH
LEGITIMATE CHANNELS, ANYWAY.
Gon: YEAH, I WOULDN'T CALL
THAT KIND OF ARM WRESTLING
LEGITIMATE.
Killua: ALL OF THE CHALLENGERS
TOWARD THE END
WERE A BUNCH OF DESPERATE LOSERS
LOOKING FOR REVENGE.
Leorio: AND THAT'S OKAY.
SEE, THAT WAS MY GOAL
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
( both gasp )
Leorio: THE MORE EXAGGERATED
THE RUMORS, THE BETTER.
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
Leorio: THE ARM WRESTLING
WAS JUST BAIT.
Gon: IT WAS?
Leorio: THAT IS
WHAT'S GONNA DRAW
ALL THE MOLES OUT OF HIDING!
Gon: WAIT. MOLES?
I DON'T THINK I GET IT.
WHY DO WE WANT MOLES?
Leorio: OKAY, TAKE IT EASY.
JUST LET ME EXPLAIN.
( both sigh )
Leorio: STEP RIGHT UP!
CONDITIONAL AUCTION!
WE'VE GOT A DIAMOND SITTING HERE
THAT'S WORTH 3 MILLION JENNY!
ARM WRESTLING
DECIDES THE WINNER!
THE FIRST PERSON TO BEAT
THIS BOY WINS THE DIAMOND!
THE ENTRY FEE'S 10,000 JENNY!
Man: WHAT? HE'S JUST A KID.
I JUST MIGHT TRY IT.
‐ Man #2: DON'T BOTHER.
‐ Man #1: EH?
Man #2: THAT KID
BEAT 500 PEOPLE YESTERDAY,
NO PROBLEM.
Man #1: REALLY?
Man #2: YEAH, REALLY,
AND MORE THAN 20 OF 'EM
GOT THEIR ARMS BROKEN.
Man #1: SERIOUSLY?
( crowd murmuring )
( Leorio chuckles )
THE RUMORS
ARE STARTING TO SPREAD NICELY.
WELL, IN THAT CASE...
Man #3: OUT OF MY WAY.
Leorio: OH! DO WE HAVE
OUR FIRST CHALLENGER?
‐ Man #4: NOT QUITE.
‐ Leorio: EH?
Man #4: I ALREADY KNOW MY MAN
CAN'T BEAT YOUR KID.
I WAS WATCHING YESTERDAY.
Leorio THEN WHAT DO YOU WANT?
Man #4: YOU INTERESTED
IN MAKING SOME REAL MONEY?
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Man #4: I KNOW WHERE YOU
CAN MAKE SOME SERIOUS CASH,
NOT THE MEASLY POCKET CHANGE
YOU'RE PULLING HERE.
YOU CAN MAKE HUNDREDS‐‐
NO, THOUSANDS OF TIMES MORE,
EASY.
( Leorio chuckles )
♪
Gon: SO ARE THESE THE TWO MOLES?
Leorio: YEAH. IT LOOKS LIKE
WE JUST LANDED A BIG FISH.
Gon: FISH? SO THEY'RE NOT MOLES?
Leorio: WILL YOU
PLEASE STOP TALKING?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
Man #4: HERE WE ARE.
( elevator whirring )
( elevator chimes )
( crowd cheering )
( men grunting )
♪
( crowd cheering )
Killua: OH, WOW.
I CAN FEEL THE BLOODLUST.
Man #4: THIS COMPETITION
ACCEPTS ALL COMERS,
AND IT REALLY PAYS OUT.
THE SPECTATORS
BET ON EACH MATCH,
AND THE WINNER GETS 10%
OF ALL BETS PLACED.
WE'RE TALKING BILLIONS
WAGERED ON EACH MATCH.
Leorio: BUT THAT MEANS
EVERY SINGLE WIN
COULD MAKE YOU MILLIONS.
Man #4: MORE IF YOU
PLAY YOUR CARDS RIGHT.
I GET A COMMISSION,
BUT IT'S ONLY 50%
OF WHATEVER YOU EARN.
Leorio: 50?
ISN'T THAT A BIT STEEP?
Man #4: IF I DON'T
ENTER YOUR NAME,
YOU CAN'T PARTICIPATE.
BESIDES, YOU CAN BET
YOUR OWN MONEY.
THAT KID'LL GET GREAT ODDS,
SO YOU CAN MAKE IT BACK
A HUNDRED TIMES OVER.
Leorio: OKAY, I'M SOLD!
WE'RE IN.
‐ GON, DO IT.
‐ Gon: EH?
Referee: WELL, DO WE HAVE
ANY OTHER CHALLENGERS?
Man #4: RIGHT OVER HERE!
THIS KID THINKS
HE'S GOT WHAT IT TAKES.
Referee: EH...
ALL RIGHT!
HUH?
( crowd murmurs )
Man #5:
SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU, FOLKS,
BUT THE ARM WRESTLING
HAS OFFICIALLY BEEN CANCELED.
INSTEAD, WE'RE GOING TO DO
A BIT OF CONDITIONAL AUCTIONING.
( crowd protesting )
Leorio: WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY'S IT CANCELED?
Man #4: I, UH‐‐
I DON'T ACTUALLY KNOW.
Man #5: AND ALL
YOU HAVE TO DO TO WIN
IS PLAY A GAME
OF HIDE‐AND‐SEEK!
‐ ( crowd gasping )
‐ Leorio: HIDE‐AND‐SEEK? REALLY?
Man #5: WE'LL START
BY PASSING OUT FLIERS!
Leorio: HMM.
Man #5: NOW TAKE A GOOD LOOK
AT THOSE PICTURES, FOLKS!
( Gon gasps )
Man #5: DON'T FORGET 'EM,
BECAUSE THE SEVEN GUYS AND GALS
YOU SEE ARE YOUR TARGETS!
Leorio: HEY, I'VE SEEN
THAT GIRL WITH THE GLASSES.
Gon: ME, TOO.
SHE ARM‐WRESTLED ME.
Man #6: WAIT.
YOU THINK THEY'RE THE ONES
RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT?
Man #7: YEAH. YOU MEAN
THE ATTACK
ON THE AUCTION, RIGHT?
( Killua gasps )
Man #5: IN ORDER TO WIN THE BID,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CAPTURE A TARGET
AND DELIVER THEM TO US.
FOR EACH, YOU'LL WALK AWAY
WITH THE TIDY SUM OF‐‐
WAIT FOR IT‐‐
TWO BILLION JENNY!
( crowd gasping )
Man #5: THERE IS NO TIME LIMIT,
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF THEY'RE DEAD OR ALIVE.
INTERESTED?
THEN CATCH ONE, AND CALL US!
Gon: TWO BILLION EACH IS A LOT.
Leorio: AND IF WE CATCH
ALL SEVEN, THAT'S 14 BILLION!
Man #5: ALL IT COSTS
TO PARTICIPATE
IS A MERE 5 MILLION JENNY!
Leorio:
WE'RE PARTICIPATING, RIGHT?
Gon: SURE.
( overlapping chatter )
♪
Man #8: CLEAR THE WAY!
Man #9: THAT'S RIGHT.
I'LL FAX YOU THE INFORMATION.
Man #10: CHECK THE WEBSITE.
WE'LL PAY FOR ANYTHING CONCRETE.
Leorio: WE'RE GONNA
NEED TO HURRY.
Killua: NO RUSH. THEY WON'T BE
ABLE TO CATCH OUR TARGETS.
( both gasp )
Killua: EVEN THE MAFIA'S
HAVING A HARD TIME WITH THEM.
Leorio: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Killua:
THE "CONDITIONAL AUCTION"
THEY'RE HAVING, IT'S NOTHING
MORE THAN A BIG BOUNTY HUNT.
IT'S LIKE THE MAFIA'S ADMITTING
THEY CAN'T CATCH THESE TARGETS,
OR NOT ALONE, ANYWAY.
Leorio: YOU'VE GOT
A POINT THERE.
THEY WERE WILLING
TO PUT EVERYTHING ELSE ON HOLD
JUST SO THEY
COULD TRACK THEM DOWN.
Killua: I HEARD LAST NIGHT,
SOMEONE ATTACKED
THE UNDERGROUND AUCTION.
Leorio: BUT WHO WOULD DO THAT?
UNLESS, MAYBE IT WAS THEM.
YOU THINK THAT'S THE REASON
THEY'VE GOT A BOUNTY
ON THEIR HEADS?
Killua: YEP, AND IF THEY
STOLE FROM THE MAFIA,
THEY'VE GOT A SCREW LOOSE.
BUT THINK. WHO DO WE KNOW
THAT'S CRAZY ENOUGH TO DO THAT?
Leorio: THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
( somber chorus vocalizing )
Gon: NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
WHAT'S KURAPIKA BEEN UP TO?
Killua: DON'T KNOW. HE SHOULD
BE HERE IN THE CITY BY NOW,
BUT HE HASN'T CALLED YET.
Gon: THEN I'LL CALL HIM.
( cell phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
HE'S NOT ANSWERING.
Leorio: MAYBE HE'S WORKING.
‐ Killua: WORKING?
‐ Leorio: YEAH.
I HEARD HE PICKED UP A JOB
AS A BODYGUARD A WHILE BACK.
I BET IT'S SOME BIG‐SHOT V. I. P.
HE'S LOOKING
FOR THE SCARLET EYES,
SO PROBABLY
SOMEONE IN THE UNDERWORLD.
Gon: WHAT IF HE WAS GUARDING
THEM AT THE AUCTION HALL
AND THEN GOT CAUGHT UP
IN THE ATTACK?
Leorio: HE WOULDN'T HAVE
LET SOMETHING LIKE THAT HAPPEN.
IF THE TROUPE ATTACKED,
KURAPIKA WOULD BE TRACKING
THEM DOWN EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF HE'S CAPTURED
A FEW OF 'EM ALREADY.
Gon: I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
( cell phone ringing )
( ringing stops )
Uvogin: YOU'RE BY YOURSELF?
THAT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
I'LL LET YOU
DECIDE THE LOCATION.
Kurapika: I'D PREFER
SOMEWHERE REMOTE
SO WE WON'T BE A NUISANCE.
I DON'T WANT YOUR SCREAMS
TO BOTHER ANYONE.
( Uvogin gasps )
♪
Narrator: UVOGIN HAS COME
TO GET REVENGE FOR HIS CAPTURE
AND RESTORE HIS WOUNDED PRIDE,
AND KURAPIKA
HAS LONG AWAITED THE CHANCE
TO EXACT REVENGE
UPON THE PHANTOM TROUPE.
THEIR BATTLE IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE INTRODUCING
SQUALA, ONE OF NEON'S GUARDS.
Killua: A MANIPULATOR WHO
CONTROLS DOGS USING HIS NEN.
Gon: AND HE'S ACTUALLY DATING
NEON'S MAID, MISS ELIZA.
‐ Killua: MEOW, MEOW!
‐ Gon: WOOF, WOOF!
♪
NEXT TIME,
"CONDITION AND CONDITION."
EXPLAIN THE DIFFERENCE
USING 30 WORDS OR LESS.
Killua: A CONDITION'S A RULE,
AND A CONDITION'S
A CONTRACT WITH YOURSELF.