( chorus vocalizing )
Narrator: NEN ABILITIES
FALL INTO THE FOLLOWING
SIX DISTINCT CATEGORIES.
ENHANCERS ARE ABLE
TO STRENGTHEN AND REINFORCE
THE NATURAL PROPERTIES
OF ANY OBJECT THEY ENCOUNTER.
TRANSMUTERS CAN MANIPULATE
AND CHANGE
THE QUALITY OF AURA AT WILL.
SIMILAR TO TRANSMUTERS,
CONJURERS HAVE THE ABILITY
TO MATERIALIZE AN OBJECT
OUT OF AURA.
EMITTERS CAN PROPEL THEIR AURA,
SHOOTING OR
PROJECTING IT FORWARD.
MANIPULATORS CAN USE THEIR AURA
TO CONTROL OBJECTS
OR LIVING THINGS.
SPECIALISTS POSSESS
RARE ABILITIES
WHICH DO NOT FIT WITHIN
THE OTHER FIVE CATEGORIES.
ONE MUST DETERMINE WHICH
CATEGORY THEIR AURA FALLS INTO.
THIS IS THE FIRST STEP
TO BECOMING A SKILLED NEN USER.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Employer: THE AUCTION,
AS YOU ALL KNOW
WILL BEGIN IN ONE MONTH.
BEFORE THAT TIME, FIND ONE ITEM
FROM THE LIST PROVIDED,
AND THEN BRING IT
SAFELY BACK HERE.
( Kurapika gasps )
Employer: IF YOU'RE SUCCESSFUL,
YOU'LL BE HIRED
AND BEGIN YOUR TRAINING
IN SECURITY AND ACQUISITIONS.
Kurapika: IN ALL LIKELIHOOD,
THE MAN WE SAW
WAS NOT THE ACTUAL CLIENT,
THUS ILLUSTRATING THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN THE CLIENT AND MYSELF.
IT'S CRITICAL THAT I GET
AS CLOSE TO THEM AS POSSIBLE
UNTIL THEY EVENTUALLY
LET THEIR GUARD DOWN
AND SHARE THEIR SECRETS.
I WILL PASS THIS TEST.
FIRST I MUST INGRATIATE MYSELF
AND WIN THEIR TRUST.
♪
Poet: HEY, IT WON'T OPEN.
‐ Kurapika: HUH?
‐ ( screen whirs )
Employer: I FORGOT
TO MENTION ONE THING.
THE MINIMUM REQUIREMENT
FOR THE POSITION IS STRENGTH,
ENOUGH STRENGTH
TO GET OUT OF THIS MANSION...
WITH YOUR LIVES.
♪
( butler yells )
( bullets ping )
( all gasp )
Poet: HE USED A CHAIN TO STOP
THE BULLETS. IMPRESSIVE.
Kurapika: THREE WITH GUNS.
SIX WITH SWORDS.
( gasps )
TWO MORE WITH SWORDS ABOVE.
Poet: GOOD JOB CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE, GUYS,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
YOU'RE TOO WEAK.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DON'T EVEN NEED
TO USE MY NEN!
( gasps )
SO THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
I GET IT NOW.
Kurapika: IT'S HIM.
♪
( all gasping )
Kurapika:
CALL THEM OFF RIGHT NOW.
I'LL COUNT TO THREE.
1, 2...
Man: OKAY, OKAY.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
‐ ( Hunter gasps )
‐ Woman: WAIT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Poet: THEY WERE MADE OF NEN.
I KNEW AS SOON
AS I PUNCHED ONE OF 'EM.
THEY'RE JUST MASSES OF AURA
SHAPED LIKE MEN. THEY'RE WEAK.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
IT WAS HIS NEN.
Man: IMPRESSIVE,
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
Kurapika: YOU WERE CAREFUL
TO STAND NEXT TO THE OTHERS
FOR CAMOUFLAGE,
BUT WHEN I WATCHED YOU
FROM ABOVE, IT WAS CLEAR.
EVERY ONE OF US
WAS UNDER ATTACK EXCEPT YOU.
Poet: OH?
Kurapika: I REALIZED
SOMETHING WAS WRONG
WHEN TWO OF THEM APPEARED
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
AFTER I JUMPED
OVER TO THE CHANDELIER
AND OUT OF THEIR REACH,
THEY JUST STOOD THERE,
CONTINUING TO SWING THEIR SWORDS
IN A FUTILE ATTEMPT
TO REACH ME.
I HAVE TO ASSUME
THEY RECEIVED A BASIC ORDER
TO ATTACK
WHICHEVER ENEMY WAS NEAREST.
THE INSTRUCTIONS
THE ASSAILANTS HAD WERE SIMPLE,
SO THEIR ATTACKS WERE AS WELL.
HOWEVER, IT WOULD TAKE
AN INCREDIBLY SKILLED NEN USER
TO CONTROL 11 HUMAN‐SIZED
AURA SIMULTANEOUSLY.
AND IT STANDS TO REASON
THAT THIS NEN USER
WOULD MOST LIKELY BE AN EMITTER.
AND GIVEN THE SIZE
OF THE AURA INVOLVED,
HE WOULD HAVE TO BE WITHIN
A FEW METERS OF THE ASSAILANTS,
WHICH MEANT THAT THE NEN USER...
WAS SOMEONE
INSIDE THIS VERY ROOM.
( poet whistles )
Man: WELL, YEAH, YOU NAILED IT.
MY NAME IS SHACHMONO TOCINO.
AS YOU MIGHT HAVE GUESSED,
I'M A HUNTER.
OF COURSE,
I'M ALSO AN EMPLOYEE HERE,
WHICH MEANS
I'M BASICALLY YOUR SENIOR.
NOW THAT'S CLEARED UP, THINK YOU
COULD PUT AWAY YOUR KNIFE?
( chandelier jingling )
( sighs )
BASED ON THE CHAINS, I THINK
IT'S FAIRLY SAFE TO ASSUME
THAT YOU'RE A MANIPULATOR,
AREN'T YOU?
WELL, I SURE HOPE
YOU WON'T HOLD A GRUDGE.
SEE, I WAS ONLY FOLLOWING
THE ORDERS THE BOSS GAVE ME.
"TEST THE APPLICANTS
BY ATTEMPTING TO KILL THEM."
BUT I HONESTLY NEVER EXPECTED
TO BE EXPOSED SO QUICKLY.
WELL, I'M WILLING TO BET
THAT THE FOUR OF YOU TOGETHER
SHOULD BE ABLE
TO ESCAPE THE MANSION,
SO BEST OF LUCK.
Hunter: "FOUR OF YOU"?
Poet: THAT MAKES IT SOUND
LIKE THERE'S ANOTHER ONE
IN THE ROOM.
( Tocino chuckles )
Kurapika: I IMAGINE
THAT WAS MEANT TO BE
SOME SORT OF DIVERSION,
BUT IT WAS THE WRONG CALL.
Tocino: HUH?
Kurapika: BEFORE WE
ALL SUCCUMB TO PARANOIA,
I SHALL DETERMINE IF THERE ARE
ANY OTHER INFILTRATORS AMONG US.
♪
( woman grunts )
( man grunts )
( all gasping )
( Hunter sighs )
Kurapika: THERE YOU ARE.
YOU ARE THE INFILTRATOR.
( chain jingles )
Man: THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
WHAT GROUNDS
ARE YOU BASING THAT ON?
JUST 'CAUSE YOUR CHAIN
STARTED SWINGING?
Hunter: IT'S CALLED DOWSING.
Man: HUH? AND WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
Hunter: DOWSING WAS ORIGINALLY
A TECHNIQUE FOR LOCATING WATER
OR METALS
HIDDEN BENEATH THE GROUND,
BUT IT WAS ALSO USED
IN DIVINATION.
I'VE EVEN HEARD
OF THE TECHNIQUE
BEING EMPLOYED
AS A KIND OF LIE DETECTOR.
Man: OKAY, MAYBE SO, BUT THAT
STILL ISN'T CONCRETE PROOF
THAT I'M THE INFILTRATOR!
IT DOESN'T PROVE ANYTHING!
Hunter: WELL, IN ANY CASE,
HE'S PROBABLY RIGHT.
YOUR HEART,
I NOTICED IT BEGAN TO POUND
AS SOON AS HE POINTED
HIS FINGER AT YOU.
( man gasps )
Hunter: OF COURSE,
IF YOU WERE INNOCENT...
YOUR HEART RATE WOULD HAVE
INCREASED MUCH MORE GRADUALLY
DUE TO THE STRESS
OF BEING WRONGLY ACCUSED,
BUT YOUR HEARTBEAT
SPED UP ALMOST IMMEDIATELY
BEFORE GRADUALLY
SLOWING BACK DOWN AGAIN.
( chuckles )
THE TYPICAL MELODY OF A LIAR,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
( man gasps )
Hunter: THAT'S TRUE
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
( knuckles cracking )
Poet: WELL, I'M CONVINCED.
BOTH OF THEM
ARE SAYING IT'S YOU.
THAT'S TWO ACCUSATIONS
OUT OF FIVE.
Man: HOLD ON! WAIT A SECOND!
THAT DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MAKE IT TRUE!
MAYBE THREE OUT OF FIVE OF US
ARE THE APPLICANTS
AND THOSE TWO
ARE THE INFILTRATORS!
Kurapika: NOT SO.
HE IS NOT
ONE OF THE INFILTRATORS.
Hunter: EXCUSE ME, BUT...
I THINK YOU MEAN "SHE,"
NOT "HE." HEH.
I CAN VOUCH FOR YOU, TOO.
Man: MY POINT IS THAT NONE OF US
CAN REALLY TRUST EITHER OF YOU!
HOW DO WE KNOW YOU'RE
NOT WORKING TOGETHER, HUH?
Woman: HMPH.
( Hunter sighs )
( man gasps )
ANYWAY, ALL WE'RE
DOING IS WASTING TIME.
WE CAN STAND AROUND HERE
ALL YOU LIKE,
BUT IT ISN'T
GONNA GET US ANYWHERE.
Poet: HMPH.
THAT'S IT, THEN.
I'LL HAVE TO SETTLE THIS MYSELF.
♪
"MY HAND MAKES A PUNCH,
AND WHATEVER I HIT
WILL BURST IN FLAMES A BUNCH."
( all gasp )
THIS IS MY POWER,
THE WANDERING HAIKU POET!
WELL, DAMN IT.
IT DIDN'T BURN WELL.
GUESS IT WAS A DUD.
‐ Tocino: HUH?
‐ ( man stammers )
Poet: THAT WAS A HAIKU,
IF YOU COULDN'T TELL,
PRIZED LITERARY ART
OF MY HOMELAND.
WHATEVER I COMPOSE BECOMES REAL.
( man gasps )
Poet: SO THERE'S
YOUR EXPLANATION.
BACK TO THE SUBJECT AT HAND.
♪
"IF YOU'RE A LIAR,
"YOUR PAINFUL DEATH
WILL BE SWIFT
IN TRIAL BY FIRE."
IN OTHER WORDS,
ANYONE WHO LIES TO ME
WILL BURN IN HELL.
( man swallows )
Poet: MY QUESTION IS...
ARE YOU AN INFILTRATOR?
Kurapika: NO, I'M NOT.
Poet: WHAT ABOUT YOU?
Hunter: I AM NOT.
Poet: AND AS FOR YOU?
Woman: ME NEITHER.
Poet: AND ARE YOU
AN INFILTRATOR?
Tocino: YEAH, I SURE AM.
Poet: I'LL ADVISE YOU TO THINK
CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU ANSWER.
ARE YOU ONE OF THE INFILTRATORS?
WELL? I'M WAITING FOR AN ANSWER.
♪
( man sighs )
MY ANSWER'S YES, I AM.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
I'LL REWARD YOU
WITH SOME INFORMATION.
MY NAME IS SQUALA,
AND WHILE I MAY NOT HAVE
AN OFFICIAL LICENSE,
I'M A HUNTER WHOSE SKILLS FALL
INTO THE MANIPULATOR CLASS.
HEH.
I'VE USED THOSE ABILITIES
TO INSTRUCT SOMETHING
TO FOLLOW A CERTAIN ORDER.
IT'S TRUE YOU MANAGED
TO UNMASK ME,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO ESCAPE
THIS MANSION ALIVE.
Woman: WHAT'S THE SOMETHING,
AND WHAT WAS THE ORDER?
( Squala scoffs )
THAT WOULDN'T BE MUCH OF A TEST
IF I JUST TOLD YOU,
NOW, WOULD IT?! IMBECILE.
( scoffs ) I'M NOT GONNA TALK
EVEN IF YOU TORTURE ME.
HUH?
Girl: WOW!
Woman: THIS IS MY NEN ABILITY...
INSTANT LOVER.
I AM ALSO A MANIPULATOR.
I CAN KISS ABSOLUTELY ANYONE
AND MAKE THEM MY SLAVE.
( Squala laughing )
M‐M‐MISTRESS!
( laughing )
Woman: TAKE THAT AND THAT
AND THAT AND THAT AND THAT!
( Squala wails ) MORE!
OH, PLEASE! STEP ON ME MORE!
Woman: NOW ANSWER MY QUESTION
WHAT DID YOU USE YOUR NEN ON,
AND WHAT WAS YOUR COMMAND?
SAY IT. COME ON.
IF YOU DON'T ANSWER ME,
I'LL STOP!
( Squala yelps ) DON'T STOP!
I'LL TALK. YES,
I'M JUST A LOWLY DOG TRAINER.
Kurapika: SUCH A...
Poet: FEARSOME POWER.
( Hunter gasps )
Squala: I'LL TELL YOU
EVERYTHING!
I USED MY NEN ON THE DOGS
THAT RUN AROUND THIS MANSION.
FOR EXAMPLE,
THE MALTESE WERE TOLD
TO NIP AT A TARGET'S FEET
TO TRY AND SLOW THEM DOWN.
THAT'S WHEN
THE SAINT BERNARD COMES IN.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO USE
ITS LARGE BODY TO SMOTHER THEM!
AND AT THE EXACT SAME TIME,
THE DOBERMANS WILL RUSH IN
AND FINISH OFF
THE TARGET FOR GOOD!
IF THE TARGET STILL ESCAPES,
THE BULLDOGS WILL‐‐
‐ AAH!
‐ Woman: THAT'S ENOUGH!
RELEASE THE NEN
YOU USED ON THE DOGS!
Squala: RIGHT AWAY!
♪
( dogs growling )
Poet: SO THE DOG TRAINER
HAS BEEN REDUCED DOWN
TO A LOYAL PET, HUH?
Woman: AH, DON'T SAY THAT.
THE ONLY REASON I DID IT
WAS TO MAKE HIM TALK.
IF I WANTED A MAN AS A PET,
I COULD DO
A WHOLE LOT BETTER THAN HIM.
Poet: THAT REMINDS ME,
I DON'T THINK
I EVER CAUGHT YOUR NAME.
MINE IS BASHO,
AND AS YOU SAW
JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO,
I'M A CONJURER.
Woman: MY NAME IS BAISE.
Hunter: I'M MELODY.
Basho: IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU CAN HEAR HEARTBEATS.
WHAT CATEGORY IS THAT?
Melody: OH, YOU'LL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH, I'M SURE.
Basho: AH, I SEE.
PLAYING COY THEN, ARE WE?
( Melody chuckles )
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
HEH. I'D LIKE TO KNOW
YOUR NAME, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL US?
Kurapika: I WILL NOT.
WE DON'T KNOW YET
IF WE WILL BE WORKING TOGETHER.
Melody: HMM.
Basho: YES, HE HAS A POINT.
WE CLEARED THE FIRST STAGE
BY ESCAPING THE MANSION,
BUT THE REAL TEST
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN.
Baise: YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE NEED TO LOCATE
ONE OF THE DESIGNATED ITEMS
FROM THE LIST WE RECEIVED,
OR WE CAN'T GET THE JOB.
Basho: IF WE'RE ALL
AFTER THE SAME GIG,
WE'RE BOUND
TO RUN INTO EACH OTHER AGAIN.
Employer: WHAT'S YOUR OPINION
OF THIS GROUP?
Tocino: THIS ONE
IN PARTICULAR LOOKS PROMISING,
AT LEAST, MORE THAN HIM.
Employer: HEH.
IT WILL BE A WHILE
BEFORE I REQUIRE HIM,
SO JUST PUT HIM AWAY
FOR THE TIME BEING.
I TRUST YOU CAN HANDLE THAT,
SQUALA.
Squala: Y‐YES, SIR.
♪
Kurapika: IF I FIND
ONE OF THE OBJECTS
AND EARN THE CONTRACT,
I WILL HAVE PASSAGE
TO THE YORKNEW CITY AUCTION.
YES, I WILL ATTEND.
AFTER ALL, THE PHANTOM TROUPE
WILL UNDOUBTEDLY BE
IN ATTENDANCE AS WELL,
THE BAND OF THIEVES THAT
SLAUGHTERED MY FELLOW KURTA.
( chorus vocalizing )
WHEN WE'RE OVERCOME
WITH EMOTION,
OUR EYES BURN A DEEP SCARLET.
THEY WERE WILLING TO KILL
IN ORDER TO OBTAIN THOSE EYES,
CONSIDERED ONE OF THE WORLD'S
SEVEN MOST BEAUTIFUL COLORS.
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE THAT ACT.
I WILL TRACK THEM DOWN,
AND I WILL DESTROY THEM.
♪
( vocalizing ends )
( bird shrieks )
( typing )
Milluki: HMM,
SO THIS IS "GREED ISLAND."
♪
IT'S STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE THE MEMORY CARD KIL FOUND
MIGHT ACTUALLY BE
THE REAL DEAL.
Killua: I FIGURED
THAT YOU COULD ANALYZE THE DATA
AND REVERSE‐ENGINEER
THE GAME ITSELF, COULDN'T YOU?
Milluki: YOU BET I CAN.
I'LL STRIP DOWN THE CODE
AND CLEAR THE ENTIRE GAME.
I'LL PUT AN END TO THE LEGEND
AND WIN 50 BILLION JENNY
IN THE PROCESS.
OH, RIGHT. THIS WAS A TRADE.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO TELL KIL THE U. R. L.
FOR THE HUNTER‐ONLY WEBSITE.
( typing )
IF I DON'T HOLD UP
MY END OF THE BARGAIN,
THAT LITTLE BRAT
MIGHT START TALKING
ABOUT BREAKING
MY PRECIOUS FIGURES AGAIN.
( waves crashing )
Gon: THAT'S IT
RIGHT OVER THERE, KILLUA!
Killua: YEAH.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, YORKNEW.
Gon: CAN YOU BELIEVE
WE'RE GONNA GET TO SEE
KURAPIKA AND LEORIO AGAIN?
I CAN HARDLY WAIT!
Killua: YOU'RE KINDA
JUMPING THE GUN.
WE'VE STILL GOT TWO WEEKS BEFORE
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO MEET UP.
Gon: OH, RIGHT.
IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS
SINCE WE SAW THEM LAST,
AND I'M GETTING EXCITED!
Killua: HEH.
AND SIX MONTHS AGO,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE DREAMED
WE'D COME TO YORKNEW CITY,
NOT FOR THIS, ANYWAY.
Leorio: 'TIL NEXT TIME.
Kurapika: YES. THAT WILL BE...
All: SEPTEMBER FIRST
IN YORKNEW CITY!
Killua: THE AUCTION STARTS
ON SEPTEMBER FIRST,
SO WE NEED TO GATHER
AS MUCH INFO ON "GREED ISLAND"
AS POSSIBLE BEFORE THEN.
Gon: MM, AND IF WE'RE LUCKY,
WE MIGHT EVEN FIND OUT SOME MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT GING.
Killua: WELL, HE DID
LEAVE YOU A MEMORY CARD
ALONG WITH
THAT RECORDED MESSAGE.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A CONNECTION.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
ONCE MY BROTHER
SENDS THAT U. R. L. TO US,
WE CAN CHECK IT OUT, RIGHT?
Gon: MM‐HMM.
♪
( bird shrieks )
( Killua gasps )
THIS IS IT, GON.
MY BROTHER SENT THE U. R. L.
Gon: WOW, THAT'S AWESOME!
LET'S GET STARTED!
Killua: YEAH.
♪
Narrator: DRIVEN BY
THEIR VARIOUS GOALS,
GON AND KILLUA PREPARE
FOR SEPTEMBER FIRST.
WITH THE YORKNEW CITY AUCTION
MERE WEEKS AWAY,
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT
THEY'LL DISCOVER WHEN IT BEGINS.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
‐ Gon: I'M GON.
‐ Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE INTRODUCING
MELODY. SHE'S A MUSIC HUNTER.
Killua: SHE READS YOUR
STATE OF MIND BY YOUR HEARTBEAT.
Gon: SO HER SENSES
MUST BE AMAZING.
HEY, KILLUA,
YOU ATE MY CHOCOLATE?
‐ Killua: NAH.
‐ Gon: NOT CONVINCED.
♪
NEXT TIME,
"GATHERING OF HEROES."
KILLUA, DID YOU KNOW
I CAN TELL FORTUNES?
Killua: REALLY?
Gon: EVERYBODY WHO WATCHED
"HUNTER HUNTER" TODAY
IS REALLY HAPPY.