( Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
roars )
Narrator:
STRANGE BEASTS AND MONSTERS,
VAST RICHES,
HIDDEN TREASURES...
EVIL HAUNTS,
UNCHARTED FRONTIERS,
THE MYSTERIOUS UNKNOWN,
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE CAPTIVATED
BY THE MAGIC IN THOSE WORDS...
ARE CALLED...
HUNTERS!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Hisoka chuckles )
I'VE DECIDED
TO LET YOU LIVE FOR NOW,
UNTIL SOMEDAY YOU BECOME
TRULY WORTHY OF KILLING.
♪
I WILL TAKE IT BACK,
BUT ONLY WHEN YOU CAN PUNCH ME
IN THE FACE LIKE THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU JUST HOLD ON TO IT FOR ME.
( birds squawking )
Narrator: GON WAS
UTTERLY HUMILIATED
AFTER HISOKA RETURNED THE BADGES
THAT GERETTA HAD TAKEN.
AS FOR KILLUA...
Killua:
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
FOLLOW ME ALL YOU WANT,
BUT I'LL NEVER GIVE YOU
A CHANCE TO ATTACK.
( Imori chuckles )
♪
BE AFRAID, KID.
BE VERY AFRAID.
I'M A VERY CAUTIOUS GUY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES,
EVEN WHEN I'M UP AGAINST A KID.
ONCE HE'S EXHAUSTED
AND HE HAS TO GO TO SLEEP,
I'LL STRIKE.
( laughs )
LIKE I SAID,
I'M A CAUTIOUS GUY.
( Killua sighs )
COME OUT, OR I'LL COME TO YOU!
( Imori gasps )
THIS REALLY IS A PAIN,
YOU KNOW?
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE
ONLY WORTH ONE LOUSY POINT.
Imori: HE WANTS TO FIGHT?
HE'S JUST A KID.
I CAN'T LOSE, RIGHT?
BUT...
WHY'S HE SO RELAXED?
HE CAN'T BE THAT STRONG, CAN HE?
RIGHT. BE CAUTIOUS,
'CAUSE I'M A CAUTIOUS GUY.
OH, I SHOULD ESCAPE.
I MEAN RETREAT AND REASSESS.
BUT...
IF I DO, MY BROTHERS
MIGHT YELL AT ME!
WAIT. WHAT AM I SAYING?
IF I GO BACK WITHOUT HIS BADGE,
THEY'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA YELL AT ME!
( aloud )
BIG BROTHER!
( Killua gasps )
Amori: WE RAN INTO
A LITTLE TROUBLE.
Umori: YOU MUST BE DONE
BY NOW, RIGHT?
‐ Amori: HUH?
‐ Umori: HUH?
( Imori sputters )
Amori: WHAT ARE YOU, AN IDIOT?!
Umori: YOU CAN'T EVEN BEAT
A LITTLE KID?! GIMME A BREAK!
Imori: HOLD ON. YOU GOT IT
ALL WRONG, BIG BROTHER!
Amori: AND WHAT PART
DO I HAVE WRONG?
Imori: I‐‐I DIDN'T WANNA HURT
A LITTLE KID. THAT'S ALL.
I THOUGHT I'D JUST HOLD OFF
AND TAKE IT WHILE HE SLEPT.
Umori: YOU'RE SO FULL OF IT!
Imori: FINE! YOU GOT ME!
AND YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS I SHOULD WRAP THIS UP.
TIME FOR A BEAT‐DOWN.
♪
AT LEAST IF I START TO LOSE,
I'VE GOT MY BROTHERS HERE
TO STEP IN AND BACK ME UP.
ALL RIGHT, KID,
HOW ABOUT YOU HAND IT OVER?
DO AS I SAY,
AND YOU WON'T GET HURT.
Killua: IDIOT.
( Imori grunts )
DON'T GO SAYIN'
I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
( laughs )
BAM! RIGHT IN THE GUT!
Umori: MUST HURT LIKE HELL.
( Imori gasps )
Amori: WHAT THE HELL, BRO?
YOU GO EASY ON THE SQUIRT?
Umori: YEAH,
YOU'RE WAY TOO NICE, IMORI.
Imori: OH. UH, RIGHT.
Killua: YOU'RE NUMBER 198, HUH?
( Imori gasps )
NO WAY!
Killua: SINCE IT'S
ONLY A NUMBER OFF
FROM THE ONE
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR,
I'M BETTING THAT 199
MUST BE ONE OF YOU TWO.
AM I RIGHT?
♪
( brothers gasp )
Amori: HEY, UMORI.
Umori: YEAH.
Amori: GET INTO FORMATION.
LET'S DO THIS.
I'M PRETTY SURE
HE AIN'T NO ORDINARY KID.
Hanzo: HMM.
Amori: I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
HOW STRONG HE IS.
HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST OUR GROUP ATTACK.
NOBODY DOES.
Umori: THE THREE OF US
HAVE BEATEN
A LOT TOUGHER OPPONENTS
THAN HIM WITH THIS FORMATION.
Imori: JUST YOU WAIT, YOU BRAT.
WE'RE GONNA TEAR YOU TO SHREDS.
♪
Amori: UP THERE!
Killua: DON'T MOVE, OKAY?
MY FINGERS HERE
CUT A LOT BETTER THAN ANY KNIFE.
( Amori shuddering )
Killua: AH, MAN!
YOU'RE NUMBER 197.
DAMN. I REALLY AM BAD
AT GUESSING THESE THINGS.
HEY! ARE YOU 199?
Umori: YEAH.
Killua: GIVE IT.
( Umori growls )
THANK YOU.
NOW THEN,
FOR THE ONES I DON'T NEED.
Hanzo: HEH.
( Imori gasps )
Killua: AND THIS ONE
GOES THIS WAY!
( both gasp )
Killua: GOOD LUCK.
YOU GOT THREE DAYS LEFT
TO FIND 'EM.
I'LL SEE YA LATER.
Amori: DAMN!
( gasps )
♪
Hanzo: HUMPH.
NUMBER 197 WAS ALWAYS WITH 199.
THEY WERE BASICALLY INSEPARABLE.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
I NEVER EXPECTED THAT LITTLE KID
TO DEAL WITH THEM FOR ME.
IT'S A GOOD THING
I WAS WATCHING FROM THE SHADOWS.
MADE IT REAL EASY
TO GRAB THE BADGE I NEE‐‐
( gasps )
AHH!
♪
HE‐‐HE KNEW.
THE KID KNEW I WAS THERE.
( gasping )
I'VE FAILED.
Killua: OH, MAN.
THIS IS SO BORING.
I WONDER WHAT GON'S
UP TO RIGHT NOW.
♪
HMM?
HUMPH.
♪
( birds chirping )
Leorio: WE'VE BEEN HERE
FOR SIX DAYS.
ONLY ONE DAY LEFT.
Kurapika: IT'S BEEN FOUR DAYS
SINCE WE RAN INTO HISOKA,
AND WE HAVEN'T FOUND
ANYONE ELSE.
Leorio: HMM.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO BACK
TO THE LANDING.
Kurapika: HUH?
Leorio: IT'S POSSIBLE
THERE ARE A FEW PEOPLE
WHO'VE ALREADY FINISHED.
‐ Kurapika: NO, IMPOSSIBLE.
‐ Leorio: EH?
Kurapika: THIS PHASE OF THE EXAM
IS DIFFERENT
FROM ALL THE OTHERS.
IF YOUR BADGE IS STOLEN,
YOU STILL HAVE
THE OPPORTUNITY TO RECOVER IT.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVE
SIX POINTS WORTH OF BADGES NOW
DOESN'T GUARANTEE YOU'LL
HAVE THEM WHEN THE PHASE ENDS.
THIS TEST
CAN'T BE COMPLETED EARLY.
Leorio: I SEE.
Kurapika: BUT IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
WITH JUST A DAY LEFT,
THERE MUST BE A FEW
WHO'VE ALREADY GOTTEN
THEIR SIX POINTS,
AND IT'S SAFE TO ASSUME
THEY WOULD THEN GRAVITATE
TO THE SAME PLACE,
NEAR THE GOAL.
AT LEAST,
THAT'S WHAT I WOULD DO.
Leorio: OKAY. LET'S GET GOING.
WELL? SEE ANYONE?
Kurapika: NO.
THAT IS TO SAY NO ONE
WHO CAN BE EASILY SPOTTED.
Leorio: DAMN IT.
Kurapika: PERHAPS WE SHOULD
SPLIT UP AND KEEP LOOKING,
BUT FIRST WE SHOULD CHOOSE
A TIME AND PLACE
FOR US TO RECONVENE.
Gon: AND IT'LL GO WAY FASTER
WITH THREE PEOPLE.
‐ Leorio: UHH!
‐ Kurapika UHH!
Both: GON!
Gon: I GUESS WE ALL MUST HAVE
HAD EXACTLY THE SAME IDEA.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING FROM ABOVE,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE THERE ARE
A LOT OF PEOPLE NEARBY.
Leorio: REALLY? FROM ABOVE?
NOW, WHY DIDN'T WE
THINK OF THAT?
Kurapika:
IT WOULDN'T HAVE WORKED.
WITHOUT EYES AS SHARP AS GON'S,
WE'D NEVER HAVE SPOTTED ANYONE.
GON...
WERE YOU ABLE TO GET
ALL THE BADGES YOU NEED?
Gon: YEAH. I GUESS.
Leorio: AH, DAMN.
YOU GOT YOURS, TOO?
SO I'M THE ONLY ONE LEFT.
Gon: WELL, WHO'S YOUR TARGET?
Leorio: NUMBER 246,
A WOMAN NAMED PONZU.
THE ONLY THING
I REALLY KNOW ABOUT HER
IS THAT SHE USES
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
GON, YOU DIDN'T HAPPEN
TO SEE ANY WOMEN
WHEN YOU WERE UP THERE, DID YOU?
Gon: I'M AFRAID NOT.
Leorio: I SEE.
Kurapika: ALL RIGHT,
THERE ARE FOUR POSSIBILITIES
WE SHOULD CONSIDER:
SHE'S SAFE AND STILL
IN POSSESSION OF HER BADGE;
SHE'S ALIVE,
BUT NO LONGER HAS HER BADGE;
SHE'S OUT OF THE COMPETITION,
BUT HAS HELD ON TO HER BADGE;
OR SHE'S DEAD NOW
AND DOESN'T HAVE HER BADGE.
Leorio: DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S LIKELY THAT SHE'S
BOTH OUT OF THE RUNNING
AND STILL HAS HER BADGE?
Kurapika: SHE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN
IN SOME KIND OF ACCIDENT,
OR IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT SHE WAS DEFEATED
AFTER HIDING HER BADGE
SOMEWHERE FOR SAFEKEEPING.
IF THAT'S THE CASE
AND SHE WAS KILLED
AFTER CONCEALING HER BADGE,
HER BADGE
MAY NEVER BE FOUND AGAIN.
Leorio: THE MORE YOU TALK,
THE WORSE THIS SCENARIO GETS.
Gon: HEY, DO YOU KNOW
ANYTHING ELSE ABOUT PONZU?
LIKE DOES SHE WEAR SOME KIND OF
SPECIAL FRAGRANCE LIKE LEORIO?
Leorio: HUH?
( Kurapika gasps )
THAT'S RIGHT!
GON MIGHT BE ABLE TO TRACK HER
BY HER SCENT.
Leorio: OKAY, BUT SHE MIGHT
NOT EVEN WEAR PERFUME, YOU KNOW.
WHAT DO WE DO THEN?
Kurapika: HE'LL TRACK
HER CHEMICALS.
SHE'S WELL KNOWN
FOR USING CHEMICALS, ISN'T SHE?
WITH A VARIETY OF CHEMICALS,
SOME ARE SURE TO HAVE
DISTINCT ODORS. WELL, GON?
Gon: RIGHT.
I'LL GIVE IT A SHOT.
AFTER ALL, IT'S WHY I'M HERE.
♪
( no audible dialogue )
Leorio: IS SHE IN THERE, GON?
Gon: YEP. NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
Kurapika: WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
Leorio: I'M GOING IN.
I WANT YOU GUYS TO WAIT HERE.
( footsteps echoing )
( stick clatters )
DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE THERE ARE ANY TRAPS.
I'LL HEAD INSIDE.
WAIT UNTIL I GIVE THE OKAY.
THEN YOU TWO CAN COME IN.
‐ Kurapika: 30 MINUTES.
‐ Leorio: HMM?
Kurapika: IF, AFTER 30 MINUTES,
WE HAVEN'T HEARD FROM YOU,
WE'RE COMING TO FIND YOU.
Leorio: NO WAY.
IF YOU DON'T HEAR FROM ME,
YOU BOTH GO
RIGHT BACK TO THE START.
Kurapika: THAT'S NOT AN OPTION.
WE HAVE FORMED AN ALLIANCE,
AND I WILL NOT ABANDON YOU NOW.
Leorio:
THEN THIS ALLIANCE IS OVER.
I KNOW IT'S SELFISH, CONSIDERING
HOW MUCH YOU HELPED ME,
BUT I'VE GOT TO DO THIS ALONE.
Gon: NO WAY.
( Leorio gasps )
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
Gon: WE'RE BOTH STAYING HERE
BECAUSE WE WANT TO.
IT'S OUR CHOICE.
SO IS THAT A PROBLEM?
( Leorio scoffs )
FINE. SUIT YOURSELF.
HANG ON TO THAT FOR ME.
( Kurapika chuckles )
♪
Leorio: I'VE JUST
GOTTA GO FOR IT.
( footsteps echoing )
( panting )
HEY, ISN'T THAT‐‐
IT'S BOURBON.
Ponzu: LET ME GUESS.
I MUST BE YOUR TARGET.
AM I RIGHT?
Leorio: PONZU!
Ponzu: IT'S POINTLESS.
THERE'S NOTHING FOR US TO GAIN
BY FIGHTING DOWN HERE.
Leorio: I HAVE
EVERYTHING TO GAIN.
IT'S JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
YOU'RE MY TARGET, ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS HAPPENING,
NO MATTER WHAT!
( Ponzu sighs )
LET'S ASSUME THAT WE DO FIGHT
AND, BY SOME MIRACLE,
YOU ACTUALLY BEAT ME.
THERE'S STILL NO WAY YOU'RE
EVER GETTING OUT OF THIS CAVE.
Leorio: WAIT. WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
( animals chittering )
Gon: HE'S TAKING TOO LONG.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS HE OKAY?
Kurapika: YES,
BUT HIS 30 MINUTES
ARE ALMOST UP.
Leorio: KURAPIKA, GON,
DON'T COME IN!
♪
Gon: LEORIO!
( Leorio shuddering )
Leorio: YOU IDIOTS.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NOT TO COME IN.
Kurapika: HE'S COVERED IN BITES.
IF THOSE SNAKES ARE VENOMOUS,
THEN...
Gon: THEY'RE A KIND OF VIPER,
AND THEY ARE POISONOUS,
BUT IT ISN'T THAT STRONG.
STILL, WITH THIS MANY BITES...
Leorio: STOP IT, WILL YOU?
ONE CUT IN YOUR MOUTH
OR EVEN A LITTLE CAVITY...
Gon: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
Kurapika: LEORIO! DO YOU HAVE
ANY ANTIVENOM IN HERE?
Leorio: IF I DID,
MAYBE I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO SAVE YOU GUYS, AT LEAST.
Gon: LEORIO!
Kurapika:
LET'S STOP THE BLEEDING.
( Leorio gasping )
Kurapika: THAT SHOULD DO IT.
Gon: WE STILL NEED
TO GET HIM TO A DOCTOR.
Ponzu: I WOULDN'T ADVISE THAT.
YOU AREN'T GETTING OUT
SO EASILY.
Kurapika:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
Ponzu: WHAT I MEAN
IS THAT WE'RE TRAPPED.
WHENEVER SOMEONE
TRIES TO LEAVE THIS CAVE...
( rustling )
THE SNAKES
WILL ATTACK YOU EN MASSE.
( snakes hissing )
IT'S A TRAP SET BY BOURBON,
THE SNAKE CHARMER.
IF YOU'RE BITTEN, YOU'LL END UP
COMPLETELY PARALYZED,
JUST LIKE YOUR FRIEND HERE.
AFTER THAT, YOU DIE.
( both shudder )
Kurapika: BOURBON!
YOU'RE LOOKING TO COLLECT
MORE BADGES, RIGHT?
WE'LL GIVE YOU
EVERY ONE WE HAVE.
JUST PLEASE LET US OUT OF HERE!
Ponzu: DON'T BOTHER.
YOU SEE, HE'S ALREADY DEAD.
♪
Kurapika: WHAT?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
Narrator:
GON AND FRIENDS ARE CAUGHT
IN A TRAP SET BY BOURBON
THE SNAKE CHARMER
AND CAN'T LEAVE THE CAVE.
WILL THEY PASS THE HUNTER EXAM,
AND WILL LEORIO SURVIVE
THE VENOMOUS SNAKEBITES?
( snake hisses )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"BIG TIME INTERVIEW."
THANKS A LOT, KURAPIKA.
Kurapika: NO, THANK YOU, GON.