Narrator: HEAVENS ARENA.
THE 251‐STORY BUILDING
WHICH STANDS 991 METERS TALL
‐ IS A MECCA FOR FIGHTERS.
‐ ( crowd cheering )
WHEN COMBATANTS WIN A FIGHT,
THEY MAY ADVANCE BY ONE CLASS
AND RECEIVE
A CORRESPONDING REWARD.
AFTER REACHING THE 100th FLOOR,
THEY ARE ASSIGNED
A PRIVATE ROOM.
AND THOSE CONTESTANTS WHO ARE
SKILLED AND FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO REACH THE 200th FLOOR
EARN THE RIGHT TO CHALLENGE
THE STRONGEST FIGHTERS,
THE FLOOR MASTERS, IN AN INTENSE
BATTLE FOR SURVIVAL.
THIS IS, WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE BEST STAGE
A WARRIOR COULD ASK FOR.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Wing: YOU SAY THAT YOUR BROTHER
IS ABLE TO USE NEN?
Killua: I NEED TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT NEN AND REN EVEN MEAN,
AND NOT JUST HALFWAY.
I NEED TO KNOW IT.
Wing: WELL, IN THAT CASE...
♪
Narrator:
AFTER KILLUA FOUGHT ZUSHI,
THE YOUNG PRACTITIONER
OF SHINGEN‐RYU MARTIAL ARTS,
ZUSHI MENTIONED
THE FOUR EXERCISES.
GON AND KILLUA
ARE ABOUT TO LEARN
THE SECRET OF THOSE PRINCIPLES
FROM ZUSHI'S MASTER, WING.
♪
Wing: PAYING ATTENTION?
NEN, OR FLAME,
IS A POWER THAT FIRES OUR SOULS.
( marker squeaking )
IN OTHER WORDS,
IT'S THE STRENGTH OF YOUR WILL.
AND THE FOUR EXERCISES
IS A TRAINING REGIMEN
THAT STRENGTHENS YOUR WILL.
Gon: STRENGTHENS YOUR WILL?
Killua: TRAINING?
‐ ( marker squeaks )
‐ Wing: CORRECT.
TEN, FOCUS THE MIND
ON A SINGLE POINT,
REFLECT ON THE SELF,
AND DETERMINE THE GOAL.
ZETSU, TO PUT INTO WORDS.
REN IS TO INTENSIFY YOUR WILL.
HATSU IS TO RELEASE IT
INTO ACTION.
Gon: TEN, ZETSU, REN, HATSU.
THE FOUR EXERCISES.
Wing: SEE, ZUSHI TEMPERED
HIS REFUSAL TO LOSE
DURING HIS BATTLE
WITH YOU, KILLUA.
( Killua grunts )
( gasps )
Wing: NOW ALLOW ME
TO DEMONSTRATE.
‐ KILLUA...
‐ Killua: EH?
Wing: FOR THIS DEMONSTRATION,
I WOULD LIKE TO "KILL" YOU NOW.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
Killua: SURE. WHY NOT?
BUT YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO.
Wing: LET'S DO THIS IN ORDER.
FIRST, TEN.
I FOCUS MY MIND
ON A SINGLE POINT.
ZETSU,
EXPRESS YOUR DESIRED INTENT
EITHER MENTALLY OR VERBALLY.
I WILL KILL YOU.
♪
( both gasp )
( Gon gasps )
( Killua gasping )
Wing: THAT WAS A TASTE OF REN.
WITH ENOUGH STRENGTH AND FOCUS,
THE WILL FUNCTIONS
AS ACTION, OR HATSU.
WITH A STRONG WILL,
YOUR OPPONENT WILL BACK DOWN.
A MORE FAMILIAR TERM
WOULD BE BLUFFING.
REN HARDENS THAT WHICH IS SOFT,
AND YOU SUDDENLY FIND
THAT YOU'VE LOST YOUR ABILITY
TO CORRECT AN INCORRECT IDEA.
THEREFORE, UNTIL YOUR SOUL
HAS FULLY MATURED,
AVOID USING REN.
AS IT STANDS NOW,
YOU THREE BOYS SHOULD REALLY
FOCUS ON TRAINING YOUR SOULS.
( Killua sighs )
LET'S GO, GON.
Wing: IF YOU TRULY WISH
TO LEARN ABOUT NEN,
SET YOUR SIGHTS
ON MASTERING TEN FIRST.
IF YOU MASTER TEN,
YOU NO LONGER FEEL THE PRESSURE
OF AN OPPONENT'S WILL.
Gon: THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
WAIT UP, KILLUA!
( Wing sighs )
ZUSHI.
Zushi: YES, SIR?
Wing: LET'S BEGIN YOUR TRAINING.
Zushi: OSU!
Wing: FIRST OFF...
Gon: HE LIED?
Killua: YEAH.
WHAT HE SAID WAS TRUE,
FAR AS IT WENT,
AND HIS POWER
IS THE REAL DEAL, TOO,
BUT THERE ARE A FEW THINGS
IT DOESN'T COVER.
Gon: LIKE?
Killua: LIKE HOW TOUGH ZUSHI IS.
IN OUR FIGHT, HE GOT UP
EVERY TIME I KNOCKED HIM DOWN.
THAT WAS PRETTY ANNOYING,
WHICH IS WHY I GOT A LITTLE
PUSHY WITH HIM AT THE END.
( Gon gasps )
( crowd cheering )
( Zushi panting )
♪
( Killua gasps )
WHY, YOU...
( Zushi gags )
( Killua gasps )
OOPS.
Cocco: OHH!
ZUSHI SAILS OUT OF THE RING!
AND STRAIGHT TO THE HOSPITAL,
BY THE LOOKS OF IT.
THAT'S GOTTA HURT!
( crowd cheering )
( Killua gasps )
Cocco: HE'S GOTTEN
BACK UP, FOLKS.
ZUSHI MUST BE INVINCIBLE!
( Zushi panting )
Killua: NO WAY.
Cocco: BUT THE REFEREE
HAS AWARDED
A CRITICAL HIT AND KNOCKDOWN.
KILLUA WINS BY T. K. O.
WITH 11 TOTAL POINTS.
( crowd cheering )
Killua: IT WASN'T
HIS STRENGTH OF WILL ALONE
THAT KEPT HIM STANDING
THAT WHOLE TIME.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOMETHING ELSE HE'S HIDING.
Gon: HMM.
♪
Wing: WHAT'S THE MATTER, ZUSHI?
YOUR TEN IS AGGRAVATED.
‐ Zushi: MASTER...
‐ Wing: HMM?
Zushi: WHY DID YOU LIE
TO GON AND KILLUA JUST NOW?
Wing: LIE?
ARE YOU REFERRING
TO MY EXPLANATION?
Zushi: YES.
THE FOUR EXERCISES ARE
TEN, ZETSU, REN, AND HATSU,
BUT THEY DON'T MEAN
WHAT YOU TOLD THEM.
DID YOU DECIDE TO LIE TO THEM
BECAUSE THEY AREN'T
YOUR STUDENTS?
Wing: I DIDN'T LIE.
THAT NEN IS
AN IMPORTANT DISCIPLINE
IN TRAINING THE MIND...
FOR THIS NEN.
HOWEVER, IT'S TRUE
THAT I CANNOT TEACH NEN
TO SOMEONE WHO IS NOT A STUDENT,
SO I USED THE OTHER NEN
AS A HINT
JUST TO HELP THEM ALONG.
IF THE NEN I TEACH
IS USED IN THE WRONG WAY,
IT CAN BECOME
A TERRIBLE WEAPON, ZUSHI.
( page flutters )
‐ FOR EXAMPLE...
‐ ( rip )
Zushi: HUH?
Wing: YOU COULD TURN
A SIMPLE PIECE OF PAPER
INTO QUITE A HARMFUL BLADE.
FURTHERMORE,
YOU COULD HARDEN YOUR BODY
AS A DEFENSIVE MEASURE.
WITH ENOUGH WORK,
ANYONE CAN USE NEN,
WHICH IS WHY
YOU MUST BE VERY CAREFUL
WHEN CHOOSING
WHO TO TEACH IT TO.
Zushi: MASTER, IT'S JUST...
THAT I HADN'T GOTTEN THE CHANCE
TO READ THAT BOOK YET.
( Wing gasps )
Zushi: AND THAT JUICE...
IT WAS MINE.
( Wing stammers )
I'M SORRY!
♪
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: IT'S TIME FOR
THE BIGGEST MATCH OF THE DAY!
TWO ROOKIES HAVE ADVANCED
TO THE 190th FLOOR
WITHOUT LOSING A SINGLE FIGHT,
GON AND KILLUA!
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO CLEAR
TODAY'S MATCH IN ONE SHOT, TOO?
OKAY, EVERYONE,
GET READY TO PRESS
YOUR WAGER BUTTONS!
( fighter scoffs )
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
THAT LITTLE PUSH MOVE OF YOURS
WON'T WORK ON ME.
THAT'S BECAUSE
I'M AS SLIPPERY AS A SNAKE,
AND MY FANGS ARE JUST AS SHARP,
FANGS THAT ARE JUST DYING FOR
A TASTE OF YOUR VITAL POINTS.
( fighter #2 laughs )
YOU MIGHT SPORT
A VICIOUS CHOP, KID,
BUT IT WON'T BE ENOUGH
TO SAVE YOU FROM THESE MUSCLES!
AND DO YOU WANNA KNOW WHY?
( grunts )
BECAUSE I'M TOTALLY RIPPED,
OBVIOUSLY!
( Killua sighs )
Referee: AND BEGIN!
Fighter #1: Hee‐yah!
( fighter #2 yells )
( crowd cheering )
Referee #2:
THAT'S A CRITICAL HIT
AND KNOCKDOWN!
THAT'S THREE POINTS!
IT'S A KNOCKOUT!
AND WINNER IS GON!
Referee #1:
CRITICAL HIT AND KNOCKDOWN!
THAT'S THREE POINTS!
KNOCKOUT! KILLUA WINS!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: ONCE AGAIN,
GON AND KILLUA
HAVE KNOCKED OUT THEIR OPPONENTS
WITH ONE ATTACK,
MEANING BOTH OF THEM
HAVE SUCCESSFULLY CLEARED
THE 190th FLOOR!
BOTH COMPETITORS ADVANCE
TO THE 200th FLOOR!
Zushi: THE 200th FLOOR ALREADY?!
Wing: ZUSHI.
Zushi: MASTER WING.
Wing: KILLUA AND GON
HAVE ALREADY REACHED
THE 200th FLOOR, HAVE THEY?
Zushi: YES!
THEY'RE BOTH AMAZING FIGHTERS.
I REALLY NEED TO TRAIN M‐‐
UH, WHAT THE? MASTER?
Wing: I GUESS
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
Guide: ENJOY.
Gon: THE 200th FLOOR.
SO WHAT'S IT LIKE?
Killua: BEATS ME.
NEVER ACTUALLY BEEN THERE.
BUT I GUESS
WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT.
♪
( ding )
Gon: WOW!
THE 200th FLOOR
SURE IS FANCY, HUH?
Killua: WHERE'S RECEPTION?
MAYBE THIS WAY.
Gon: WE FINALLY MADE IT.
Killua: YEAH.
( both gasp )
♪
Gon: WHAT IS THIS?
IT SUDDENLY FEELS LIKE WE'RE IN
A JUNGLE SWARMING WITH MONSTERS,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
AN ORDINARY HALLWAY.
Killua: LET'S GO.
WE CAN DO THIS.
Gon: IT'S NOT WORKING.
I CAN'T GO ON!
I DON'T WANT TO!
DO YOU FEEL THAT BLOODLUST?
IT'S DIRECTED RIGHT AT US!
Killua: OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH!
WHO'S THERE?!
SHOW YOURSELF!
( receptionist chuckles )
♪
YOU MUST BE KILLUA AND GON.
THE RECEPTION DESK IS THIS WAY,
SO PLEASE REGISTER
FOR A 200th‐FLOOR MATCH TODAY.
BE ADVISED THAT YOUR ELIGIBILITY
FOR THIS FLOOR
EXPIRES AT MIDNIGHT,
SO PLEASE DON'T DELAY.
Gon: DID THAT FEELING
COME FROM HER?
Killua: I CAN'T TELL.
Receptionist: BY THE WAY,
ON THE 200th FLOOR,
THERE ARE CURRENTLY
173 CONTESTANTS.
AND FROM THIS FLOOR UP,
ALL WEAPONS ARE ALLOWED
IN ALL MATCHES,
SO PLEASE FEEL FREE
TO USE WHATEVER YOU HAVE.
ALSO, AS OF THE 200th FLOOR,
YOU WILL NO LONGER RECEIVE
PRIZE MONEY.
NOW YOU WILL BE FIGHTING
ONLY FOR HONOR.
PLEASE KEEP THAT IN MIND
IF YOU PARTICIPATE.
( both gasp )
( receptionist gasps )
Killua: H‐HISOKA.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
Hisoka: IT ISN'T
THAT STRANGE, IS IT?
I LOVE TO FIGHT, AND THIS IS
A TEMPLE DEVOTED TO THE CRAFT.
THE REAL QUESTION IS,
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
JUST KIDDING.
THIS MEETING IS
NO MERE COINCIDENCE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
REMEMBER HOW YOU
ORDERED YOUR TICKETS
FOR THE AIRSHIP
OVER THE INTERNET?
WITH ONLY A LITTLE EFFORT
ON MY PART,
I WAS ABLE TO FIND OUT
EXACTLY WHEN YOU WOULD ARRIVE.
WELL, IN ANY CASE, I KNEW
YOU WOULD COME HERE EVENTUALLY.
AND SO AS YOUR SENIOR,
I HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
A WARNING FOR THE BOTH OF YOU.
( both grunt )
Hisoka: YOU'RE STILL NOT READY
TO SET FOOT ON THIS FLOOR...
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
‐ ( force strikes )
‐ ( both grunting )
Hisoka: WHEN YOU WILL BE
DEPENDS ON YOUR EFFORTS.
FOR NOW, LEAVE THIS FLOOR.
IT'S FAR TOO EARLY.
Killua: WAIT. WHAT?!
THAT'S STUPID!
WE JUST GOT UP HERE!
I WON'T LET YOU PASS,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU COULD, ANYWAY.
( Killua groans )
WHAT THE HELL?!
Gon: WHAT IS THIS?
Man: DON'T BE RECKLESS.
( footsteps )
Gon: MR. WING!
Wing: WHAT HE'S SAYING IS TRUE.
YOU HAVE NO DEFENSE
AGAINST HIS NEN.
Gon: NEN?
Wing: AS IT STANDS, YOU ARE
BOTH NAKED IN A BLIZZARD,
BOTH OF YOU WONDERING
WHY IT'S SO COLD.
IF YOU CONTINUE TO STRAIN
YOUR BODIES, YOU MAY DIE.
Killua: SO THIS IS NEN?
HE CAN STOP US FROM MOVING
FORWARD THROUGH WILLPOWER?
YOU LIAR!
Wing: YES, I WAS LYING.
( both gasp )
Wing: THOUGH SOME OF WHAT I SAID
WAS TECHNICALLY TRUE.
I WILL TEACH YOU
THE TRUTH ABOUT NEN,
SO FOR THE TIME BEING,
I SUGGEST WE WITHDRAW.
Gon: UH, 'SCUSE ME.
Receptionist: OH. YES?
Gon: IF WE DON'T REGISTER
FOR A FIGHT TODAY,
HOW WOULD THAT AFFECT US?
Receptionist: WELL, YOU WOULD
HAVE TO START ALL OVER AGAIN
FROM THE FIRST FLOOR.
KILLUA, HOWEVER,
HE'S BEEN HERE BEFORE
AND REFUSED TO REGISTER.
SO IF HE FAILS TO DO SO AGAIN,
HIS COMMITMENT
WILL BE CALLED INTO QUESTION,
AND HE WILL BE BANNED
FROM PARTICIPATING.
( Killua groans )
‐ MR. WING.
‐ Wing: HUH?
Killua: IF WE WITHDRAW,
WILL WE BE ABLE TO MAKE IT
BACK HERE BY MIDNIGHT?
Gon: HMM.
Hisoka: HMM.
Wing: THAT ALL DEPENDS ON YOU.
( beep )
SIMPLY PUT, THIS IS NEN.
( water trickling )
NEN REFERS TO THE ABILITY
TO CONTROL YOUR AURA,
WHICH, AS YOU MAY KNOW,
IS ALSO KNOWN AS LIFE ENERGY.
EVERYONE IN THE WORLD HAS
A SMALL AMOUNT OF LIFE ENERGY,
BUT IN MOST CASES,
IT SIMPLY LEAKS AWAY.
THE ABILITY
TO BUILD UP AND CONTAIN
THIS LIFE ENERGY
IS KNOWN AS TEN.
USING TEN,
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR BODY TOUGHER
AND CONSIDERABLY SLOW
THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
THEN COMES ZETSU,
WHICH SHUTS OFF
THE FLOW OF AURA.
IT IS QUITE EFFECTIVE
FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE FROM OTHERS
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
WHICH BRINGS US TO REN.
IT ENABLES YOU
TO PRODUCE MORE AURA.
( both gasp )
Wing: CAN YOU FEEL THAT?
Killua: YEAH.
IT'S LIKE PRESSURE.
Gon: BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL
WEIRD OR CREEPY.
Wing: THAT'S BECAUSE
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO MALICE.
( thinking )
I MUST ADMIT I'M IMPRESSED.
THEIR SENSES ARE AMAZING.
PERHAPS IT'S A PRODUCT
OF THE ENVIRONMENTS
IN WHICH THEY WERE RAISED,
BUT THEIR INNATE GIFTS
ARE ALSO A FACTOR.
AURA IS AN ENERGY
DWELLING WITHIN ALL HUMANS,
WHICH MAKES IT VERY EFFECTIVE
AGAINST OTHER HUMANS,
FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE.
IF YOU ATTACK A HELPLESS PERSON
WITH MALICE,
YOU CAN KILL USING AURA ALONE.
ONLY ONE THING CAN PROTECT YOU
FROM A USER OF NEN.
YOU MUST LEARN
TO USE IT YOURSELF
AND USE TEN FOR DEFENSE,
BLOCK THE OTHER PERSON'S AURA
WITH YOUR OWN.
OTHERWISE...
( both gasp )
YOUR BODY WILL BE SHATTERED
BEYOND ALL RECOGNITION.
♪
Narrator: HISOKA BLOCKS THE PATH
LEADING BEYOND THE 200th FLOOR.
GON AND KILLUA
HAVE BEGUN THEIR STUDIES,
BUT WILL THEY BE ABLE
TO LEARN ENOUGH ABOUT TRUE NEN
TO PASS HISOKA
AND REACH THE RECEPTIONIST
ALL BEFORE THE CLOCK
STRIKES MIDNIGHT?
( Hisoka chuckles )
NOT YET.
IT'S TOO SOON.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'LL
INTRODUCE MR. WING,
ZUSHI'S MASTER
AND AN EXPERT AT SHINGEN‐RYU.
Killua: IT SEEMS LIKE HE'S
PRETTY GOOD WITH NEN.
Gon: OH, YEAH,
BUT ISN'T HIS SHIRT UNTUCKED?
Killua: AND HE'S GOT BED‐HEAD.
♪
( music playing only )
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"AWAKENING AND POTENTIAL."
( grunts, yells )
DID YOU FEEL ANYTHING?
Killua: NOPE. NOTHING.