Narrator: HEAVENS ARENA.
THE 251‐STORY BUILDING
WHICH STANDS 991 METERS TALL
‐ IS A MECCA FOR FIGHTERS.
‐ ( crowd cheering )
WHEN COMBATANTS WIN A FIGHT,
THEY MAY ADVANCE BY ONE CLASS
AND RECEIVE
A CORRESPONDING REWARD.
AFTER REACHING THE 100th FLOOR,
THEY ARE ASSIGNED
A PRIVATE ROOM.
AND THOSE CONTESTANTS WHO ARE
SKILLED AND FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO REACH THE 200th FLOOR
EARN THE RIGHT TO CHALLENGE
THE STRONGEST FIGHTERS,
THE FLOOR MASTERS, IN AN INTENSE
BATTLE FOR SURVIVAL.
THIS IS, WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE BEST STAGE
A WARRIOR COULD ASK FOR.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Sadaso: TODAY, I'LL BEAT
KILLUA FOR MY SIXTH WIN.
TOMORROW, I'LL BEAT GON
FOR MY SEVENTH WIN.
AFTER THAT, ALL I'LL NEED TO DO
IS FIND THREE MORE SUCKERS.
HEH HEH HEH.
THEN I'LL BE A FLOOR MASTER.
WITH THE KIND OF FAME
AND FORTUNE THAT'LL GET ME,
I'LL BE SET
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
( gasps )
Killua: YOU MOVE, YOU DIE.
YOU USE NEN, AND YOU DIE.
MAKE A SOUND, AND YOU DIE.
IF YOU UNDERSTAND,
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
DO YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU BREAK YOUR PROMISES?
IF YOU DO, OPEN YOUR EYES,
LOOK AT ME IN THE MIRROR,
AND LISTEN CAREFULLY.
DON'T EVER SHOW YOUR DIRTY FACE
IN FRONT OF US AGAIN.
YOU'LL KEEP THIS PROMISE.
♪
( overlapping chatter )
Narrator: THERE ARE MANY
WHO WOULD RESORT
TO USING UNDERHANDED TACTICS
TO BECOME A FLOOR MASTER.
GON, ON THE OTHER HAND,
HAS BEEN FIERCELY CONCENTRATING
ON IMPROVING HIS NEN
AND GROWING STRONGER,
AND TONIGHT, HE HAS
HIS BATTLE WITH SADASO.
Sadaso: HIS EYES,
THEY BELONG TO SOMEONE
WHO LIVES IN THE WORLD
OF DARKNESS.
I WAS FILLED WITH DESPAIR.
I COULD SENSE
THE DIFFERENCE IN STRENGTH
THE SECOND OUR EYES MET.
IT WAS CLEAR
THAT HE WAS THE PREDATOR,
AND I WAS HIS PREY. ( shudders )
IT WAS A HUGE MISTAKE
TO UNDERESTIMATE HIM.
HE ISN'T JUST
SOME NORMAL KID. HEH.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE,
SO I'M GETTING THE HELL
OUT OF HERE. ( shudders )
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
HE'LL BE COMING AFTER
YOU GUYS NEXT. ( shudders )
( phone line beeping )
( beeping continues )
( phone beeps )
Gido: NOW WHAT?
Riehlvelt: WELL, I'M STILL IN,
AND I'M WILLING
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
I'M ALMOST A FLOOR MASTER.
10 VICTORIES ON THIS FLOOR,
AND YOU'RE ALLOWED
TO CHALLENGE A FLOOR MASTER.
IF YOU WIN, YOU GET
AN ENTIRE FLOOR TO YOURSELF.
( Gido shudders )
Riehlvelt: AND AS SOON
AS THAT TITLE IS IN YOUR HAND,
YOU CAN LECTURE,
TEACH, AND ADVISE,
OR START UP
A MARTIAL ARTS SCHOOL.
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
YOU'VE GOT IT MADE.
Gido: DO YOU THINK THAT KID'S
GONNA COME BACK HERE
TO THREATEN US?
Riehlvelt: THE BOY HAS NO CLUE
WHAT MY ABILITIES ARE.
AS LONG AS WE'RE
CAREFUL ABOUT IT,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HANDLE HIM QUITE EASILY.
‐ Killua: YOU'RE WRONG.
‐ ( both gasp )
Killua: IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHAT YOUR ABILITIES ARE.
( Gido gasps )
Killua: THERE'S NO RUSH,
YOU SEE.
‐ I CAN ALWAYS GET TO YOU...
‐ ( both gasp )
WHENEVER AND WHEREVER I WANT.
AT NIGHT, WHEN YOU'RE
SOUND ASLEEP IN YOUR BED,
WHEN YOU'RE TAKING A CRAP,
RIGHT?
♪
LISTEN UP.
YOU SHOULD FOLLOW THE RULES.
WITHOUT THE RULES, THE ONLY ONES
BENEFITTING WOULD BE US.
( Riehlvelt chuckles )
AS I WAS SAYING,
CHEATING IS A TERRIBLE IDEA.
A FAIR FIGHT IS THE WAY TO GO.
Gido: RIGHT.
♪
Referee: SADASO'S TIME IS UP!
GON WINS BY DEFAULT!
‐ ( crowd booing )
‐ Man: WHAT?! AGAIN?!
Man #2: YEAH, WHAT THE HELL
IS SADASO DOING?
♪
Wing: ALL RIGHT. SO TODAY,
GON WILL BE FIGHTING GIDO.
AFTER THAT, OF COURSE,
KILLUA WILL BE GOING UP
AGAINST RIEHLVELT.
ARE YOU BOTH FEELING ALL RIGHT?
Both: YES, SIR!
Wing: NOW, THIS WILL BE
YOUR SECOND MATCH AGAINST GIDO,
SO I DOUBT YOU'LL
REQUIRE MUCH ADVICE.
HAVE YOU SETTLED ON A STRATEGY?
Gon: YES. I, UH, THINK I HAVE.
WELL, HERE'S THE THING.
MY STRATEGY IS TO USE THAT.
Killua: HUH?
Wing: YES, I UNDERSTAND.
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: THE REMATCH
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR
IS FINALLY HERE,
GIDO VERSUS GON!
THEIR LAST MATCH
LANDED GON IN THE HOSPITAL,
BUT THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT WE'RE IN FOR THIS TIME!
FOR TODAY'S MATCH,
GON IS CARRYING A FISHING ROD.
BUT HOW EXACTLY
DOES HE PLAN TO USE IT?
WILL HE BE INCORPORATING IT
INTO HIS FIGHTING STYLE?
LET'S FIND OUT.
Referee: THIS IS A POINTS AND
K. O. SYSTEM, NO TIME LIMIT!
BEGIN!
Cocco: RIGHT OFF THE BAT,
GON TAKES OFF IN A MAD DASH!
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE GIDO
WAS PREPARED FOR THIS.
HE'S ALREADY RESPONDING
WITH HIS TORNADO TOP.
IF GON CHARGES IN,
HE'LL BE IN THE SAME POSITION
HE WAS LAST TIME.
Gon: HE'S WAY AHEAD OF ME.
( Gido laughs )
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
ONCE I'VE STARTED SPINNING,
IT'S VIRTUALLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO STOP ME.
THE ONLY LOGICAL COURSE
WOULD BE TO HIT ME
WITH A PREEMPTIVE ATTACK
BEFORE I EVEN START.
WELL, IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO MAKE A MOVE, I WILL!
SHOTGUN BLUES!
Gon: HE CAN FIRE OFF
HIS TOPS MIDSPIN?
Gido: AS YOU CAN SEE,
THIS TECHNIQUE IS NOTHING
LIKE THE BATTLE WALTZ.
ALL MY TOPS WILL BE
AIMING RIGHT FOR YOU.
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO DODGE THEM ALL.
Gon: REN!
♪
Gido: WHAT?
Man: WHOA! HE STOPPED THEM!
Man #2: DID YOU JUST SEE THAT?
Man #3: OH, WOW.
Cocco: THAT WAS INCREDIBLE!
GON JUST BLOCKED
THE TOPS HEAD‐ON!
HE IS NOT THE SAME COMPETITOR
HE WAS TWO MONTHS AGO.
( Gido groans ) DAMN.
HIS NEN DEFENSES
HAVE SHOT WAY UP.
WILL MY TOPS STILL BE
ENOUGH TO BEAT HIM?
Killua: THOSE TOPS
WERE COMING STRAIGHT AT HIM.
WITH HIS REFLEXES,
GON COULD HAVE KNOCKED THEM
ALL DOWN WITH HIS FISHING ROD,
BUT HE CHOSE TO GO
WITH REN INSTEAD,
AND THAT DID WAY MORE
PSYCHOLOGICAL DAMAGE TO GIDO.
♪
HE MUST BE THINKING ABOUT HOW
THEY USED ZUSHI TO BLACKMAIL US,
AND HE'S FURIOUS.
Gon: OKAY, IT'S MY TURN NOW.
Cocco: I WONDER WHAT TECHNIQUE
GON WILL USE THIS TIME, FOLKS!
Gido: HE'S USING A FISHING ROD,
AND THAT CAN
ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
HE'LL TRY TO SNAG MY CLOTHES
AND BRING MY SPINNING TO A HALT.
BUT IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE THAT EASY.
♪
Cocco: THERE IT IS!
HE'S GOING STRAIGHT FOR GIDO!
Gido: HEE HEE HEE! I KNEW IT.
NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
( gasps )
Cocco: OH, NO!
HIS ATTACK MISSED ITS TARGET!
( Gido cackles )
WHAT WERE YOU EVEN AIMING AT?
( Gon yells )
Gido: WHAT THE...
Cocco: UNBELIEVABLE!
GON FLIPPED THE FLOOR TILE
AND GIDO ALONG WITH IT!
( Gido yells )
( groans )
( yelps )
( Gon grunts )
( Gido shuddering )
( Gon yells )
Gido: NO! WAIT!
♪
Cocco: G‐GON HAS JUST BROKEN
GIDO'S STEEL PROSTHETIC LEG,
MAKING IT VERY UNLIKELY
THAT HE'LL BE ABLE
TO CONTINUE THE FIGHT.
Gon: IF YOU GUYS
RESORT TO ANY MEANS,
THEN WE WON'T
HOLD BACK EITHER.
AND IF YOU EVEN
TOUCH ZUSHI EVER AGAIN,
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU,
I'LL BREAK YOUR FACE IN HALF!
( Gido shuddering )
Referee: THE WINNER IS GON!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: GON WAS
FINALLY ABLE TO AVENGE
HIS INITIAL LOSS TO GIDO.
HIS RECORD ON THE 200th FLOOR
IS NOW TWO TO ONE!
♪
Killua: ALL RIGHT.
GUESS I'M UP NEXT.
Cocco: AND NOW FOR
THE MAIN EVENT OF THE DAY,
KILLUA VERSUS RIEHLVELT!
SINCE SADASO FORFEITED
THE PREVIOUS MATCH,
THIS WILL TECHNICALLY BE
KILLUA'S 200th‐FLOOR DEBUT.
WHAT KIND OF STRATEGY
ARE WE ABOUT TO SEE NOW?
Killua: YOU DO REALIZE THAT YOU
BROKE YOUR PROMISE FIRST.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'LL LET YOU WIN NOW.
Sadaso: HIS EYES,
THEY BELONG TO SOMEONE WHO LIVES
IN THE WORLD OF DARKNESS.
Riehlvelt: "SOMEONE WHO LIVES
IN THE WORLD OF DARKNESS"?
SO WHAT IF THIS BRAT IS
A PROFESSIONAL ASSASSIN?
HEAVENS ARENA IS MY TURF.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO SHOW HIM
THAT WITHIN THE FOUR SIDES
OF THIS SQUARE STAGE, I RULE!
( crowd cheering )
Zushi: GO, KILLUA!
YOU CAN DO IT!
( Gon sighs )
Referee: THIS IS A POINTS AND
K. O. SYSTEM! NO TIME LIMIT!
BEGIN!
Riehlvelt: HE VANISHED?
BEHIND ME.
AURA BURST!
Cocco: RIEHLVELT BOOSTED
OUT OF HARM'S WAY!
HE PROPELS HIS WHEELCHAIR
BY RELEASING HIS STORED AURA,
GUIDING IT
TO WHEREVER HE WANTS TO GO.
Killua: I JUMPED TOO HIGH.
Riehlvelt: WHEW. THAT WAS CLOSE.
TWO‐HEADED SNAKE,
TWIN SERPENTS!
SONG OF DEFENSE!
Cocco: THERE IT IS, FOLKS,
RIEHLVELT'S SONG OF DEFENSE!
HE PROTECTS HIMSELF
WITH TWO WHIPS
MOVING AT
RIDICULOUSLY HIGH SPEEDS,
THEN WAITS PATIENTLY
FOR HIS CHANCE TO STRIKE!
Riehlvelt: HEH.
YOU PLANNED TO ATTACK FIRST
AND TAKE THE LEAD.
TOO BAD
THAT DIDN'T WORK FOR YOU.
NOW THAT I'VE TAKEN THIS STANCE,
THERE IS NO WAY
YOU COULD POSSIBLY WIN!
Killua: WHY'S THAT?
Riehlvelt:
IT'S OBVIOUS, ISN'T IT?
NO NORMAL PERSON ON THE PLANET
CAN KEEP UP
WITH THESE TWO WHIPS!
AND ON THIS LITTLE PLATFORM,
THERE'S NOWHERE
YOU CAN RUN AND HIDE!
♪
( Killua sighs )
Riehlvelt: TAKE THIS!
Killua: YEAH?
WELL, I'M NOT NORMAL.
SORRY 'BOUT THAT.
Riehlvelt: WHAT?!
FINE, THEN.
♪
THUNDER SERPENT!
( gasping )
( Gon sighs )
Riehlvelt:
I'M SURPRISED, KILLUA.
YOU'RE THE FIRST PERSON
I'VE FOUGHT
WHO COULD SEE
MY WHIPS IN MOTION,
SO I'VE GOT
A LITTLE PRESENT FOR YOU.
THOSE TWO WHIPS TOGETHER
CARRY ONE MILLION VOLTS,
MORE THAN ENOUGH TO PARALYZE
AND INCAPACITATE A GIANT.
ANYONE FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO RESIST MY WHIPS
WILL FALL VICTIM
TO THE MIGHTY THUNDER SERPENT!
WHAAH!
Killua: I'M TRAINED
TO ENDURE TORTURE,
SO ELECTRICITY WON'T WORK.
IT HAS NO EFFECT ON ME.
I MEAN, I CAN TOLERATE IT,
BUT IT ISN'T LIKE
IT MAKES ME HAPPY.
IT STILL REALLY HURTS A LOT
AND EVERYTHING.
THAT'S WHY I'M A LITTLE PISSED.
( Riehlvelt laughs nervously )
Killua: THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN SURVIVE
A FALL FROM THAT HEIGHT,
SO WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
Riehlvelt: CATCH ME! PLEASE!
DON'T LET ME DIE!
Killua: OKAY, THEN.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M RIGHT HERE FOR YOU.
( Riehlvelt screams )
( screams )
( stammering )
Killua: DAMN IT.
AT LEAST NOW YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
THAT HURTS, YOU IDIOT.
♪
Referee: RIEHLVELT IS DOWN,
AND SO BY VIRTUE OF A KNOCKDOWN,
KILLUA TAKES THE VICTORY!
( crowd cheering )
♪
( Killua gasps )
Gon: NICE JOB, KILLUA.
( chuckles )
Killua: HEH. THANKS.
THAT MEANS YOU'RE UP NEXT.
HOW LONG 'TIL YOU FIGHT HIM?
10 DAYS?
Gon: YUP.
IT'LL BE ON JUNE TENTH.
Killua: JUST REMEMBER
WHAT WORKED FOR ME
ISN'T GONNA WORK FOR YOU, OKAY?
IF THOSE ELECTRIC WHIPS
SO MUCH AS TOUCH YOU,
YOU'LL BE OUT COLD BEFORE YOU
EVEN KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING.
Gon: MM‐HMM.
Killua: WHAT'S YOUR STRATEGY?
Gon: OH, DON'T WORRY.
I THINK I HAVE AN IDEA.
Killua: OH?
YOU WEREN'T WATCHING
FOR NOTHING, WERE YOU?
GUESS YOU PREFER COMBAT
TO OBSERVING, TOO.
Hisoka: HMM.
( chuckles )
♪
Cocco: IT APPEARS THAT
THE DAMAGE GIDO SUSTAINED
IN HIS MATCH WITH GON
WAS SO SEVERE
THAT HE HASN'T RETURNED
FOR TODAY'S FIGHT.
Referee: THE WINNER
BY DEFAULT IS KILLUA!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: AFTER LOSING TO KILLUA,
RIEHLVELT'S RECORD
IS FIVE‐THREE.
HE CAN'T AFFORD ANOTHER LOSS.
AS YOU KNOW, AFTER FOUR LOSSES,
YOU'RE OUT OF THE CONTEST
AND HAVE TO START OVER
FROM SQUARE ONE.
HE MUST BE WARY OF GON'S SPEED,
BECAUSE HE'S GOT
HIS WHIPS OUT ALREADY.
MEANWHILE, GON ISN'T
CARRYING HIS FISHING ROD.
HE'S COMPLETELY EMPTY‐HANDED.
HOW DOES HE PLAN
TO FIGHT THIS TIME?
Referee: BEGIN!
Cocco: SONG OF DEFENSE
RIGHT FROM THE START!
RIEHLVELT WANTS TO END
THIS FIGHT IN A HURRY!
♪
( Gon grunting )
Cocco: WHAT'S THIS?
GON IS SQUATTING?
Riehlvelt: EH?
( Gon yells )
Cocco: HE JUST
RIPPED UP THE STONE TILE
WITH HIS BARE HANDS, FOLKS!
( Gon yells )
Cocco: AND NOW HE THREW IT!
Riehlvelt: AURA BURST!
Cocco: HE ESCAPED
IN THE NICK OF TIME!
Killua: HE LEFT HIM
A WAY OUT ON PURPOSE.
( Riehlvelt gasps )
Cocco: BUT GON
ANTICIPATED THAT MOVE,
AND HE'S ALREADY
ONE STEP AHEAD!
Hisoka: WHEN YOU'RE
TRYING TO ESCAPE,
EVERY FRACTION
OF A SECOND COUNTS,
AND WITHOUT TIME
TO CHANGE DIRECTION,
ALL YOU CAN DO
IS CONTINUE TO MOVE FORWARD.
AND ACCELERATING
AS QUICKLY AS THAT
WILL THROW YOU OFF BALANCE.
HIS ONLY OPTION AT THAT POINT
WAS TO STOP THE WHIPS.
THAT'S THE TIME TO MOVE IN.
( Gon laughs )
( popping )
( Riehlvelt screams )
( shuddering )
Gon: SO THIS IS THE SWITCH, HUH?
LET'S SEE.
I'LL JUST TURN IT UP TO THE MAX.
Riehlvelt: NO! STOP!
Gon: SWITCH IT...
‐ Riehlvelt: STOP IT!
‐ Gon: ON!
( silence )
JUST KIDDING.
( grunts )
Referee: RIEHLVELT IS DOWN.
THAT COUNTS AS A KNOCKOUT.
THE WIN GOES TO GON!
( crowd cheering )
Zushi: HEY, GON!
( Gon laughs )
♪
( Killua chuckles )
( Gon chuckles )
( clapping )
Hisoka: SPLENDID. JUST SPLENDID.
INCLUDING YOUR LAST TWO MATCHES,
YOU'VE MADE PROGRESS.
YOU'VE MADE THE GRADE,
SO SET THE TIME AND PLACE
OF YOUR CHOOSING.
I'LL TAKE YOU ON ANYTIME.
( Gon grunts )
♪
Narrator: THE STRENGTH THAT GON
DEMONSTRATED IN HIS MATCHES
DID NOT ESCAPE HISOKA UNNOTICED.
IT WON'T BE LONG NOW
BEFORE THEIR FIGHT BEGINS.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE
INTRODUCING COCCO.
SHE ANNOUNCES ALL
OF THE FIGHTS AT HEAVENS ARENA.
Killua: OH. YOU MEAN THE LADY
WHO'S ALWAYS TALKING, HUH?
Gon: I WONDER.
HOW MANY OF HER ARE THERE?
Killua: YOU THINK
THERE ARE MOR‐‐
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME, "THE TRUE PASS."
KILLUA, WHAT DOES "SO‐AND‐SO"
AND "SUCH‐AND‐SUCH" MEAN?
Killua: YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW?
IT MEANS SO‐AND‐SO
AND SUCH‐AND‐SUCH.