Narrator: TEN, THE ABILITY
TO ENVELOP YOUR BODY
IN A SHROUD OF NEN AURA,
MAKING IT TOUGHER AND
SLOWING THE EFFECTS OF AGING.
ZETSU, A TECHNIQUE
WHICH SHUTS OFF
YOUR FLOW OF NEN AURA,
EFFECTIVE FOR CONCEALING
YOUR PRESENCE
AND RECOVERING FROM FATIGUE.
REN, A TECHNIQUE FOR CREATING
AN ESPECIALLY STRONG NEN AURA.
IT IS CRUCIAL
FOR INCREASING YOUR POWER.
HATSU, THE RELEASE
OF YOUR NEN AURA
AFTER USING REN TO BOOST IT.
THESE FOUR ELEMENTS ARE KNOWN
AS THE FOUR EXERCISES
AND ARE CRITICAL
TO THE MASTERY OF NEN.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( Hisoka clapping )
SPLENDID. JUST SPLENDID.
INCLUDING YOUR LAST TWO MATCHES,
YOU'VE MADE PROGRESS.
YOU'VE MADE THE GRADE,
SO SET THE TIME AND PLACE
OF YOUR CHOOSING.
I'LL TAKE YOU ON ANYTIME.
Narrator: HISOKA FINALLY
CONSENTS TO A FIGHT WITH GON,
WHO PREPARES BY CONTINUING
TO TRAIN TIRELESSLY
IN THE USE OF NEN.
Wing: TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO BEGIN OUR STUDY OF HATSU.
ONCE YOU MASTER HATSU,
THEN YOU WILL HAVE MASTERED
ALL OF THE BASICS OF NEN.
AT THAT POINT IN YOUR EDUCATION,
YOU'LL NEED TO START DEVELOPING
YOUR OWN NEN STYLE.
All: OSU!
HATSU IS THE TECHNIQUE
BY WHICH YOU CONTROL YOUR AURA.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IT'S THE CULMINATION
OF NEN ABILITIES, OF WHICH
THERE ARE SIX CATEGORIES.
ENHANCERS STRENGTHEN AND
REINFORCE NATURAL ABILITIES.
EMITTERS PROPEL AURA.
TRANSMUTERS CHANGE
THE QUALITY OF AURA.
CONJURERS MATERIALIZE OBJECTS
OUT OF AURA.
MANIPULATORS
CONTROL THINGS WITH AURA.
AND SPECIALISTS ARE THOSE
WITH A UNIQUE AND DISTINCT AURA
THAT DOESN'T FALL
WITHIN THE OTHER FIVE CLASSES.
IT'S INCREDIBLY IMPORTANT
THAT YOU FIND AN ABILITY
THAT SUITS YOU.
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"SUITS YOU"?
Wing: NEN ABILITIES
ARE HIGHLY PERSONAL,
WITH TWO AREAS
OF PARTICULAR PROMINENCE...
THE ABILITY
THAT YOU'RE BORN WITH
AND OF COURSE THE ABILITY THAT
YOU'VE REFINED LATER IN LIFE.
FOR EXAMPLE, GON HERE
WAS BORN WITH MUSCLES
THAT ARE MORE FLEXIBLE
AND SPRINGY THAN MOST.
HIS ACUTE SENSES WERE HONED
BY A CHILDHOOD
SPENT MOSTLY IN NATURE.
SO YOU SEE,
FROM THE MOMENT OF BIRTH,
YOUR NEN ABILITY FALLS WITHIN
ONE OF THE SIX CATEGORIES.
IT'S POSSIBLE FOR YOUR NEN AURA
TO CHANGE TYPES LATER ON,
ALTHOUGH THAT'S QUITE RARE.
IF YOU ATTEMPT TO LEARN
A NEW ABILITY,
ONE THAT DOESN'T FIT
YOUR NATURAL AURA,
YOU WILL HAVE A HARD TIME.
THIS DEPICTS THE COMPATIBILITY
OF THE SIX CATEGORIES.
THE CLOSER A CLASS IS
TO YOUR OWN,
THE GREATER YOUR CHANCES
OF LEARNING IT.
IF YOU ARE BORN WITH AN AURA
OF THE ENHANCER CATEGORY
YOU WILL FIND ENHANCER ABILITIES
EASIEST TO LEARN AND MASTER.
THE ADJACENT TRANSMUTER
AND EMITTER CLASSES
WILL ALSO BE EASY TO PICK UP.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THE SPECIALIST CLASS
WHICH IS FURTHEST AWAY
WOULD UNDOUBTEDLY
PROVE QUITE DIFFICULT.
I'LL DEMONSTRATE USING SKILLS
YOU'VE ALREADY SEEN.
( chorus vocalizing )
HISOKA IS ABLE
TO CHANGE HIS AURA
INTO A RUBBER‐LIKE SUBSTANCE,
SO HE'S A TRANSMUTER.
GIDO USES HIS TOPS AS A WEAPON
BY MAKING THEM SPIN FASTER,
WHICH IS AN ENHANCER POWER.
BUT TRYING TO MANIPULATE
SO MANY TOPS AS WEAPONS
ALSO REQUIRES
THE SKILL OF A MANIPULATOR.
SINCE THAT ISN'T
VERY COMPATIBLE,
HE WASN'T VERY EFFECTIVE.
AS FOR KASTRO,
HIS TIGER BITE FIST
WAS INCREDIBLY STRONG.
HAD HE MASTERED IT,
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN AMONG
THE STRONGEST NEN USERS.
I BELIEVE THAT HIS AURA
FELL INTO THE ENHANCER CLASS.
HOWEVER, HE MADE THE CHOICE
TO FOCUS HIS ENERGY
ON THE POWER TO CREATE A DOUBLE,
WHICH IS A CONJURER ABILITY.
HE ALSO REQUIRED
THE ABILITY OF A MANIPULATOR
TO CONTROL THE DOUBLE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
BOTH OF THOSE
ARE RELATIVELY FAR
FROM THE ENHANCER CATEGORY.
Gon: SO NEITHER OF THEM
WAS COMPATIBLE
WITH AN ENHANCER TYPE?
CORRECT.
LEARNING AN INCOMPATIBLE ABILITY
REQUIRES A GREAT DEAL
OF WORK AND NATURAL TALENT.
AS A RESULT OF THE FOCUS
OF HIS TRAINING,
HE SQUANDERED MOST OF HIS TALENT
IN NEN ABILITY.
Killua: WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS
KASTRO MADE THE WRONG CHOICE.
Zushi: HE WAS SUCH
A GREAT FIGHTER. WHAT A SHAME.
Wing: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ARE YOU ALL BEGINNING TO SEE
THE IMPORTANCE
OF FULLY UNDERSTANDING YOUR OWN
AURA AS WELL AS ITS NATURE?
Gon and Zushi: OSU!
Killua: OKAY, SO IF YOU
DON'T KNOW YOUR AURA'S TYPE,
LIKE WHAT CATEGORY IT'S IN,
IS THERE A WAY TO FIND OUT?
Wing: THERE IS.
♪
WATER DIVINATION,
A SHINGEN‐RYU SCREENING TOOL
FOR CLASSIFYING AURA.
IT'S ALSO USED
IN TRAINING HATSU.
PERFORM REN
WITH YOUR HANDS PLACED
ON EITHER SIDE OF THE GLASS.
YOUR ABILITY WILL BE
REVEALED BY WHAT HAPPENS.
( all gasp )
Gon: THE WATER'S OVERFLOWING.
Wing: IF THE VOLUME
OF WATER CHANGES,
THEN YOU'RE AN ENHANCER.
THIS CHANGE DEMONSTRATES
THAT MY AURA
FALLS WITHIN
THE ENHANCER CATEGORY.
OKAY. NOW IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO TRY.
( Gon and Zushi gasp )
Killua: SO GON'S
AN ENHANCER, TOO?
Killua: HMM?
Zushi: THE LEAF MOVED!
Wing: THAT MOVEMENT INDICATES
THAT YOU'RE A MANIPULATOR.
Zushi: AH.
Killua: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
THAT JUST LEAVES ME.
( groans )
WHAT GIVES? NOTHING'S HAPPENING.
Wing: INDEED.
Gon: THE LEAF
ISN'T MOVING EITHER.
Killua: DOES THAT MEAN
I DON'T HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?
Wing: OH, NO.
TRY TASTING THE WATER, KILLUA.
Killua: TASTE IT?
HEY, I THINK IT MIGHT
HAVE GOTTEN SWEETER.
Gon: YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT!
Zushi: THAT'S TRUE.
IT DOES TASTE SWEET.
Gon: WAIT.
THEN THIS ISN'T PLAIN WATER?
Wing: PERFECTLY ORDINARY.
ONLY THE TASTE OF IT
HAS CHANGED
DUE TO KILLUA'S AURA.
Killua: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Wing: IT MEANS
YOU'RE A TRANSMUTER.
‐ Killua: AH?
‐ Gon: AH.
Zushi: YOU'RE A TRANSMUTER?
Wing: OKAY,
NOW THE THREE OF YOU KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT KIND OF AURA
YOU'RE WORKING WITH.
FOR THE NEXT FOUR WEEKS,
I WANT YOU THREE TO TRAIN
UNTIL YOU CAN MAKE A MORE
PRONOUNCED CHANGE IN THE WATER.
Boys: OSU!
♪
( telephone ringing )
HELLO. THIS IS GON.
Hisoka: HEY, I'VE BEEN WAITING.
SO, HAVE YOU MADE A DECISION?
Gon: YEAH. JULY 10th.
THAT'S THE DAY I'VE CHOSEN.
( Hisoka chuckles )
OKAY.
I'LL BE LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
( overlapping chatter )
♪
Wing: OKAY. TIME TO SEE
WHAT YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED
WITH YOUR TRAINING.
KILLUA, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
Killua: ALL RIGHT.
♪
I'M DONE.
Wing: AH!
Zushi: SO SWEET!
Gon: YOU'RE RIGHT!
IT TASTES LIKE HONEY!
Wing: EXCELLENT.
AND ZUSHI?
Zushi: OSU!
( Zushi grunting )
( Gon gasps ) WHOA!
( Zushi gasps )
THAT'S THE BEST I CAN DO.
Wing: THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT ISN'T
GOING TO BE ENOUGH TO PASS.
I'M AFRAID YOU'LL NEED
TO TRAIN A BIT MORE.
Zushi: OSU.
Wing: NEXT, GON.
Gon: OSU!
( deep breath )
( both gasp )
Wing: STOP! GON, STOP!
( thinking ) THE WATER
INCREASED SO FORCEFULLY,
IT CRACKED THE GLASS.
HONESTLY...
( aloud ) I'M IMPRESSED.
( Gon chuckles ) I WAS FEELING
PRETTY GOOD ABOUT THIS.
Wing: ALL RIGHT, GON, KILLUA,
TODAY YOU ARE BOTH GRADUATING.
‐ ( Gon gasps )
‐ Killua: REALLY?
Gon: WE DID IT, KILLUA!
Killua: THAT'S AWESOME.
Zushi: MASTER,
DO I GRADUATE, TOO?
Wing: YOU STILL NEED TO TRAIN
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
Zushi: OSU.
Killua: JUST KEEP AT IT.
Gon: YEAH. YOU'LL GET IT!
Zushi: OSU.
Wing: AND, GON...
I'VE ONE MORE THING FOR YOU,
SOMETHING IMPORTANT
I STILL NEED TO SAY.
WHAT IS IT, MR. WING?
THE OTHER HUNTER EXAM,
YOU'VE PASSED IT, GON FREECSS.
( Gon gasps )
HMM?
Wing: CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU MADE IT.
Gon: THE OTHER HUNTER EXAM?
Wing: THAT'S CORRECT. YOU WERE
ABLE TO PASS WITH FLYING COLORS.
Gon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SIR?
Wing: ONE CANNOT BE
A FULL‐FLEDGED HUNTER
WITHOUT LEARNING HOW TO USE NEN.
SUCH SKILL AND POWER
ARE REQUIREMENTS
OF A TERRIBLY
DANGEROUS PROFESSION.
ONE OF YOUR DUTIES AS A HUNTER
WILL BE ATTEMPTING TO APPREHEND
EVIL POACHERS
AND OTHER SUCH CRIMINALS.
YOU MUST BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO FIGHT CRIME
IF YOU ARE TO BE
A TRUE DETERRENT.
BUT THIS POWER IS HIGHLY
DESTRUCTIVE WHEN ABUSED.
REVEALING THE EXISTENCE OF NEN
DURING THE EXAM
WOULD BE QUITE RISKY.
THEREFORE ONLY THOSE
WHO HAVE ALREADY PASSED
THE MAIN EXAM ARE TESTED.
Killua: OH, I GET IT.
YOU WOULD HAVE TESTED US,
GON, AT LEAST,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENED,
WOULDN'T YOU?
Wing: YES.
I SHOULD ALSO HAVE MENTIONED
THAT THE GRAND MASTER
OF SHINGEN‐RYU
HAPPENS TO BE CHAIRMAN NETERO.
‐ ( gong reverberates )
‐ ( both gasp )
Wing: THE MASTER HAS TOLD ME
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
Killua: THAT GOOFY OLD MAN?
‐ Wing: KILLUA.
‐ Killua: WHAT?
Wing: I WANT YOU TO GO BACK
AND TAKE THE HUNTER EXAM AGAIN.
YOU'LL DEFINITELY PASS
NEXT TIME.
Gon: HE'S RIGHT!
Wing: AT THIS POINT, YOU ARE
MORE THAN QUALIFIED ENOUGH.
THAT, I CAN GUARANTEE.
Killua: WELL...
IF I FEEL UP TO IT.
Gon: HEY, MR. WING,
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING
ABOUT THE OTHER PEOPLE
WHO PASSED?
Wing: I HAVE.
♪
HANZO AND KURAPIKA
HAVE LEARNED NEN
FROM OTHER TEACHERS.
POKKLE, ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS STRUGGLING WITH REN.
LEORIO HAS BEGUN STUDYING
FOR THE MEDICAL SCHOOL EXAM.
HISOKA AND ILLUMI WERE ALREADY
WELL‐VERSED IN THE USE OF NEN,
SO THEY WERE QUALIFIED,
OF COURSE.
Gon: SO KURAPIKA AND LEORIO
ARE WORKING HARD!
Killua: YEAH.
Wing: THAT'S NOT ALL, GON.
I HAVE ONE BIT OF ADVICE.
WHEN YOU FIGHT HISOKA TOMORROW,
DON'T PUSH YOURSELF TOO HARD.
ALL RIGHT?
Gon: RIGHT!
♪
Wing: ZUSHI, YOU WILL
CONTINUE YOUR TRAINING
FOR FOUR MORE WEEKS.
Zushi: OSU.
Wing: HAVE MORE CONFIDENCE.
( Zushi gasps )
Wing: YOU'RE REALLY PROGRESSING
AT AN INCREDIBLE PACE.
YOU'RE ONE IN 100,000.
Zushi: WAIT.
I'M ONE IN A 100,000?!
OSU!
Wing: THOSE TWO, HOWEVER,
ARE EVEN RARER TALENTS,
PERHAPS ONE IN 10 MILLION.
Zushi: OSU!
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MAKE ME
FEEL BETTER, MASTER?
BUT...
ONE DAY, I'M GONNA CATCH UP
TO BOTH OF THEM!
( Wing chuckles )
Cocco: HELLO, EVERYONE!
IN THE ARENA TODAY,
WE HAVE A MATCH
BETWEEN GON AND HISOKA!
THE BATTLE YOU'VE ALL BEEN
WAITING FOR IS ABOUT TO BEGIN,
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE STANDS ARE PACKED!
THE FIGHT HASN'T EVEN STARTED,
AND THE TENSION IN THE AIR
IS PALPABLE!
Man: HOW MUCH LONGER?
Man #2: COME ON! LET'S GO!
( joints pop )
( Gon grunts )
( crowd roars )
♪
Cocco: THE FIRST
TO ARRIVE IS GON!
AFTER FOUR FIGHTS,
HE HAS A THREE‐ONE RECORD.
HE'S REALLY ON A ROLL!
Man #3: YOU CAN DO IT, GON!
Man #4: HEY,
WHERE'S YOUR FISHING ROD?
YOU CAN'T CATCH HISOKA
WITH YOUR BARE HANDS!
Cocco: AND NEXT, ARRIVING IN
THE ARENA WITH A FIERY DISPLAY
IS HISOKA!
( crowd cheering )
Cocco: THE MEMORIES
OF HIS LETHAL BATTLE WITH KASTRO
ARE STILL FRESH
IN EVERYONE'S MINDS!
A NINE‐THREE RECORD
MEANS A WIN TODAY
EARNS HIM THE RIGHT
TO CHALLENGE A FLOOR MASTER!
HE'S WON EVERY SINGLE MATCH
HE'S ACTUALLY SHOWED UP FOR.
WILL HIS UNDEFEATED STREAK
CONTINUE?
♪
( crowd roars )
Hisoka: OH,
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
IT'S REALLY TURNING ME ON,
Wing:
WHAT A SINISTER AURA HE HAS.
GON, DON'T OVERDO IT.
( crowd gasps )
Referee: YOU WIN
BY POINTS OR KNOCKOUT.
NO TIME LIMIT!
ONE ROUND!
BEGIN!
Cocco: THIS IS THE MATCH
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR, FOLKS!
THE DIE HAS BEEN CAST!
WHO WILL MAKE THE FIRST MOVE?
IT'S GON!
‐ ( Cocco gasps )
‐ ( crowd roars )
( Gon yells )
Referee: A CLEAN HIT!
HISOKA, ONE POINT!
( crowd cheers )
Cocco: THAT WAS
AN AMAZING EXCHANGE,
SO AMAZING THAT I COULD
BARELY GET A WORD IN EDGEWISE.
( Gon grunts )
( Hisoka chuckles )
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I HAVEN'T MOVED A SINGLE STEP
FROM WHERE I STARTED.
Gon: WHAT? REALLY?!
( groans )
DAMN IT! WELL, JUST YOU WAIT!
OKAY. I SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO CONNECT EACH HIT.
I CAN MIX IN SOME FEINTS
TO GET THE SAME EFFECT.
Killua: HISOKA LOOKS
LIKE HE'S HAVING FUN.
IN TERMS OF ACTUAL SKILL,
THERE'S A WORLD OF DIFFERENCE
IN THEIR COMBAT EXPERIENCE,
BUT HE STILL HAS A WEAKNESS.
HISOKA THINKS HE'S STRONGER,
SO THERE'S NO WAY
HE'LL EVER BACK DOWN.
THAT'LL GIVE GON A CHANCE.
Gon: FINE.
I KNOW JUST THE TRICK.
( Gon growls )
( Gon yells )
Cocco: THERE IT IS,
GON'S STONE FLIP!
( Gon yells )
Hisoka: HE SHATTERED THE TILE
TO CREATE A HAIL OF RUBBLE.
GON...
WHERE IS HE?
♪
( gasps )
( all audio stops )
♪
Narrator: GON HAS FINALLY LANDED
A CRITICAL HIT ON HISOKA,
BUT THE MATCH
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN,
AND IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE GON
EXPERIENCES HISOKA'S TRUE POWER.
( singing in Japanese )
Gon: COMING UP, GON...
Killua: AND KILLUA'S...
Both: HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: I'M GON.
Killua: I'M KILLUA.
Both: AND THIS IS
OUR HUNTERPEDIA!
Gon: TODAY WE'RE
INTRODUCING HISOKA.
HE REELS IN OPPONENTS WITH
RUBBERY NEN CALLED BUNGEE GUM.
Killua: AND HE USES
TEXTURE SURPRISE
TO DUPLICATE OTHER OBJECTS.
Both: SHWEEN!
♪
Gon: NEXT TIME,
"A BIG DEBT AND A SMALL KICK."
Killua: GO, GON! GO!
Gon: GON SHOT!