[SUBARU]
Good! And finally...
Victory!
[VILLAGERS]
[VILLAGERS laughing]
[SUBARU]
All right! Line up, everyone!
[KIDS laughing]
It's time to
collect your stamps!
Okay, then, who's first?
The kitty's so cute!
The kitty's awesome!
The kitty's so sad!
[EMILIA] The villagers seem to
be happy and full of life again.
Thanks to you, Subaru.
[SUBARU chuckles]
Well, what can I say, you know?
I mean I did kinda
put my neck on the line
to rescue them.
I went into the forest
and got bitten by dogs
to save the kids...
I got bitten by dogs
when I tried to save Rem
after she turned into a demon,
then I had to be
saved by Roswaal
when I was about to be
bitten by a giant dog...
Wait.
Did I really even do
that much of anything?
You're obsessing too much
over trivial details.
Stop worrying!
There are those
who know the truth
about what you went through.
That includes Roswaal and Ram...
And especially Rem.
And, don't forget...
I know everything that
you went through, as well.
[SUBARU]
A dragon-drawn carriage?
[WILHELM]
Welcome home, my lady.
I offer my most humble apologies
for parking in front
of your mansion.
[SUBARU]
Hm?
[RAM] An emissary from the
capital is here visiting us.
Lord Roswaal is
attending to them now.
Please join him, Miss Emilia.
An emissary?
I believe it concerns
the royal selection.
All right.
I know this is important,
so I'll be on my best behavior.
I know I'm a goof, but...
Well, uh, sorry,
but this is really important.
I think it would be best if
you remained behind, okay?
[SUBARU chuckles]
Aren't you bored
waiting out here
all by yourself?
It tastes lovely.
Drinking it feels as
though I'm indulging
in a great luxury.
To be honest, it's the most
expensive tea in the mansion.
If the pink-haired
maid discovers
that we drank it
without permission,
she'll totally freak.
[WILHELM]
I see...
And what exactly
is it you hope to gain
from this old man using
such precious bait?
I only wanna know the reason
for this visit, that's all.
If you could maybe just
give me a vague idea...
As I'm unsure as to
what your standing
or status is in this mansion,
it's in my best interest not
to say anything careless
about our dealings here.
Please understand.
[SUBARU groans]
That being said, however,
I did notice that you
seem to be quite close
to Miss Emilia.
Oh, yeah?!
Did it look like
things were serious
between Mee-Lee and me?!
[giggling]
"Mee-Lee"?
A steep path you're
choosing to climb...
Need I remind you
that you're dealing with
one who may be the
future queen of Lugunica?
"Future" is the key word there.
Right now, we're just
a super cute girl
and a useless servant boy.
You probably think your
wife is the prettiest girl
in the whole wide world,
am I right?
I mean, isn't that what
you thought the day
that you got down on one
knee and proposed to her?
My wife, huh?
Why, yes, of course.
Indeed, you're
absolutely correct.
I believed my wife was
the most beautiful lady
in the entire world.
[FELIX]
I'm back, Old Man Wil!
Sorry to make
you wait outside.
I bet you were bored, huh?
Not at all.
In fact, I've been
passing the time
having a rather
interesting discussion
with this young man here.
Hm-mew?
Hm-mew mew... huh?
Hm-mew.
Ah, nyow I see.
Of course, of course!
You must be the boy
that Miss Emilia
was talking about earlier.
She mentioned me?
Wow, looks like you're
totally clueless, aren't you?
Let's go, Old Man Wil.
See you in the capital.
Listen, we're not going
there for fun, okay?
I received an important
summons that--
[SUBARU] If it's important,
all the more reason!
You're in a battle
for the throne, right?
I wanna be there and help
you in any way that I can!
Pretty please!
Based on prior discussions,
it seems there are several
people in the capital
who helped Subaru.
This may be a good opportunity
for him to thank them.
Very nice assist, Rem!
She's right, you know!
Some people in the capital
were a big help to me.
So, I need to let them
know that I'm alive and well.
Ooh, why not let him?
That can be kept separate from
our royal selection business.
Subaru should go to the
capital to thank everyone,
as well as receive treatment.
This trip would be an
opportunity for both.
Huh? Treatment?
You overused your
already-exhausted gate
in the mabeast battle
out in the forest.
Your wound will need treatment.
I believe that you met
the emissary earlier,
did you not?
Do you mean the cutesy-face
with the cat ears?
That "cutesy-face with cat ears"
was one of the capital's most
brilliant users of water magic,
as well as healing magic.
Felix is a peculiar one, whose
cooperation was difficult
even for Miss Emilia to enlist.
Wait a minute!
Is he for real, Mee-Lee?
You did that for me?
[EMILIA]
W-Well, it's partly my fault
that you haven't healed yet.
So you could say
I'm repaying a debt.
I consider this as
equal compensation
for what you went
through to help!
I just wanna
make things right!
[FELIX] I must admit, I was
surprised to see you talking
with that boy.
I always thought you'd
rather chop people in half
than talk to them.
That's a grave misunderstanding.
I merely took a bit of a
liking to what I saw there
in that young man's eyes.
[FELIX]
Hm?
[WILHELM] Those are the
eyes of one who has been
at death's door... many times.
[FELIX]
Huh...
Nyow you've lost me.
Either way...
If Wilhelm van Astrea,
the Sword Demon,
says something like that,
then I'm sure the boy faces
quite a bumpy road ahead.
[SUBARU]
Hey, uh... Mee-Lee...
Maybe we should
stop doing this...?
No way! Absolutely not!
'Cause I know how
your mind works.
The first moment I look away,
you'll be off doing
something crazy.
Oh, man! I can't believe
we're doing this!
I'm seriously moved!
I'm totally living out
a fantasy right now, baby!
Subaru is so cute.
Parallel worlds rule!
[yelling]
[EMILIA]
Subaru!
Look, I'm really
sorry about all that...
But this chaperoning makes
me feel like I'm a little kid!
Yet on our "date"
in the village,
you were the one who
wanted to hold hands
so desperately.
[SUBARU] Because I was
physically and mentally
prepared for it then.
This time, I'm not!
My hand is sweating like crazy!
[KADOMON]
Come on!
Would you two cut out
the flirting already?
All that nonsense
is gonna drive away
my customers.
After I came to make
good on my promise to you?
That's pretty cold, man.
Just giving you a hard time.
I appreciate you felt
obligated to shop here
now that you're
not broke anymore.
Here you go!
The appas I promised.
[SUBARU] Next will be
Felt and Old Man Rom.
[EMILIA] I assumed we'd
wrapped everything up
rather neatly without
blame the first time.
But, then, right at the end...
Reinhart's expression went dark
and he took the girl away.
When you say it like that,
it sounds like kidnapping,
or an abduction
and confinement...
Hot guys have
really got it good.
[EMILIA] If we want
to contact Reinhard...
...then we should probably
go to the guard station
that's in front of the
noblemen's district.
Uh, hey, Mee-Lee...
I wanted to ask you
about the royal selection
--that starts up tomorrow...
--[EMILIA] Don't start, Subaru.
We discussed this thoroughly
before going on
this trip together
and I thought you understood.
I brought you out here
to fulfill your promises
and to get you healed.
You don't have to
worry about me, okay?
[JULIUS]
Well, if it isn't Miss Emilia.
Good to see you again.
I hope that you've been
well since we last met?
Yes, everything's
basically the same.
And you also seem well, Julius.
[JULIUS] The mere fact
that you remember me
is an honor.
And I must say,
you have only grown more
beautiful, Miss Emilia.
[SUBARU yelling]
You're very kind.
Forgive me for
asking so abruptly,
but I have business here,
and I'd like you
to act as my agent
while I'm in the castle.
Is that so?
Does your business involve
this young man?
Heh. His attitude is
ill-matched with his attire.
That's no way
to conduct yourself
before one you've just met...
Thanks a bunch for the warning!
And while we're on the subject,
I've got a warning for you, too.
You shouldn't eat
curry udon in that suit.
If the soup splatters, the
stains will really stand out.
I have no idea what
this "curry udon" is
but I'll certainly
keep that in mind.
Now, allow me to show you
to the conference mirrors.
So what's he talking about?
They're a type of
metia that allows you
to have a discussion with
someone through two mirrors
facing each other.
[SUBARU]
Ah. Cool magic stuff?
--Well, then...
--[EMILIA] Subaru, wait here.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
I don't think it would
be a pleasant experience
for you.
[SUBARU] Oh, I've already
had an experience
that wasn't pleasant.
That bastard,
taking your cute little hand
and licking all
over it like a dog.
I'll try to come back
before things run too long.
Be good, please.
Stay here, okay?
Jeez, I look so
pathetic right now.
Bold thing to do in front
of the guard station...
"It's darkest at the foot
of the lighthouse," I guess.
You little...
[CHIN]
Don't screw around with us!
[KAN] You wouldn't want
us to mess up that pretty face
of yours, would ya?
Don't make such a racket,
you commoners.
Fools with no character
at all pick fights
for the most absurd reasons.
[SUBARU] Hey, honey!
Sorry I'm late!
It looks like there's
been a bit of trouble
in my absence,
but remember who I am
and cut me some slack. Okay?
Come on, let's go.
Get your hands off me,
you filthy pleb!
[SUBARU]
Cliffhanger...
I don't want
drooling commoners
following me around.
Of all the nerve...
[SUBARU]
Figure out what's going on here!
It was supposed to be
the classic scenario
where I save a girl
from hoodlums!
[SUBARU]
Wait...
No way.
Are the three of you the only
hoodlums in the capital?
It's the guy from behind
the shopping district.
The brat from the alleyway?
The very same!
So for my sake,
could you just--
Are you dumb? Forget it!
This just makes it three on two
instead of three on one.
[PRISCILLA]
Correction...
It isn't three on two;
it's more like three
on one on one.
Oh, would you be quiet
for just a second?!
I have no choice.
This is the last trick
I wanted to use, but...
Just so you know,
I happen to be good friends
with Reinhard.
If I call for him,
he'll come running as fast
as he possibly can!
[SUBARU] Secret Technique:
Fox in Tiger's Clothing!
[ROM] Hm? It's been a while
since I've seen you
around these parts.
What brings you back
to this neck of the woods?
Old Man Rom!
[CHIN, TON, KAN]
Damn you! We won't forget this!
[SUBARU sighs]
Thanks a lot. You saved me.
I seriously doubt
that either one of us
could've handled those
three thugs on our own.
Speak for yourself.
Whether either of
you had stepped in
to interfere or not,
I was never in the
least bit of danger.
You're kidding, right?
"I didn't need your
help, understand?
I'm a super strong,
fiery, independent woman!
I was doing just
fine on my own!"
Something like that?
No.
This world is designed
to operate in the way
that works best for me,
so I'm never
disadvantaged whatsoever.
Whoa. R-Really?
Well, I guess I shouldn't
have butted in, then.
Sorry to interfere.
Oh, by the way, boy...
Is there any chance ya
know where Felt went off to?
Wait a minute, you mean you
didn't hear about what happened?
Apparently, Reinhard
took her away.
Now, why would he do that?
Well, don't that beat all.
Had to be an Astrea, huh...
[SUBARU]
Something wrong?
Nah, nah, I'm just
talkin' to myself.
Now you try not to
cause any more trouble
around these parts, y'hear?
[SUBARU]
S-Sure.
[EMILIA]
There you are!
Oh! Hey, Mee-Lee...
Wait, wait, wait!
You can't just go
and hit on Mee-Lee
while I'm away, you jerk!
[AL] Looks like your buddy's
got a screw loose, little lady.
He's more worried about
losing you to another guy
than happy to see you.
A man's heart is so complex,
it's a thrill to watch.
You've got a pretty
messed-up fashion sense,
don't ya, Mister Helmet?
[AL] Now, that's no way
to talk to someone.
I can overlook that since
I'm a cool, good-natured man,
but some might lop off
your head for that.
Easy! Relax, Subaru.
I admit, when I first saw him,
his outfit surprised
me a little, too.
[AL]
Yeah, well...
I was surprised when
she asked for my help
while I was looking
for a lost child.
So there's that.
You're way too
soft-hearted and trusting.
Most people would
think that a guy
dressed like this who's
looking for a lost child
is gonna kidnap them.
[PRISCILLA]
My, my...
How very attentive
of you to wait
where you knew I would be.
I commend you
for your dedication, Al.
[SUBARU] You mean you
were the lost child?!
Well, what do you know!
It looks like we both found
just who we were lookin' for.
--Let's go.
--[PRISCILLA] Just a moment.
Would you mind telling me
what you have in that bag?
These are appas.
Haven't you ever
seen one before?
Please, don't make me laugh.
Everyone knows appas
have white flesh.
Well, I mean, yeah,
the insides are white, but...
Hang on, are you trying
to tell me you've never seen
an unpeeled appa?
Here ya go.
Now, don't go skipping
off after any obvious
bad guys again, okay?
[EMILIA]
Subaru...
That girl from before...
[SUBARU]
Huh?
I was wondering
where you happen
to have met her, and how.
Huh? What's this?
Are you jealous, Mee-Lee?
I can't believe
you're actually feeling
that way over me, or...?
[EMILIA]
Subaru...
Mee-Lee.
What's with the serious face?
It's freaking me out a little...
Uh, nothing.
If you don't know, it's fine.
Forget about it.
Oh, wow! I guess this
thing really is an appa!
[SUBARU] What?
I have to stay here tomorrow?!
Yes, of course you do.
That was our agreement
from the very beginning.
Well, that was the plan,
but we never got in touch
with Reinhard, right?
If we go to the castle
together tomorrow,
we might run into him...
There's no need.
I'll be sure to ask about Felt.
I really think
I should go in person to--
[EMILIA] This is the reason
I can't take you with me.
If I allow you to do so,
you'll just push yourself
too hard again.
I don't want to
let you do that.
Understand?
I hear what you're saying,
but you're the one
who doesn't understand!
If I have to push
myself to help you,
then I'll do it without
a second thought.
I've gotta at least try!
Absolutely not.
Until your body fully heals,
there is to be no using
magic or pushing yourself!
I want you to promise, okay?
Okay, you win. I promise you.
I won't use magic.
Either way...
Let me go with you!
[EMILIA] I can't bring
an outsider into this.
So please, just wait here
with Rem until it's over.
All right?
I'm asking you, Subaru.
Give me reason to trust you.
[SUBARU] I know there
are those in the capital
who consider Emilia an enemy.
That's exactly why
I have to stay close to her.
[REM]
What's the matter?
I'm going to save Emilia.
[REM]
Huh?
And to do that...
[REM]
Huh...
[SUBARU]
Stare...
Wh-What is it, Subaru?
It makes me feel uncomfortable
when you stare at me
with such imposing eyes...
[SUBARU]
Stare...
[REM sighs]
It's at the castle.
Although, most likely,
there'll be heavy security.
[SUBARU]
Security isn't the problem.
I can't stand not being involved
in Emilia's important affairs.
I know, but...
When it comes down to it,
I'm only of any use
when something happens.
I want to be with her at a time
when she may need me the most!
[REM] I'm going to set
about making a brand new
appa recipe that
I just came up with
this very moment.
What?
And this culinary
adventure requires
intense concentration,
so if someone were
to leave his room,
I most likely wouldn't notice.
[SUBARU] I'm such a scumbag
for relying on Rem all the time.
[SUBARU] But now the problem
is how I'm gonna get
into the castle.
[SUBARU] I guess times
like these call for...
...hitchhiking!
[AL]
You sure are lucky, bro.
Be grateful for
this coincidence.
We just happened to be
on our way to the castle, too.
[SUBARU]
You are? Why's that?
[PRISCILLA]
What do you mean?
Today, there's only one
reason to head to the castle.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[AL]
Oh, you didn't know?
The young lady who's
seated before you
is one of the candidates
to succeed to the throne
of Lugunica,
Priscilla Barielle herself.
Whoa, seriously?
So why did you pick me up?
[PRISCILLA] For no other reason
than it seemed amusing.
A mere lark, nothing more.
I simply have a feeling
that taking you in there
will make things
a bit more interesting.
Why do you think that?
[PRISCILLA] This world
is designed to operate
in the way that
works best for me.
So with every choice I make,
it's a given that all
things will be in my favor.
In the end, it's only
a matter of choosing
whether something
amuses me or not.
[PRISCILLA] However,
if I had to name a reason
other than amusement...
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[MARCOS] Did you say,
"your appa handler"?
[PRISCILLA]
Indeed.
He's something of a wretched
clown whose sole priority
is to bring me bittersweet
appas whenever I fancy one.
[MARCOS]
Hmm.
Everyone is waiting inside.
So please make haste.
As their superior,
I like to keep
the masses waiting.
[EMILIA gasps]
Subaru?
Emilia.
I can explain, uh...
[PRISCILLA giggles]
Is there a reason you're
staring at my manservant?
It's rude to gawk, you half-wit.
[SUBARU]
Get off!
You'll give Mee-Lee
the wrong idea!
[ROSWAAL] My, how nice
to see you, Miss Priscilla!
I do hope you'll
forgive my servant
for troubling you so.
[PRISCILLA]
Hmph.
What in the world are
you doing here, Subaru?
Thought I told you, you were
supposed to wait for me.
You remember that, don't you?
[MARCOS]
Attention...
The council of wise
men will now enter.
So that's the council
of wise men, huh?
If I remember correctly,
they're the people
managing the country
in the king's absence,
aren't they?
[AL]
Hey.
That's where we're
supposed to stand.
You mean I can stand there, too?
Well, what do we have here?
I find this situation amusing,
so you may accompany him.
Wait, Roswaal!
If Subaru's allowed
to stay here,
I'm sure that he'll--!
Miss Emilia,
the conference is beginning now.
We can't make them wait.
Move to the center, but
you're going to explain this
to me later!
[SUBARU]
So those are the participants
in the royal selection...
Guess one of them
will be the future ruler
of this country...
So you decided to
come after all, Subaru.
When I heard through the
grapevine that Miss Emilia
would be here, I had
a rather strong suspicion
that you would be here, as well.
Hey, Reinhard!
I've been looking for you!
[FELIX]
Oh, how's it goin'?
You, too?!
[FELIX]
Nyaa-haha!
[REINHARD]
Oh, Subaru...
You know him, I take it?
Huh? Know "him"?
That's right.
He's a knight by the
name of Felix Argyle.
And, despite all appearances,
he is male.
You're kidding!
What's the point
in looking like that
and even having cat ears
if you're a guy?!
I don't knyow what to tell you.
You're the one who made
the wrong assumption,
silly Subaru.
[SUBARU growls]
Hey, Subaru,
what's the matter?
Where I come from,
this is the kind of face
you make whenever
you run into a guy
who's a romantic rival!
Now, if I may be so forward,
I, Marcos, leader
of the Imperial Knights,
will act as the director
for all of today's proceedings.
It all happened about
half a year ago,
when members
of the royal family,
starting with the king,
went into hiding
one by one, causing--
[ANASTASIA]
Listen...
I get that you wanna
talk things up
and put on a good show here...
But I'm kind of busy, y'know.
You may not have heard it,
but we have a saying
back in Kararagi:
"Time is money."
That attitude seems familiar,
but I can't place it.
[AL] Evidently, everybody
who's in western Kararagi
acts like that.
I couldn't agree more.
[MARCOS]
Miss Crusch,
should the head of the Karsten
family say such a thing?
I acknowledge it's important
to observe formality,
but it is also a fact that
our time is rather limited.
So, it would be wise to
immediately inform us
as to why we're here.
Naturally, however,
I do have a general idea.
Am I to understand
you already know
the purpose of
this meeting, then?
Yes, I do, Lord Miklotov.
For a drinking party.
One day soon,
we'll face each other as rivals,
but by sharing drinks and
conversing at the same table,
we'll have a chance to learn
more about one another.
No, ma'am.
That is not correct.
Felix, this is not what
you told me earlier.
What? That's not true!
All I said was, "Maybe it'll
be a drinking party."
I never said I knew it
for a fact or anything.
I see.
Then I jumped to conclusions.
Forgive me.
Please allow me to retract
everything I just said.
Now just a second!
Even if she backs down,
my opinion on this
isn't gonna change.
There's no need to explain
the royal selection process now.
We already know how it works.
Am I right?
Well...
Even so, I think maybe
we should hear the--
Sorry, but I don't
remember asking
for your opinion
on any of this business.
--Why, you little--
--[AL] Hey!
[AL] I-I don't know what's up
with the royal selection,
so I'd kinda like
to hear the rest.
Excuse me, but I was informed
that this young man is
your knight, Miss Priscilla.
Haven't you explained
the selection to him?
Whether I have or not
holds no merit.
You men will still ramble
on about it, won't you?
Please continue, Marcos.
As you wish.
There's a specific reason
we've gathered you
who are qualified to be
the dragon's priestess.
A new prophecy has been engraved
in the Dragon Stone.
This new insight says,
"From the five capable
of becoming
the nation's new leader,
choose one priestess
to enter into a covenant
with the dragon."
Wait, five?
[REINHARD]
That's right.
At the moment, there are
only four candidates
for the honor.
And the royal selection
hasn't even begun as of yet.
But today, history
will be set in motion.
[MARCOS]
Knight Reinhard van Astrea,
come forward.
[REINHARD]
Yes, sir.
[REINHARD] Honored members
of the council of wise men...
Imperial Knight,
Reinhard van Astrea,
would like to announce the
completion of my mission.
The fifth contender,
the final candidate
mentioned in the prophecy...
...has been located.
[REINHARD] The one I,
myself, revere as queen...
Her name...
...is Miss Felt!