[GIRL]
I'm glad you're here.
You won't get away this time.
[SUBARU]
What? Why is she here?
It's still light out.
Wait, is this how early
she would've arrived
if she hadn't been with me?
What is wrong with you?
Don't you know when to quit?
I'm telling you,
let it go already!
I'm sorry, but this is something
I simply cannot give up on.
If you do as I say and
cooperate, I won't hurt you.
I have but one request to make
of you: Return what is mine.
My insignia's very
important to me...
Whoa.
If she were just another
run-of-the-mill magic user,
I wouldn't back down,
but this one's trouble.
What's your problem?
You're admitting defeat
before we even start fighting?
Young lady, so, uh,
you're an elf, right?
Not exactly.
Technically speaking,
I'm only a half-elf.
Wait, seriously?
Your hair. It's silver!
Are you the--?!
It's an accidental resemblance!
And to be honest, it causes
me a lot of trouble.
I should've known better.
You set me up, didn't you?
[SUBARU]
Huh? No, I didn't do anything.
All that "I'm gonna return
it to its owner" crap?
That just made you
more suspicious!
What do you mean?
Are you saying that you two
aren't working together?
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Her nature never changes,
no matter how many times
I start over in this world.
[FELT] Hey, jerk! What
are you smirking about?!
Come on, hasn't
this been enough?
Give her insignia back already.
And you, Sat-- Hurry up
and get out of here.
And try not to let anyone
steal it again, okay?
Why are you being so nice
to me all of a sudden?
Honestly, nothing you're doing
is making any sense at all.
[FELT]
I don't understand you, either!
What's goin' on? Did you hit
your head or somethin'?
Puck, quick! Shield her!
That was fast thinking.
Cutting it a bit closer
than I expected.
You saved us!
Nice one, Puck!
Thank goodness it
was before five,
while you're still on duty!
Thanks, you're the best!
[ELSA] Well, well.
That's a spirit, isn't it?
[ELSA laughs]
[ELSA]
How wonderful.
I've never had the
pleasure of cutting open
a spirit's stomach before.
Hey, now what do
you mean by that?
We can't really
enter negotiations
if the item's original
owner is here now, can we?
And because of that,
I've changed my plans.
I'm going to slaughter
every last one of you.
You failed to see your job
all the way through to the end.
You certainly talk a good game,
but honestly,
you do terrible work.
I was hoping you were more
than just another slum dweller.
[SUBARU]
You bitch...
Cut the crap!
What kind of sicko
gets their kicks
from picking on
a little kid, huh?
You should be ashamed, you
gut-slicing, sadistic woman!
Felt is doing her best to stand
her ground and live strong!
'Cause your plan
didn't go your way,
you think you can throw a
tantrum and flip tables?
Grow up, you pathetic
spoiled brat!
You should try to learn to
value life a little more!
'Cause having your
belly cut hurts!
[ELSA] Now what are
you babbling about?
[SUBARU] I'm in the process of
letting the justice and chivalry
I never knew I had denounce
all the unfairness in the world!
And, what I consider "unfair"
is you, this situation, and...
Okay, folks,
ready for the fun part?
There! That should
buy us enough time.
All right! Get her, Puck!
I hope your brilliant
display of awkwardness
lives through the ages.
Here we go! My turn!
We haven't had the chance to
introduce ourselves, have we?
My name's Puck.
Now do your best to remember
it on the way to your grave!
Did we get her, or what?!
Don't say things like
that, you'll jinx it!
[ELSA]
One should always be prepared.
Don't underestimate
a user of spirit arts!
You're well accustomed
to battle, for a girl.
[ELSA]
"A girl", huh?
My, it's been a while
since I've been regarded
in such simple terms.
[PUCK]
Well, from my perspective,
all opponents are
little more than babies.
Still, you're so strong,
I almost pity you.
I'm deeply touched to be
praised by a spirit.
If this thing turns into
a battle of attrition,
I'd say we stand
a pretty good chance.
Well, for a spirit,
the real battle is how long
they can stay in their bodies.
That's right,
it must be almost five.
And when we were both
having so much fun, too.
What a bore.
Just one of the
drawbacks of the job.
When you're a ladies' man,
the girls won't give you
the chance to sleep.
But you know, staying up
late is bad for your skin,
so I'd say it's about
time we wrap this up.
[ELSA]
Huh?
[PUCK] Didn't think I was
just throwing those around
at random, did you?
Looks like I've
been had. Oh, my.
[PUCK]
Say goodnight!
[ELSA]
My, how lovely!
I thought I was going to die.
[ALL gasp]
But you are a tricky girl,
so I don't find that sort
of thing very impressive.
Puck, can you keep going?
Sorry... but I'm sleepy.
Think I underestimated her.
My mana's gone, so I'm done.
Don't worry, I'll take care of
things out here so you can rest.
Thank you for your help.
Remember: If anything
happens to you,
I'll act according
to my contract.
If it comes down to it, call me,
even if you have to
squeeze me out of my od.
[ELSA]
Aww, you're going away?
[ELSA] Well, that's
terribly unfortunate.
I know this is pretty
interesting, Felt,
but we can't afford to just
sit around watching anymore.
Yeah, yeah, I know, I know.
If we're gonna
make a run for it,
we need to get moving right now.
Oh, and about before...
Well, I guess you
kinda saved me.
But only just a
little bit, okay?
Also, don't call
me a little kid!
I am 15 years old, you know!
That can't be much
younger than you, jerk.
Well, actually, I'll be
turning 18 this year.
Huh?! No way! Really?!
'Cause you don't even look like
you're old enough to shave yet!
[ROM]
Here I come!
Oh, how rude! Don't cut in
on someone else's dance!
If you wanna dance,
I'll show you the best
dancing you've ever seen!
[ROM]
Here we go! Round and round!
Huh? What in the--?
[ROM gasps]
You're so strong, I was
able to stand on your club.
Now...
Not gonna happen!
[gasps]
[ELSA]
You bad girl...
You've neither the resolve
nor the strength to fight.
You'd have been better off
using your small stature
to hide away in the corner.
[SUBARU] Damn, we're finished!
There's really nothing I can do.
I'll have to use Return
by Death and start over...
[SUBARU] No... I don't
wanna feel that pain again.
I don't wanna die!
I guess, as long
as I have life...
...all I can do is fight
with everything I've got!
[SUBARU]
Haidara!
[SUBARU] Hey, are you
gonna be all right?!
Why'd you risk your life for...?
Never mind, just listen
to me carefully, Felt.
I'm gonna buy us some time,
find a way to give you an
opening somehow, and when I do,
I want you to run
as fast as you can!
Not a chance!
I'm s'posed to tuck my tail
between my legs and run?
Yeah, that's right!
Stick out your butt,
tuck in your tail, and run!
You're 15, and I'm 18.
And that means that you're
probably the youngest one
out of everybody here.
So it's a given that we're gonna
pick the method most likely
to keep you alive and
get you outta this place.
You understand?!
Ah, give me a break!
You were cowering in
fear just a minute ago!
[SUBARU] Well, that was
then. And this is now.
Don't worry about me.
Everything's fine.
[SUBARU]
Take this!
This is it! Now! Run!
You think I'll let her go?
[SUBARU]
Whoa, I'm awesome!
But that hurt the tips of my
toes more than I expected.
It looks like you
let one get away.
[ELSA] For once, I'm
feeling a tiny bit annoyed.
[GIRL]
Hey! Don't forget about me!
I hope you have
some other attacks
because I've grown
tired of that one.
Do you think you can
still keep me amused?
If you've got some
ultimate power
hidden somewhere in
your bag of tricks,
I'm thinkin' now
might be a good time.
[GIRL]
Well, I do have a trump card.
But if I use it, I'll be the
only one who's left standing.
Whoa, easy!
Now don't do anything that'll
blow us both up, okay?
I have no intention of using
it while you're still here,
doing your best...
...fighting alongside me...
[SUBARU]
I didn't see anything just now.
[GIRL]
Huh?
[SUBARU] None of that whole
conversation ever happened!
I finally remembered why
I'm here in the first place!
I'll kill you, you shitbag!
Then you won't have
to play your trump card!
I'll blow you away and get...
...a happy ending!
Energetic, huh? Too bad.
You black widow!
[ELSA] Well, there's no doubt
you'll be the first one
caught in my web.
[SUBARU]
Nice cover!
Dammit!
How do you like this?!
I've got you now.
[REINHARD]
That's enough.
[REINHARD] Looks like
I cut it pretty close,
but I'm glad I made it in time.
Now...
I know you.
What do you say? Shall we
put an end to this?
[FELT]
Someone!
Anyone! Isn't there
anybody who can hear me?!
Damn it! Please!
Please! Someone--! Someone help!
She's-She's gonna kill him!
[REINHARD]
Very well.
I'll help you.
Reinhart? But how?
[REINHARD]
Hello there, Subaru.
Seems we meet again.
Sorry I'm late.
Black hair, black clothes,
and a blade unique to
the northern provinces.
There's no mistaking
those characteristics.
You are the Bowel Hunter.
[SUBARU] Seriously? What kind
of evil nickname is that?!
It was derived from
her unique style
of killing those who oppose her.
Her name is known far and
wide as a menace to society.
Ah, Reinhart.
Yes, a true knight
among knights,
born to the Master
Swordsman's line.
It's quite remarkable that each
my opponents are so much fun!
[REINHARD] There are many
things I'd like to ask you.
I suggest you surrender.
Now do you honestly expect
a starving predator like myself
to resist the temptation
of such delectable prey?
Subaru, please,
move back a little bit.
If you'd stand next to her,
I'd appreciate it.
Whatever you say.
That woman is a monster, so
don't let your guard down, okay?
As luck would have it,
hunting monsters happens
to be a specialty of mine.
[ROM groans]
[SUBARU]
Old Man Rom is still alive?
He's not out of the woods yet.
I'm gonna have to heal him now.
Are you sure?
I mean, he's part of the gang
that stole your insignia
and caused this mess.
That's exactly
why I'm doing this.
If he recovers,
he can repay the favor
by giving me information.
He wouldn't lie to me then.
Not after saving his life.
See? This is for
my own sake, too.
I would rather not resort
to using violence on a woman.
[ELSA]
Look at you! My!
You're just as good as the
rumors say. Maybe better.
I hope that I can meet
your expectations.
[ELSA] Aren't you going to
use that sword at your hip?
Love the chance to experience
its legendary
sharpness first-hand.
[REINHARD] This sword
can only be drawn at times
when it's truly needed.
The fact that it hasn't
left its sheath as of yet
means that this is not
one of those times.
I believe you underestimate me.
[REINHARD] Truthfully,
it's an upsetting judgment
for me, as well.
Therefore... I will take
you on with this instead.
Any objections?
Of course not. It's
wonderful. Wonderful!
Do entertain me, please!
If you've lost your weapon,
then I suggest you surrender.
[SUBARU]
Watch out, Reinhart!
She's got a second one!
I'm impressed you knew.
I've experienced your
blades personally.
But I have more than two
fangs, I'll have you know.
You wouldn't mind if we
started again, would you?
[REINHARD] If I deprive
you of all your weapons,
will you be satisfied?
If I lose my fangs,
I'll use my claws.
If I lose my claws,
I'll use my bones.
And if I lose my bones,
I'll use my life.
That's how a Bowel
Hunter fights.
[SUBARU] There's no way
Reinhart's gonna fail
to land the decisive
blow, right?
Unfortunately, he's not able
to fight at his full strength
'cause I'm using my spirit arts.
What do those have to
do with each other?
If Reinhard were truly
intent on fighting,
all the mana in the atmosphere
would turn away from me.
I've almost finished
healing him, though.
So be sure he knows
when I give you the signal.
He should be all
right now. Go ahead.
Hey, Reinhart!
I don't really get it,
but do your thing!
[ELSA]
What are you going to show me?
[REINHARD] The swordplay
of the Astrea family.
You're facing the Bowel Hunter,
Miss Elsa Granhiert.
Master Swordsman's line.
I'm Reinhart van Astrea!
[SUBARU yells]
[SUBARU] "Hunting monsters
is your specialty," my ass!
Look at this place! You're a
monster yourself, you freak!
Even I'm a bit hurt by a cruel
comment like that, Subaru.
I'm sorry I asked
too much of you.
Rest well now.
[SUBARU] There's not a shadow
of her left, let alone a body.
He did all that with just
one swing of a sword?
Is it all over now?
[SUBARU]
Looks like it.
Figuratively and literally.
Why are you staring at me?
That is quite rude,
you should know better.
Oh, it's just...
You still have your arms and
legs, and even your head.
Of course I do.
Don't say such things.
[SUBARU] Yeah, you're right.
Pretty obvious, huh?
I still have my arms, too.
And there's no knife in my back.
No gaping hole in
my gut, either! Whew!
What strange things
to point out.
You talk as if you've
experienced them before.
Actually, there was
a time when I did.
Oh, yeah, and Reinhart!
I haven't thanked you yet.
You saved my ass!
You saved it back
in the alley, too.
Guess you just have
a way of knowing
when I could really
use some help.
If I had the ability to do that,
I'd certainly be proud.
This friend of yours,
I found her running
around the streets,
quite frightened and desperate.
And she asked for my help.
So I came here.
It's her...
Now, hang on a second.
If she hadn't brought
Reinhart here,
who knows if we'd even be
having this conversation.
Just take a look at this face,
and spare me the "ice statue"
punishment, okay?
I wouldn't do
anything that violent.
And what does your face
have to do with any--?
Subaru!
[SUBARU]
Huh?
She'll go for the gut!
Get away!
That boy got in my way again.
[REINHARD]
That's enough, Elsa!
Before long,
I will disembowel every last
one of you here in this room.
Until that moment comes,
be sure to take of yourselves.
Are you all right?
My being "all right"
isn't what's most important
right now, but...
Are you all right?
That was far too reckless!
Oh, it was no problem.
Now, it sure took a
long time to get here,
but the good news is,
I finally made it.
My name is Subaru Natsuki!
And I just risked it
all to save your life
from a dangerous
and heinous villain!
Is that okay?
"Okay"...?
[SUBARU] It means,
"Are we clear on that?"
So okay?
O-Okay...
I, your rescuer, am the
one who saved your life.
And you are the heroine I
saved from the clutches of evil!
So wouldn't that mean you
should repay me in kind?
Wouldn't it? Huh?!
Yes, I understand!
But only if whatever
you want reward-wise
is within my power, of course...
[SUBARU]
That sounds fair to me!
In that case, I have
only one request!
And... that request is...
...I want you to tell
me what your name is.
[GIRL giggles]
Emilia.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
My name is Emilia. Only Emilia.
Your price was easy to pay.
Thanks so much for
saving me, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
All those times I got hurt,
all the crying I did,
all the pain I felt,
all the fighting with
my life on the line...
And my reward was her
name and a single smile.
[sighs] Oh, man... Talk about
unequal compensation.
Anyway, Subaru,
I'm impressed that you're
still able to stand.
[SUBARU]
I was lucky this thing was there
to grab for protection.
Otherwise, I'd be in
two pieces right now.
[REINHARD]
True. If not for this...
What the--?
[SUBARU] Uh-oh. I should've
seen this coming.
[EMILIA]
Subaru?
Subaru!
[SUBARU]
Man...
She's so cute when she's
panicking like that.
A fantasy in another world...
[EMILIA] There. His
treatment is complete.
He should be over the hump now.
[REINHARD]
By the way, Miss Emilia,
what's the nature of
your relation to Subaru?
An acquaintance?
Honestly, I don't recall
ever seeing him before.
When we met earlier today,
I believe it was
the very first time.
But he was looking for you.
Said he had something
to give you.
Odd behavior from a stranger.
Yes, it is rather peculiar...
So what do you propose
we do with him, then?
I'd be glad to take him
to my home as a guest,
at least while he's healing.
I'll take him home with me.
That way, I can find out
what's really going on.
More importantly,
what will become of that
girl and the old man?
[REINHARD]
In an official capacity,
I cannot overlook what
they've done here.
However, as luck would have it,
I just so happen to
be off-duty today.
[EMILIA chuckles]
Well, aren't you a bad knight.
So this old man is part
of your family, I take it?
Yeah, something
like that, I guess.
Old Man Rom's the only
person I have in this world.
I suppose he's like my grandpa.
I see. I only have one
family member, too.
He's always asleep at the most
important moments, though.
'Course, I wouldn't say that
out loud when he's awake.
I'd never hear the end of it.
Considering what I did,
I figured you'd be
a lot harder on me.
You saved my life back there
and I can't let
a debt go unpaid,
so I'll return what I
stole from you, okay?
If it's important,
I suggest you keep it hidden
so no one can steal it again.
[EMILIA]
I appreciate the advice,
though, it's a little strange
to hear it from you.
[REINHARD gasps]
What're you doing?
Hey! You're hurting me!
Let go of my arm!
This can't be possible!
What's your name?
Huh? It's Felt, why do...?
Family name? And just
how old are you?
Look, I don't have anything
fancy like a family name.
I'm about... 15,
if I had to guess.
I don't know my birthday.
Just let me go!
Sorry, Miss Emilia,
but I'm afraid that I can't keep
my promise to you at this time.
I'll be taking this girl with
me for further questioning.
May I ask you why?
If it's just for stealing
my insignia, then...
That theft alone is no
small crime, certainly.
But if I overlook
what's unfolding
before me at this moment,
I know it would be the
greatest crime of them all.
I'll need you to
come along with me.
I'm sorry, but I simply can't
allow you to refuse.
Get over yourself!
Just because you saved
me doesn't mean you--
That little move didn't
seem very knightly, either.
I was careful not
to use too much.
Miss Emilia,
I will most likely be
calling upon you
again very soon.
I hope you understand.
Please take good care of Subaru.
He's been through a lot.
Tonight may be
our last chance...
...to gaze calmly at the moon...