[CHIEF]
To us of the demon clan,
twins are taboo.
[MOM] Please wait, Chief!
I beg of you!
Enough!
To protect our pride as a race,
and to ensure
its continued purity,
we must dispose of them.
Such is the demon clan's custom!
It is our law!
[BABY REM crying]
[VILLAGERS gasp]
One of the children is...
[CHIEF]
She is a true prodigy.
[VILLAGER 11-A]
Such power with only one horn!
[VILLAGER 11-B]
Imagine what she could do
if she'd been born with two!
That was very good, Ram!
Rem, you'll have to
follow your sister's example
and work hard.
Oh, don't you worry.
One day soon, Rem will show us
that she has incredible power.
I've no doubt.
She's Ram's sister.
So, I'm sure it'll
come with time.
[DAD]
'Course it will.
[RAM]
Don't worry.
Sissy, I...
Just be yourself, Rem.
There's no reason
for you to worry about
what other people say.
[REM] I could never match
my sister in demon power.
Then...
[REM]
Hey... Mom...
Yes, Rem dear? What is it?
I've decided that I'm
gonna make dinner tomorrow.
So what are you
thinking about making?
[REM] Maybe a stir-fry
with barbaro rabbit meat
and nuts from the
trees in the forest.
And some steamed tatoes!
That sounds good.
I'll help you.
Mm-mm.
I'll be okay by myself.
Just watch.
Now I just need
a barbaro rabbit...
[REM yells]
[REM]
Sissy!
I was worried, so I'm really
glad you're both all right.
[REM]
She said "both"...
Listen. Don't go into
the forest alone again.
Okay, Rem?
You don't want to worry
your sister now, do you?
No. You're right, I won't.
Wait. Let's not
forget about this.
The steamed tatoes Rem
went to so much trouble
to make turned out really good.
Just taste 'em.
And they have just the
right amount of salt, too.
Yeah, you're right!
They are good!
[MOM chuckles]
I had no idea Rem could
make something so delicious!
[MOM]
Okay. That's enough, Rem.
[MOM] In the end,
I'm really just glad
both of you are all right.
[DAD]
Yes. We're so glad you're safe.
[CHIEF]
No, would have been much better
if it had only been Ram.
[VILLAGER 11-A]
That's right.
[VILLAGER 11-B]
You said it.
Good point. If only that
useless Rem had died...
...leaving Ram as our
only surviving daughter,
that would have been best.
[REM crying]
[RAM] You were having a
scary dream, weren't you?
You were moaning.
[REM]
Sissy...
It's okay now.
'Cause I'm right here with you.
You'll never have to
worry about anything
with me around, all right?
Right. Thank you, Sissy.
[REM]
I love you.
My sister really is amazing.
I can't match her in anything.
In that case, I don't have
to do anything anymore.
I can just be myself
and walk behind her.
[REM whimpers]
[REM]
Sissy?
[crashing]
[REM gasps]
Careful, Sissy!
[RAM]
Oh, Rem.
I'm so glad you're safe.
[RAM gasps]
[REM]
It finally broke off.
Because of me,
my sister's horn was broken,
and she lost her power.
From now on...
I have to learn to do
all the things that Sissy--
That Sister could do.
This is what Sister
would have to done.
Sister is even more amazing.
Sister could do even more.
I'm only imitating
what Sister could do.
If I can't even do
that satisfactorily,
then I'm worthless.
You're doing an excellent job.
[REM] I heard those
words back home
so many times.
Easy, don't overdo it.
[REM]
Even if I overdo everything,
it will never be enough.
I don't understand.
Why do you try so hard?
[REM]
Why else?
Because nothing I do
will ever measure up.
Why should I go on living?
All of this is my
atonement for what I felt
on that fiery night.
What else can I do
to make amends?
I'll risk my life
to walk the very same path
that Sister would've walked.
The path I took from her.
Because I'm inferior
to her in every way.
I'm nothing more than
a mediocre replacement.
And that's all I'll ever be.
[SUBARU panting]
[RAM] Barusu, head to the right
of that broken tree ahead!
You're too slow!
[SUBARU]
Don't ask any more of me!
You got that?!
I'm running just as
fast as I can here!
Wh-What's going on?
Where are we?
Rem! You're finally awake!
Oh, thank goodness.
You really are a handful,
you know that?
[MABEAST growls]
[RAM]
Fula!
[MABEAST yelps]
[SUBARU, RAM panting]
[REM]
Why...?
Why what?
[REM] Why didn't you just
mind your own business
and leave me alone?
You and Sister showing up
makes it all pointless...
[crying]
I have to do it
by myself, understand?
Nobody else needs
to get hurt anymore...
It's too late for that now.
Ram and I are already
torn to shreds,
maybe even more than you are!
My right shoulder's dislocated!
[REM]
It's...
It's my fault.
So I have to
take responsibility...
If I don't I can't
do anything for Sister,
or you, either...
I'm terrible.
And I haven't changed at all.
I committed the same
sin today that I did
when I was a little girl.
Because I hesitated
to extend my hand to you...
The witch's scent?
You nearly died.
[SUBARU]
Let me get this straight...
Are you trying to tell me
that you decided
to do this alone to
make amends for that?
[SUBARU]
Rem...
Yes, what?
Super slap!
[SUBARU]
For starters, are you dumb?
No, you are dumb!
Barusu, the cut that's
on your forehead
has reopened and
is bleeding again.
Yeah, I know, I feel it!
I'm dumb too, okay?!
Thanks for the reminder!
But your sister is even dumber!
Listen to me for a second.
Where I come from,
there's an old saying that goes,
"Three heads are
better than one."
Or wait, is it two heads?
Whatever! That doesn't
matter right now.
The point is, three
heads thinking together
are way harder to break
than one arrow by itself!
So don't think
about stuff alone!
Just learn to trust and
rely on those around you!
[REM]
Subaru, I...
[rustling]
Dammit...
Ram, which way should we run
to get outside the barrier?
[RAM] We'd have to run
left at full speed.
What's your plan?
[SUBARU]
Hmm...
I could shove Rem toward you,
take a dramatic turn
and briefly stare at you two,
and then run tragically
to the right...
So you want to draw
the ulgarm's attention
while I take Rem
and run to safety?
Could you not reduce
my heroic moment
to such a simple plan?
No, there's no way you
can survive on your own.
I'm begging of you.
Please don't. You mustn't.
[SUBARU]
Don't go worrying about me.
I have a brilliant idea for
rounding up all the mabeasts
you don't know about.
[REM] Subaru, why would
you do all this?
[SUBARU]
Well, the thing is...
[SUBARU] You were my
partner on the very first date
I ever went on.
I could never be so heartless
that I'd abandon you.
Right.
I guess I'd better go ahead
and get this thing going, then.
Take care of Rem, okay?
I'm counting on you!
[RAM] I'll be praying for
our safe reunion, Barusu.
[SUBARU grunts]
[RAM] He's risking his
life to buy us some time.
So let's make the most of it.
[SUBARU panting]
[MABEAST growls]
I'd love to finish
you off right about now,
you little mutt...
[MABEAST growls]
Yeah? I've got an ace
up my sleeve, too!
It's you and me, pal.
Hope you're ready!
[REM]
Sister!
Subaru's surrounded!
He's not going to--
[RAM]
Don't look back, Rem.
Or Barusu's determination
will be for nothing.
[REM]
Sissy, please!
Subaru!
Shamac!
[SUBARU yelling]
I could do without the bugs, but
I appreciate the bocco fruit!
Thank you for that...
...you little brats!
[MABEAST growls]
[SUBARU]
Crap!
[SUBARU grunting]
[SUBARU] Think it's about
time for you to die!
[MABEAST growls]
What's the matter, mutt?
Bring it on, big boss garm!
[ROSWAAL]
Ulgoa!
[MABEAST growls]
[ROSWAAL]
Oh, my!
You look an absolute
fright, don't you, Subaru?!
Better late than never, I guess.
Right, Ross?
[ROSWAAL chuckles]
Gotta say, though...
I'm surprised you
knew where to find me.
[ROSWAAL] Miss Emilia drove
it into me quite thoroughly
in the village.
"Even if it's rash or reckless,
he'll use magic
if he's cornered,
so don't lose sight of him
from above," she said.
And there you go.
[RAM]
Lord Roswaal!
[ROSWAAL, SUBARU]
Hm?
I'm certain we caused
a lot of trouble for you.
My apologies.
Quite the contrary.
Truthfully, you both
accomplished fine work
in my absence; I'm grateful.
And I will certainly
show that gratitude
for what you've done for me.
You have my word.
--[REM] Subaru!
--[SUBARU yells]
[SUBARU]
Rem, that hurts! Stop it!
I'm kinda hurt
all over right now...
You're alive!
You stayed alive! Subaru!
I'm so happy you're safe!
This again, huh?
Suppose I should
be used to it...
[REM]
Hey... Are you awake?
Was I the one who did this?
Like, grabbed you
and never let go?
Uh, well, not exactly. It, uh...
It was me... to be honest.
I was watching you
and it looked like you
were in pain while
you slept, so I...
[SUBARU]
You held my hand?
[REM] I don't know what
to do at times like these.
It's always so confusing
and overwhelming.
So I did what would have
made me the happiest
if I were in your place...
I'd like to hear
the rest of that.
I mean, uh...
I'd like to find out
how everything ended.
Like, were my curses removed?
They were.
Lord Roswaal was
meticulous and took care
of all the mabeasts
in the forest.
So there's no chance
the curses placed on you
will ever activate.
[SUBARU sighs]
[REM]
I'm so sorry, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
Hey, come on...
Lift your head up, Rem.
There's nothing wrong with me.
You know, you always look
so calm and collected.
But you're not either of
those things at all, are you?
I'm aware of my shortcomings.
At the heart of it all,
I'm a powerless and incompetent
demon clan dropout.
So no matter what I do,
I can never match my sister.
I'm only her replacement.
One far inferior
to her, at that.
Good for nothing.
I don't get it.
Why was I the only
one between us
that kept her horn?
Why couldn't it have been her?
Why couldn't Sister
be the one to keep hers?
Why was she born
with only one horn?
I've caused her
nothing but trouble
since the day of our birth.
It's my fault.
Why did we have come
into this world as twins?
Goodness, I'm sorry.
That was a strange
thing for me to say.
Please forget it.
[SUBARU]
You know, Rem...
You keep putting
Ram on a pedestal
while undermining yourself
at the same time.
Putting yourself down.
But I don't think her
situation would be any better
if she were in your position.
Ram is weaker than you,
she can't cook,
she slacks off on the job,
she says mean things...
[REM]
Y-You're wrong!
If she had her horn, you
wouldn't say things like that.
[SUBARU]
But Ram doesn't have her horn,
so I don't know that Ram.
I've never seen her
any other way.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm pretty sure you're
the only one who cares
whether she has one or not.
And what Ram
doesn't have, you do.
You should just acknowledge
and accept that.
You're kind, hardworking,
and you always do your
best, no matter what.
Your chest is even
bigger than hers, too!
But seriously, if you
hadn't been around,
those dogs would've
chewed me to death.
I was saved because
you were there.
As you can see,
I'm alive right now.
Not only because of
everything your sister did,
but because of you.
My true Sister could've
done much more back there.
[SUBARU]
You may be right.
But the one who was
there for me was you.
[REM gasps]
[SUBARU]
I'm glad you were there.
Thanks for saving me.
Didn't you hear?
I told you that I'm only
my sister's replacement,
nothing more.
Don't define yourself
that way, all right?
It's too sad.
'Course, I haven't
actually heard the details
about how she lost her
horn in the first place.
And I won't ask,
so I'll never know.
Since I don't,
that means I get to talk
as if I know all about it.
Listen carefully.
All you have to do is be
the horn Ram doesn't have.
If you do that, you two
can be a demon together.
Also, you call yourself
a replacement...
but no one could
ever take your place.
But I...
[SUBARU] Where I come from,
there's an old saying,
"Demons laugh when
you talk about next year."
And you're a demon.
So just laugh, Rem.
Wipe off that sad face,
and laugh.
Laugh while we talk
about the future!
Let's talk about things
while we look forward to
making up for all
the time you've wasted
by looking back.
We can start by
talking about tomorrow.
[REM]
Wait... Tomorrow?
[SUBARU]
Yep! Absolutely!
You can say anything...
Like, uh...
Whether you'll make
a Japanese, Western,
or local-style
breakfast tomorrow...
Or whether you'll put on
your right or left shoe first.
It can be something
silly like that.
No matter how it might sound,
you can talk about tomorrow
because you have a tomorrow.
How about it?
Listen. I-I'm very weak.
So I'm certain that
I'll end up depending
and leaning on you.
[SUBARU]
What's wrong with that?
I may be weak, stupid,
and scary-looking.
And, as I'm sure you've noticed,
I'm pretty dense...
But I never let that stop me.
I still live my life expecting
others to take care of things
for me when I can't handle it.
We can just lean on each
other as we move forward.
Let's laugh and
talk about tomorrow,
with our arms around
each other's shoulders.
After all, I've dreamed
of laughing and talking
about next year with
a demon since I can remember.
You are demonically inspired.
You know it.
[REM laughing]
[ROSWAAL]
By the way, Ram...
Did you happen to find the one
who was controlling
the mabeasts?
[RAM]
Yes...
But the trail has
already vanished.
One of the children
Barusu and Rem brought back
from the forest
mysteriously disappeared
from the village the next day.
[ROSWAAL] Was this connected
to the battle for the throne,
as well?
The Bowel Hunter,
mabeast masters...
We've certainly gotten involved
with some bizarre characters,
haven't we...?
No matter how many
strange characters you face,
you aren't the sort of man
who would lose heart
and turn tail, are you?
My goodness!
You've grown so very audacious.
Come here.
Now, then... Shall we begin?
After all, I was unable
to attend to you
for a whole night.
Yes, I realize that.
I'm sorry, please do.
[ROSWAAL] You've used
quite a lot of mana.
May the stars protect you.
[ROSWAAL] I will be busy
again for a time.
I know it will be
difficult for you,
but I'll be counting
on you and Rem.
[RAM]
As you wish.
Since that fiery night,
my body has belonged
to you, Lord Roswaal.
This battle for the throne...
I must win, no matter
what it takes to do so.
For the sake of
my ultimate goal...
For the coming day
when I kill the dragon...
[EMILIA]
I've noticed something.
You're constantly getting hurt,
aren't you, Subaru?
You came to this mansion
because you were injured
in the first place.
And it's only been
four days since then.
Hey, give me a break.
It's not like I get hurt
because I want to.
The world's a
pretty harsh place,
but I think it's a little,
uh, harsher on me.
With that in mind, you're
welcome to spoil me rotten,
since no one else will, Mee-Lee!
What do you say?
[EMILIA]
Don't joke around.
Puck kept trying to stop me
from leaving the cottage
and going after you
guys to help, too.
Who knows what would've
happened if Roswaal
hadn't made it back?
You understand now?
[EMILIA]
Still...
I suppose you saved me again.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[EMILIA] I brought you
to the mansion
as thanks for rescuing me,
and you've gone and
repeated that favor
without a second thought.
So I just wanted
to say thank you!
Hey, it's fine! Really!
I only did it because
I wanted to!
There's no thanks needed!
I thought you
might say that,
but I don't feel any better
about you putting yourself
in danger.
I should do something
to show my gratitude...
I see.
Well, I'll take you
up on that...
...by having you go on a
date with me, Mee-Lee!
And what is a "date"?
[SUBARU] We'll go out together,
see the same things,
eat the same things,
do the same things,
and share the same memories.
We'll spend our time just
laughing and having fun.
And that's really all you want?
That's exactly what I want.
I wanna show you off
to those bratty village kids,
and there's this
awesome flower field
to walk through, too!
Even if all we do is stroll
around and look at stuff,
it'll be a special
occasion for me!
All right, then.
I'll go on a "date" with you.
It sounds like fun!
[SUBARU]
Yes!
That's why you're my EMF!
Oh! That's just a cool acronym.
"EMF" stands for
"Emilia, major fairy"!
[EMILIA laughs]