[GIRL]
I'll ask one more time.
Why did you call me by the
name of the Witch of Envy?
W-Well, because
you said I should.
[GIRL] I don't know
who told you that,
but they have a
terrible sense of humor!
The Witch of Envy is the
very definition of taboo.
And you call me by her name,
which most dare not even say?!
Yeah, she's right, kid!
You crossed the
line there, buddy!
If you don't have anything
to say, then I'm leaving.
I have things to do.
[SUBARU]
What?
[chuckles]
That's Felt!
[gasps]
Wait, were you a distraction?
Are you working with her?!
What? No!
Hey! Wait a minute,
come back here!
You've got it all wrong!
[SUBARU]
Damn it!
Come on! Would someone please
be a little nicer to me?
This world sucks.
Why was I even summoned here?
[KAN] What are you
goin' on and on about?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
then cough up
whatever you've got!
[KAN, CHIN chuckle]
Just stop it already!
Nobody could be this
damn persistent!
[CHIN] You think you
can mouth off to us?
[SUBARU]
Now move it!
I have somewhere I need to
go and you guys are in my way!
[SUBARU grunts]
[TON]
You stabbed him?! Oh, man...
[SUBARU]
You've gotta be kidding...
It hurts... It hurts...
Hey, what are you doing?!
[KAN]
Well, no sense in wasting him!
Take anything he's
got that's worth selling!
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[TON] Whoa, wait! The guards
will be here any second!
[SUBARU]
But Old Man Rom ate those...
How...?
C-Could... this be...?
[CHIN]
C'mon, move it! Run!
Speak up! You want it?
Hey, mister?
[KADOMON]
Huh?
How many times have you
seen me here before?
What are you talkin' about?
I've never seen you before.
Well? Decide! You want it?
Sorry, but I don't have any
money at all! Totally broke!
[KADOMON]
Then get the hell outta here!
[SUBARU] Wallet, cell phone,
corn potage, cup of noodles...
It looks like my tracksuit
and sneakers are intact, too.
And hopefully...
[sighs] That's a relief.
'Cause a wound to the back
is a warrior's greatest
shame, for sure.
Well, with this much
circumstantial evidence,
there's absolutely
no denying it.
It's kinda hard to believe,
but this has to be...
...a time leap.
And each time, I return
to my initial state.
I'll call it...
"Return by Death."
So I have the ability to
leap backwards in time,
but it only
activates when I die.
Guess even my special power
knows what a loser I am.
[SUBARU] If I've gone back in
time to this moment once again,
then Satella hasn't helped me.
We haven't even met yet.
Consequently, that means
the debt I owed her
for saving me is
completely gone.
That's actually a
stroke of good luck!
I can forget everything,
sell this, save some funds,
and use my knowledge
of the modern world
to create a paradise!
Things are finally lookin' up!
Huh?
Am I right, mister?
Wh-Why're you asking me?
I don't have any idea what
you're talkin' about, all right?
Come on. Don't be like that.
[GUY A] I don't wanna get caught
up in other people's problems.
So don't talk to me about 'em.
[SUBARU] Well, I guess the old
saying "Let sleeping dogs lie"
applies no matter
what world you're on.
Even so, there are
always softies...
People who'll help others,
even when they really
can't afford to.
She'd just had something
precious stolen.
She didn't have time for me.
Yet she saved some
useless stranger.
And even healed him.
Then she let that
useless stranger
feel all pleased with himself.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Even if Satella doesn't know me,
that doesn't change everything.
Felt still stole her insignia,
and Elsa will...
No matter how many times I
repeat this, that won't change.
History's a compelling
force, right?
[SUBARU]
Yeah.
If I'm fully aware that people I
used to know will be murdered...
...then I can't just ignore it!
Huh...?
[SUBARU]
Hey, mister...
What do you want now, broke boy?
[SUBARU] Th-There's something
I need to ask you...
Have there been any
pickpocketing incidents
around here?
Asking questions
without buyin', huh?
You got some nerve, kid.
But yeah, stuff like that
happens all the time.
Though, that last
one was unusual...
They threw some magic around
in the street a coupla times.
Things that looked like
icicles flew around
and lodged in the wall.
They disappeared quick, though.
[SUBARU]
I was too late.
I thought if I could keep the
insignia from being stolen,
then maybe things
wouldn't have...
What are you goin' on about?
Oh, it's nothing
important. But, uh...
Thanks, mister. Really.
You helped me even though I
didn't actually buy anything.
[KADOMON]
Ah, it's no big deal!
A broke kid a lot like yourself
just helped my daughter
after she got separated
from her mother earlier.
I guess fate is a compelling
force, too, huh?
[KADOMON]
What are you smilin' about?
[SUBARU]
It's nothing.
I'll be sure to buy an
appa next time, okay?
Sounds good. Buy one and
you'll be a customer.
Get to work, broke boy! See ya!
[SUBARU]
Later!
This means there's
only one way!
I have to buy the
insignia from Felt
before Elsa comes
to the loot house,
and return it to Satella!
Wait... "Satella" was just an
alias that she used, wasn't it?
Then I'm gonna need to do
whatever I can this time around
to make sure she tells me
what her real name actually is.
What are you goin'
on and on about?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
then cough up
whatever you've got!
Listen, Dumb, Dumber,
and Dumberest,
I'm getting sick of
seeing your faces.
After doing this four times,
I've learned my lesson!
[ALL]
Huh?
Guards, help me!
What the hell, you bastard?!
[chuckles]
[SUBARU] It seems my memory
from before was right.
This world does have some
kind of police force!
[SUBARU]
Someone! Please, I need a man!
[CHIN]
Damn it, shut up!
[SUBARU] No, don't touch me!
Stop! I can't hear you!
You're not being sincere enough!
Someone, please help me!
Polic... Huh?
Don't scare me like that.
All that yelling freaked
me out a little bit.
Just a little bit, though.
Yeah, just a
teeny-tiny little bit.
[chuckles nervously]
Yrying to run away
won't help you.
[REINHARD]
That's enough.
[ALL gasp]
[TON]
Red hair...
And a knight's sword
with scratches
made by dragon claws...
Can that be...
...Reinhart, the Master
Swordsman?!
Looks like I don't need
to introduce myself.
Though, to be honest, that
nickname is a bit much for me.
I don't know how much help my
modest strength can be to him,
but if you wish to resort
to extreme measures,
let me warn you.
As a knight... I will
have to fight back.
[TON]
S-Screw this business!
It's not worth it!
Glad we both came out
of that unscathed.
Lucky break, huh?
Uh! Allow me to thank you
from the bottom of my heart!
You helped me out without ever
once giving it a second thought!
I, Subaru Natsuki, deeply admire
your selfless act of
bravery and kindness!
Hey, come on now, there's no
need for such formality.
Once it was two of
us against three,
those thugs lost their
advantage on the situation.
Things might've been
different if I were alone.
[SUBARU] Wow, his nice-guy
index is off the charts.
So you're... Master
Swordsman Reinhard, right?
It's "Reinhart," Subaru.
Just Reinhart.
[SUBARU] We went from
zero to buddy-buddy fast!
Well, thanks again,
Reinhart. I appreciate it.
I shouted for help
over and over,
but you're the only one
who answered my call.
I'm so pathetic.
Don't be so down on yourself.
For most, it's too risky to face
off against people like them.
Listen, as far as I'm concerned,
you were right to
call for the guards.
[SUBARU] So would that
make you a guard, then?
You don't look like one.
Well, today I happen
to be off-duty,
so I'm not in the
standard uniform.
And I know that I don't look
particularly
intimidating either way.
[SUBARU] But they did call you
"Master Swordsman," didn't they?
So...
[REINHARD]
My family is a bit unique.
Most of the time,
I don't feel like
I live up to their
expectations.
Anyway, Subaru...
Your name, your clothes,
and that haircut are... unusual.
What nation are you from?
At the moment, Lugunica
is a bit more on edge
than in peacetime.
If you're having problems
while you're here,
I'm happy to help out
in any way I can.
Would you come to the
loot house with me?
[REINHARD]
What?
Uh... Never mind.
Forget about it.
I don't wanna bother you.
Especially on your day off.
I'll handle the rest of
this on my own, somehow.
But... I'd appreciate it if you
could deliver a message for me.
Of course, I'd be glad to.
What would you like me
to say, and to whom?
[SUBARU] Well, I don't exactly
know her name, but...
Have you seen a girl with
white robes and silver hair
around here lately?
White robes and
silver hair, huh?
Oh, and she's also
exceptionally beautiful!
No. It doesn't ring a bell.
[SUBARU] Well, if you
do happen to see her,
tell her not to come near the
loot house, no matter what.
I'll find what she's looking for
and bring it to her myself,
no problem at all, 'kay?
[REINHARD]
Very well then.
If I see her, then I'll be sure
to relay your message.
Thanks a lot.
I'll repay you one day!
[REINHARD]
Sure!
Take care.
[GUY A] You're lookin'
for Felt's den, huh?
You're close.
Just head straight this way
another two blocks or so.
[SUBARU] Great. Thanks,
I appreciate it, man.
Hey, not a problem at all, kid.
Now live strong and take care.
[SUBARU] The question is whether
Felt will come back there
before the meeting.
I'd rather catch her before she
makes her way to the loot house
and trade her the cell
phone for the insignia,
which should prevent--
[ELSA] Oh, dear! I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. Sorry!
I don't look it, but toughness
is one thing I've... got...
[gasps]
[ELSA giggles]
[ELSA] What's wrong? You
don't have to be so scared.
I'm not gonna do
anything to you.
What? I'm not scared!
Just a little
surprised, that's all.
Whatever gave you that idea?
[ELSA]
Your scent....
When people are scared,
I can smell the fear on them
like a kind of perfume.
And you're definitely
scared right now.
You're angry as
well, aren't you?
At me.
[ELSA]
It's fine.
I am rather curious,
but now isn't the time
to start a commotion.
That's not a very
nice thing to say.
If you're too scary, that beauty
of yours will go to waste.
Oh, very good.
Conceal your hostility,
and you'll be even better.
[ELSA]
Well, I'll be going now.
Something tells me
we'll meet again.
[sighs]
[SUBARU] What a dump.
Someone actually lives here?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say Elsa had already been
here and trashed the place.
I-It's fine, I'm sure.
I don't smell blood.
It does smell like a bunch
of garbage, though.
[FELT]
Hey!
What do you think you're doin',
peeking into someone's house?
You're wasting your time.
There's nothing worth
stealing in there, anyway.
Now, beat it!
No, hang on a second!
That's not what I was doing!
Don't gimme that!
Whoa! Stop it!
Calm down! This is no time to
fight! It's gonna be dark soon!
[FELT] Before then,
you'd better be gone.
[SUBARU] I already told you,
you've got it all wrong!
You don't give up, do you?
I told you to get
outta here, so do it!
Stop it! Just listen to me!
[gasps]
[SUBARU screams]
[SUBARU] P-Please! Listen to
me! Just hear me out, Felt!
[FELT]
Hm?
I'm here on important
business, okay?!
How do you know
my name, anyway?
Do you want me to steal
something for ya?
You shoulda just said so.
You're the one who attacked
me right off the bat!
This is a greedy business
you're running, you know that?!
Do you pride yourself on
your sticky fingers?!
I'm just tryin' to
stay alive out here.
If it weren't for this, I'd be
forced to sell my body.
So what do you want
with me? Spit it out.
There's only one thing I want,
and that's to buy the
insignia you stole,
right here and now!
My client didn't mention any
partners when I was hired.
Hang on, are you a business
rival or something?
Call her a rival, or call her
the one who killed my parents,
or the one who killed me, even.
At the end of the day, it
doesn't make any difference.
You're not making any sense.
But when it comes down to it,
I only care about selling
to whoever pays the most.
If you've got an offer that
might be profitable to me,
I'll listen.
How shrewd. It's all
about the money.
I have a rare item in my
possession that's worth
more than 20 holy coins.
I want to buy your
insignia with it.
And it's something that's
in high demand nowadays.
See? A metia.
[SUBARU]
That is the power of a metia!
This little number is
a one-of-a-kind item
that can capture and
freeze a moment in time.
So how about it?
Well, you don't
seem to be lying...
But is that supposed to be me?
I look much prettier than that.
If you look this good without
makeup, you're doing just fine.
Don't complain about it.
[FELT] It is unusual,
I'll give you that much.
But I really doubt it's worth
more than 20 holy coins.
You're a prospective
buyer in this situation.
You don't think I'm
just gonna believe
whatever you tell me
as fact, now do you?
Come on.
[SUBARU] I see your point...
No, probably not.
There's a loot house down at
the far edge of these slums.
Think the fair thing to do is
have it appraised by the guy
who lives there, Old Man Rom.
So it still comes to that...
Okay, got it. Let's go.
Right now! Let's get
moving! On the double!
We'll just have him
take a look at it
and then get out of there
as soon as possible!
[FELT]
Take it easy!
What's your problem? Slow down!
Why're you in such a hurry?
You're sweating like crazy.
Oh, well, anyway, live strong.
Someone else here in the slums
said that a little earlier.
Is it like a slogan
or something?
Look, don't lump me in
with those other guys.
They're all talk. They don't
"live strong" at all.
They're nothing but a
bunch of stingy losers
who've got nothing
going for them.
[SUBARU] Wow, that's kinda
harsh. Judgmental much?
I'm not like the other
people around here, okay?
I have no intention of living
out the rest of my life
in these dingy,
dirty back alleys!
Is that so?
And you think 20 holy coins
will make these dreams
of yours come true?
Not by themselves,
but it would be a huge
leap toward my goal.
Even if I were alone, it's
not as if I couldn't get by
with some effort.
If you were alone?
[FELT]
Just forget it.
What are you standing
there smirking about?
You really piss me off,
ya know that?
Don't worry about it.
H-Hey, what are you doing?
Stop!
I'll make this all
work out somehow.
It's something only I can do.
Don't get all sentimental one me
while you're babbling nonsense!
I'll bite you!
[SUBARU]
It's not just for her.
I'll change the fate
that's waiting for me.
And to do that, I'll...
[FELT]
I told you to cut it out!
[SUBARU screams]
[ROM]
Hmm...
So this is a metia...
Well, I've heard of 'em,
but I've never seen
one with my own eyes.
[SUBARU]
It's a fairly delicate device,
so I suggest you
handle it with care.
Just think of it
along the lines of,
"If you break it,
you have to die."
In the sense that
you get no do-overs.
[ROM]
Yeah, I'm definitely impressed.
If I were to sell this,
I'd take no less than
15, no, 20 holy coins.
'Cause I'd likely not
come across one again.
So it's worth at least that.
[SUBARU chuckles]
[SUBARU] All right!
Negotiations complete!
Now, if we're done talkin',
let's go for drinks to celebrate
a properly completed sale!
What do you say?!
[FELT]
Hold it.
Why are you in such
a hurry to leave?
Well, life doesn't last
forever, you know?
Make every second count.
Don't waste any time.
Live every moment--
[FELT] Yeah, yeah. I don't
care about all that stuff.
Fess up.
Why exactly do you want the
insignia so badly anyway?
I mean, if I've got two
interested parties
in this thing, it must be worth
a lot more than it looks.
That's why everyone's
gunning for it.
In other words,
in an open bidding,
this would sell for way
more than a me--
Hang on, Felt!
You're stepping into dangerous
territory right now!
You heard what
the metia's worth!
You're getting a good deal here!
Just trade it to me
and be done with it!
El-- I mean the woman
who asked you for it
can't go higher
than 20, either.
She's not gonna
pay more than that!
[FELT]
Hmph.
How do you know what
she's willing to pay?
So you're not working
together, huh?
You're tryin' to con me.
It's not like that!
Please, we're running
out of time!
Begging will get you nowhere.
I'll be fair and acknowledge
you as a negotiating party.
But it wouldn't be right not to
hear from my original client.
[SUBARU] Okay, fine. The reason
I want that insignia...
...is so I can go and
return it to its owner.
[FELT]
Huh?
I need to take it back
to the one it belongs to.
That's why I want
the insignia, okay?
It's the truth! So please!
Listen, I don't
think he's lying.
I've got a sense about
these sorts of things.
Now don't get
taken in by his act.
He's obviously not sincere.
Return it to the owner?
Ridiculous!
If you're gonna lie,
make it believable!
I won't be fooled,
you got that?!
Felt, please...
[knocking]
Who could that be?
[FELT]
It's probably for me.
It's a little early, though.
[SUBARU]
Don't open it!
[FELT]
Huh?
We'll be killed!
I'm not here to kill you!
Why would you think I'd try
and do something so insidious?
[gasps]
[grunts]