As long as you do not resist,
I can make your death
a painless one.
[SUBARU]
Why...? Why are you doing this?
Look, might be a cliché to ask,
but I gotta know.
It's simply the rule of maids.
"If someone's suspicious,
punish them."
Tell me, does Ram know, too?
I intend to finish
this before my sister
sees anything.
[SUBARU]
Is that...
Is that how little
you trusted me?
Yes.
[SUBARU gasps]
Damn, I'm so pathetic.
And I was so sure that
we were getting along well...
My sister--
[SUBARU] I don't wanna
hear it! Take this!
--[SUBARU grunts]
--[REM gasps]
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU grunts, yells]
[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU screaming]
[SUBARU]
My leg!
[screaming]
[REM] Mana of water,
heal this damaged body.
If I let you die too quickly,
then I won't be able to get
any information out of you.
[REM] If you had
stabbed me with this,
you would have been
able to flee a bit further.
I ask you this...
Are you a faction
member supporting
one of Miss Emilia's
rivals for the throne?
My heart belongs
to Mee-Lee forever,
until the end of--
[screams]
Answer me. Who hired you?
And under what conditions?
[SUBARU] Mee-Lee's smile did,
and it was priceless--
[SUBARU screaming]
Let's try again.
Are you affiliated
with the Witch's Cult?
The Witch's Cult?
I don't know what that is.
My family's been secular
for generations. Why--
Don't you play dumb with me!
[SUBARU gasps]
Your bald-faced lies
can only take you so far
when the foul stench of
the witch is covering you
from head to toe!
Every time I watched
you conversing with my sister,
I felt as if I would
go out of my mind
with anger and unrest...
Someone associated with the one
who has caused my sister
so much agony having the
audacity to boldly encroach
on the place in which
she and I belong...
I can't bear it any longer.
Even if I know deep down
my sister only acts friendly
with you and only
pretends to care for you!
[SUBARU crying]
[SUBARU]
Look...
I don't cut my hands...
...when I peel
vegetables anymore.
I can read. And I can
even write now, too.
Just the basics, but hey...
I kept my word
and I studied hard.
I can read those
fairy tales...
All thanks to you two...
Fairy tales?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
all the wonderful things
you guys gave me.
I have no memory of any of that.
[SUBARU crying]
Why?!
Why don't you remember?!
Why do all of you keep
leaving me behind like this?
What did I ever do to you?!
What am I supposed to do?!
What did I do wrong?!
I don't understand!
Why do you guys
hate me so much?!
[crying]
Even when you said
you'd cut my hair...
[crying]
All that time, I...
[SUBARU crying]
[REM]
I...
I really like you both. You--
[RAM]
My sister... is too kind.
[SUBARU gasps]
[REM]
Sir, have you awakened?
[RAM]
Sir, you're awake?
[SUBARU panting]
[screams]
[EMILIA]
Subaru, what was that all about?
Ram and Rem
were really worried.
They were
unusually despondent,
wondering if they'd
been impolite...
[SUBARU]
Don't worry about it...
Nothing happened
between them and me.
Subaru, are you all right?
Cause if something's
troubling you,
you're welcome
to talk to me about it.
[SUBARU] If I could tell
Emilia that it's no use,
that I can't take any more...
[SUBARU gasps]
Wait. That's it.
[EMILIA]
What?
[SUBARU]
All this time...
I've been struggling
to change things alone...
But what if...
Subaru, are you
sure you're okay?
There's something important
I want to tell you.
Yes?
[SUBARU]
Emilia...
Several times up until now,
believe it or not, I've died...
[SUBARU]
Whoa...
Wait...
This is seriously no joke...
What's happening?!
[EMILIA]
What is it?
[SUBARU gasping]
Subaru!
What happened all of a sudden?
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU]
My body moves.
My voice works.
My heart doesn't hurt.
But...
The fear is engraved in me...
Wh-What's wrong?
You've been acting
really strange.
Tell me if
something's going on--
[SUBARU]
I have a favor to ask.
Yes?
I want you to have
nothing to do with me.
[EMILIA gasps]
[SUBARU] I can't tell anyone
about Return by Death.
I've died in this
mansion three times.
I didn't experience a fourth
time while I was in the capital.
If I die again...
I might not come back...
[BEATRICE] My, that's quite
a cowardly look on your face,
I suppose.
[SUBARU]
Why are you here?
Bubby and the brat told me
I should take a moment
to stop by and check on you.
You mean Puck and Emilia?
Since you were acting
so strange earlier,
I believe they suspect
that I did something to you
when you first
woke up, I suppose.
My goodness, talk about rude!
I get it.
I'm okay now.
You came here
to apologize to me.
That's enough.
And why in the world
should I apologize to you,
I suppose?!
I can't leave until I correct
that preposterous notion.
Hmm...
Not only do you look gloomy,
but that disgusting scent I
noticed before is heavier now!
Huh?
The stench of
the witch, I suppose.
I feel like it's
bending my nose.
Wait a second...
You mean the Witch of Envy?
Well, of course I do!
What else in this world
would somebody mean
when they bring up a witch?
What are you talking about?
Why do you smell her on me?
Meh...? I don't know.
Regardless, as someone who
receives special attention
from her, you're a burden.
It's not comforting
to hear I'm getting
special treatment from
someone I've never even met.
If you have nothing
to say, I'm leaving.
I'll tell Bubby everything
that you told me,
I suppose.
Goodbye.
Hey, wait a minute!
You feel sorry for what
you did to me, right?
[BEATRICE]
I do not.
[SUBARU]
I'm telling Puck!
Well, I might feel just
a teeny-tiny bit sorry,
I suppose.
If you regret what you did
and want my forgiveness,
do me the one favor
that I ask of you.
[BEATRICE]
Fine, let's hear it.
I'm not sure what's happening,
but I want you to keep me safe.
Until the fifth morning comes,
the day after tomorrow.
[BEATRICE] I don't want
you bringing dissension
into this mansion, I suppose.
For various reasons, this place
is vitally important to me.
[SUBARU] I have no intention
of doing anything.
I just want to stop
any sparks from flying.
What an admirable
motive for one who leaves
even something like that
in the hands of others.
Strangely enough, for once,
I have no response to that.
[BEATRICE sighs]
[BEATRICE]
Hold out your hand.
I have decided that
I shall grant your wish.
I, Beatrice, on my honor,
am henceforth bound
by this contract.
[BEATRICE] Temporary or not,
a contract must be upheld.
I will grant you the nonsense
favor you requested.
Come on, seriously?
I'm gonna cry
because of a little girl?
Don't you ever
call me a little girl!
And if you tell Bubby, you're
gonna regret it, I suppose!
Hmph!
Is it really that
important to you?
That desperation of yours
is demonically inspired.
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU]
No! Stop!
[SUBARU panting]
[BEATRICE] Come on. You can't
keep sleeping forever,
I suppose.
[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU]
Oh, that hurt!
I came against my will because
it's the designated time,
yet you seem
awfully unconcerned.
Did I really fall
asleep on the fourth day?
What kind of reckless
idiot am I?
[BEATRICE]
Quit your grumbling, I suppose.
Sit wherever you want,
but do it quietly.
The forbidden archive?
Did you carry me in here
while I was asleep?
Given the option, I'd rather
not stay in that room
filled with your
stench, I suppose.
The forbidden library
is the only place for me.
Now, observe proper
manners, I suppose.
Hey, Beatrice.
I'm sure I'm wrong,
but you didn't hold my hand
while I was asleep, did you?
You are absolutely wrong.
Even if Bubby asked me to,
I would still refuse, I suppose.
Flat-out denial, huh?
I'm not sure what you
mean by "proper manners."
So, hey, are you--
[BEATRICE] You're annoying
me with all your questions!
Just be still
and quiet, I suppose.
They're calling...
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[BEATRICE]
I've been summoned, I suppose.
[SUBARU gasps]
Oh... That's right,
you're here.
I forgot, I suppose.
[SUBARU]
H-Hey, hold on!
If you go out there now...
[BEATRICE] Guess it's fine
if you want to stay.
You'll be safe here, I suppose.
[SUBARU grunts]
Damn it, come on!
What the hell is this?
[door opens]
[SUBARU]
The sun...?
Did I... make it through
the fourth night?
[chuckles]
And I figured that doing
so was next to impossible.
In the end,
it was that easy...
[chuckling]
[EMILIA]
Subaru?
[SUBARU]
Emilia...
There you are.
Where have you been?
[SUBARU]
Oh, I was just... uh...
You know...
No. Never mind.
Here. Come with me.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
Where are we going?
Uh, Mee-Lee...
Why are you making that face?
Everything's gonna
be just fine now.
I mean, look.
I'm still alive, right?
And you're...
Oh, I know!
Let's go to the village!
There's so much I want
to do and tell you about!
So much has happened!
[EMILIA]
Subaru...
Wait, what's the matter?
[RAM screaming]
[RAM crying]
[crying continues]
[SUBARU]
But, how...?
Why...? Why is Rem dead?
[RAM crying]
[SUBARU grunts]
Don't you touch her!
Don't touch Rem...
Keep your hands
off my little sister!
It appears that she
died of weakness.
It was as if she
just fell asleep.
The method was more
of a curse than a spell.
[SUBARU] I thought it was
Rem who used that curse.
So she isn't the shaman?
[ROSWAAL] My dear guest,
have you any idea
what might have happened here?
After this has happened to
a dear member of my staff,
I seem to be a tiny
bit angry, you see...
[EMILIA]
Subaru...
If you know anything,
then please tell us.
[SUBARU] I just want to spill
it all and get it off my chest.
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU yells]
[RAM] If you know something,
you'd better tell me!
I'm warning you!
[SUBARU]
Wait, Ram! That's a--!
I always uphold
my end of promises.
As long as he continues
to remain in this mansion,
I am contracted to
protect him, I suppose.
B-But, Miss Beatrice...!
Roswaal, he spent last night
in the forbidden library.
So surely, he couldn't have
had anything to do with--
There's no further
need to emphasize
the situation at hand.
However, Beatrice...
If you agreed to guard
him with your life,
you must have taken
quite a liking to him.
Save the jokes for your
makeup and weird fetishes,
I suppose.
[RAM gasps]
Stop it...
None of that even matters!
Get out of the way!
Let me through!
I must avenge Rem.
If you know anything,
then you have to tell me.
Help me. Help Rem!
Say something!
[RAM crying]
I'm sorry, Ram.
Despite all this,
I'm choosing to trust him.
Subaru, please.
If you can save Ram...
If you can save Rem,
I beg you...
Please do so.
I'm sorry.
[EMILIA]
Subaru!
[SUBARU panting]
[RAM]
I'm going to kill you!
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU]
I ran.
As fast as I could.
I ran away from them.
[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU]
I can't go back there again.
What choice did I
have back there?!
What could I have...
And I was... having
so much fun with them!
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU] This looks like
the place where I died.
Is this it?
[SUBARU] If I die, will I be
saved from this whole situation?
Of course...
If I do, everything will change.
If I struggled and fought
so much only to end up here,
then what's the point?
[SUBARU]
The cliff...
[SUBARU] If I close my
eyes and take one step,
it'll all be over.
[SUBARU]
What will happen to me...
...if I die again?
[SUBARU]
It's just one more step...
I can't even...
...do something
as simple as that...
[BEATRICE]
I finally found you.
[SUBARU]
Why...
What's the matter, I suppose?
Why did you come
out here for me?
Didn't I...
How quickly you forget.
The contract I entered
into was to protect you.
You're still my bodyguard?
I thought you were
only supposed to do that
until this morning...
In that case, you must
be mistaken, I suppose.
I don't remember discussing
there being a time limit.
Clinging to faint hope just
serves your own convenience,
I suppose.
What was lost
can't be reclaimed.
You'll have no more
chances to explain yourself
to the older sister.
That opportunity
has come and gone.
No matter which is lost,
they'll never be
complete again, I suppose.
[SUBARU]
But...
I really cared about
those two very much,
and I wanted to do whatever
I could to protect them...
[BEATRICE]
Why...?
What do you know
about them, I suppose?
Either way,
they'll never be restored
to what they once were.
They can't be.
So, in the end...
What I was really doing
was making a selfish,
disgraceful fuss without
actually knowing
anything at all.
[BEATRICE]
At the very least,
you need to die
where I can't see you,
or I'll just have
bad dreams, I suppose.
So I'll do what I can to help
you escape this territory.
[SUBARU]
Come to think of it, back then,
somebody was holding
both of my hands...
[SUBARU]
Ram... Rem...
If they couldn't bear to see me
suffering and in pain...
And they held both my hands...
If that's the kind
of people they are,
how can I leave them?
[RAM]
I'm going to kill you!
[SUBARU] I heard a voice
filled with hatred.
But more than that...
[RAM screams]
[SUBARU]
Her cries were haunting.
They won't leave my mind.
[SUBARU] All my life,
I've always been the type
to drift toward whichever
path was easiest.
[SUBARU] Hey, Subaru,
you're thinking of something
pretty stupid here.
And after all I that went
through to save this life...
That's right.
I simply saved
my own life, so then...
[SUBARU] What's wrong with
taking the path that's easiest
that will let me live longer?
I'll decide...
...how I use my life!
Afraid you were a bit too slow.
I finally found you.
I'm not gonna let you get away.
[BEATRICE]
Stay back, I suppose.
So long as my contract exists,
I won't hold back,
not even against you.
And you, Miss Beatrice,
you seem to have forgotten
we're not in the mansion now.
We're in the forest,
away from the forbidden library.
Are you so certain that
you'll be able to protect him
from me?
[SUBARU chuckling]
Oh, yeah, that feels good!
[BEATRICE panting]
What are you doing,
you buffoon?!
Do you want to die
or something?!
'Course not, don't be dumb.
That isn't what I want at all.
I only wanna die once,
at the end of a long
and happy life.
That's how I really feel.
You've got guts.
So you finally accept your fate?
That's not a very
accurate description.
If anything, I would say that
now I've made up my mind.
Sorry. I caused a lot
of grief for you guys
by being such a pathetic loser.
[RAM] So you do know
something about Rem!
Nope. Sorry, but I honestly
don't know a thing.
Frankly, there's
too much I don't know.
Even so...
I decided to learn
more about the things
I don't understand,
and to not be in the dark.
How can you possibly say that?!
My sister, Rem, is already dead!
What can you do by
learning anything now?!
It's way too late for that!
I won't make any cool statements
about what I'll be able to do.
After all, this is what happened
when I couldn't do anything.
I know better than
anyone that my words
aren't convincing in the least.
But I do remember.
I know parts of you two
that you've forgotten!
What are you saying?!
What is it you think you
know about Rem and me?!
Don't get me wrong.
'Cause in the grand
scheme of things,
what I know
doesn't really matter.
But it does to me!
And you have no idea
what it is, do you?!
Tell me!
I care! For all of you!
Every one of you
means the world to me!
[SUBARU growls]
Wait!
This is something only I can do!
[RAM]
I'm going to kill you!
[SUBARU]
I'm going to save you!
[crash]