That familiar ceiling again...
[REM]
Sister, Sister.
It would appear that our
guest is still half-asleep.
[RAM]
Rem, Rem.
For one who's so young in age,
it's quite sad how
out of it he is.
[REM]
What's wrong, sir?
Do you feel unwell?
Is there pain?
[RAM]
What's wrong, sir?
Do you have a chronic
illness flaring up?
[SUBARU]
Let me see your hands.
[REM, RAM]
Uh...
[SUBARU]
Ah...
So it's true, then...
Thought so.
I'm glad I wasn't mistaken.
[REM]
No, sir.
I think you are definitely
mistaken about everything.
No sir, not at all.
I honestly think your
very birth was a mistake.
[SUBARU] When I think
about what's coming,
that comment's kinda
hard to laugh off...
But right now,
even that's a good feeling.
Sister, Sister.
Could our guest
be a troubled man
who takes pleasure from torture?
Rem, Rem.
Our guest appears
to be a big pervert
who's somehow
turned on by insults.
Sorry to do that
out of the blue,
but I trust you both,
so it's all good.
Let's be friends, okay?
[EMILIA]
It was awfully noisy,
so I thought I should check.
I'm glad to see you're
feeling better, Subaru.
There was a whole lot on my mind
just a few seconds ago,
but seeing you
blew it all away, Mee-Lee!
I guess you were the
miracle wonder drug
that my heart needed.
Sorry, but I have no idea
what you're saying.
Good morning, though.
I'm glad you're up and about.
Good morning to you.
Okay, then. Guess I might
as well get started.
All right, I want you
to hire me on
to work in this place!
[SUBARU] There are two broad
conditions I need to clear
in order to survive a week
in Roswaal's mansion.
The first one is to earn
the trust of the staff here.
If I don't gain the
favor of those two girls,
they're likely to kill
me to keep me silent.
The "winning them over"
plan goes not only
for Rem and Ram,
but for their master,
Roswaal, as well.
And the second one
is to defeat the shaman
that attacks his mansion.
Let's do this.
I'm exhausted...
You're quite the hard
worker, aren't ya?!
[SUBARU]
I'm not done yet.
I still need to prepare
dinner and clean the rooms.
I'll just take a quick break,
then get back to work.
It's your first day,
and you're so pumped up.
I'm only tryin' to do my part.
Besides, some important
things are at stake here.
By the way, exactly
what kind of magic
does Mee-Lee use, anyway?
Technically speaking,
Lia doesn't really use magic.
And for that matter,
her contract with me
doesn't, either.
She's a spirit arts user.
You mean magic users
and spirit arts users
are different?
Magic users are
able to cast magic
by using their own mana.
On the other hand,
spirit arts users are able
to draw their power from
mana in the atmosphere.
And just what makes
those two different,
Professor Puck?
[PUCK] Basically, it depends
on whether or not
you use a gate.
[SUBARU]
A gate?
Exactly!
Mana passes through a gate
that's within your body.
You draw mana in as
well as expel it out
through that gate.
[SUBARU] I see.
So it's like a faucet for MP.
You should have
one, too, Subaru.
Whoa, really?!
So you're saying that I
can also use magic, then?
Want me to figure out what
your magical attribute is?
Magic users are divided
into four categories:
Fire, water, wind, and earth.
[PUCK]
Meow meow meow..
[SUBARU] That's a totally
magic sound effect!
[PUCK] I now know
what your attribute is.
Yes! I can't wait for this!
Is it the fire of passion?
Or a relaxed,
cool-guy water type?
A gentle wind blowing
across the plain?
Or possibly the solid,
reliable earth?
[PUCK]
It's shadow.
Are you serious?!
Wow, you got shadow?
That's quite a rare one.
[SUBARU]
So, what is "shadow," anyway?
Must be a category error!
Weren't there
only four attributes?
[PUCK] In addition
to the four basic ones,
there're two bonus categories:
shadow and light.
I bet it's something amazing!
A talent that comes along
once in 5,000 years!
With the shadow
magic attribute,
you can obstruct an
opponent's vision,
block sound, slow down
their movements,
and other things like that.
[SUBARU]
It's just debuffs?!
An easy one would be
something like Shamac.
[EMILIA]
Of course...
That's a blinding spell,
isn't it?
[PUCK]
Hmm!
Would you like me to show you?
--[SUBARU] For real?! Yeah!
--[EMILIA] Wait, Puck!
And Shamac!
[SUBARU gasps]
[choking]
[grunting]
[PUCK]
Okay, that's it.
So what'd you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
[EMILIA]
Are you all right?
Yeah! I'm totally fine!
It's not too flashy,
but it seems pretty effective!
So you're saying that I can use
this Shamac thing, too, right?
Well, that all depends
on your training.
Do you wanna try
the beginner's course?
Very much so! Please, Master!
[PUCK] I'll be here to act as
support and use the mana
inside you so the
magic will be coming
from your own gate.
Lia, in case Subaru's
magic goes out of control
and explodes,
you should step away
so your clothes don't get messy.
That's a really long way away!
You don't think I'm gonna
mess up that bad, do you?!
Not if you're relaxed enough
to make those kinda comments.
Now, let's begin...
Visualize the flow of
mana through your body,
then expel a part of it out
of your body through your gate.
Got it?
Visualizing I can do.
I fantasize like a champ.
Meow meow meow...
Meow meow...
What the--?
Well, that's not good.
Looks like the gate just...
[SUBARU yelling]
Long story short,
you don't have very good
control over your gate,
so I suggest you
shouldn't try too hard.
[SUBARU] You're the one
who said I'd be fine.
[PUCK chuckles]
That's so not cute.
[PUCK]
Well, for better or for worse,
it doesn't seem like your
gate is very well used.
That would explain
why the mana inside
ignored the user's will and
simply burst its way out.
What am I?
Some kinda soy sauce bottle
w-with a loose cap?
You shouldn't move.
That little experiment used
up all the mana in your body.
You might not be able
to work anymore today...
[SUBARU]
No! I have to!
Don't try to overdo it!
This is exactly when
I need to overdo it!
I can't waste a single day!
Goodness, you
really are hopeless.
Take this.
[SUBARU]
What--
Chew it up.
[SUBARU]
Hm?
Chew it up and swallow it.
Ready? Go!
[SUBARU yelling]
Whoa.
What did I just eat?
A little something
called a "bocco fruit."
When you eat one of these,
the mana in your body activates,
and then your gate regains
some of its strength back.
Sorry.
I guess I've caused you
some trouble, haven't I?
I don't think you
understand, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
It's infinitely more satisfying
to hear a single "thank you"
than to be subjected
to a barrage of
"sorry" after "sorry."
I did it because
I wanted to help you,
not because I was
looking for an apology.
Okay?
So, given what you've
seen of our new guest
and everything he can do so far,
what do you think
of him, dear Ram?
[RAM] In terms of abilities,
he's completely incompetent,
but he can be excessively
quick-witted when it counts.
I believe it may be necessary
to keep an eye on him
for a time.
[ROSWAAL] This is a problem we
must handle with the utmost care
and caution.
And I ask that you be sure
to give the proper warnings
to your sister so that
she doesn't act rashly.
[SUBARU] I guess that's
about all I can expect
of the first day.
I earned quite a bit of trust
from Ram and Rem, I think.
Way to go.
But the bigger problem here
is that shaman's attack...
How do I go about fighting that?
[BEATRICE] You want to know
more about shamans, I suppose?
Yeah.
Like, "how do you avoid
curses," for instance.
There is no way to do so.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
It's impossible to undo a
curse once it's been activated,
I suppose.
Once they've begun, that's it.
That's what curses are.
It's possible to nullify
instant death resistances?
However, before
they're activated,
curses are nothing more
than simple spells,
so I can easily undo them.
[sniffs]
That is the witch's scent...
You know,
Rem mentioned that, too.
Who is this witch?
Are all of these witches
related to shamans
in any way?
In this world, when one
says the word "witch,"
they're really just referring
to one person in particular.
The Witch of Envy, right?
Exactly.
The Witch of Envy, Satella.
Long ago, she devoured
the six witches
who bore the names
of the deadly sins,
and drained half the world dry.
She's pretty much the worst
of the worst, I suppose.
The story goes that
she was starved for love.
It's said that she doesn't
understand human language.
It's also been said that her
body never withers from age,
weakens from sickness, or dies.
And although she was sealed
by the powers of a dragon,
a hero, and a sage,
they were still never
able to destroy her flesh.
It's said
that her body is that of a
half-elf with silver hair.
[EMILIA]
It's...
...Satella.
[SUBARU] What would it take
to make somebody steal
the Witch of Envy's name?
Hang on, I guess "steal"
makes the person
sound bad...
Maybe I should say
to make somebody "borrow"
the Witch of Envy's
name instead.
Either way, they must
have no fear of death,
I suppose.
One who would steal the
name of the Witch of Envy
can be called
nothing but insane.
I see...
--So that's why.
--[BEATRICE] Huh?
She wouldn't have to be involved
in this royal selection mess
if everyone just saw her
as some kind of crazy freak.
What are you talking about?
Nothing at all,
don't worry about it.
[SUBARU]
Good morning!
It's another sunny day,
perfect for drying laundry!
Let's make this a day
filled with happiness!
Make this a day of victory!
[SUBARU]
Victory!
You're so energetic
again this morning.
[SUBARU]
Yep!
Even as I'm ordered
around and disciplined
by the maid sisters,
I'll enjoy my life of servitude
to the fullest once again!
But when that lifestyle
wears me out,
and you know it will, I'll come
rest my head in your lap.
So save it for me, okay?
When you wash
your face that way,
you really look like a cat!
So, do spirits get
sleepy and worn out?
Do they ever oversleep?
[PUCK] Yeah, don't you
people get sleepy
when you're fatigued, too?
Spirits can go through
something that's similar
when their mana... is depleted.
[EMILIA yawns]
Did you two
stay up all night?
I bet you were up late talking
about who you like, right?
That's it, isn't it?
Come on, let me in on the fun!
Huh? So who do I like?
Well, uh...
It's embarrassing to say, but...
The one that
I like is Puck,
and the one that
Puck likes is me.
There. Conversation's over.
It's mutual?!
Then where do I fit in?!
Nowhere.
Lia is head-over-heels
for my charms.
It's not like you're
a bad guy or anything,
but compared to me,
you've got nothing to offer.
Gah!
You should give up
on Lia and just--
[SUBARU, PUCK yell]
Don't get carried away,
you two.
I'm going to get mad if
you keep up this foolishness!
Sorry! Sorry!
Didn't mean to make you mad!
[SUBARU]
Whoopsie!
I'd better get going, or the
maid sisters will be angry!
Bye!
[PUCK]
Hey, what's wrong?
You don't look very happy.
I just feel...
...sort of uneasy.
I don't think
I can explain it...
[PUCK] Well, I can't exactly
blame you for being confused.
'Cause this has gotten
to be kind of a problem.
Hey, don't worry!
Forget about it!
Everything's fine!
What do you mean, "problem"?
Just relax, okay?
I'll clean this up so fast,
no one will get hurt!
See? Already done!
What I'm saying is...
Subaru's mind is mixed up.
The inside and outside
are all jumbled.
I think that attitude of
yours is quite admirable,
but you were the one
who knocked it over
in the first place.
I'll go find a replacement--
No, that's okay!
Let me take care of
the vase and flowers!
I insist!
You can just keep
doing your own work!
[PUCK] If he keeps this
state of confusion going,
he'll wear himself
out before long.
[SUBARU sighs]
It feels pretty
great to finish a job,
huh, Rem-Rem?
It was work that you created
and then took care of
on your own, though.
When did you learn
where the vases are kept?
[REM]
Did my sister...
That's right!
Your sister told me!
Since she knows me and
how much of a klutz I am,
she said, "You're bound to
break a vase eventually.
I'll tell you where
the extra vases are
so you'll always be prepared."
--[SUBARU laughing]
--[REM] Subaru...
Whoops!
I totally forgot about some work
that Ram asked me to do!
Would you excuse me for a bit?
I can take care of it quick.
See you later!
I'll come find you soon!
[SUBARU]
I feel sick...
[chopping]
Don't you think
my knife technique
has come a long way
in just one day?
I think my talent has
finally awakened!
[SUBARU]
I feel sick. I feel sick.
[SUBARU] Rem-Rem,
check out my aptitude
that makes such
amazing crafting possible!
There must be a miracle
residing in my fingertips
right now!
Illusion!
[SUBARU] I feel sick...
I feel sick... I feel sick...
Honestly, Mee-Lee!
Every time we meet,
you stir up my heart!
You're such a sinful girl!
You're guilty, I tell ya!
[SUBARU] I should be
able to laugh better.
I should be able to make
them laugh better.
I can't fail this time.
I can't waste a single second.
I have to throw all
my strength into my work
and produce some
kind of results, or...
Oh, Ram!
I wasn't slacking!
I'll finish up all my work!
Just you wait!
Now, why don't you go
kick back in your room
and take a well-earned
siesta while I--
[SUBARU vomiting]
[SUBARU]
Damn, I look so lame...
I don't have time to
spend whining like this.
You idiot.
Subaru...
Mee-Lee!
Subaru, come with me.
Uh-oh! A personal
invitation? From Mee-Lee?
This is moving so fast!
How joyous!
How embarrassing! How rare!
Say anything!
Tell me to do anything!
For you, I'd dive
into fire, water,
the loot house, anywhere!
Listen to me.
Hey, come on!
The Mee-Lee I know
would never be so cold.
Wait! Are you
some kind of fake?!
No way, that's impossible!
How could anyone else be capable
of looking so gorgeous
that when I see her,
all I want to do is hug her?
All right.
Subaru, you heard me.
[SUBARU]
Wha--?
[EMILIA]
Let's go.
Now, sit down right here.
Can't I sit on
the bed or a chair?
Why does it have
to be the floor?
[EMILIA]
Just sit down!
With pleasure! Right away!
Yes, ma'am!
[EMILIA]
Only this once. All right?
Huh?
[EMILIA]
Your position is a little weird.
And... it tickles a bit...
I can rest in your lap?
Don't say that out loud,
it's embarrassing!
And no looking up here.
Face the wall...
Close your eyes.
You're even more adorable when
you're embarrassed, but...
Why did you suddenly
let me do this, anyway?
I mean, when did I do
something worthy enough
to earn a reward this awesome?
Enough of that weird tough act.
You don't need to
do that right now.
Isn't this what you wanted...?
Didn't you tell me
to lend you my lap
when you were exhausted?
I can't do this all the time,
but today is special.
Hey, it's only my second day
of working here.
If I'm already
completely worn out,
what kind of weakling am I?
It's plain to see
that you're overwhelmed
about something.
But you're not going to tell me
what's really going on, are you?
I don't know if doing
this will make things
any easier for you.
But if it helps at all,
I'm happy to.
[chuckles]
Mee-Lee, come on, now...
You don't have to...
Are you tired?
[SUBARU]
No. I'm totally fine.
Really.
Do you feel troubled?
[SUBARU]
If you're this nice to me,
I'm gonna fall
in love with you...
When you...
I mean... like that...
It's been rough, hasn't it?
[SUBARU]
Yeah... It was rough.
And it was so painful.
I was just so terrified.
I was so sad, it hurt.
It hurt so much,
I thought I'd die.
I tried so hard, and I...
I couldn't get
things to work out!
I was so desperate
to set things right.
So desperate to make
everything turn out okay!
It's the truth!
I've honestly never tried
so hard to do anything
in my entire life!
Yes, I know.
Because I loved
this place so much.
Because it was
so important to me.
I was so scared.
I just...
I was so desperate to set
everything right again!
I didn't want those eyes
looking at me like that.
It was so completely terrifying!
And I hated myself so much.
[crying]
So much for feeling that way...
[REM]
Subaru?
[EMILIA]
Shh.
[REM]
Is he just asleep, or...?
[EMILIA]
Yes.
[chuckles]
He looks like a child,
doesn't he?
A little bit, but he
definitely looks like
he can't do any more work today.
You're right there.
Think he's done for the day.
What a bad boy,
taking all this time off
on his second day working here.
When he feels better,
you can punish him then.
When I see him like this,
I almost don't want to.
[REM] I'll go inform
my sister that Subaru
will be useless for today.
--[EMILIA] Rem...
--[REM] Huh?
Subaru is a good boy.
[SUBARU]
No... Please...!
Did I really just bawl
all over the girl I love
and fall asleep with tears
and snot all over my face?!
Oh, man, I'm so ashamed!
I'm totally hopeless!
What a loser!
You burst in here late at night,
and that's what you say,
I suppose?
[SUBARU] Don't say that, Beako!
We're tight, aren't we? [whines]
What kind of relationship
do you think we--
Wait a sec.
What did you just call me?!
Oh, "Beako"?
Well, I think pet names
are indispensable
when it comes to showing
affection to others.
So I've decided that's
what I'm gonna call you.
It's the best proof of my
affection that I can give.
What do you think?
What a ridiculous
display of goodwill!
That isn't just disgusting;
it's revolting!
Hmph!
[SUBARU] Come on,
don't be so cold, Beako.
The thing is...
I'm really backed into a corner.
I need your help
with those curses,
to be honest with you.
Told you curses can't be undone
once they're activated,
I suppose.
That's right, I remember.
But would it be possible
for you to detect them
before they've been
activated instead?
I am capable of
discovering curses
before that happens, I suppose.
[SUBARU] So... how are
they placed, anyway?
There is one rule
of casting curses
that cannot be broken,
I suppose.
A rule that can't be broken?
Physical contact with
the target of the curse.
That is the single prerequisite.
So far, the only
people I've touched
other than the ones in this
mansion are the villagers
at the base of the mountain.
I was cursed in the village,
and then it activated
in the mansion that night,
and after that I died?
That would explain
why the shaman
was able to get Rem
the last time around.
I didn't go to the village,
so she ended up
being the target.
Yes, that fits.
Everything fits now!
I've finally found a lead!
Hell yeah!
Is that any attitude
to take toward someone
you asked for help, I suppose?
If my insight was
beneficial to you,
I think there's something
you should say.
Wait, of course! That's right!
Thanks for your help!
I can finally
see the light! Yes!
--Beako, I love you!
--[BEATRICE] Enough--
Put me down, now!
[SUBARU]
Dorowazu!
And so, in summary,
a lot's happened,
but today is a fresh start!
I'm a new me!
The lap pillow, right?
Definitely the lap pillow...
[SUBARU]
Huh?
Wait, you guys knew?!
Good morning, Subaru.
Oh! Mee-Lee!
Uh, well...
This is a little
embarrassing, but...
Are you feeling okay today?
I wasn't completely sure
until I heard your voice
just then, but...
Yes, I'm okay now.
So, um, Listen, Mee-Lee...
I'm sorry about what hap--
No. I mean, thanks
for everything.
Of course.
You're most welcome, Subaru.
[REM] Well, are you
ready to get started
on this morning's work?
We need to begin our
list of morning duties.
Before all that, I have
a favor to ask of you...
[REM]
Lap pillow, right?
It's a lap pillow.
[SUBARU]
I'm not that much of a perv!
Actually, I want
to go to the village.
It's not far, right?
Do we have any plans to
go shopping for anything?
Actually, if I recall correctly,
we are low on seasonings,
so I was thinking of going
to the village tomorrow.
Then why don't we
just go today instead?
I mean, if we're running low, it
never hurts to restock sooner!
I don't see a problem
with that at all.
Are you sure, Sister?
You do need to go shopping,
and we have no urgent
duties right now.
Plus, you have Barusu
to carry your packages.
[REM] All right,
if you say so, Sister.
Yes!
However, I'm coming
along with you.
You'll have a pretty
flower on each arm, Barusu.
Huh?
Uh, I'm just hoping...
...those flowers
aren't poisonous...