[SUBARU coughing]
[SUBARU]
No... This is bad... Very bad...
[SATELLA]
Subaru? What's wrong?
I see where this is going.
It's how they suck you in.
[SUBARU]
Run away! Get out of here!
[sighs]
[SATELLA screams]
Ah, maybe this one instead.
[SUBARU]
Stay with me...
That's 363 yen.
[SUBARU]
A jagged-edge ten.
Hang on...
No matter what...
[SUBARU]
...I'm gonna save you...
That's what I get for holing up
in my room all day gaming.
Guess my eyes are tired.
[bell tolls]
[SUBARU]
What's going on?
I'd say I was dreaming, but this
is obviously really happening.
Totally not fake.
So does this mean...
...I've been summoned across
the universe to another world?!
Well, from the looks of things,
I'd say this is some
kind of fantasy world
with a medieval-style culture.
A realm where demihumans
are commonplace,
and there's always a war
or an adventure to go on.
And in this magical
world, I must've...
[CARRIAGE DRIVER]
Hey! Watch out!
This is it!
It's totally happening!
This must be an event pop where
I'll learn to produce magic!
Ha!
[KNIGHT A]
Look out!
[KNIGHT A laughs]
Yes! Woo!
[BOY A]
Well done!
Guess it's a little
too early for me
to use magic in this world.
[SUBARU]
I can't read any of this.
[KADOMON] Hey, boy. Those are
some weird-lookin' clothes.
You're not from
around here, are ya?
So are these...?
Appas, the freshest you'll find.
[SUBARU] At least we
speak the same language.
Let's see if...
Huh? Where's that money from?
You can't use that stuff
out here in Lugunica.
And if that's all you got,
then you're flat broke.
So don't waste my time,
freeloader! Get outta here!
That answers that.
Guess I'll have to stick to good
old information gathering.
[ALL scream]
This place is for
demihumans only!
[SUBARU]
Ow! My eye! I can't... see...
[screams]
Is this how it's supposed to be?
'Cause none of it makes sense.
This is a different-world
summons, right?!
Where's my main character
set-up and status bar?
Damn.
Tch.
[SUBARU] Looks like my
cell phone still works.
But there's no point
in even having it now!
And the gear they've started
me off with is a joke!
If you're gonna summon lazy-ass
kids like me to your world,
you'd better overhaul your
crappy welfare program!
Start me off with an Excalibur
sword or a magic cloak!
And besides, if I were
transported all this way,
where's the cute girl
who brought me here?
Why would she do that
and then bail on me?
Yes! You're finally here!
It's nice to meet
you, cute girl...
What are you goin'
on and on about?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
Aw, crap. It's already
"compulsory event" time.
[FELT]
Move it, move it!
Move it, you guys!
Hurry! Outta my way!
Yes!
I knew you'd find me eventually,
cute girl who summoned me!
[FELT]
Hm? Summoned?
I dunno what you're talkin'
about, but I'm really busy!
Sorry! Now live strong, okay?
Wait, what?!
Where are you going?!
[SUBARU]
So did seeing that make you feel
any less hostile by any chance?
Actually, it rained on our
parade and made things worse.
Of course, it did...
[SUBARU]
Calm down, Subaru Natsuki.
Since ancient times, it's the
rule that anyone summoned
into a different world
displays supernatural powers!
If I just believe in
myself hard enough,
those powers will kick on and
pave my way to future glory!
[SUBARU]
You lumps of EXP!
That's the first time
I ever hit somebody!
Guess I never
expected it to hurt me!
But it doesn't matter.
Because this world is
set up so I'll be strong!
My adrenaline is surging!
I can do anything!
[yelps]
[SUBARU] I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It was all my fault! Seriously!
Forgive me! Please, spare me!
[CHIN]
Woo-hoo!
[SUBARU screaming]
[KAN] Play games with us,
will you?! Die, scum!
You like that?! Huh?!
[GIRL]
That's enough.
[BOTH]
Huh?
And just who in
the hell are you?!
[GIRL] Stop now,
and I'll forgive you.
If you would be so kind as
to give back what you stole.
[TON]
You can't be serious.
[GIRL] Please.
It's very important to me.
I'll turn the other cheek
concerning the other belongings,
but I can't let you have that.
So hand it over.
You mean you didn't
come to save this kid?
[GIRL]
What strange clothes he has...
If you're asking me if I
have any connection to him,
I'd have to say no.
Well, then you've got no
business with us, little girl!
If someone stole from you, it
was that brat who just ran by!
Yeah, what he said!
That way! She ran that way!
[GIRL]
Hmm...
Those three don't
appear to be lying,
so I need to go after her!
[BOTH sigh]
[GIRL]
But regardless of that...
...I can't overlook
what's going on here.
[SUBARU]
Magic?
Mess with us, will you?
I don't care if you can use
magic, I'm gonna kill you!
You think you can win when it's
two against one?! Do you?!
Indeed. Two against
one may be unfair.
[PUCK]
All right, then.
Two against two
should even things up.
Meow.
[TON]
You use the spiritual arts?
Correct. Retreat now,
and I won't chase you.
Decide quickly. I'm in a hurry.
[CHIN]
You bitch!
Next time I see you,
I won't go easy on you!
Do anything to her, and I'll
haunt you and your kin forever.
Not that you'll have any kin
if I take care of things now.
[BOTH gasp]
[SUBARU sighs]
You really saved me. Thank you.
[GIRL]
Don't move.
A-ha! You avert your eyes due
to your guilty conscience.
Looks like my judgment
was spot-on, as always.
[PUCK]
You sure?
I think it was just an
instinctive male reaction
to avoid tension or rudeness.
I didn't sense
any malice at all.
That's enough out of you, Puck.
Now, listen. I want you to
tell me who stole my insignia.
Uh, yeah, really
sorry 'bout this,
but I don't have the slightest
clue to be honest with you.
Wait! Oh no, it couldn't be!
Did I really make a wrong turn,
or maybe come
around the long way?
Heh.
If I were you, I'd hurry after
her before she gets too far.
I could help, if you...
[PUCK] Aw, you shouldn't
have tried to get up.
What should we do?
It's none of our business.
He won't die or anything.
We'll just leave him as-is.
[PUCK]
Really?
Yes, really.
[PUCK] You say that, but
I bet you'll still help him.
[GIRL]
I will not!
[PUCK]
Uh-huh, yeah, right.
Absolutely not!
There's no way I'm gonna
save him, understand?!
[SUBARU] Man... she's even
super cute when she's mad.
That's another world's
fantasy for you.
Whoa, hang on.
Am I on somebody's lap?
[GIRL]
You're awake?
A little weird for a cute girl
to be this hairy, but whatever.
Wait! This can't be right!
[SUBARU yelps]
We were just trying to make
you happy and comfortable
until you woke up.
There's no reason
to get freaked out.
First of all, stop talking
in that high voice.
Nobody with half a brain
would confuse a cat
for the main heroine!
Aww, just listen to you!
Seeing you so happy made turning
myself bigger totally worth it!
I'm not happy at all!
[PUCK chuckles]
[SUBARU]
I'm sorry about this.
You stayed with me the whole
time I was unconscious.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I only stuck around because
there are some things
I want to ask you.
I took the time and trouble
to heal your wounds for you.
I also made Puck
act as your pillow
until you finally woke up.
This was for my own benefit.
But now that you're up,
I need you to repay me in kind.
Well, for such a normal favor,
you're makin' it sound like
I really owe you big time.
That's not the way I see it.
Now then.
You have an idea who
stole my insignia, right?
What?
Hang on, is your insignia
one of those badge things
that shows your social status?
A rather crude description,
but that's it, more or less.
About this big with a
jewel in the center.
I'm sorry, but no matter
how many times you ask,
I still won't know.
[ I see. I guess there's
no helping that.
But you've given
me the information
that you know nothing,
and that answer was in
exchange for healing you,
so I'm still somewhat satisfied
with how things turned out.
Okay?
Well, I'm in quite a
hurry, so I have to go.
Your wounds should
be better now,
but I highly suggest
that next time
you don't do dangerous things
like wander into
deserted alleys alone.
I'm not concerned.
I'm just warning you.
If anything like that
happens to you again,
I already know that saving you
won't be of any benefit to me,
so don't expect any help. Bye!
Sorry. She's so
insincere sometimes.
But don't think
badly of her, okay?
Insincere, huh...
I think this goes beyond that.
She was in such a hurry to
find what was stolen from her,
yet she stopped to help me.
She even came up with that
lame excuse for a favor
even though I'm
a total stranger.
Anyone who lives like that...
...is just gonna end up
wasting their whole life!
Hey! Wait up!
Was there something
else you needed?
Just so you know,
I can only spend
a little more time
with you, okay?
Ah, figured you were
gonna shut me down...
Anyway, you lost something
important, right?
Well, then let me
help you find it.
You said you didn't know
anything about my insignia.
But I can remember her face!
If I see her again, I'll know!
You're so strange.
Well, anyway, I won't be
able to offer you any reward.
Listen, I don't need one.
I'm here because
I wanna thank you.
And to show how much
I appreciate your help.
I didn't do anything
deserving of that.
I told you, I've already
received amicable compensation
for healing your wounds.
In that case...
I guess I'm gonna help
you for my own sake, too.
I should probably set
an objective so, uh...
Right! One good deed per day!
Uh...
I don't sense any malice here,
so I think you can
just accept his offer.
After all, the more shields
between you and ruffians,
the better.
A shield?! That's what
you want me around for?!
I meant what I said, though.
I can't do anything
to reward you.
No problem at all.
Just leave everything to me!
[SUBARU]
I know what I told you before,
but isn't this town too huge
to find one little thing in?
This "town" is the
capital of Lugunica.
How could you possibly
not know that? Uh...
[PUCK] Hey, that's right.
How rude of us!
We haven't asked his name yet.
Shouldn't we all
introduce ourselves?
Oh, yeah, guess so.
Might as well go ahead and get
the ball rolling first, then.
My name is Subaru Natsuki.
Not only am I totally clueless,
I'm also broke beyond compare!
Nice to meet ya!
[PUCK] When that's how
you introduce yourself,
you really do sound hopeless.
And my name is Puck!
It's nice to meet you!
It's very unusual
to see someone
who can touch a spirit
so casually like that.
Where are you from exactly?
Well, if things follow
the usual pattern,
it's a small island
nation to the east.
But Lugunica is the easternmost
nation on our continental map.
There are no more countries
in that direction.
No way, really? There's
nothing east of here?
You have no idea where you are,
you have no money,
you can't read,
and you seem to have no one
around who can help you.
You might be in an even more
precarious position than I am...
Uh, Subaru, right?
[SUBARU]
Uh.
Yes, that's my name.
All that aside, I gotta admit,
you seem like you're
in pretty good shape.
I do try to work out every day.
Ya see, when you're the shut-in
protector of your own house,
you gotta stay fit
as much as possible.
I'm not sure if I understand
exactly what a "shut-in" is,
but I assume it means you're
from a reputable family, right?
[SUBARU]
Hey, what're you...?
[GIRL] Your fingers, too.
They're very pretty.
They don't look like the working
hands of a peasant at all.
And your muscles don't look
like the kind you gain
from doing field work.
Uh, um, yeah, so anyway,
I know your cat's name now,
but I still haven't heard
you say your name yet.
Oh, my name?
[SUBARU chuckles]
It's...
It's Satella.
No family name.
So that's the way you may
address me, all right?
I see. Satella it is.
That's a nice name.
[gasps]
[PUCK sighs]
You have got terrible taste.
Right, time to get
back to askin' around!
[SATELLA]
Subaru...
That child over there, do you
get the feeling she's lost?
Maybe, but what
about our questioning?
That's also important.
But if she's lost,
we have to do something.
I'm in no place to talk
after you saved me,
but do you fully comprehend
the position we're in?
I do.
But there's a little girl who's
crying! You can see that, right?
If you don't want to do
this with me, that's fine.
Thanks for your
assistance, Subaru.
I'm sure I can handle things
on my own from here on out.
But first, I'm gonna
help that little girl.
[gasps]
Hey, there. It looks like
something's the matter.
Maybe I can help you.
Did you come here on your own,
or with your mommy and daddy?
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to make you cry!
I'm just here to help, not to
do anything bad, I promise.
[SUBARU] What you see before
you is a rarity around here.
A jagged-edge ten-yen coin!
Observe closely as
I take this coin
and clutch it
tightly in my hand.
Tight, tight, tight. Like that!
Now, where'd it go?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Well, take a look at this!
I figured out where
the coin was hiding.
Here ya go, it's yours.
Like I said, it's rare,
so take good care of it.
Thank you, sir!
[SUBARU] I see. You got
separated from your mom, huh?
Yeah, that can be kinda scary.
Well, don't worry.
We'll help you.
Me and this young
lady right here?
We'll find them
in no time for ya.
Wow, look at us.
People who don't know
us probably think
they're looking at a
young married couple
and their kid, huh?
Is that embarrassing or what?
[SATELLA] At best I can't really
see you as anything more
than her older brother.
What makes you think
I'm so young, huh?!
Ah! Mommy!
[GIRL A]
Mommy!
It looks like she
finally found her.
Yeah. I'm so relieved.
[SUBARU]
Okay... so...
In my opinion, that whole string
of events with the little girl
was nothin' but a side-quest,
but what benefit will you
insist that you got out of it?
Go on, tell me!
That's easy.
Now we can continue our
search with our minds at ease
knowing we did the right thing.
Anyway, why'd you end up
helping me with that?
Thought you said you
were against the idea.
Could say I just wanted
to show off my magic trick,
but that'd be a lie.
Like I told you before,
finding your insignia
will be my one good
deed for the day!
[SATELLA]
I know that was the plan,
but since you helped
the little girl,
isn't your one good deed over?
You are being super nitpicky!
It doesn't hurt to do more
than one nice thing in a day,
does it?
I just got tomorrow's
out of the way.
My plan is to get a week's
worth of good deeds
taken care of early!
If I were to guess,
you're the type that basically
wastes their whole life, right?
Seriously?
You're the last person who
should be saying that to anyone.
I admit you're not
a bad boy, though.
Why do you act like I'm
so much younger than you?
Honestly, I'm
guessing there aren't
that many differences
between us.
Well, you may think that,
but all of your guesses
would be wrong.
Because... I'm
actually half-elf.
[SUBARU]
Ah, no wonder.
It makes sense now.
From the moment I saw you...
I thought you were cute!
Elves are always
beautiful, aren't they?
[SATELLA gasps]
What is it?
Didn't you hear
what I just said?
Listen, I'm trying to tell
you that I'm a half-elf.
Yeah, I heard you.
[PUCK yells]
What the heck did
you do that for?
I just had to do something
about this unbearable
tingle I'm feeling!
That's the weirdest reason
for punching somebody
I've ever heard.
Though I'll forgive you
since it was squishy.
I didn't hit you in the face
out of anger or anything.
In fact, it was
quite the opposite.
Subaru, you are
such a dunderhead!
Yeah, so who says "dunderhead"
in this day and age?
And why are you insulting
me in the first place?
Ugh! Whatever!
More importantly, we have
to get back to the search.
So let's go.
Hey, wait a minute!
Just running around without
a plan is never a good idea.
There's a basic
rule of searches.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, like revisiting
the scene of the crime.
Where exactly was your
insignia stolen?
And then she told me it
was right around here,
so after I insisted that she
leave everything to me,
I valiantly came back
to this fruit stand
to look for some clues.
I thought I had a customer,
but you're that same
broke kid from earlier.
[SUBARU] You really
wanna take that attitude?
Haven't you noticed I'm
not who I was before?
[KADOMON]
Huh?
Just look who I brought with me!
I bet it's someone who just
might become a regular!
[SATELLA]
Uh, Subaru...
I'm not exactly sure what
you expected of me,
but I actually don't
have any money, either.
[SUBARU]
Huh? S-Seriously?
So what did you
wanna ask me about
now that I'm stuck
here with not one,
but two broke customers, boy?
Well, we're actually
looking for someone,
and we were hoping we could
ask you a few questions,
if you wouldn't mind...
That was a sarcastic
way of saying
I don't have time
for broke losers!
Now get outta here! Scram!
[GIRL A]
Hey, mister!
[ALL]
Huh?
Thanks for your help earlier.
[SUBARU]
What brings you back this way?
It's my husband's shop,
so we just wanted to stop by.
[KADOMON sighs]
Your husband?
[KADOMON]
Hey, there's my girl.
Now wait a second,
how exactly do you know
these two good-for-nothings?
She got lost, and
these two found her,
then helped bring
her back to me.
[SUBARU chuckles nervously]
Thanks again, lady. Here!
She was hoping we'd find you.
Please accept that token as
her way of showing gratitude
for what you've done.
Thank you very much.
[KADOMON clears throat]
Sorry about all that before.
You helped my daughter,
and I wanna show
my appreciation,
so ask me anything.
There, you see?
A little bit of extra effort
on our part came back around
and worked in our favor!
The air, the atmosphere,
and, most likely,
the attitudes of the people
living here are awful.
Are you sure she's
really out here?
You're sayin' she's a
nimble little blonde, right?
'Cause it might
be that Felt girl
I see around from time to time.
She's well-known in the slums.
Dunno where she lives, though.
That's about all I can tell ya.
[SATELLA] Maybe someone
will tell us if we ask.
[PUCK]
No one would sell out their own,
especially to a
couple of strangers,
so asking would be useless.
Maybe we should just
come back later.
Whatever it is you wanna do,
I suggest that
you decide quickly.
'Cause I've just about
run outta time here.
"Out of time"?
What do you mean?
I'm able to take on this cute
appearance, but I'm a spirit.
It takes a lot of mana for me
to appear in physical form.
So when the day becomes night,
I return to the crystal
I was summoned from
and prepare for
the sun to emerge.
On average, my ideal
time to stay out
is roughly nine to five.
Nine to five?
Sounds like you
work in an office.
Employment terms for
spirits are pretty severe.
We'll be fine without Puck.
We need to keep
moving forward on this.
Sorry, but I'm at my limit.
Good luck, you two.
It's almost like he's
dying when he disappears.
Sorry to've worked you
so hard today, Puck.
We'll handle things from here,
so settle in and get some rest.
Don't do anything
reckless, all right?
If it comes down to it,
you can always use the
od to summon me again.
I'm leaving things in your
hands, Subaru! Good luck!
Hey, wow, I don't think
I've been in one of these
"alone with a girl" situations
since I was in grade school.
Don't get any pervy
ideas, Subaru.
I can use magic, you know.
I won't, okay?!
The more important issue at
hand is how we find Felt now.
[SATELLA]
I'll contact the lesser spirits.
[SUBARU]
Lesser spirits?
[SATELLA]
Precisely.
They're beings that
haven't quite become
full-fledged spirits yet.
They grow little
by little over time,
and when they gain enough
strength and self-awareness,
they become full
spirits, just like Puck.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[SATELLA] It's getting
more desolate and quiet.
Hard to believe that she
actually lives out here.
I know, but the lesser
spirits specifically said
they saw someone who looked like
Felt headed in this direction.
'Scuse me, man!
Know if a girl named Felt
lives somewhere up this way?
Huh? You're lookin' for Felt?
There's nothing that way except
Old Man Rom's loot house.
Hah, I guess she must've stolen
something pretty important
for you two to come out here.
Well, I wish you
luck on bargaining
to try to get it back.
Live strong, okay?
[SATELLA]
What was he talking about?
Why do I have to pay money
to get back something
stolen from me?
[SUBARU]
Don't worry about a thing.
Just leave everything to me.
I can handle the negotiations.
All right, then. I'll just
leave everything in your hands.
You agreed to that
pretty easily.
I figured you'd
say something like
"You want me to leave this
to a useless boy like you?
That's such a ridiculous idea,
it actually hurts my stomach!"
And although that would
stomp all over my feelings,
I'd still decide to keep
helping you anyway.
I'd never say something
that mean to anyone!
Of course, to tell you the
truth, I'd be lying if I said
you haven't been holding
me back a little bit.
Oh, great! That's good to know!
But again...
...I'm leaving
this in your hands.
If it actually goes well,
I'll consider it a bonus.
Now, ya know, if you said
something more like,
"Work hard for me, okay?"
I'd probably feel a whole
lot more motivated.
Sorry, I can't force myself
to say something like that.
However, please do your best.
Yeah, you got it.
I'll go in first. You stay
outside and keep watch.
I won't be back too late,
but you can have dinner without
me if you get too hungry.
[SATELLA] Don't say dumb things
like that. And be careful.
[SUBARU]
Sure, sure.
Now don't come in until I say
it's all right, Satella.
What's the matter?
Nothing, never mind.
If you can manage to
get my insignia back,
then I'll apologize.
Anybody here?
Nope.
[SUBARU] So am I walking into
a demon nest or a snake pit?
In a fantasy world,
either is totally plausible.
This is all stolen loot?
Impressive. But why
isn't anyone here?
A shack full of stolen goods
and no one around to guard it?
[squelching]
[SUBARU]
Uh.
[gasps]
[VOICE]
Oh, dear, you found that?
Well, I have no choice, then.
No choice at all...
[SUBARU]
Agh... that burns...
[SUBARU] Oh, crap...
Is all of this my blood?
[SUBARU]
No... This is bad... Very bad...
[SATELLA]
Subaru? What's wrong?
You okay...?
Don't come in!
Run away! Get out of here!
--[thud]
--[SATELLA screams]
[SUBARU]
Stay with me...
Hang on.
No matter what happens...
...I'm gonna save you...
What's the matter with you, kid?
It looks like you've seen
a ghost or somethin'.
Huh?
You were askin' about these
and I told you they were appas.
So are you interested
in buying some or not?
Huh?
"Huh?" Stop screwin' around!
Do you want one or not?
You even have any money?
Ohh! No.
Like I said before, I don't
have any money on me,
I'm just browsing.
I figured as much;
should've known better.
Go on, beat it.
I run a business here.
I don't have time for
window-shoppers, understand?
What's going on?
It was nighttime just a
few minutes ago, right?
The wound on my
stomach is gone.
Oh, that's right!
Satella! Damn it.
Puck asked me to take care of
her and I totally blew it!
I have to find my way
back to that shop!
What's got you so spooked?
Why are you in such a hurry?
If you don't wanna get hurt,
then cough up
whatever you've got!
You guys again?
Tryin' to get revenge for what
happened before, is that it?
Huh? The hell are
you talkin' about?
I think he must've hit
his head or something.
Nah, he'll be all right.
Just give us everything
you've got, understand?
Put it on the ground
and we'll let you go.
Fine, whatever.
Everything I've got, right?
I'm in a hurry,
so I don't even care.
Now start acting like a dog.
Just get on all fours like and
howl, "Help me!" like a mongrel.
[SUBARU]
Don't get cocky, you bastards!
[SUBARU yells]
[SUBARU] Don't ever
underestimate a truant kid
with too much free time.
'Cause I usually end up swinging
around a wooden sword all day
for no reason, which has
given me a significant bump
to my grip strength!
I'm in a hurry, okay?!
So don't get in my way again!
Easy now, don't freak out, don't
freak out, don't freak out!
[SUBARU]
Am I stupid?
After coming this far, I can't
just leave without answers!
Hello, is anyone there?
Look, I know someone's
in there, all right?!
Just answer the door and
show yourself! Come on!
[ROM]
Shut your trap!
Why don't you use
signal or a password
instead of knockin'
my damn door down?!
[ROM]
Huh?
Wait, you're...
[ROM] What're you
actin' all fidgety for?
You got a wedgie, or
are your balls chafin'?
Why don't you stop worrying
about the condition
of my privates, okay?!
This is no time for potty humor!
You're already interruptin'
my evenin' booze.
Start talking about boring
stuff, and I'll pass out.
And if you drink that hard
while the sun's still up,
you'll die young.
By the way, ya think I could
ask you a dumb question?
You didn't happen to, I dunno,
die recently, did you?
[ROM]
Huh?
[ROM laughs]
Well, while I do admit to being
an old man at death's door,
I'm still here,
alive and kickin'.
Okay, then have you seen a girl
here with long, silver hair?
Silver hair?
I ain't seen nobody that fits
that description. I'd remember.
[SUBARU]
Was it all a dream, then?
If it was, how much of it?
And why am I in this
world in the first place?
So what are you
doin' here, anyway?
You never made that clear.
O-Oh, right. I'm out looking
for a small insignia.
It belongs to a silver-haired
girl who helped me out, earlier.
Don't know why, exactly, but
it's really important to her.
Let's see...
I think she said it had
a jewel in the middle...
Insignia with a jewel, huh?
Sorry, but I ain't got anything
that fits that description.
Are you positive?
Think long and hard about it!
Maybe you're just
old and senile.
I'm at my best full of booze,
so if I don't remember it now,
I must not know
anything about it.
But... I've got
somebody bringin' in
a few goods later on.
I'm told it's a pretty
fine pile of loot.
And there's a good chance
that what you're lookin' for
is mixed in there somewhere.
Would the one bringing it
happen to be a girl named Felt?
Well, Mister Know-It-All,
you even know who swiped it!
Of course, whether or not
you'll be able to afford it
is a different matter.
Money talks, and B.S. walks.
Well, you're outta luck!
There's no use playing
these mind games
and trying to size me up.
I'm about as broke
as they come, buddy.
Then there ain't no
use talkin' about it.
Just a second.
I told you I was broke, but what
about the option of trading?
[ROM]
Hmm...
Now that you mention it,
you do have a lot of
unusual stuff there.
[SUBARU]
That I do!
For example, this is
a corn potage snack.
You've never tasted
anything like it!
[ROM]
That's food?
I see now! Yeah!
What an odd flavor!
These things would
go great with booze!
That's right!
Now you're talkin'!
Hey! Don't just
start eating them!
I dunno what you
plan on tradin',
but you'll have to come back
after Felt gets here, okay?
This is good stuff!
I guess no matter what
world you're on,
there are always people with
money and people without.
I will say, the difference
here is pretty stark.
[FELT]
Hey, what're you doin' there?
You're in my way, ya know.
[SUBARU]
Felt!
Hang on a second,
have we met before?
[SUBARU] Not formally, no.
But I've been waiting for you!
Oh, yeah? Why's that?
Come on, try and
think about this.
Do you really not remember
seeing me before?
Huh, nothin's ringing any bells.
Listen, I'm a busy woman, okay?
So if you don't leave
a huge impression,
there's no way I'm
gonna remember you.
I'd say it was a pretty huge
impression, but whatever.
Just forget about that.
I want to negotiate
for the insignia
you're bringin' in there.
[FELT]
Hmm...
So that's all ya wanted, huh?
In that case, I guess
I'll hear you out.
[ROM]
For a rat...
Poison.
[ROM]
For a whale...
A harpoon.
[ROM]
To the noble dragon lord...
We're bags of shit.
I'm sorry to keep you
waiting, old man.
My target was more
persistent than I thought.
It took a while to shake them.
Hey, did you water down this
milk or what, Old Man Rom?
'Cause there's definitely
something wrong with it.
Pretty nasty stuff.
I give you somethin' outta
the goodness of my heart,
and you call it gross?
You two are a whole lot closer
than I had either
hoped or expected.
Feelin' kinda left
out over here...
Come on, don't start
talkin' like a wuss
when you've got a face that
looks almost as scary as his.
Tellin' me I look like
an old man at my age
is the most savage thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Okay, yeah, I probably went
a little too far that time.
I'm sorry, dude.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you two were in some
contest to try to piss me off.
All right, well then,
what do you say we get
down to business, huh?
How much are you
willing to pay for it?
Wow, you don't waste
any time at all.
Before I give you an answer,
you do have the insignia, right?
Yeah, of course I do, silly!
Satisfied?
This one not only
has a cool design,
it's got that jewel in it.
So I had to work pretty
hard to get a hold of it.
If you can pay enough to
match all the effort involved,
we'll both be happy.
I don't have any money.
Then it sounds like we don't
have anything more to discuss!
[SUBARU]
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
I don't have any money, but
I have a few things worth money.
What I have in my hand
here is a magical device
that can stop time for
everyone, everywhere.
It's called a "cell phone"!
[FELT]
What's that?
[ROM]
Never seen one of those before.
Take this!
Nine shots per second:
Continuous Shot!
[BOTH yelp]
Hey, what's that
clicking sound?!
And that was way too bright!
Stop! What are you
tryin' to do, kill me?
Don't you go tryin'
to trick this old man
with your dodgy tricks!
[SUBARU]
Now, hold on.
Wait, is that...?
[ROM]
Those are me and Felt's faces.
What sort of magic is that?
[SUBARU]
It's like I was tellin' you,
it's a mystical item that can
freeze a moment in time.
With this unique device,
you can capture moments in time,
store them inside of it,
and look at them later!
[FELT]
Oh, wow! That's amazing!
[ROM]
Never seen the like.
Is that one of the "metia"
I've been hearin' about?
What's a metia?
It's the name for devices
that allow people whose
gates aren't open
to use magic in the very same
way that real magic users do.
I'm more concerned
with the price.
How much do you think
I'll be able to get
outta this thing, anyway?
Don't ask me.
It's my first time
havin' to deal
with one of these metia, too.
But I feel pretty confident
that it'll fetch way more
than that insignia.
Then that settles it! This
cell phone for the insignia!
Negotiations complete!
Thank you for your business.
Hey!
Uh, not so fast.
[SUBARU]
What's the problem?
You're not the only one
I'm negotiating with
for the insignia.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
It's not like it was
just some random grab,
somebody specifically
asked me to get it for them.
In exchange, that same client
said I could get ten holy coins.
You've already got
a deal set up for it?
I have no idea what ten holy
coins are worth to compare.
[ROM]
Judging by what it can do,
I'd say your metia is worth
at least 20 holy coins.
Actually, I'm guessin'
there're people out there
who'd be willin'
to pay even more.
[FELT]
Really?
Then that means I can get
away with overcharging for it!
So when and where are
you planning on meeting
this client of yours?
Hey, no need to worry.
Negotiations will take
place right here.
If a little thing like me
dealt with them alone,
I'd be screwed if a client
decided to cheat me.
But with Old Man Rom standing
there, that's not a concern.
[knocking]
The password?
[FELT] Oh, I didn't
mention it to them.
That's probably for me.
I'll go check.
[SUBARU] You're okay with
letting her use you like this?
It ain't like we're total
strangers, or anything.
I've known her for a long time,
so I help her out
whenever I can.
Even I have to smile a little
when I see somebody who
looks like such a barbarian
standing right
here in front of me.
Well, look at where we are.
Everyone around
here is desperate
just to survive each day.
Normally, people join
forces with others
to try and keep themselves
safe when things get rough.
But Felt ain't
cut out for that.
That's why I gotta look out for
her and keep her outta trouble.
[FELT]
Yep, I was right. It was for me.
Over here. Care to sit down?
There seem to be
several outsiders here.
[FELT] Well, I'd be in
trouble if you jipped me.
We weaklings have our own
way of playing it smart.
I know this older fellow,
but I'm afraid I don't
recognize the young man.
He happens to be your rival.
So he'll be the other person
negotiating with you today.
I see now.
Believe I understand
the situation.
I'm pretty sure he's only
interested in the insignia,
so that means you two will be
bidding against each other.
I honestly don't care
who ends up with it,
so I'll sell it to
the highest bidder
and be completely
satisfied doing so.
I think I like that
personality of yours.
Exactly how much did this
young man bid for the item?
I'm putting up this metia.
It's pretty rare too,
probably the only one of its
kind in this entire world.
It can capture moments in time.
The big muscleman
over here tells me
it's worth no less
than 20 holy coins.
A metia.
Well, luckily for me,
the client sent along extra
funds in case anything came up.
That way, I'd be prepared
to sweeten the deal.
The client, huh?
So I suppose that means you were
asked to fetch it too, then,
weren't you?
Yes, that's correct.
The client is the one
who wants to acquire it.
Would you happen to be
in the same business?
Doubt it, unless your client
is gamefully unemployed.
So this unemployed
guy has named a price
that puts him pretty
far ahead in the lead.
And that brings us to this:
What price is your
master putting on it?
[ROM]
Hmm. Twenty, exactly.
These are the holy coins
my employer sent with me
to seal this deal.
So do you think they
should be enough?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know how to bargain?
Stop lookin' so pathetic!
Your metia's worth no less
than 20 holy coins, remember?
The way I see it,
victory in this deal
is definitely leaning
toward the boy.
Sorry for all the trouble for
you and your employer,
but you'd better bag up those
coins and be on your way.
[SUBARU]
Yeah!
[SUBARU] Wh-What? What's wrong
with a little victory pose?
I'm totally psyched about this!
[FELT]
So... no one said anything.
Go as crazy as you want.
I don't care as long
as I get my profit.
[SUBARU]
Uh, sorry, Miss Elsa.
You'll probably get in trouble
about this, won't you?
[ELSA]
These things can't be helped.
The way I see it, this
was my employer's fault
for trying to underpay.
It ended in disappointment, but
at least I got to have a drink.
So I'll be taking my leave now.
[ELSA]
By the way,
what do you intend to do
with that insignia, anyway?
Oh, I'm gonna look for its
owner, then return it to her.
[BOTH gasp]
I see. So you're
with them, then.
What's goin' on here?
Do you want to die?!
[ELSA] Oh, my. It seems
you've dodged my strike.
[clatter]
This is my first battle
to the death with a giant!
Quiet, jumpy little girl!
I'll grind you up and
feed you to the rats!
Crap!
Don't worry, there's no
way Old Man Rom will lose.
Take this!
Old Man Rom!
[ROM]
Damn it.
[ELSA]
I forgot to say--
I'm gonna take you with me!
Thank you for that
nice glass of milk.
I suppose I should
return this now.
What have you done?
How dare you put your filthy
hands on him, you bitch.
Oh, my. Seems you have more
courage than your friend.
But I would advise against
doing anything stupid,
unless you wanna get hurt.
As if you didn't intend
to kill me either way.
You psychopathic monster!
Wouldn't move around too much,
dear. My hands might slip.
Believe it or not, I'm not
the best at handling blades.
I'm sorry you got caught
up in all of this.
[SUBARU]
Wait, I--
[ELSA]
Divine protection of wind...
[yells]
How wonderful. I can see you're
loved dearly by this world.
I truly envy you.
The old man and the
girl have fallen,
yet you remain frozen
over there on the floor.
I take it you've given up?
Dammit...
There we go,
you finally stood up.
'Course, it's less fun
since you took so long.
But still, not bad.
[yells]
[ELSA] It's no use.
I see you're a novice.
You've no divine
protections or techniques.
I'd hoped to squeeze wisdom out
of you, but you lack that, too.
[SUBARU]
Shut up! I do have my pride!
I can't believe you...
After you've put me
through all this...
I do acknowledge that you have
extraordinary determination.
If only you could've stood up
and done that sooner,
things might have gone a bit
differently for these two.
I think it's time to
end this little game.
I'll send you to
meet the angels.
[ELSA]
Ah, you're full of surprises.
I certainly felt that one.
Didn't feel it?
I managed to open up
that belly of yours
when we passed by one another.
The one thing I excel
at when using a blade.
[ELSA]
Just as I thought.
Your entrails have such an
interesting shape to them,
and such a lovely color, too!
[SUBARU]
It hurts... It hurts...
[ELSA] Does it hurt?
Are you suffering?
[SUBARU]
It... doesn't hurt?
[ELSA]
Do you want to die?
[SUBARU]
Die?
Am I dead? Am I still alive?
When will I die?
When will I die? When?!
I'm scared... I'm scared...
I'm scared! I'm scared!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna
die! I'm gonna die!
[ELSA] Yes, you're slowly
losing body heat...
You're slowly growing cold...
[SUBARU]
Oh... I'm dead.
[KADOMON]
What's the matter, boy?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Say somethin'. Are you okay?
[sighs]
I have no idea.
That woke you up.
You feelin' better?
Just forget about the money.
Here, I'll give you
these. Take 'em.
Hey. Wait up...
Hang on! Please, wait for me!
Wait up! Satella!
[SUBARU]
Please don't ignore me!
My disappearing and not doing
what you said were my fault!
But I was desperate! I didn't
know what else I could do!
So I went back to the
loot house after that,
but I still couldn't find you...
I'm sorry for only
thinking of myself.
But I'm glad you're
all right, Satella.
What in the world
is wrong with you?
Huh?
Now, listen, I don't know
who you think you are,
but don't ever call me by the
name of the Witch of Envy!
What were you thinking?!