[SUBARU]
And now for the final exercise!
Swing your arms out wide...
...then cross them in front
of you as you take slow,
deep breaths.
I came to check on him since
break time's almost over.
Things are quite lively here.
Now, big finish...
Victory!
[KIDS]
[KIDS chattering, cheering]
[SUBARU]
All right!
[YOUNG MEN'S LEADER]
Yeah!
[BOTH laughing]
I feel so much
younger after that.
[laughing]
[SUBARU] Okay, everyone
has touched me now.
[RAM]
Barusu...
Exactly what
sort of game is this?
[SUBARU]
Radio calisthenics.
I think the fact that everyone,
young and old, can enjoy it
is the key secret to its many
long years of success!
[RAM]
Who cares?
[MILDO]
Ram-Ram, that was cold.
Ram-Ram, that was mean.
Ram-Ram, you're scary.
Did you teach all
these children to call me
by that name?
Well, it was more like...
I wanted to share
some friendliness around
with everybody.
I suppose I don't mind it.
What about Rem?
You mean Rem-Rem?
She's Rem-Rem.
Or Rem-Rem-Rem-Rem.
So, then. Enjoy the village
trip you wanted so much?
I sure did!
Nothing to worry about there.
When Muraosa patted
my shoulder at the end,
my trip was complete.
What's up?
If you wanna say something,
then just tell me.
Uh, take a look.
Over there.
All right, have your
way a little bit longer.
Well, if you say so, sister.
Yes!
Really appreciate it,
my dear senpais!
That's right,
there was an event like this.
I remember.
[DOG growls]
And this little pup
still hates me.
Weird, she's usually so tame.
She only growls
like that at Subaru.
What'd you do to make
her so mad at you?
I wish I knew
the answer to that one,
believe me.
If it's happened
three times,
I guess we're
just incompatible...
Oh, now's my chance!
If you'll excuse me...
[SUBARU chuckles]
There's the sensation
I've longed for!
You know, for a stray, your fur
feels pretty fantastic, pup!
Hey, you've got a
big bald spot
on top of your head.
Is it a scar?
What did you walk int--
Yow!
You even bit me in almost
the exact same spot!
Are you a time-traveling canine?
Guess you got carried away!
It's what you get for
touching her so much.
She is a girl, after all.
I really don't think
that's the problem here.
Also, isn't anybody
worried about me?
I was just bitten, you know.
[KIDS laughing]
Holy crap, I made it!
Well done, me! Good job!
Seriously,
really nice work there.
Yes, yes, job well done.
Yes, yes, excellent work.
[ROSWAAL] Ah, I see the
three of you are together.
Good.
That will save me precious
time on my way out.
[RAM, REM]
Lord Roswaal.
Pretty fancy clothes
you've got there.
Nice.
Thank you so much.
I'm getting together
with someone
who's absolutely dreadful
to deal with in normal attire,
so I had no choice but
to wear dress clothes
for the occasion.
Is it a visitor?
Or will you be going out?
Ram is correct.
I'll be going out.
I received a message
earlier today
that was a tad troublesome.
So now I'm off to make
the rounds outside.
There's a fairly high likelihood
that I won't be
back home tonight.
Ram, Rem, take care
of things until I return.
Yes, sir.
We will do as you command.
Even if it costs our lives.
[SUBARU]
Roswaal didn't leave the mansion
any of those times before...
I've great expectations
for you too, Subaru.
I want you to keep
an eye on Miss Emilia
and take good care of her.
Sure. You can definitely
count on me for that!
[ROSWAAL] Look after things
while I'm away, everyone!
Whoa! Roswaal can fly?!
[SUBARU]
Magic is incredible...
The difference in circumstances
from my previous experiences
of this day must have
been triggered by my visit
to the village.
That means my strategy
of acting as a decoy
is working as planned.
And that's why I'm here for
my long-awaited Beako time!
[BEATRICE] Your face looks
quite different than it did
half a day ago.
You've been busy, I suppose.
I'd love to take it easy
for a change, you know...
But I can't.
'Cause there's something
I want you to check out for me.
I think I've been cursed.
Could you look me over head
to toe and find out for sure?
[BEATRICE]
What are you talking about?
I think I've been cursed.
Could you look me over head
to toe and find out for sure?
Gah! No one asked you to
repeat yourself, I suppose!
It hasn't even been a full
day since I first told you
about shamans.
You're far too
impressionable for--
Wait just a minute...
You really have been
cursed, I suppose!
So it turns out the shaman
was one of the villagers
after all.
Think you'll be
able to figure out
what kind of curse it is?
Well, that wouldn't be possible
simply by looking at it.
But as I told you
a little earlier today,
once it's been activated,
chances are you'll die,
I suppose.
How strange.
Even after that reminder,
you don't seem afraid
of dying at all.
Huh? Are you out of your mind?
I'm insanely scared of dying!
There's nothing in the
world that freaks me out
more than even
thinking about it!
Wish people who say
"I'd rather die"
would actually die before
saying stuff like that!
Which is why, this time,
I'm determined to
find a way out...
...of this fate.
Okay, so get rid of this
curse for me, would you?
I'm runnin' out of time here.
[BEATRICE] Now, why should I
have to go through the trouble
of saving your life, I suppose?
I expected an unlovable
and cold response like that,
so I came fully prepared
to convince you.
If I die, your dearest
Puck is bound to be sad.
[BEATRICE]
Hm?
You think too
highly of yourself.
Bubby wouldn't be all
that disturbed if you died.
Oh, on the contrary!
If I did, then Emilia would be
at least a little bit shocked.
And when Emilia feels
shock like that,
Puck takes damage, too.
If you had the chance
to have stopped it,
but chose not to,
what would he think of you?
[BEATRICE whines]
All right! I'll go along
with your smooth talk this time!
But when all of this is over,
I won't have anything to do
with you again, I suppose.
Okay, but I'll always come back
to ask for your help
when I'm in trouble!
[BEATRICE sighs]
I'll destroy the spell that
was used in the curse now,
I suppose.
It's burned into you on
the exact spot on your body
that the shaman touched
while casting it,
so that'll act as our reference.
Yeah, I prepared for this.
I've got it covered.
[SUBARU] The young men's
leader with the short hair...
The old lady who
patted my butt...
And Muraosa,
the fake village head.
I made sure all the suspects
touched different parts of me.
[SUBARU]
Black mist? Creepy.
[BEATRICE] Abhorrent is
more like it, I suppose.
[SUBARU gasps]
There we go. All done.
So relax, you'll be just
fine now, I suppose.
So the place that the
black mist came from...
That's also the spot
where the shaman
touched me earlier, isn't it?
[SUBARU]
Could that puppy actually be...
[SUBARU] I have to get
to the village.
They just keep
messing with me!
They're gonna pay for this!
[RAM]
The village...?
What for?
Beatrice said that the
one who gave me this wound
is also the one who's
responsible for placing
the curse on me.
And that means it was the dog
that the kids were playing with!
It may have looked
innocent at the time,
but that little beast
cursed everyone it bit!
If I don't do something,
they'll be in grave danger.
If you don't think
you can trust me,
you're welcome to come along.
But we can't just leave
Emilia defenseless here
all by herself.
And that means only
one of you can come!
You made up that rule.
And if we are to obey
Master Roswaal's orders
to the letter, then there's
absolutely no reason
for either one of us
to go with you.
Right, there's not.
Fair enough.
But do you happen to recall the
only order Roswaal gave to me?
Very well, Barusu.
I will allow you to act
on your best judgment.
But Sister...
And Rem will be
accompanying you.
Exactly what I wanted to hear!
That's my decision,
so please respect it
and go with him, Rem.
I'll confirm everything
with Miss Beatrice
and remain here to
protect Miss Emilia.
I'll be sure to keep
an eye on other things, too.
[REM]
Sister, wait. You shouldn't...
[EMILIA]
Subaru, are you going somewhere?
I heard voices,
so I wanted to come down
and see what was going on.
What happened?
It's more like something
might be happening.
But, you won't need
to worry about all that.
I'll bet you're going to do
something dangerous again...
Interestingly enough,
we were just wrapping
up a dispute
on that particular subject.
I can't talk you
out of it, can I?
[chuckling]
I guess not, no.
As a matter fact,
if you tried to,
it'd be a hindrance
in several ways...
Fine, fine, it's okay, I get it.
I won't try to stop you.
It's probably no use
telling you not to be rash
or reckless either, right?
Well, that depends, I guess...
I mean, it isn't like I want
to do rash or reckless things.
Go with grace.
May the blessing of
the spirits be with you.
Huh? What's that mean?
It's a good luck prayer.
It means "come back safe."
So you better.
Thanks, Emilia.
I'll do my best.
[SUBARU]
Okay, I'm off.
[EMILIA]
Take care.
[SUBARU gasps]
[REM]
Has something happened?
Yeah. It's awful.
Several of the village children
have suddenly gone missing
and now everybody's out
looking all over for them.
Was I too late?
Wait, don't tell me they're...!
What is it?
The barrier's been broken.
[GUY 09A gasps]
When something like
that's been disturbed,
what happens?
Mabeasts can cross the
boundary and enter the village.
Mabeasts?
They're known as
unholy creatures
of the witch's creation.
Enemies of humanity
that have magic powers.
Within the forest,
they live wild
and in great numbers.
[SUBARU]
Whoa, hang on a sec...
Are you tryin' to tell me
tons more dogs like that one
are out there?
It looks like the kids
are out in the forest.
Get some help! Tell everyone!
[GUY 09A]
Right!
Wait, what is it
you're going to...
I have to go out there
and rescue those kids!
Hold on!
You can't make that
decision on your own.
With Lord Roswaal
away from home,
can you be certain
this isn't just a ruse
to divert our attention
away from the mansion?
No, but what do you think
we should do about this?
Ignore the poor kids who
are in trouble right now,
go back to the mansion,
and tighten security?
If it's not gonna bother
you that all the villagers
might wind up dead tomorrow,
then I guess that's
a solid option.
You know I'm right, Rem.
We're the only ones who're
able to do something about this.
But why go so far?
What is it about this village
that matters so much to you?
[SUBARU]
You remember Petra?
Someday,
when she's all grown up,
she wants to move to the
capital and make clothes.
[REM]
Huh?
Lucas wants to prove himself
and eventually be the
village's best woodcutter
like his dad.
Mildo wants to take some
of the prettiest flowers
growing in the field,
craft them into
a beautiful crown,
and give it to his mother.
Meina is excited
because it won't be long
before she'll have
a little baby sister.
And the brothers, Dyne and Cain,
are always fighting over
which one of them'll
be lucky enough to marry Petra.
All of those kids matter to me.
I know their names,
I know their faces,
and I know what they each
want to do in the future.
On top of that, I promised them
we'd do radio calisthenics
again tomorrow.
I keep my promises,
and I make sure
others keep theirs.
No matter what happens,
I'm gonna do those exercises
with those kids again.
That means I'm going in there.
[REM]
Very well, then.
I was given orders
to keep an eye on you.
It wouldn't be right
if I failed to do so.
Yeah, absolutely.
After all, you need
to be there to make sure
I don't do anything shady!
Right.
[metal clanks]
[SUBARU]
Um, Rem-Rem, is that, uh...
[REM]
It's for protection.
[SUBARU]
But it seems so...
[REM]
It's for protection.
[SUBARU grunts]
[sniffs]
We're getting closer.
I smell living creatures.
[SUBARU]
Is it the kids?
[REM] I'm not certain, but it
doesn't smell like beasts to me.
Look! Up ahead! It's them!
[SUBARU] She's breathing.
They're still alive!
[REM] That's true.
But their breathing is shallow.
They're all unconscious
and weak.
If left alone...
They're weak?
Is it the curse?
And we finally found them...
Rem, can't you do
anything to reverse it?
Not a spell of this magnitude.
If only my sister were with us.
I'm sure she could do something.
I'll try what I can.
And cast a healing
spell to comfort them.
When they're calm, we can
carry them back with us.
Yeah, sounds good.
Then I'll...
Who am I kidding?
I'm so useless.
I'll keep an eye out for--
[PETRA]
Subaru?
[SUBARU]
Petra! You're awake!
All right, good.
You're a tough girl.
I need you to save
your strength, though.
Don't overdo it.
I'll take you back home
where you can say goodbye
to the pain.
--Just rest up for the time--
--[PETRA] One is...
One is... still in... in the...
Hold on, what did you say?
Petra!
[SUBARU]
Damn it, she's right.
I don't see the little girl
with the braid anywhere!
No, please don't go!
It's far too dangerous.
And if the mabeasts took her,
it may already be...
Look, I understand what
you're trying to tell me.
I really do...
But you heard what Petra said.
She was trying to tell us the
other girl was taken away.
Even in her state,
she showed concern
for her missing friend
before asking for my help.
Don't you see?
She put her friend's life
and wellbeing before her own!
I want to respect
Petra's feelings.
If you take something on,
you should see it through
to the bitter end.
If you get too greedy,
then you run the risk
of taking on much more
than you could ever
possibly carry back with you.
I know.
But that's the reason
you came along, isn't it?
And what does this situation
have to do with me?
Those kids need you now.
More than they ever did before.
leave the children with
them and then follow me
out into the forest.
We don't know the threat
our opponent presents,
or when the villagers
will arrive.
At worst, there's always
a chance that you'll
wander off somewhere
and I would never be able
to find you.
It'll be fine.
'Cause I'm confident that
you won't lose track of me.
What makes you so sure?
[SUBARU]
Even if no one else does,
I know that you can
pick up my scent.
The foul odor
that hangs on me...
The witch's scent.
Isn't that right?
Wait, Subaru.
How do you know about...
[SUBARU]
No idea, heh.
There's a ton
I don't understand.
So much that no matter
how many times I start over,
I can't seem to find
the answer I'm looking for.
Just like there are many
things you want to ask me,
there are a ton
of things that I want
to ask you about, too.
So when all of this is
taken care of, we should talk.
We can chat until
our voices are hoarse!
It's a promise!
I just want you to
know I trust you, Rem.
And this is my attempt at
showing you can trust me, also.
So that promise I made,
I'm sticking to it!
All right, very well.
Then I promise on my end, too.
I plan on asking you
many questions,
so be ready for them.
You got it!
And once the villagers
arrive to help the children,
I'll join you.
Just be careful out there.
Don't do anything reckless.
Appreciate the concern,
but don't worry about a thing!
I'm demonically
inspired tonight!
Demonically inspired?
Demon version of
divine inspiration.
For some reason, it's my
favorite phrase lately!
Please take care!
I'll join you soon!
If the one who
cursed those kids
from the village really
turns out to be that dog
from earlier today,
then there's no way
I can lose this fight, right?
I can smell beasts.
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU]
Is it a trap?
Emilia wouldn't
hesitate to save her.
[MAILI breathing]
Thank goodness she's alive...
[rustling]
[SUBARU gasps]
That is not the little
puppy from before.
Did it transform
into this monster?
And was the sneaky
little bastard waiting around
for me to come out
and rescue her?
[MABEAST growling]
There's nowhere to run. Damn.
Fine! Let's go!
If you wanna fight, bring it on!
[SUBARU yells]
That doesn't hurt!
Now you're stuck
and you can't get away!
[MABEAST yelping]
[SUBARU panting]
I... I won...
Come on, you've
gotta be kidding...
If you wanna fight,
then bring it on!
[SUBARU yells]
[REM] The children have been
safely returned to the village.
I truly appreciate you
buying some time.
Rem, watch ou--!
[REM]
Shh.
Whoa! You're strong!
I'm not sure if that's
a nice thing to say
to a girl, Subaru.
But thank you.
Well that's the best
word I can think of
to describe you.
You're seriously incredible!
[MABEASTS growling]
[SUBARU]
So, Rem...
Do you think you'd be able
to take those things out
--in one shot?
--We're completely outnumbered.
With this many, I don't
think it's possible.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
In that case... Right there!
[REM]
Now!
[SUBARU growling]
[MABEASTS yelp]
[MABEASTS growling]
Rem, I don't know
which way to go!
[REM]
That way. Straight ahead.
The battle will end
once we cross the barrier.
Run toward the village bonfire!
Got it!
[MABEAST yelps]
Rem, over here! I see light!
We're almost to the barrier!
[SUBARU]
Rem!
[grunts]
[SUBARU]
Rem, no!
[MABEASTS growling]
Damn it...
[clinking]
[REM laughing]
[laughing]
[REM]
Mabeast! Mabeast!
Witch!
[panting]
[REM laughing]
[SUBARU]
She's a demon...
[MABEASTS growling]
[REM gasps]
[SUBARU yelling]
Subaru!
Please hang in there!
Don't die...
Don't die! Don't die!
Don't die!