[INVESTIGATORS screaming]
[INVESTIGATORS gasp]
[INVESTIGATOR B panting]
[gun shots]
[INVESTIGATOR B groaning]
[phones ringing]
Hello, CCG Control Center-
This is Marude speaking!
Give me a report!
[INVESTIGATOR C]
Sir, A band of ghouls we believe
to be Aogiri Tree has
attacked the branch and--
[INVESTIGATOR C screaming]
[MARUDE] Are you there?
[static]
[TATARA] Now that he's dead,
we've killed them all.
[INVESTIGATORS clamoring]
Who the hell are you?
Answer me! Now!
[ETO]
You done?
[TATARA] Yeah. Are
you ready to go, Eto?
[ETO] Mm-hm. Ready when
you are, Mr. Tatara.
This is terrible. What
do we know about them?
[YOMO] Apparently,
they're a band of ghouls
who call themselves Aogiri.
Unfortunately, we don't know
how many of them there are.
But we do know that
their leader...
...would be the
One-Eyed King.
Is that so?
Well.
[YOSHIMURA] Come on Yomo,
let's head back to Anteiku.
I wonder why it's
been so slow lately.
Prob'ly 'cause of the
increase in doves.
Nobody wants to
risk going outside
while they're snooping around.
Hello. Welcome sir.
[door slams]
[KANEKI]
Uh. Can I help you?
Is your manager here?
[KANEKI]
Excuse me?
I asked you if your manager
is here, ya dumb ass!
No, I'm sorry. he stepped
out for a little while.
You wanna tell me
where he went, buddy?
[TOUKA]
Let him go!
Huh?
You heard me the first time.
If you've got business here,
then you could at least
order a cup of coffee.
What?
[KANEKI]
Um, sir.
If you need to talk
to our manager,
I can relay a message
to him for you.
Nah, don't bother. I'll just
ask the two of you instead.
Know a girl named
Rize Kamishiro?
My name's Banjo Kazuichi.
I'm lookin' for her.
I'm from the 11th Ward, in fact,
that's where I first met her.
So, what makes you think
that she would
show up here?
Well, I knew she was
headed to the 20th Ward.
and that she loved
coffee shops--
[BANJO sniffing]
No way.
You wanna tell me why
I can smell Rize all over
you, ya little prick?
Well?
Let him go! No rough
stuff in the shop!
[ICHIMI]
Banjo, chill out!
So, it's you?
Huh? 'Scuse me?
Are you the lucky
bastard dating Rize?
It's not like that! But I guess
you could say we're close--
Damn, you!
[BANJO grunting]
[KANEKI] Listen, you've
got it all wrong!
Now back off!
[ALL gasp]
[JIRO] Holy crap!
Are you okay, Banjo?
[KANEKI]
I'm so sorry!
[JIRO]
Huh?!
He's out cold.
[ICHIMI] Can't say
I'm surprised.
[SANTE] I'd like to apologize
on behalf of our leader.
[TOUKA]
What a wuss.
Shinohara and Amon, reporting.
[AMON] Assistant
Special Investigator Chino
and Senior Investigator Tainaka,
and Special Investigator Arima's
old partner,
Senior Investigator Hirako.
[AMON] Special Investigator
Kuroiwa's here, too?
Now. Everyone
please take a seat.
[MARUDE coughs]
[MARUDE] As you may
have already heard,
the 11th Ward Branch
was attacked.
The enemy inflicted
plenty of damage
in the short amount of time
they occupied the building.
We've lost a number
of brave souls.
According to police
reports from the scene,
the number of
survivors... was zero.
[ICHIMI] Oh good,
he's coming to.
[BANJO groaning]
[KANEKI] Here you go,
have some water.
Listen, I'm really
sorry about earlier.
No worries. What's your name?
I'm Kaneki.
[BANJO]
Nice to meet ya.
Y'know, you're a lot stronger
than you look, man.
Thank you.
I get it now.
That's the reason she's with
you, 'cause you'll protect her.
Uh, no. It's not what you think!
Rize and I aren't
together or anything.
[BANJO]
You mean I was wrong?
Well, yeah.
I'm sorry!
[BANJO] That was my bad!
Please forgive me!
It's okay. Seriously,
lift up your--
No, I can't! I gotta pay my dues
for makin' a stupid mistake!
Hey, man. Do you have any
idea where I can find her?
[KANEKI]
This is tough, but,
The truth is...
She's, uh...
She isn't here anymore.
Oh. I gotcha.
I should've known. Ya can't
tie down a free spirit like her.
[KANEKI] I'm sorry. I
know that's not much help.
Kaneki, listen. Ya mind
if I ask a favor of you?
Uh, no. So what's up?
Thanks, man. If you
see Rize again,
I need you to tell
her something for me.
Please tell her to run.
What?
[BANJO] A few months
ago, a band of ghouls
called Aogiri Tree
popped up outta nowhere.
They muscled their way
into the 11th Ward
and made it clear that
they were takin' over.
Since then, they've set their
sights on overpowering the doves
and driving them
out of our ward.
And I'm sure they'll do it. In
fact, I wouldn't be surprised
if they've killed all
of the doves by now.
Look, I've got nothing to do
with them, I'm just a runner.
[BANJO] But I know
they're headed this way.
They're searching for Rize.
I don't know why but it
can't be anything good.
They're headed here?
[BANJO] They're gonna pull the
same shit in the 20th Ward
that they pulled on us.
If I were you, I'd get outta
here before it's too late.
Trust me on this one.
[ALL gasping, grunting]
[KANEKI] Whoa, what the hell?
[MAN] I gave you one
job, and you blew it.
Ya dumbass.
I guess you didn't
learn your lesson
the last time I
kicked your face in.
Didya?
Uh, sorry, sir.
[BANJO whispering]
Hey! Wait!
[KANEKI]
What're you doing?
Ayato.
[KANEKI] No way.
That's her brother?
What's up? Long time
no see, dear "sister".
[TOUKA]
Don't ever call me that.
So where've you
been all this time?
I've been out learning
about the world.
See, I'm not a close-minded
hermit, like you.
What, you think you're
better than me?
I don't "think"
that, I know it.
Look around you. It's clear.
[YAMORI] Okay, we've
given you plenty of time.
Can we come in now?
Tch.
[BANJO gasps]
What're they doing here?
[NICO]
Please forgive the intrusion.
[JUZO humming]
[JUZO] Aw great, now
what am I gonna do?
I dunno where I am.
[JUZO]
I've spotted a police box!
Things are looking up!
The group we're dealing
with is called Aogiri Tree.
They have over two hundred
members that we're aware of.
We've never seen this many
ghouls band together before.
[MARUDE] So we don't
know what to expect.
What do you think
their objective is, sir?
I really wish I
could tell you.
Who knows what the
ghouls are thinking?
At this point, they have
control of the 11th Ward.
That's all we know for certain.
[MARUDE] We expect
their numbers to grow.
When word gets out
that Aogiri Tree
have taken control
of an entire ward,
the ghouls who've been
acting on their own
will most likely
join their ranks.
We must prepare for a war
between humans and ghouls!
And the CCG is going to be
fighting on the front lines!
We'll give our lives
for the cause!
And that's an order, by the way!
From here on, the 11th Ward
special task force will be--
Um, excuse me!
[INVESTIGATORS]
Huh?
Hi, I'm
Mr. Shinohara's underling,
the name's Juzo Suzuya!
Sorry to barge in late but I
kinda got lost on my way here.
[MARUDE gasping]
Juzo.
I hope that you can find it
in your heart to forgive me.
So, who's this, Ayato?
[NICO] My, my. Y'know, I'd heard
your older sister lives here.
But no one told me she's
as gorgeous as you.
Oh, I'd ravish you both.
So, how did you know
I was here, Yamori?
[YAMORI] Easy. I just
followed your boy, Banjo.
Gotta say, your men
are first-rate.
They lead me right to ya.
Look, Rize isn't here
so leave them--
[BANJO groaning]
[YAMORI sniffing]
That stench. It reeks in here.
[knuckle cracks]
I feel like I've smelled
it somewhere before.
And it seems to be
comin' from you.
Hey, Nico.
You think that this one'll do?
Sure, why not? If that's who
you want, let's kidnap him.
[YAMORI chuckles]
Just try it! You'll
have to get through me!
Yeah? Okay.
[TOUKA grunts]
[KANEKI gags]
[YAMORI] There's no
standing between me
and what I want, little lady.
[KANEKI grunting]
[KANEKI groaning]
[TOUKA]
Kaneki!
Okay, kid. Get up, or stay down.
Y'know, if you play
your cards right
you might be able to make
it outta this ordeal alive.
But you've gotta behave, got it?
[KANEKI screaming]
[AYATO gasps]
Oh, my.
Whoa. You're one of
them one-eyed ghouls.
[KANEKI grunting]
[KANEKI coughing]
Damn, you!
[TOUKA groans]
You're such a weakling,
Touka. A carbon copy of Pop.
[TOUKA]
He was a hero.
Dad stood up and
fought for our sake.
You don't even have a clue!
[AYATO] You're the one who's
clueless, my dear sister.
Mom and Pop are dead and gone.
They didn't protect anything,
they were just taken from us.
But that's not
gonna happen to me.
It's time to teach
the humans a lesson.
That ghouls are superior
to them in every way!
[AYATO] You can't fly anywhere
on that wing of yours.
Crawl, like the insect you are.
You're so ridiculously
cool, Ayato.
Touka!
[KANEKI grunts]
[YAMORI]
Looks like this one
still has some
spunk left in him.
Crazy how much you
smell like her, kid.
[KANEKI grunting]
Yeah, there ya go.
Give it to him, baby.
[KANEKI groaning]
[YAMORI] You're a
tough guy, aren't ya?
Well, in that case.
How ya like this?
What about this?
Or this?
[KANEKI grunting, gasping]
[YAMORI] All right,
then how do ya like...
...this?
How about this?
How's this feel?
What about this?
How ya like this?
No... Kaneki.
[YAMORI]
How do ya like this?
Well, Answer me, kid!
What about this?
Or this?
Oh, wow!
I can't seem to break
this little guy!
Chill out, Mr. Yamori!
Uh, I mean, we should go, sir.
Huh?
[NICO] I hate to say it, but
goatee here is right.
Okay.
Oh--
yeaaaaah.
Hubba-hubba.
[NICO moaning]
[NICO] Let's save the rest
for when we get home,
Big boy.
[YAMORI]
Thank you, Nico.
[NICO]
Aw, no problem, precious.
[AYATO] You heard the man, we've
gotta start heading back.
Hurry and stuff the one-eyed
freak in the bag, Banjo.
[YOSHIMURA]
Are you all right?
They kidnapped him, didn't they?
Yomo. Round everyone
up for a meeting.
Anteiku...
...will have to be
closed for a while.
[JUZO humming]
[MARUDE] They are clearly
starting to show signs
of an organized movement.
Unfortunately, that's
all we know
about Aogiri Tree
at this time.
As much as I would love to
charge after them right now,
I'm afraid we have
to be patient.
We will engage the
enemy in one week.
Until then, the 11th Ward
must be evacuated.
Allow me to handle the media.
Be sure to work alongside
local police. That is all.
[MARUDE]
Dismissed!
[INVESTIGATORS]
Yes, sir!
[MARUDE]
So you're Juzo Suzuya?
I gotta admit, you're not
what I was expecting at all.
Uh-oh.
You're an awfully slender
young man, aren't ya?
Well, It's either that or
you're a flat-chested woman.
[SHINOHARA]
Now, now, Maru.
Suzuya just got here and
I'm sure he's gotta be tired.
Cut him some slack, would ya?
What gives? I was
just making small talk.
[SHINOHARA] Yeah, I know.
But it can wait until tomorrow.
[AMON] Suzuya's only a
3rd Class Investigator?
[SHINOHARA]
From what I can tell,
Maru's pulling all
his resources.
He must've decided that
we can use Juzo somehow.
In any case, he was
personally admitted
by Chairman Washu
himself, following Arima.
[AMON]
I see.
We aren't the only ones
with a problem child,
they've got one too.
And who's that, Jason?
Yeah. He's S-rated.
Hails from the 13th Ward.
He's a sadistic bastard
who kills for fun
rather than for food.
I wouldn't wanna go up against
him, that's for damn sure.
[SHINOHARA]
Wait a minute,
you came fact-to-face with
him once, didn't you?
Yeah. Well, Mr. Mado and I.
Oh, that's right.
[AMON] Why can't I get
his words out of my head?
Please, go.
I don't want to be the
monster you think I am.
[AMON]
What he said,
and his expression.
It's dredging up memories that
I don't want to remember.
[YOUNG AMON panting]
Kotaro. Who said that
you could come in?
[SHINOHARA]
Amon.
Amon!
I'm sorry. Could you
repeat that, please?
It's no big deal.
Breathe. I just asked
if your quinque's broken.
Oh. Yes, sir.
In that case, why don't you
take one from Mado's collection?
[AMON]
Huh?
He left them all to you.
Well, I'll see ya later.
[AMON]
Thank you, Mr. Mado.
[JUZO]
Guess what Rei?
I've heard there are lots
of ghouls in the 11th Ward.
And I might be able to
get a new quinque.
I'm so excited. I can't wait!
[JUZO laughing]
Don't want mama mad again.
So I'd better behave.
I have to be a good boy.
[MARUDE]
At this point in time,
we're increasing our
presence in the 11th ward.
and working to pinpoint this
ghoul organization's base.
Once we can do that,
I'm confident
it won't take us long
to close the case.
[MALE REPORTER]
Do you really think
a full-scale evacuation
of the area is needed?
I mean, doesn't that
seem like overkill?
[MARUDE]
We feel it's necessary
to guarantee our
citizens' safety.
You can count on us. The
CCG are fighting for you.
In return, I ask--
C'mon, text me Kaneki.
I'm worried.
[TOUKA]
Hey, Hinami.
He'll be okay.
[NISHIKI] Yeah, No doubt.
The kid can take a licking.
Yeah, I guess so.
[door clicking]
[YOSHIMURA] I'm glad
to see you're all here.
A few more will
be joining us later.
but let's go ahead
and get started.
[YOSHIMURA]
We need to discuss
the problems unfolding
in the 11th Ward.
And then we must decide what
action Anteiku should take.
[YOSHIMURA]
But before we get into that,
let me address
Kaneki's kidnapping.
and what it means
for the rest of you.
Do yourselves a favor
and forget about ever
seeing him again.
What the hell? How could
you say such a thing?
[TOUKA]
Shut up!
Quit yelling.
We're going, right?
[NISHIKI]
To save him? Well?
You have to understand,
Aogiri Tree is a
heartless organization.
They are ghouls who
live to fight.
[YOSHIMURA] It won't be easy
to sneak into their base
and rescue Kaneki.
They'll do everything
in their power to stop us.
But why? That's so mean.
[YOSHIMURA]
And then, there's the CCG,
we can't ignore their movements.
I'm sure it's only a matter
of time before they start
sending their troops
to the 11th Ward
in the hopes of wiping
out Aogiri Tree.
If we try to save him,
there's a very good chance
that we'd be the ones
who end up dead.
We gotta do something!
We can't just abandon him!
He's one of us!
[TOUKA]
I'm going.
Have you forgotten
our policy, sir?
If you're not gonna save him...
...then I'll go alone.
I'll go with you.
Might as well. I owe him one.
[HINAMI]
I wanna help, too!
Kaneki's done so much for
me, it's the least I can do.
Just let me know how I
can help and I'll do it!
[TOUKA]
Hinami.
It appears that there's
been a misunderstanding.
I'm in no way abandoning Kaneki.
I always planned
on rescuing him.
[ALL gasp]
[YOSHIMURA] I would never
abandon a ghoul in need,
especially not one of our own.
That being said, I cannot
guarantee your lives.
If you want to save Kaneki,
then you have to be
willing to risk everything.
It will be tough.
But you won't be alone,
Yomo and I will protect you.
After all, it is
Anetiku's policy
to help those who are in need.
There's one more thing.
You can come in now!
No way! Not that bastard!
[TSUKIYAMA]
Amour!
Je le coeur brisé!
Imagine my horror
when I was told,
my best friend Kaneki's
life is in grave danger.
The low-life scum who
captured him must pay!
Yes.
I'll make sure of that!
[BANJO]
Hey Jiro.
Think I have a chance with Rize
or is she outta my league?
[JIRO] Where's this coming
from, all of a sudden?
Listen. If you wanna
get on her good side,
why don't you give
her a present?
Get her a present, huh?
I could but I don't know
what kinda stuff she likes.
And If I ask--
[JIRO] He's gonna
make me go ask her.
Ugh, what a coward.
[JIRO]
Excuse me, Miss Rize?
I have a question for you.
[JIRO] She says she likes
any and all internal organs.
Yeah. I should've known.