- ( instrumental music playing )
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- YES.
( coughing )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( coughing continues )
YOSHO.
- Yosho: I WILL
ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- WOW.
( laughs )
IT'S LIKE A CARPET
OF CHERRY BLOSSOMS,
BUT THEN IT WOULD BE
A WHOLE LOT OF WORK
TO CLEAN ALL OF THIS UP.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- YEAH, BUT THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE'VE GOT TO DO.
SO LET'S GO.
THE LONGER YOU WAIT,
THE HARDER IT GETS,
YOU KNOW?
- HMM.  CAMELLIAS.
AS THE OPENING OF SPRING
MAKES THIS OLD MAN'S HEART SING,
I FEEL THE BEAUTY
OF THE HOURS
AS THE CAMELLIA BLOOMING FLOWER
FLOATS BY ON GOSSAMER WINGS.
- Ryoko: COME ON!
GIVE IT HERE!
- Ayeka:
WHY SHOULD I?!  IT'S MINE.
- OH, RIGHT.  YOU'RE NOT
DOING ANYTHING WITH IT.
YOU'RE JUST HOGGING IT.
- WHAT I'M DOING WITH IT
IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- OH, YEAH?!
- ( both straining )
- HEE HEE!
- ( screams )
- I'M SO SORRY.
IT WASN'T ON PURPOSE,
I SWEAR.
- ( growls )
( grunting )
( laughs )
OH, PARDON ME.
I DIDN'T DO THAT
ON PURPOSE EITHER.
- YOU BITCH!
- OOH!  HA HA!
OH, YOU WANT TO FIGHT ME,
DO YOU?
- Ryoko: WHAT DID YOU THINK?
- OH, NO.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD
BE DRIVING A SPACE--
- RYOKO, AYEKA, DON'T
YOU EVER GET ENOUGH?
- ( growls )
TENCHI, AYEKA
STEPPED ON MY FOOT
'CAUSE SHE'S JEALOUS!  UGH!
- I'M SURE.
SHE TOOK MY BROOM FROM ME
SO I TAUGHT HER
A LITTLE LESSON IN COURTESY.
- THAT BROOM
WAS LYING ON THE GROUND,
PRINCESS AIRHEAD!
- LOOK HOW YOU
TWIST THINGS AROUND!
- I LEFT IT THERE
TO GIVE IT A REST, YOU TROLL!
- RYOKO, YOU JUST NEVER
KNOW WHEN TO LET UP.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SAYING THIS
WHOLE THING WAS MY FAULT NOW?
- Tenchi: NO, I'M
NOT BLAMING YOU.
- OH, SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT
IT WAS MY FAULT THEN, TENCHI?
- I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
- Ryoko: MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
- WHOSE SIDE?
- Ayeka: SHE'S RIGHT.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU CHOOSE BETWEEN US
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
NOW WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
- HOW DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU CAN TAKE
THE LOVELY PRINCESS
OR THE UGLY OGRE.
IT'S UP TO YOU. BUT CHOOSE.
- CHOOSE THE TWIT!
I DARE YOU!
- I'M TRYING TO FIND
THE LOGIC HERE.
- LOGIC HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
YOU ARE INDECISIVE.
THAT'S THE WHOLE TROUBLE HERE.
JUST TELL MISS SPACE PIRATE
TO GO BACK TO THE DOG STAR.
AND SAY IT CLEARLY.
- HA!  THIS IS
THE PERFECT CHANCE
TO GET RID OF
THAT LITTLE DITZ.
- ( both growling )
- LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS LATER.
- Both: HMPH!
COME ON, TENCHI.
YOU MUST DECIDE.
- EH-- AH-- OH.
AH, LOOK OUT BEHIND YOU.
IT'S A BEAR CHARGING DOWN
FROM THE MOUNTAIN.
- ( both gasp )
- HUH?
- Both: HUH?
WHAA--?!
- ( meows )
- TENCHI?
- Ryoko: TENCHI!
YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY
FOREVER!
- ( pants )
( sighs )
WHAT IS IT?
WHY DO THEY ALWAYS
HAVE TO PUT ME
ON THE SPOT THAT WAY?
OH.
HUH?  HMM.
OH, IT'S A CAMELLIA.
( gasps )
OH.
- TENCHI.
- ( gasps )
- COME HERE.
- Ryoko: TENCHI!
- Ayeka: LORD TENCHI!
- TENCHI!
- ( pants )
( sighs )
HUH?
- Ryoko: AND THAT'S
HOW IT HAPPENED.
TENCHI SIMPLY VANISHED
WITHOUT A TRACE.
- HMM.
- ( scanner beeps )
- ( sighs )
- Mihoshi: ISN'T WASHU AMAZING?
- HUH?
- A FAKE SCIENCE
ACADEMY I.D. CARD!
WHO WOULD EVER KNOW
IT WAS PHONY?
( laughing )
- MIHOSHI!  QUIET.
SHH!  NUH-UH.
- WHAT?  DID YOU SAY
SOMETHING, KIYONE?!
- ( groans )
YOU ARE HOPELESS!
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI, THANKS
FOR THE RIDE HOME.
- Kamidake: PRINCESS.  PRINCESS.
- HUH?
- Both: HELLO.
WELCOME HOME TO JURAI.
- HMM, TO THE THRONE ROOM.
- Noboyuki: FATHER.
- NOBOYUKI.
- I JUST SAW THE POLICE
AND REPORTED TENCHI
AS A MISSING PERSON.
- AH, I SEE.
- THE AUTUMN HAS COME.
- IT HAS BEEN SIX MONTHS.
- ( sighs )
SIX MONTHS AND NO WORD.
IF TENCHI WERE ALIVE,
HE WOULD HAVE CONTACTED US.
I CAN'T BEAR TO THINK
WHAT MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED TO HIM.
- NOBOYUKI, TENCHI IS STRONG.
AND HE KNOWS
THE WAYS OF JURAI.
TRY TO HAVE FAITH.
BELIEVE IN TENCHI.
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( distant chatter )
- MM-MM.
- ( sighs )
- NOT A SINGLE CLUE.
- WE'LL SEARCH.  YEP.
WE'VE GOT WASHU'S ORB.
- Ayeka: I'LL BE YOUR WAITRESS.
CAN I TAKE YOUR ORDER?
- OH, WELL, LET ME SEE.
I THINK I'LL HAVE
A DOUBLE HAMBURGER
JAPANESE STYLE
WITH CHICKEN RISOTTO.
- YES, SIR.
ALL RIGHT THEN,
LET'S SEE
IF I HAVE THIS RIGHT.
YOU WOULD LIKE ONE
DOUBLE HAMBURGER
JAPANESE STYLE AND
ONE CHICKEN RISOTTO.
OH, AND WOULD YOU LIKE
ANYTHING TO DRINK WITH THAT?
WE HAVE FRESH-BREWED COFFEE,
WHICH IS VERY GOOD.
- Woman:
AFTER WE FINISH EATING.
- ( sighs )
TENCHI SHOULD BE
IN THIS AREA
ACCORDING TO WASHU.
WELL, I HOPE
THAT SHE'S RIGHT.
- RYOKO!
- ( gasps )
- I'LL DEDUCT IT
FROM YOUR SALARY.
- ( groans )
- ( sighs )
I'M EXHAUSTED.
- THE BATHHOUSE
CLOSES AT 10:00.
- I THINK I'LL PASS TONIGHT.
- I KNOW WE HAVE TO,
BUT HOLDING DOWN A JOB
WHILE WE SEARCH FOR TENCHI
IS SO DRAINING.
- WE'RE LUCKY THAT THEY HIRED US
WITHOUT REFERENCES.
EVERYBODY COMES
IN THERE TO TALK.
WE MIGHT GET SOME NEWS
ABOUT TENCHI.
- IF WE'RE LUCKY.
FALL IS HERE.
- YES, THE SEASONS
ARE CHANGING.
IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS SINCE...
- WE'VE TRAVELLED
TO SO MANY PLACES
LOOKING FOR TENCHI.
WELL, I THINK THAT EVERYTHING'S
GOING TO CHANGE
NOW THAT WE'RE HERE.
NOW WE HAVE
THE ORB AS WELL.
- WHY DON'T YOU CHECK IT?
- OH, IT'S TIME TO
CALL IN ANYWAY.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
- ( beeps )
- WHAT'S UP, GIRLFRIENDS?
ANY BIG CLUES?
- NOT EVEN A LITTLE CLUE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
HAVE SOMETHING.
- HMM, I DETECTED
SOME TEMPORAL ANOMALIES
AROUND HERE.
THEY MAY HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH TENCHI,
SO STAY IN THE AREA.
LET'S BE VIGILANT, LADIES.
- Ryoko: RIGHT.
( yawns )
WELL, LET'S GET
SOME SLEEP, HUH?
- YES, WE'LL NEED AN
EARLY START TOMORROW.
- RYOKO.
AYEKA!
WHERE AM I?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME.
WHAT KIND OF PLACE
IS THIS?
- ( clock ticking )
- ( groans )
( groans )
- ( chopping )
- ( grunts )
- WAKE UP NOW, TENCHI.
YOU'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- ( groans )
- ( window opens )
- IT'S A LOVELY DAY.
( kisses )
ARE YOU AWAKE?
- UH,
YES, HARUNA, OF COURSE.
- OH, HARUNA.
HERE, TAKE SOME
FRESH PERSIMMONS.
- OH, THEY LOOK SO NICE.
THANK YOU.
- ( static )
- HERE YOU GO.
- DARN THING,
I CAN'T GET A PICTURE.
- MH-HMM.
SOUP WITH FRIED TOFU.
WELL, BON APPETIT.
MMM.
DELICIOUS.
- HERE, HAVE SOME MORE.
- OH, JEEZ,
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU
I DON'T LIKE FERMENTED BEANS?
- DID YOU?
GUESS I FORGOT.
- WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- HAVE A GOOD DAY.
- Washu: I NEED YOU TO
USE THE JURAI NETWORK.
YOU HAVE TENCHI'S
WAVE IMPRINT.
SEARCH FOR TRACES
IN THE TEMPORAL NETTING.
SASAMI, CAN YOU
DO THAT FOR ME?
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- ( bus engine running )
- ( mutters sleepily )
- ARE YOU GONNA SNORE
THE WHOLE WAY, SLEEPING BEAUTY?
HOW ABOUT WAKING UP
FOR A WHILE
TO HELP ME LOOK
FOR TENCHI, HUH?
- ( grunts )
SHUT UP AND LEAVE ME ALONE.
I COULDN'T GET
A WINK LAST NIGHT
'CAUSE YOU KEPT
TALKING IN YOUR SLEEP
LIKE A CHIPMUNK.
- I DO NOT TALK
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
ALWAYS GRINDS HER TEETH.
AND LAST NIGHT,
YOU EVEN FARTED.
- RIGHT, LIKE
PRINCESSES NEVER DO.
- ( beeping )
- TENCHI IS NEARBY.
- RYOKO, I SEE TENCHI.
- Ryoko:
DRIVER, STOP THE BUS!
TENCHI!
( grunts, pants )
DARN!
VERY STRANGE.
- RYOKO?
- ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY SURE
THAT WAS TENCHI?
- YES, BUT HE LOOKED DIFFERENT,
LIKE HE'D GROWN OLDER.
- Washu: YOU LOST HIM, HUH?
HMM?
- HE WAS RIGHT THERE
AND THEN HE JUST VANISHED
INTO THIN AIR.
- SOMETIMES TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS
CAN BE PARTIALLY INTERSECTED.
I'LL GO BACK AND
REVIEW THE DATA.
AND I'LL SEE IF
SASAMI'S PICKED ANYTHING UP.
- WAIT!  WASHU!  WASHU!
- WASHU, COME BACK!
- ( both sigh )
- AREN'T YOU GETTING COLD?
- MM-MM.
- YOU MUST BE TIRED.
- I'M FINE.
- WELL, THAT DOES IT.
HERE'S THE SKETCH.
- IT'S A GREAT LIKENESS.
IT'S GOOD, TENCHI.
- YOU THINK SO?
TO BE HONEST, HARUNA,
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE REALITY SOMEHOW.
- I THINK IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
I LIKE THE PORTRAIT
THAT MY TENCHI'S DRAWN OF ME.
- I THINK YOU'RE
JUST BEING KIND.
- I REALLY MEAN IT.
- HARUNA.
- IT'S SO GOOD
BEING CLOSE TO YOU.
- IT FEELS LIKE...
- WHAT, TENCHI?
- LIKE I'M DREAMING.
- DREAMING?
- BEING WITH YOU
THIS WAY,
THE WHOLE THING IS LIKE--
IT'S LIKE A DREAM, HARUNA.
- YOU'RE NOT DREAMING.
- NO.
YOU'RE NOT DREAMING,
MY SWEET.
- I'M NOT.
- ( moans )
YOUR HANDS ARE SO WARM
AND COMFORTING.
- OHH... OH, NO!
- HMM?  OH, GREAT.
NOW IT'S RAINING.
- Girl: COME ON,
WE'RE GONNA RIDE TOGETHER.
- Boy: I GOT A LOT OF HOMEWORK.
- Girl: IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
COME WITH US.
- Boy: OKAY.
- Girl:
WASN'T THAT CLASS GREAT?
- HUH?
- Girl: SO INSPIRING!
- OH.
- Girl: I'M SO HUNGRY,
I COULDN'T WAIT
FOR CLASS TO BE OVER.
- Boy: ME TOO.
- Girl: COME ON.
- ( laughs )
YEAH, LET'S GO.
COME ON.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD
HAVE BROUGHT AN UMBRELLA.
( laughing )
COME ON, THERE'S ROOM
FOR YOU GUYS, COME HERE.
- LOOK OUT FOR THE PUDDLE.
- ( yelps )
- ( sighs )
- UM, HARUNA.
IT LOOKS LIKE I FOUND
A LITTLE LOST KITTEN.
- ( giggles )
I THOUGHT THAT YOU HAD
ALREADY GONE HOME OR SOMETHING.
- AND YOUR JOB?
- OH, I JUST THOUGHT
I'D TAKE THE AFTERNOON OFF.
- I SEE.
PLAYING HOOKY, ARE WE?
- I BROUGHT THIS.
- NO, THANKS.
I'LL JUST WALK UNDER
YOUR UMBRELLA.
WHAT IS IT?
- ( sighs )
NOTHING.
JUST THINKING HOW
HANDSOME YOU ARE.
- OH, NOW YOU'RE TEASING ME.
- ( both laugh )
- ( sighs )
( gasps )
WE COULD CHECK
REAL ESTATE OFFICES TODAY.
- ( sighs )
YES, GUESS WE COULD.
- ( slurps )
WHAT?
ARE YOU SAD BECAUSE YOU GOT
A SMALLER PIECE OF BREAD?
- HUH?
DID YOU EAT THE REST?!
- ( snickers )
WONDER WHAT THEY'RE
DOING AT HOME?
WHAT DO YOU THINK, AYEKA?
- HUH?
- I THINK THE HOUSE
MUST BE QUIET
AND REALLY LONELY
WITHOUT US.
HE'S AROUND HERE.
I KNOW IT.
- SASAMI IS AT
THE JURAI ROYAL PALACE.
AND KIYONE AND MIHOSHI
ARE AT THE SCIENCE ACADEMY.
- AND WE'RE ON THE ROAD,
FOLLOWING THE CLUES,
TRYING TO KEEP
HOPE ALIVE.
TENCHI, YOU BIG FATHEAD!
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HOW COULD YOU LEAVE
A WONDERFUL
PRINCESS LIKE ME?
I'M HERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
- FORGET ABOUT HER.
JUST COME BACK TO ME.
WE'LL DITCH AYEKA
AND THEN WE CAN PLAY!
- WHAT?!
- FACE IT.  I'M THE ONE
HE REALLY LIKES.
YOU'RE JUST IN THE WAY.
- ( growls )
- ( blows raspberry )
- YOU'RE THE REASON
THAT HE LEFT!
- YEAH?!
- ( both growl )
( both sigh )
- OH MY.
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE WE'VE FOUGHT
LIKE THIS.
- YES, IT HAS.
THANK YOU
FOR TRYING, RYOKO.
- STOP IT.
- ( orb beeps )
- ( gasps )
- ( beeping continues )
I GOT A READING!
( growls )
- OH!
LORD TENCHI!
- MEET ME DOWN THERE!
TENCHI!
TENCHI?
TENCHI...
I LOST HIM!
- Ayeka: RYOKO!
( panting )
( gasps )
THAT GIRL WHO WAS WALKING
WITH TENCHI, WHO IS SHE?
- ( gasps )
HOW THE HELL
WOULD I KNOW?!
I HAVE TO KNOW
WHO SHE IS.
- Boss: RYOKO.
RYOKO!
- ( gasps )
UH, YES?
- THE CUSTOMER AT THE COUNTER
WOULD LIKE SOME COFFEE.
- HUH?  OH, YEAH.
- HMPH!
( sighs )
- ( glass shatters )
- HMM?
- BROKE A CUP?  WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU GIRLS TODAY?
- SORRY, IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I GUESS I'M
A LITTLE TIRED TODAY.
OUCH.
- I'LL CLEAN IT ALL UP.
GET A BANDAGE FOR THAT.
GO ON NOW.
- THANK YOU.
( cries )
- HUH?
AYEKA?
HMM.
- ( sniffling, sobbing )
( cries )
TENCHI!
- Mihoshi: KIYONE!  KIYONE!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?  HUH?
- BE QUIET, MIHOSHI.
I REALLY MEAN IT!
YES, THE MAIN DATA BANKS
OF THE CENTRAL COMPUTER.
THESE DIMENSION STABILIZERS
ARE ABSOLUTELY OFF LIMITS.
IF I GET CAUGHT
HACKING IN HERE,
I'LL BE BEHIND BARS FOREVER.
- ( echoes )
I'M HOME.
- HMM?
( gasps )
- TENCHI, IT'S YOU?!
- SORRY I MADE YOU WORRY.
( chuckles )
- OH, LORD TENCHI,
IT'S REALLY YOU.
( gasps )
LORD TENCHI!
HUH?
( sighs )
ARE YOU AWAKE?
- NO.
- WHO IS THAT
GIRL WE SAW?
SHE LOOKED SO CONTENT,
YOU KNOW?
LAUGHING AND SMILING.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
SO RADIANT WITH JOY.
- WHO?  THAT GIRL?
- NO, I MEAN LORD TENCHI.
IT SEEMED LIKE HE'D
FORGOTTEN ABOUT US,
LIKE WE DIDN'T EXIST.
IS SHE REALLY
THAT PRECIOUS TO HIM, RYOKO?
IS HE SO IN LOVE WITH HER THAT
HE CAN'T EVEN SEE US AT ALL?
JUST WHO IS SHE?
HOW DID SHE MEET
LORD TENCHI?
WHY IS HE WITH HER?
- WHO KNOWS.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING MORE
THAN YOU DO, AYEKA.
- BUT LORD TENCHI AND HER
ARE TOGETHER!
( cries )
I'M SORRY I YELLED.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
- YOU WANT TO GO HOME?
- WHAT?
- IF YOU WANT TO GIVE UP,
I WOULDN'T MIND.
I UNDERSTAND
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
AND WE BOTH SAW IT
WITH OUR OWN EYES.
IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS
SINCE WE WERE WITH HIM.
THAT'S A LONG TIME.
MAYBE HE'S GONE
BEYOND OUR REACH.
HE LOOKED OLDER
AND MORE MATURE.
AND HE SEEMED HAPPY.
AND THE GIRL,
SHE WAS VERY PRETTY.
- BUT, RYOKO...
( cries )
- THINGS CHANGE, AYEKA.
HE MAY NOT WANT US
TO FIND HIM.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT THAT?
WELL, DON'T TORTURE YOURSELF.
YOU'LL GET ALL WORN OUT.
IT'S BAD
FOR THE COMPLEXION.
- RYOKO, YOU'RE SO STRONG.
- GO TO SLEEP.
- ( orb beeps )
- HUH?
- ( beeping continues )
- THAT WAY!
- LORD TENCHI!
- I'VE GOT HIM NOW.
- ( gasps )
- ( brakes squeal )
- OH, LOOK OUT FOR THAT CAR!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I LOST HIM AGAIN.
- RYOKO.
- I'M GETTING
TIRED OF TENCHI.
HE'S SUCH A PAIN.
- ( sighs )
( sobs angrily )
- Tenchi: HARUNA. HARUNA, WHAT
DID YOU DO WITH THAT PORTRAIT?
THE ONE I HAD PINNED UP.
IT'S TORN.
HARUNA, YOU MUST
HAVE DONE IT.
WHY WOULD YOU
WRECK MY PORTRAIT?
HUH?
- ( cries )
- HARUNA, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE YELLED.
IT WAS JUST A SKETCH.
IT'S NOT REALLY IMPORTANT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- ( crying )
- LET'S FORGET IT.
COME ON, MAYBE WE CAN
GO OUT AND EAT FOR A CHANGE.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER.
WE'LL FIND SOME
COZY LITTLE PLACE.
AND WE CAN GO
WINDOW SHOPPING.
- I LIKE THE DESIGN
OF THIS ONE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- IT'S A LITTLE BIT EXPENSIVE.
- HMM, WE SHOULD
GIVE IT BACK.
- HMM, NO, DON'T.
I WANT TO
BUY IT FOR YOU.
- YOU DO?!
OH, TENCHI!
- AND WOULD YOU CARE
FOR MORE COFFEE, SIR?
- NOPE.
- OKAY, ENJOY YOUR MEAL.
- SHE SURE IS
FULL OF ENERGY TODAY.
VERY GOOD.
- Ayeka: WOULD YOU
LIKE MORE COFFEE?
- Man: YES, PLEASE.
- THIS IS NICE AND FRESH.
- WHAT ARE YOU SO CHEERY ABOUT
ALL OF A SUDDEN, PRINCESS?
- NOTHING, I'M SIMPLY BACK TO
MY NATURALLY OPTIMISTIC SELF.
WHO KNOWS? LORD TENCHI COULD
DROP BY THIS VERY RESTAURANT.
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE,
YOU KNOW?
- FINE, ENJOY YOUR WORK,
MISS BRIGHT EYES.
BUT REMEMBER,
YOU'RE STILL AT MINIMUM WAGE.
- MINIMUM WAGE IS BETTER
THAN NO WAGE AT ALL, RYOKO,
IF YOU GET MY MEANING.
NOW YOUR CUSTOMER
IS WAITING FOR YOU.
- I WAS ONLY KIDDING
OF COURSE.
WORK, WORK, WORK.
HERE'S YOUR ORDER, SIR.
- HUH?  I DIDN'T ORDER THAT.
- OH, REALLY?
YOU SURE?
WELL--
THIS IS YOUR ORDER, SIR.
WELL, WE'VE GOT IT
ALL STRAIGHT NOW.
AND HERE'S YOUR BILL--
- ( orb beeping )
( beeping continues )
- HUH?
- HEY.
- HUH?  WHAT--
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( gasps )
IT'S TENCHI.
- HE'S RIGHT THERE.
- HARUNA, I REALLY
HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT I THINK
I WENT A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
- HMM?
- WE'LL HAVE TO
WATCH OUR EXPENSES
TO MAKE PAYMENTS
ON THESE RINGS.
- I'M STILL GLAD
WE GOT BOTH OF THEM.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE MONEY, TENCHI.
- HUH?  BUT YOU DON'T
BRING IN MUCH MONEY
AND I DON'T
HAVE MUCH EITHER.
- HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S FUNNY WHEN THE MACARONI
STICKS TOGETHER LIKE THAT.
- HUH?
( sighs )
- TENCHI!
- LORD TENCHI.
- Ryoko: TENCHI?
CAN'T YOU HEAR ME, TENCHI?
- ( Haruna laughs )
- MAYBE THIS
IS A WOMAN THING
BECAUSE I SURE DON'T GET IT.
CLUE ME IN.
IS MACARONI REALLY
THAT ENTERTAINING,
OR AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
- NO, I'M SORRY.
- JEEZ.
- IT'S STRANGE.
I DON'T THINK HE CAN
SEE US AT ALL.
- I KNOW, BUT WHY CAN'T HE?
TENCHI.
( gasps )
- HE'S NOT REALLY THERE.
IT'S LIKE HE'S AN APPARITION.
- ( groans lightly )
- LOOK AT ME.
I'M RIGHT HERE
IN FRONT OF YOU.
JUST LOOK.
( gasps )
- MY HEAD HURTS.
- WHAT?  OH, TENCHI.
- ( gasps )
- I'M HERE.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
- ( groaning )
- AAH!  YOU BITCH!
GIVE ME BACK TENCHI!
( grunts )
( groans )
- RYOKO.
- I CAN'T REACH THEM.
- WHO ARE YOU?  TELL ME!
- LET'S GO HOME, SWEETHEART.
- OKAY.
- ( rumbling )
- ( zapping echoes )
- Both: HUH?
- ( rumbling, whirring )
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
VANISHED!
- HOW COULD THAT
HAPPEN, THOUGH?
- Washu: HMM.
HARUNA.
WHO IN THE WORLD
IS SHE?
- Azaka:
AH, HERE YOU ARE, PRINCESS.
- AZAKA, KAMIDAKE.
- WE HEARD THAT YOU'RE
RETURNING TO EARTH NOW.
- YES.
- I'M SORRY THAT
YOU HAD TO TRAVEL
ALL THE WAY TO JURAI
ONLY TO LEAVE
WITHOUT FINDING
THE ANSWERS YOU CAME FOR.
- PRINCESS SASAMI,
I'M SURE LORD TENCHI
WILL RETURN TO YOU
IN TIME.
- HMM.
- IT MUST RUN IN THE FAMILY.
LORD YOSHO WAS
EXACTLY THE SAME.
- HUH?
- LONG AGO,
WHEN HE WAS YOUNG,
LORD YOSHO
DISAPPEARED SUDDENLY,
JUST LIKE LORD TENCHI HAS.
- CAN YOU TELL ME THAT STORY?
- WHEN HE LEFT THIS PLANET,
HE GAVE UP
HIS ROYAL THRONE
AND ALL FOR A LOVE THAT
COULD NOT BE FULFILLED,
FOR THEY COULD NOT MARRY.
THE GIRL WAS VERY BEAUTIFUL.
HER NAME WAS CAMELLIA,
ALSO KNOWN AS HARUNA.
- HARUNA?
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID
HER NAME WAS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- YOU REALLY HIT
THE JACKPOT, SASAMI.
THAT'S HER!
( cackles )
- HE WAS RIGHT
IN FRONT OF US.
- SO CLOSE.
- AND THEN IT WAS LIKE
HE JUST FADED AWAY.
- ( sighs )
- HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THAT?
IT'S LIKE A NIGHTMARE,
BUT IT'S REAL.
- IT'S WORSE
THAN A NIGHTMARE.
AT LEAST WITH A NIGHTMARE,
YOU WAKE UP.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON WITH ALL THIS?
I NEED AN EXPLANATION!
- ( sniffles )
- ( static crackles )
- HI, NICE DAY, ISN'T IT?
YOU TWO LOOK
BRIGHT AND CHEERY.  NOT.
INCIDENTALLY, TENCHI DIDN'T
JUST VANISH INTO THIN AIR
RIGHT BEFORE YOUR EYES
BY ANY CHANCE, DID HE?
- ( both gasp )
- WASHU?
- HOW'D YOU KNOW?
WE DIDN'T TELL A SOUL.
A PARALLEL WORLD?
- YOU'RE SAYING THAT
THERE'S A WORLD THAT EXISTS
IN ANOTHER DIMENSION
AND IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO OUR OWN?
- YES, IT'S LIKE A MIRROR
OF OUR WORLD.
IN A SENSE, IT'S COUNTLESS
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY
AND YET IN A FLASH,
IT CAN BE THE VERY SPOT
WHERE YOU'RE STANDING.
- WASHU, ARE YOU TELLING US
THAT LORD TENCHI
NO LONGER EXISTS HERE WITH US
IN THE REAL WORLD.
- HE POPS IN AND OUT OF IT
LIKE A MIRROR
REFLECTING ANOTHER MIRROR.
- BUT A REFLECTION CAN
GO AWAY FOREVER, WASHU.
- TRUE, BUT HE'S NOT STABILIZED
IN THIS MIRROR WORLD YET.
HIS THOUGHTS KEEP
BRINGING HIM BACK HERE.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE A CHANCE
OF REACHING HIM,
BUT IT WON'T LAST LONG.
OF COURSE YOU KNOW
THE ONE WHO PULLED HIM INTO
THIS MIRROR WORLD WAS HARUNA.
AND SHE'LL TRY TO
KEEP HIM THERE TOO.
- THAT GIRL HE WAS WITH!
- MM-HMM.
- HOW CAN WE
GET TO HIM, WASHU?!
WE'VE GOT TO REACH HIM.
- FIRST, I'LL CALIBRATE
THE INTERSECT PROBABILITIES
OF THE TWO WORLDS,
OURS AND THE PARALLEL DIMENSION
WHERE TENCHI IS.
- Ryoko: YOU CAN DO THAT?
- OH, SURE I CAN,
BUT ONLY WITH
THE SCIENCE ACADEMY'S
DIMENSION STABILIZING SYSTEM.
WITH THAT, I CAN EVEN CHANGE
THE ORBIT OF A PLANET IF I WANT.
I'VE ALREADY SENT
KIYONE AND MIHOSHI
TO BREAK INTO
THE SCIENCE ACADEMY.
ALTHOUGH, IT IS
A LITTLE BIT DANGEROUS.
- Ryoko: HOW MUCH TIME
DO WE HAVE TO DO ALL THIS?
- WELL, EVEN NOW,
TENCHI IS BECOMING
MORE AND MORE A PART
OF THIS PARALLEL WORLD.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO WORK
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
AS SOON AS MIHOSHI AND KIYONE
COMPLETE THEIR MISSION,
I'LL SEND YOU TWO INTO ACTION,
SO BE READY.
- ( lightly moan )
( groans )
HMM.  AH.
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
( pants, gasps )
( panting )
- HARUNA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING, BUT DON'T YOU WANT
ME TO POSE FOR YOU NOW?
YOU NEVER ASK ME
ANYMORE, TENCHI.
- NO, I THINK
I'LL CALL IT A DAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT I'VE BEEN
HAVING TERRIBLE HEADACHES.
- YES, YOU DO LOOK
A LITTLE BIT PALE.
MAYBE YOU BETTER NOT
PAINT FOR A WHILE.
- HM-HMM.
HARUNA.
- OH, I DIDN'T
HEAR YOU COMING.
- MM-HMM.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT THIS ROOM
AND, WELL, CAN
YOU DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THE COLOR
OF THESE CURTAINS?
- WHAT?
- WELL, ANY COLOR, BUT
PINK, YOU KNOW.
HOW ABOUT BEIGE
OR LIGHT BLUE?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
DIDN'T LIKE THEM.
I'LL CHANGE THEM TOMORROW.
- THANKS.
- ( exhales, moans )
- WHAT IS IT?
- I'M AFRAID.
AFRAID YOU MIGHT
GO FAR AWAY FROM ME.
- OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
I'M JUST NOT
FEELING TOO WELL.
WE'LL GO TO BED
EARLY TONIGHT.
- MM-HMM.
- I'LL BE FINE
AFTER I GET SOME REST.
- HARUNA.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
SO LONELY.
- LORD KATSUHITO.
- OH, WASHU, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- SASAMI FOUND OUT
ABOUT HARUNA.
AND SHE TOLD ME ABOUT IT.
- AH, I SEE.
- LORD KATSUHITO,
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
TENCHI'S BEING DRAWN
MORE AND MORE
INTO THIS OTHER WORLD,
FARTHER AWAY FROM US.
NOW I NEED SOME ANSWERS.
- HE'S IN DANGER?
YES, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT, WASHU.
I'LL TELL YOU
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG LORD
ON JURAI.
HARUNA HAD THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL EYES I HAD EVER SEEN.
I LOVED HER VERY MUCH,
BUT THAT WAS LONG AGO.
HARUNA AND I
LEFT JURAI TOGETHER.
WE JOURNEYED
TO A DISTANT PLANET, EARTH.
BUT THE LONG JOURNEY
THROUGH SPACE
WAS TOO MUCH FOR HER.
SHE FELL ILL,
GRAVELY ILL.
- THANK YOU, DEAR.
- FOR THE FLOWERS
YOU MEAN?
- NOT THAT.
FOR EVERYTHING YOU'VE DONE.
( sniffs )
THANK YOU.
- DON'T TALK ABOUT
THE PAST, HARUNA.
THINK ABOUT THE FUTURE,
EVERYTHING
WE'LL SHARE TOGETHER.
HARUNA?
HARUNA!
( whispers )
HARUNA.
HARUNA!  HARUNA!  HARUNA!
HARUNA!
- Present-day Katsuhito:
I LANDED ON EARTH.
AND BURIED HER
IN THIS GROUND.
AND BESIDE HER,
I PLANTED THE TREE
THAT HAD LOST ITS MASTER.
- YOU MEAN YOU BROUGHT
THAT TREE FROM JURAI?
- YES, YOU SEE, EACH JURAIAN
HAS A SPECIAL TREE
THAT IS THEIRS ONLY.
THIS WAS HERS--
THIS BEAUTIFUL CAMELLIA.
AFTERWARD, WHEN I SAW
THE TREE TAKE ROOT
AND SPRING BACK TO LIFE,
BEARING FLOWERS AS BEAUTIFUL
AS HARUNA HERSELF,
THAT'S WHEN I DECIDED
TO LIVE IN THIS LAND AS WELL.
I WANTED HARUNA'S SPIRIT
TO KNOW THE MAJESTY
OF THIS PLANET
AND TO GRACE IT
WITH HER OWN BEAUTY.
SO AS I GREW OLDER,
WHEREVER I WENT, I PLANTED
THE BRANCHES FROM THAT TREE.
SO SHE WAS ALWAYS WITH ME.
- THEN THE TREE BEHIND THE
MASAKI SHRINE IS ONE OF THEM?
- YES, IT'S FROM THIS TREE.
IT WAS WHEN
I PLANTED THAT BRANCH,
THAT I MET MY WIFE ITSUKI.
SHE WAS DIFFERENT
FROM HARUNA.
SHE SPARKLED WITH
ENERGY AND EXCITEMENT.
SOON OUR DAUGHTER
ACHIKA WAS BORN.
- AND SO ACHIKA GREW UP
AND MARRIED NOBOYUKI.
AND THEN, IN TIME,
SHE GAVE BIRTH TO TENCHI.
- YES.
WHEN I MARRIED AGAIN,
I BELIEVE THAT IT DISTURBED
HARUNA'S SPIRIT.
SHE MUST HAVE FELT BETRAYED
WHEN I FOUND SO MUCH JOY,
JOY THAT SHE AND I
NEVER EXPERIENCED TOGETHER.
- SO THAT'S IT.
SHE MUST HAVE TAKEN TENCHI
TO EXPERIENCE
THE LIFE SHE NEVER HAD.
- SHE WAS SO KIND AND GENTLE.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BELIEVE IT.
I THOUGHT OF CUTTING DOWN
THIS TREE TO FIND OUT.
LOOK AT IT, WASHU.
CAN YOU SEE
THAT IT'S DYING?
IT MUSTERED
ALL ITS ENERGY
TRYING TO BLOOM
ONE LAST TIME.
THAT'S WHEN HARUNA'S SOUL
WAS AWAKENED
FROM ITS DEEP SLEEP.
AND SHE REMEMBERED
ALL SHE HAD LOST.
HARUNA MUST HAVE
WANTED DESPERATELY
TO FEEL THE LOVE THAT HAD BEEN
TAKEN AWAY FROM HER SO LONG AGO.
- BUT WHY DID SHE TAKE TENCHI
INSTEAD OF YOU?
THAT'S WHAT I DON'T GET.
- TENCHI HAS A TENDER HEART.
I'M OLD AND WEATHERED NOW,
BUT HE IS LIKE THE YOUNG MAN
SHE USED TO KNOW
AND LOVE.
- ( gasps )
- I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS GIRL.
SHE'S NOT REAL.
SHE'S JUST AN IMAGE
THAT I'M PAINTING.
AN IDEA.
OH, HOW CAN
I EXPLAIN THIS?
I FEEL THIS PRESENCE
AND I HAVE TO PUT IT ON CANVAS.
WHY WOULD THAT UPSET YOU
WHEN IT'S ALL IMAGINARY?
I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT.
- I DON'T LIKE HER.
THAT'S ALL.
- YOU DON'T LIKE HER?
WHY IS THAT?
EXPLAIN IT TO ME.
I HAVE TO PAINT WHAT'S IN
MY HEART AND IN MY HEAD.
YOU KNOW THAT.
HOW CAN YOU HATE A SKETCH,
A PIECE OF ART?
( groans )
THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO I AM ANYMORE.
I FEEL LIKE
I LOST MYSELF SOMEWHERE
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE.
UH!
- TENCHI...
- ( moans, exhales )
- DO YOU--
DO YOU LOVE ME?
- ( breathily )
HA-- HARUNA.
- DO YOU LOVE ME?  HUH?
- ( moans )
YOU KNOW THE ANSWER.
- I NEED TO
HEAR YOU SAY IT.
TENCHI, DO YOU LOVE ME?
DO YOU?
- I LOVE YOU.
- WILL YOU LOVE ME
FOREVER AND EVER?
- YEAH.
- WILL YOU STAY WITH ME
FOREVER AND EVER?
- UH-HUH.
- LOOK AT ME.
KEEP YOUR EYES ON ME
AND NEVER LEAVE MY SIDE.
PROMISE ME.
- WITH THE DIMENSION
STABILIZING SYSTEM,
I CAN CREATE
AN INTERSECT BETWEEN
OUR WORLD AND
THE PARALLEL WORLD.
THE PROBLEM IS POWERING
THE FIELD JUMP
AND FOCUSING THAT
ENERGY ON TENCHI.
I'LL NEED SEVERAL
RELAY POINTS.
NOW WHERE AM I GOING TO FIND
A JURAI ENERGY SOURCE
HERE ON EARTH?
ENERGY IN A FIXED FORM
THAT I CAN PINPOINT AND HARNESS.
WELL, AN ORGANIC LIFE FORM
WOULD SURE DO THE TRICK
IF I COULD FIND ONE.
THAT'S IT.
THE CAMELLIA TREES THAT
LORD KATSUHITO PLANTED,
THEY'D BE PERFECT.
- Mihoshi: WE'RE HERE!
- HMM?
- HI.
- WE DID IT!
- WE GOT THE DATA FROM
THE DIMENSIONAL SYSTEM.
- ALL RIGHT.
WHEN IT COMES TO COVERT OPS,
YOU TWO ARE THE TOP.
HEY, I RHYMED.
OH, BY THE WAY, I HAVE
ANOTHER MISSION FOR YOU.
- ( gulps )
ANOTHER ONE?
- WHEN WOULD WE GO?
- ( snickers )
NOW, OF COURSE.
- ( groans )
- THAT'S IT.
I'M POWERED UP AND
LOCKED ONTO THE SPOT
WHERE TENCHI
FIRST CROSSED OVER
INTO THE OTHER WORLD.
IF MIHOSHI AND KIYONE
CAN SET UP THE RELAY SPOTS,
WE'LL BE READY TO DO
A FIELD TRANSFER.
- ( pants ) WASHU,
CERTAINLY KNOWS HOW
TO MAKE THE BEST USE
OF HUMAN RESOURCES.
HERE IT IS.
OF COURSE SHE HAD
TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE HER.
- IS IT MY FAULT
I GET LOST?
THEY ALWAYS MAKE
THE DIRECTIONS SO COMPLICATED:
LEFT, RIGHT, AND ALL THAT.
HEY, THAT'S IT.
- ( buzzing )
- THIS AND THIS AND THIS!
PHEW.
- ( phone rings )
- ( giggles )
KIYONE, IT'S ME.
I'M ALL DONE.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'M PROUD OF YOU, MIHOSHI.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
TENCHI, WE'RE
GONNA FIND YOU!
- TENCHI,
YOUR DINNER IS READY.
- ( groans )
I DON'T REALLY
FEEL LIKE EATING.
( groans )
- I MADE A NICE SALAD
WITH LOTS OF GREENS.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD
GIVE YOU SOME ENERGY.
HERE, TRY IT.
- ( static )
- ( pounding on TV )
- ( Tenchi groans )
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THIS THING?
THE ANTENNA'S CONNECTED,
BUT I CAN NEVER GET ANYTHING
ON THIS SCREEN!  UGH!
WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THIS WORLD?
I KNOW-- THE MONEY WE SAVED
FOR THE RING,
I'LL USE IT TO FIX THE TV.
WHAT'S THIS?
WHAT HAPPENED TO OUR ACCOUNT?
THIS IS JUST CRAZY.
- DON'T THINK ABOUT IT, TENCHI!
JUST PUT IT AWAY!
- DON'T THINK ABOUT IT?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?!
SOMETHING IS WRONG HERE
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
HARUNA! WHAT IS IT?!
I'M TIRED OF BEING
KEPT IN THE DARK.
YOU'RE HIDING
SOMETHING FROM ME
AND I CAN'T
TAKE IT ANYMORE!
UGH!  UGH.
IF YOU WON'T TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON,
I CAN'T...
- OH, TENCHI.
- ( groans )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW ANYMORE.
- I HOPE YOU CAN FORGIVE ME.
I'M SO VERY SORRY.
I JUST WANTED TO HAVE
A HAPPY LIFE WITH YOU.
THAT'S ALL I EVER WANTED.
- HUH?
- OH.
MMM.
( kisses )
OH.
( whimpers )
- I LOVE YOU SO MUCH THAT
I'VE MADE YOU MY WHOLE WORLD,
BUT NOW...
I DON'T THINK I CAN KEEP
LOVING YOU LIKE THIS, HARUNA.
IT HURTS TOO MUCH.
- NO, PLEASE.
- ( groans )
- ( sniffles )
- ( electricity crackling )
( static )
( crackling continues )
- HARUNA.
- DIMENSION STABILIZING
SYSTEM IS ON.
- YOU READY, AYEKA?
- VERY READY.
- WE'VE BEEN WAITING
A LONG TIME.
- I PRAY WE FIND HIM.
- ( beeping )
- GOOD MORNING, LADIES,
FEEL LIKE A LITTLE
DIMENSION JUMP?
- OH, YES.
- JUST SAY THE WORD, WASHU.
- HMM.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG,
WASHU?
- I WAS JUST THINKING.
WOMEN ARE SO STRONG
AND DARING WHEN THEY'RE IN LOVE.
SO GOOD LUCK.
- Ryoko: WOMEN ARE
STRONG AND DARING
WHEN THEY'RE IN LOVE.
HMM.
- I'M HERE, TENCHI.
- ACTIVATE
JURAI POWER SOURCE.
- ( beeping )
- ( static )
- ( wind rushes )
- ( thunder rumbles )
- READY, RYOKO?
- MM-HMM.
- ( wind rushing )
- INTERSECT LOCKED.
OUR TWO WORLDS
ARE IN LINE.
- ( zapping )
- HUH?
( groans )
- ( groaning )
- WE'RE COMING
TO SAVE YOU, TENCHI!
- ( screams )
- RYOKO, I--
- TENCHI, YEAH!
- UH!
- ( yelps )
- ( growls )
- I KNOW HER.
SHE'S REAL.
- OH, YEAH, WAIT TILL
YOU SEE HOW REAL.
NOW-- WHAT?
- Ayeka: RYOKO!
OUCH.
I DIDN'T QUITE GET
THE LANDING RIGHT.
- HEY, TO THE FRONT,
AYEKA, GO!
- EVERYTHING HURTS,
BUT I'LL DO IT FOR TENCHI.
OH.  HUH?
- HERE, TAKE SOME PERSIMMONS.
I JUST PICKED THEM, HARUNA.
- UH, NO, THANKS.
THAT'S OKAY.
( giggles )
- YOU!  HOW DID
YOU GET HERE?
- LET'S GO, COME ON
WITH US, TENCHI, HURRY!
- NO!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- TENCHI, IT'S RYOKO.
I CAME HERE FOR YOU.
- RYOKO...
DO YOU MEAN-- HAVE YOU
COME OUT OF MY DRAWING?
- SHE'S JUST AN ILLUSION.
- GET OUT OF MY WAY.
LET HIM GO.
- NO, HELP ME, TENCHI.
TELL HER TO GO BACK TO WHERE
SHE CAME FROM RIGHT NOW.
- ( growls )
YOU WITCH, YOU'LL PAY!
- ( static )
- HUH?
- ONE, TWO, YEAH!
COME ON, STRETCH, LADIES.
UP, DOWN.
- OH, WHY DID YOU
HAVE TO DO THAT
WHEN IT WAS FINALLY WORKING?
WHY?
- FORGET THE TV.
PLEASE.
- YOU CAN'T GET AWAY.
- LORD TENCHI.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- IT'S ME, AYEKA.
- SEE?
THERE'S NO WAY OUT.
SO HAND TENCHI OVER NOW.
- WE WON'T HURT YOU.
JUST GIVE TENCHI BACK.
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
I WON'T.
- HUH?
- YOU BARGE INTO MY HOME
AND YOU MAKE THESE DEMANDS.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'VE GONE THROUGH.
I'LL NEVER LET TENCHI GO.
TENCHI BELONGS HERE.
NOW GO BACK
TO YOUR OWN WORLD.
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( screams )
- HARUNA, WHAT--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO THEM?
- I SAID GO BACK
TO YOUR WORLD!
- ( both screaming )
- HMM?  WHAT--
WHAT IN THE--
- ( thunder crashes )
- WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( thunder crashes )
- ( screams )
- IMPOSSIBLE.  SHE'S SENDING
OUR ENERGY PULSE BACK HERE
FROM THE PARALLEL WORLD.
- ( tree rumbles, cracking )
- HARUNA.
- Ayeka: RYOKO.
- HMM, HUH?
HUH?!
- I'M GLAD YOU WOKE UP.
- AYEKA.
- DID YOU THINK I HAD
NO POWER TO DEAL WITH YOU
TRESPASSING INTO MY WORLD?
- GIVE TENCHI BACK!
- HE'S MY MAN.
I'M HIS WOMAN.
THAT'S REALITY.
AND, BY THE WAY,
HE LOVES ME,
IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T NOTICE.
- OH, PLEASE.
IT'S JUST A TRICK.
- YOU MADE HIM FORGET.
HOW COULD HE LOVE YOU
IF HE DOESN'T KNOW WHO HE IS?
- HE KNOWS ENOUGH.
HE KNOWS HOW HE FEELS
IN HIS HEART.
IT'S VERY SIMPLE, REALLY.
I WANTED HIM, SO I DREW
HIM INTO THIS WORLD
AND GAVE HIM
WHAT HE WANTED.
- Ryoko: THEN WHY
IS HE SO UNHAPPY?
- WAS HE HAPPY WITH YOU
FIGHTING OVER HIM,
DRIVING HIM AWAY
INTO THE FOREST?
- YOU LISTEN!
I'M NOT LEAVING HIM
WITH A WITCH
WHO KEEPS HIM IN SOME
MADE-UP FANTASY WORLD.
- ( giggles )
YOU'RE SO BRAZEN.
HE DOESN'T LIKE THAT.
- HARUNA, THIS IS WRONG.
IT'S NOT FAIR TO TENCHI.
- REALLY?  AND ARE YOU
FAIR TO HIM
OR DO YOU JUST WANT HIM?
I THINK WE'RE ALL
JUST THE SAME.
WE ALL WANT TENCHI,
AND WHOEVER WANTS
HIM THE MOST
WILL HAVE HIM.
AFTER HALF A CENTURY
OF WAITING,
MY DESIRE IS STRONG.
I'M LETTING YOU GO,
BUT DON'T COME BACK.
- TENCHI!
- ( wind rushes )
- EXTRAORDINARY.
THIS PARALLEL WORLD
HAS A SHORTER AXIS.
THAT'S WHY TIME
MOVES FASTER THERE.
- ( both grunt )
( groaning )
- WHERE ARE WE?
- AAH.
SHE TRANSPORTED US BACK.
- ( beeping )
- OH.
- OH, WASHU, PLEASE.
TELL US WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- WELL, I SUSPECTED
THERE WAS A FLAW
IN THE FIELD INTERSECT.
YOU SEE, TIME MOVES FASTER
IN THAT WORLD.
YOU SAW HOW TENCHI LOOKED,
DIDN'T YOU?
HE'S OLDER THERE.
HARUNA SHORTENED
THE TIME AXIS ON PURPOSE.
SO SHE COULD HAVE TENCHI
EXACTLY THE WAY SHE WANTED HIM.
THAT WORLD IS MADE
ENTIRELY OF HER DESIRES.
- BUT WHY WOULD
SHE DO SUCH A THING?
- BECAUSE SHE'S ACTING OUT
HER EMOTIONS.
SHE'S CREATED THAT WORLD
OUT OF HER FEELINGS.
I'M AFRAID ANY FURTHER
SCIENTIFIC INTERFERENCE
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
- UGH!
- BUT, WASHU,
IF WE DON'T GO BACK THERE,
WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO TENCHI?
- UNLESS SOME INCIDENT
JARS HIS MEMORY,
HE'LL JUST REMAIN THERE.
AND IT GETS WORSE.
TENCHI'S JURAI ENERGY IS KEEPING
THAT WORLD STABILIZED.
WHEN HE GETS TOO EXHAUSTED,
THE WHOLE WORLD WILL FALL APART.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- UGH!
WASHU, THERE MUST BE A WAY
TO GET BACK THERE.
- HARUNA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- Ryoko: TENCHI!
- Ayeka: LORD TENCHI!
- I HEAR VOICES
CALLING MY NAME,
BUT WHO ARE THEY?
- Ryoko: TENCHI, YOU DAMN FOOL!
- ( clock ticking )
- ( groans )
( sighs )
- ( water running )
- ( chopping )
- WAKE UP, TENCHI.
YOU'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- ( groans )
- ( window opens )
- IT'S A LOVELY DAY.
- ( rumbling, crashes )
- OH!
- HELLO, SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
- I NAILED THE LANDING THIS
TIME. PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHEN
TO GIVE UP, DO YOU?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I WAS GONNA SAY TO YOU.
THIS WHOLE WORLD'S
A DEATH TRAP.
NOW LET HIM GO!
- NO, I'LL NEVER LEAVE HIM.
- HARUNA, YOU SAID
WE'RE ALL THE SAME,
BUT THERE'S A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN US.
WE DON'T LIE TO TENCHI
OR KEEP HIM TRAPPED
IN AN IMAGINARY WORLD
OF MAKE-BELIEVE.
- IT MAY BE MAKE-BELIEVE TO YOU,
BUT IT'S REAL TO ME.
AND NOW IT'S REAL
TO TENCHI AS WELL.
HE DOESN'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHO YOU ARE, EITHER ONE OF YOU.
- LOOK AT US.
THINK HARD.
I KNOW THAT YOU REMEMBER
WHO WE ARE, DON'T YOU?
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
- I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU!
- I'M TELLING YOU
HE DOESN'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING BUT THIS WORLD.
- Ayeka: YOU DO REMEMBER,
LORD TENCHI, DON'T YOU?
- LET TENCHI ANSWER, HARUNA.
- WE'RE FROM YOUR WORLD,
TENCHI, THE REAL WORLD.
- Haruna: HOW DO YOU
KNOW WHAT IS REAL?
I HOLD HIM IN MY ARMS
AND FEEL HIS WARMTH
AND HE FEELS MINE.
THERE'S NOTHING
MORE REAL THAN THAT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
CREATED THIS WORLD?
NOT SCIENCE, NOT MAGIC.
IT'S THE POWER OF MY HEART.
- VERY WELL THEN.
I'LL REACH OUT TO TENCHI
WITH MY HEART.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WITH FEELINGS, HARUNA.
LET'S SEE WHOSE HEART
IS STRONGER.
- YOU DON'T REALLY THINK
YOU CAN GET PAST ME
HERE IN MY OWN WORLD,
DO YOU?
- AND YOU DON'T THINK WE'LL
LEAVE WITHOUT A FIGHT, DO YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WE DON'T NEED WEAPONS.
GET UP.  I'LL SHOW YOU
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU FIGHT A SPACE PIRATE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- ( gasps )
- RYOKO, AYEKA, STAY BACK
AND LEAVE HER ALONE.
- WHY ARE YOU DEFENDING HER,
LORD TENCHI?
- WE CAME HERE FOR YOU, TENCHI.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW SHE FEELS RIGHT NOW,
BUT I DO.
- TENCHI.
- YOU MEAN THAT YOU--
YOU WANT TO
STAY HERE WITH HER?
- ( gasps )
IT'S VANISHING AGAIN.
- NO, WE DON'T
WANT YOU TO GO, PLEASE!
- DON'T LET US GO!
TENCHI!
- LORD TENCHI!
- ( orb beeps )
- WELL, I WARNED YOU
NOT TO GO BACK THERE,
NOW, DIDN'T I?
- ( whimpers )
- NO MORE.
HE'LL NEVER COME
BACK TO US NOW.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
HE CHOSE HER.
I COULDN'T REACH HIM
WITH MY HEART.
- ( clock ticking )
- ( groans )
( sighs )
- ( chopping )
- HUH?
- HMM?
WAKE UP, TENCHI.
YOU'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- ( groans )
- ( window opens )
- IT'S A LOVELY DAY.
- HARUNA, WE NEED
TO TALK ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
WE CAN'T IGNORE IT.
YOU KNOW WE NEED TO FACE
THE TRUTH ABOUT THIS WORLD.
- SO YOU REMEMBER.
EVERYTHING IS CLEAR NOW?
- HMM.
- LOOK OUTSIDE.
CLEAR SKIES, SUNSHINE.
EVERYTHING IS CALM
AND PEACEFUL HERE.
ISN'T THAT
THE WAY IT SHOULD BE?
WE CAN LIVE
LIKE THIS FOREVER--
HAPPY, LOVING.
YOU JUST NEED TO MAKE UP
YOUR MIND TO ACCEPT IT.
TRY, TENCHI.
WE CAN MAKE
A BEAUTIFUL LIFE TOGETHER.
IT'S A--
- I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
HOW YOU AND I MET, HARUNA!
- ( gasps )
- ( inhales )
( growls )
HARUNA, I AM COMING!
( screaming )
- ( screams )
AAH!
- HARUNA!
- NO!
( screams )
- ( screaming )
( screaming stops )
- STOP IT, PLEASE!
- HARUNA, CALM DOWN.
THIS IS YOUR WORLD
WE'RE IN, RIGHT?
WHY'D YOU TRY TO DECEIVE
EVEN YOURSELF?
THERE'S THINGS
I STILL DON'T KNOW,
THINGS YOU'VE BEEN HIDING
FROM ME FROM THE BEGINNING.
I'M RIGHT HERE WITH YOU
FACE-TO-FACE.
WHAT ARE YOU SO AFRAID OF?
- NO!
- HARUNA!
- Young Yosho: HARUNA.
HARUNA.
WE'VE ARRIVED, HARUNA.
WE'RE HERE.
- SO THIS IS EARTH?
IT'S RADIANT.
WE REALLY DID IT, YOSHO.
- YES.
THE AIR AND WATER
ARE FRESH HERE.
THEY'LL CURE YOU
IN NO TIME.
JUST HANG ON
A LITTLE LONGER.
- I CAN'T, YOSHO.
I'M SORRY.
I'LL NEVER SURVIVE
THE LANDING.
MY JOURNEY IS OVER.
- HARUNA, WE MADE IT.
WE'VE COME ALL THIS WAY.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP NOW.
- YOSHO, I'M HAPPY
BECAUSE WE DID
WHAT WE SET OUT TO DO.
AND WE'RE TOGETHER.
- FORGIVE ME.
IF I HADN'T TAKEN YOU AWAY,
THIS NEVER WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
YOU'D STILL BE HEALTHY
AND FULL OF LIFE.
I WISH WE'D
STAYED ON JURAI.
- WE COULDN'T LOVE
EACH OTHER THERE.
AND NOW WE'VE HAD THIS
WONDROUS JOURNEY TOGETHER.
I DON'T REGRET
ANYTHING, YOSHO.
I CHERISHED EVERY
MOMENT WITH YOU.
( sighs )
HOW LOVELY IT IS.
YOU CHOSE SUCH
A PERFECT PLANET
FOR US TO LIVE ON.
I CAN IMAGINE
HOW OUR LIVES
WOULD HAVE BEEN
SO PEACEFUL...
( strained )
AND SO FULL OF JOY.
( coughs )
- HARUNA!
- HOLD MY HAND.
- MY LOVE.
- DO YOU LOVE ME EVEN NOW?
- MORE THAN EVER.
- AND WILL YOU LOVE ME FOREVER
THROUGHOUT ALL TIME?
- YOU KNOW I WILL.
- YES, ARE HEARTS
WILL BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
- I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU
RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
- THEN I'M CONTENT.
JUST THINK WHAT OUR LIVES
WOULD HAVE BEEN LIKE
ON THAT SHIMMERING PLANET.
TIME SLIPPING AWAY
AS ONE SWEET DAY
FLOWED INTO ANOTHER.
- IT WILL BE LIKE THAT,
MY LOVE.
JUST HANG ON
A LITTLE LONGER.
YOU CAN DO IT.
WE'LL LIVE TOGETHER,
YOU AND I,
FOREVER,
IN A WORLD OF OUR OWN.
AND WE'LL BE SO HAPPY.
- ( sniffling )
- HARUNA, ARE YOU--
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, HARUNA?
- ( cries )
- HUH?
OH.
- THE PARALLEL WORLD
IS DESTABILIZING.
ALL PARAMETERS ARE SHIFTING.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN? WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN, MISS WASHU?
- IT'S COLLAPSING ON ITSELF,
AND IT'S GOING FAST.
- WELL, WHAT ABOUT
LORD TENCHI, MISS WASHU?
- REMEMBER, I SAID THIS WORLD
IS LIKE A REFLECTION
IN A MIRROR.
IF THE MIRROR GOES DARK,
TENCHI WILL CEASE TO EXIST.
- NO, IT CAN'T BE.
WE'VE GOT TO STOP IT.
I CAN'T LOSE TENCHI LIKE THIS
INTO A VOID OF NOTHINGNESS!
- Washu: I KNOW HOW
YOU FEEL, AYEKA,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO.
IT'S IN THE HANDS OF FATE.
- HARUNA,
DO YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
- ( groans )
YES.
YES, OF COURSE.
ONLY A FEW MOMENTS AGO,
I SAW YOU IN MY DREAM.
- NO, YOU HAVE
IT BACKWARDS.
THAT WAS NOT
A DREAM AT ALL.
IT WAS A MEMORY
OF OUR PAST.
THE REAL PAST WHERE
AN EXTRAORDINARY GIRL
DIED BECAUSE OF ME.
- OH, IT WASN'T
YOUR FAULT, YOSHO.
YOU TRIED.  I JUST
COULDN'T MAKE THE JOURNEY.
- YOU WILL RETURN TENCHI,
MY GRANDSON, TO ME.
WON'T YOU, HARUNA?
- I'M SO SORRY, TENCHI.
YOU SEE,
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO FORGOT ABOUT
HIS OWN WORLD.
I FORGOT ABOUT
MINE AS WELL.
I HAD DREAMED OF LIVING WITH
THE MAN I LOVED
AND THAT DREAM CAME TO LIFE.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO HURT YOU,
I SWEAR.
- I KNOW.  I WISH
I COULD HAVE HELPED YOU MORE
BY UNDERSTANDING WHAT
YOU HAD GONE THROUGH.
- YOU DID HELP.
SHE REMEMBERS WHO SHE IS NOW.
AND SHE'S RECOVERED
HER SPIRIT.
THAT WAS YOUR DOING.
THANK YOU, TENCHI.
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE
WAITING FOR YOU
BACK IN YOUR OWN WORLD.
RETURN NOW TO THE PLACE
YOU CALL HOME.
- UH-HUH, AND WILL THINGS BE
THE WAY THEY WERE BEFORE?
- THEY WILL.
- TENCHI,
REMEMBER THIS?
I'LL ALWAYS TREASURE IT.
- I WANT YOU TO KNOW, I--
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU, HARUNA.
- YES, YOU WILL.
YOU MUST.
LET THE MEMORY FADE AWAY
TILL THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
BUT A WARM FEELING
IN YOUR HEART.
- HARUNA, WAIT, PLEASE.
- LET GO.  IT'S TIME.
- RYOKO, YOU HEARD HER.
THE PARALLEL WORLD
IS DESTABILIZED.
YOU CAN GO TO HIM.
MAYBE YOU CAN BRING HIM BACK
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- FORGET IT.
HE'LL NEVER COME BACK
TO US ANYWAY, AYEKA.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW?
YOU JUST CAN'T GIVE UP.
HE DOESN'T KNOW
THAT WORLD IS DYING.
- UGH!  HE WANTED
TO BE WITH HER.
SO BE IT.
- ( scoffs )
NO, YOU DON'T REALLY
MEAN THAT.
OH, THAT'S NOT
LIKE YOU AT ALL, RYOKO.
YOU ARE THE ONE WHO TOLD ME
TO BELIEVE IN TENCHI.
REMEMBER?  YOU SAID
TO NEVER GIVE UP.
- HMPH!  LOOK, AYEKA,
YOU CAN GO IF YOU WANT.
- UH... I WISH I COULD
BE THE ONE, OF COURSE.
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN REACH HIM, RYOKO.
YOU KNOW THAT.
- HUH?
- ( Washu typing )
- NO, HE'S PROBABLY
FORGOTTEN ABOUT US AGAIN.
THAT'S THE WHOLE TROUBLE.
- BUT IF THE PARALLEL WORLD
IS SHIFTING NOW,
THAT COULD ALL CHANGE.
HE MAY ACTUALLY
BE SEARCHING FOR US.
WHAT IF HE NEEDED OUR HELP
AND WE WEREN'T THERE,
WITH THAT WHOLE
WORLD COLLAPSING.
- YES, YOU MAY
BE RIGHT, AYEKA.
WITH THE SHIFTING
ENERGY LEVELS,
SOMEONE MAY BE ABLE
TO GET IN
AND BRING TENCHI
BACK TO OUR WORLD.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, RYOKO?
I CAN TRANSFER ONE PERSON.
IT'LL BE TIGHT.
- UH...
- YOU'VE GOT
TO DO IT, RYOKO.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY,
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE FEELING.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE HIM
ANY MORE THAN I DO.
SO IF THERE'S A CHANCE,
YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE IT.
BE TRUE TO YOUR
FEELINGS, RYOKO,
OR YOU'LL LOSE YOURSELF.
- ( exhales deeply )
HMM.  HMM.
THERE-- TENCHI.
- ( zapping )
- IT'S HAPPENING.
BAH!
- NICE FLIP.
YOU OKAY, RYOKO?
- YOU NEED TO WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
YOU KNOW?
- RIGHT, SORRY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S REALLY YOU AGAIN, ISN'T IT?
I MEAN, YOU CAN RECOGNIZE
ME AND ALL?
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, MAKING YOU WORRY.
- WHERE'S HARUNA?
IS SHE IN THERE?
- NO, SHE'S GONE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT HARUNA ANY LONGER.
THAT'S ALL OVER NOW.
( sighs )
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I CAME BACK HERE.
I WASN'T GOING TO.
WHEN YOU SENT US BACK,
I THOUGHT,
"THAT'S IT FOR TENCHI,
FOR GOOD."
I WAS GOING TO FORGET
ALL ABOUT YOU.
- I'M SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
- HUH?
- I KNOW I CAN ALWAYS
COUNT ON YOU, RYOKO.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME.
- ( sighs )
- THANKS FOR COMING.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT.
- WELL, DON'T THINK I'M GONNA
TAKE YOU BACK OR ANYTHING.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE YOU
WEREN'T EMBARRASSING YOURSELF,
FORGETTING WHO YOU ARE
AND ALL THAT.
- HEY, LET'S GO HOME.
LATER ON, WE CAN TALK.
- TENCHI, YOU REALIZE
THIS IS THE VERY LAST TIME
YOU'LL SEE THIS WORLD.
- I KNOW.
AND IT'S TIME
TO LEAVE IT
ALL BEHIND ME.
- ( instrumental music playing )
( music continues )
- REST IN PEACE, HARUNA.
- ( cloth flaps )
- HMM?
ITSUKI, DON'T BE JEALOUS.
- ( leaves rustling )
- ( girls laughing )
- Ryoko: AND THAT'S
HOW IT ENDED.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- Ryoko: SURPRISING HOW QUICKLY
WE WENT BACK
TO EVERYDAY LIFE.
- Mihoshi: I BET THEY'RE
GOING TO BE REALLY TASTY.
OOH, I CAN'T WAIT.
- YEAH.
- I'M HUNGRY.
- Sasami: YOU'RE ALWAYS
HUNGRY, MIHOSHI.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- ALL RIGHT,
THEY'RE READY TO EAT.
- HMM.
- YEAH!
- WOW, THEY LOOK DELICIOUS.
SASAMI,
CAN I HAVE ONE, PLEASE?
- WATCH OUT.  YOU'RE GOING
TO BURN YOURSELF, MIHOSHI.
- WHERE'S LORD TENCHI?
- I SAW HIM CLIMBING UP
THE HILL BEHIND THE HOUSE
JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- HMM.
- Mihoshi: I HAVE TO EAT!
- Ryoko: TENCHI.
- RYOKO?
- I THOUGHT
I'D FIND YOU HERE.
- DID YOU THINK
I'D DISAPPEAR AGAIN?
- WELL, IF YOU DID,
I'D JUST DRAG YOU
RIGHT BACK.
- NICE TO KNOW.
HUH?
WHAT?
- HMM, NOTHING.
I THINK I LIKE YOU
THIS WAY.
- ( grunts )
RYOKO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- ( giggles )
ARE YOU MAD?
- HUH?
- I DON'T THINK I'D MIND
IF YOU GOT ANGRY.
- INCREDIBLE.
THAT IS NOT LIKE YOU
AT ALL, RYOKO.
- HMM.
SO THEN, I SEE
YOU'VE TAKEN UP DRAWING.
- YEAH, I WAS THINKING
HOW MY FATHER USED TO DRAW
WHEN HE WAS MY AGE,
BUT THEN HE STOPPED
DOING IT, YOU KNOW?
I LIKE THE WAY
IT MAKES ME FEEL.
- GOTCHA.
AND HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- LIKE I'M REMEMBERING SOMETHING
I FORGOT LONG AGO.
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
WHEN I DRAW,
I FEEL THINGS
I LOST TOUCH WITH,
BUT ARE STILL THERE
INSIDE MY HEART.
- TENCHI.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )