- Crowd: STARTICA!
- Girl: YAY!
- ( laughing, chattering )
- ( panting )
THIS IS FOR YOU.
- WOW.
HUH? OH.
- ( growling )
- ( screaming )
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming continues )
- NO, DON'T!
DON'T HURT HER, PLEASE!
- ( grunts )
DEPART, YOU WICKED CREATURE!
- ( screaming )
( yawns )
THAT WAS SURE
A DREARY DREAM.
SHEESH, SO WEIRD.
WONDER WHAT IT MEANS.
- ( beeping )
- ♪ JINGLE BELLS, JINGLE BELLS,
JINGLE ALL THE WAY ♪
- HMM? WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS GOING ON?
WHAT? THOSE ARE
THE GUARDIANS?
- HUH? WHAT'S A JURAIAN PRINCE
DOING THERE?
- ♪ IN A ONE-HORSE OPEN SLEIGH ♪
- ♪ JINGLE BELL, JINGLE BELL ♪
- ♪ DASHING THROUGH THE SNOW ♪
- COMING THROUGH, GRANDFATHER.
- LOOK AT THAT. YOU MADE
A STUPENDOUS CAKE, SASAMI.
- YAH, TENCHI!
- ( crashes )
- OH MY WORD!
- HEY, LOOSEN UP AND HAVE
A DRINKY, COME ON.
- I'M GETTING IT NOW. HE THINKS
HE'S PRINCE CHARMING, THIS GUY.
WAIT, I'M GETTING
A BRAINSTORM. LOOK OUT.
- EH, RYOKO GETS WILD.
- HEY, TENCHI. HI THERE.
- HUH?
WHAT'S UP, SASAMI?
- ( laughs )
LOOK, I GOT YOU A SURPRISE.
IT'S A CHRISTMAS PRESENT. WHOA,
THANKS, SASAMI. THAT'S COOL.
- ( chimes )
- I'VE GOT A SURPRISE TOO.
A CHRISTMAS PRESENT.
( grunts ) NO WAIT, A
SUMMER STARTICA PRESENT!
FOR PRINCE CHARMING.
( cheering )
YEAH!
WHOA.
NOW THERE'S A GOOD GIRL.
I MADE A PROMISE THAT DAY
AND NOW I'LL SEND IT TO HIM.
STARTICA-AAA!
- ( humming )
- HI, GOOD MORNING.
- GOOD MORNING, KIYONE.
- IT'S GOING TO BE
ANOTHER HOT SUMMER DAY.
- THE FLOWERS LOVE IT.
- ( humming )
WHERE'S TENCHI, HUH?
- OH, HE WENT OUT TO CLEAN
THE TOMBSTONE.
- HELLO, MIHOSHI!
- OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
GET IN THERE!
( hums )
COMING!
- CAN ANYONE GIVE ME A HAND
MOPPING THE FLOOR?
- NOT ME.
WHERE'S RYOKO?
- LAZING AROUND
JUST DOING NOTHING, I BET.
- ( groaning )
- HUH?
HUH?
- DADDY?
- ( yelps )
- I'M SORRY I'M LATE, DADDY.
- AYEKA?
- ( meowing )
- ARE THESE OKAY, AYEKA?
- MM-HMM.
THEY'RE PERFECT.
- Tenchi: I'M HOME!
- IT'S TENCHI, HE'S BACK EARLY!
- COMING!
OH HELLO, TENCHI.
UH...
- UH, SHE IS-- THAT IS--
WELL, THE THING IS--
- YES, TENCHI?
- WHO'S THAT GIRL HE'S WITH?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HEY YOU, WHO ARE YOU?
- SAY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
OHHH.
- WOW, WE'VE GOT
A REAL VISITOR!
COME IN. SORRY ABOUT THE HEAT.
IT'LL COOL OFF SOON.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HMPH! WHAT ARE YOU HIDING FOR?
HEY, I'M TALKING TO YOU.
- EASY, RYOKO. WHAT ARE YOU
GIRLS MAKING SUCH A FUSS ABOUT?
HUH? TENCHI,
WHO'S THAT GIRL?
- UH, WELL, I MET HER, EH...
I WAS COMING DOWN
THE STEPS OF THE CEMETERY--
- ( girls all yell )
- I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
THIS STORY. SPEED IT UP.
- DON'T MAKE SUCH
A BIG DEAL ABOUT IT.
SHE FOLLOWED ME HERE.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
RIGHT?
( forced laughter )
( yelps )
- DADDY!
- ( all yell )
- SHE CALLED YOU "DADDY."
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN BY THAT?
- ARE YOU HIDING
SOMETHING FROM US?
- NO! COME ON, EVERYBODY.
YOU'RE ONLY KIDDING, RIGHT?
- NO, DADDY.
- ( moaning )
- WOW, TENCHI'S A FATHER.
- OH WELL, ISN'T THAT NICE?
- IT'S HOT TODAY, ISN'T IT?
COME IN.
- GUESS WHAT, DADDY.
- ( yelps )
DADDY-- YEAH WELL--
- ( giggles )
- I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, DADDY.
- NOW YOU'VE GOTTA
STOP THAT TALK.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN STOP?
DON'T YOU LIKE ME AT ALL?
- WELL SURE,
BUT ALL THIS DADDY TALK--
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT--
- ( growls )
I'VE HAD IT! I AM NOT GOING TO
PUT UP WITH THIS MISS INNOCENT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING--
TRYING TO TRICK TENCHI,
BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
- YOU'RE NUTS!
- HUH HA-AAA! LET'S GO.
- ( girls scream )
- HEY, HOLD ON!
- ( yelps )
ARE YOU CRAZY?
OH OH OH OH OH.
- YOU HAVEN'T SEEN CRAZY YET,
YOU LITTLE PUNK.
- RYOKO, STOP IT!
- NO, GET BACK HERE.
- DO YOU HAVE TO MAKE
SUCH A RACKET? HUH?
- ( squeals )
PLEASE STOP IT.
- OH, MISS POLITE NOW, HUH?
"PLEASE STOP IT."
TELL ME WHO YOU ARE
AND WHAT YOU'RE TRYING
TO PULL ON TENCHI, HUH?
- NO!
- WHAT?
HUH?
- ( crackling )
- Ayeka: OH, THAT'S IT.
- Tenchi: LOOK,
IT'S THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD.
- HMM, HUH.
- COME ON, HURRY!
( yells )
- ( chuckles )
IT'S A PRESENT FROM ME.
ENJOY IT, YOSHO.
- YAH!
- ( giggles )
- AH, OH. HUH?
OH.
- I'M VERY SORRY,
BUT NO MATTER WHAT
THE PROVOCATION,
I NEVER ALLOW KILLING
IN THE HOUSE.
- GRANDPA, DID YOU SEE IT?
SHE HAD THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD.
- DON'T GET BENT OUT OF SHAPE,
TENCHI. YOU KNOW I'VE WORKED UP
AN APPETITE. MAYBE WE CAN
WHIP UP SOME LUNCH, HUH?
- HUH?
- HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOU HUNGRY, MISSY?
GO FOR SOME NOODLES?
- UH-HH...
- GOOD, IT'S SETTLED THEN.
- Sasami:
I'LL BOIL UP SOME WATER.
- OUCH!
- ( laughs ) THANKS SO MUCH
FOR COOPERATING WITH MY NEW
SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH PROGRAM.
BUH-BYE!
- Tenchi: AHEM.
- ( slurps ) MM.
DELICIOUS!
- THAT'S SWELL.
- DO YOU LIKE NOODLES, DADDY?
- SURE.
- WHICH DO YOU LIKE BETTER,
NOODLES OR ME?
- WELL, I-- THAT IS--
- HERE, DADDY, LET ME HELP YOU.
- I THINK I CAN HANDLE
IT MYSELF.
- BUT I WANT TO.
AH, THERE. FOR YOU.
- UH GEE, THANKS A LOT.
- ( crashes )
- ( groaning )
- ( clears throat )
- DADDY, IS RYOKO UPSET
OR SOMETHING?
- ( yelps )
I'M SURE SHE'LL BE FINE.
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
AHHH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHATEVER I WANT.
- THAT'S MY NOODLE.
- WRONG!
- ( growls )
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- YOU'RE THE PROBLEM,
YOU LITTLE PHONY!
- OH YEAH?
- YEAH, WHAT ABOUT IT?
- AHHH, WHAT A GREAT MEAL.
- HUH?
OH?
- OH BOY, I AM STUFFED.
SEE YA LATER.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING, DADDY?
- I THINK I'LL TAKE A BATH.
- I'LL COME TOO!
WAIT FOR ME, DADDY.
DADDY!
- ( all gasp )
- ( laughs )
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
- ( beeping )
- ( slurps )
SO THAT'S HER STORY.
( chuckles )
( slurps )
- NOW EXPLAIN IT AGAIN
AND THIS TIME TRY MAKING SENSE.
- Ayeka: YOU CAN START
BY TELLING US WHY YOU CAME HERE.
- TO SEE MY DADDY.
I REALLY LOVE MY DADDY.
- HE'S NOT YOUR DADDY!
- STOP YELLING AT HER.
YOU'RE NOT HELPING THINGS.
- OH FINE!
- WE KNOW YOUR NAME ALREADY,
BUT WHERE ARE YOU FROM, MAYUKA?
- AH, WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT?!
NOW STOP PLAYING
GAMES WITH US!
- I AM NOT PLAYING A
GAME, BELIEVE ME.
- UH, WE'LL LET'S TRY
A DIFFERENT TACT.
WHERE IS YOUR MOTHER? WHY ISN'T
SHE HERE WITH YOU, HUH, DEAR?
- MY MOTHER?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING ABOUT MY MOTHER,
BUT I REMEMBER
MY FATHER'S FACE VERY WELL.
- OH. DID YOUR MOTHER
DIE, MAYUKA?
- HUH-UH.
- THEN WHY DON'T
YOU REMEMBER HER?
- I DON'T KNOW. I JUST
DON'T REMEMBER, THAT'S ALL.
- HEY, MAYBE SHE HAS
AMNESIA OR SOMETHING.
- WHOA, BUT WAIT A MINUTE,
HOW COULD SHE HAVE AMNESIA?
SHE REMEMBERS MY FACE
OR THINKS SHE DOES.
- Washu: TENCHI?
- HUH?
- OH UH, HI THERE. I WAS JUST
ON MY WAY TO TAKE A BATH.
- I DISCOVERED SOMETHING
VERY INTERESTING
ABOUT THAT GIRL, TENCHI.
- HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
- FIRST OFF, YOU REALLY
ARE HER FATHER. CONGRATS.
- HEY, YOU WANT TO HAVE
SOME WATERMELON, WASHU?
- AFFIRMATIVE.
- HEY, EVERYONE, I'M CUTTING
UP SOME WATERMELON.
WANT SOME?
- ( moans )
WASHU, HOW CAN I BE
THAT GIRL'S FATHER?
- Ryoko: AND WASHU EXPECTS US
TO BELIEVE THAT NONSENSE?
- LET'S SEE, MAYUKA SAYS
SHE'S TENCHI'S DAUGHTER,
SO THAT MEANS HER MOTHER
MUST BE TENCHI'S WIFE.
THAT'S ONLY LOGICAL.
- WHAT?
LOOK, MIHOSHI,
THERE'S NO PROOF OF ANY OF THIS
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST
QUIT CHATTERING?
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND JUST WHEN
DID TENCHI GET MARRIED ANYWAY?
TELL ME THAT, HUH?
- THAT'S EASY.
HE GOT MARRIED IN THE FUTURE.
- ARE YOU SAYING
THAT LITTLE BRAT
RIGHT THERE
IS FROM THE FUTURE?
- OH LOOK,
THEY REALLY FLEW!
- ( laughs )
- SHE IS NOT TENCHI'S DAUGHTER.
- ABSOLUTELY CORRECT.
- Washu: WRONG-O.
MIHOSHI'S GOT IT
RIGHT THIS TIME.
- HUH?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, GIRLS.
I TESTED
THE GENETIC STRUCTURE OF HER
HAIR. HEY, THIS LOOKS GOOD.
ANYWAY HALF OF HER DNA MATCHES
TENCHI'S JUST AS YOU'D EXPECT
FROM HER FATHER.
- ( gasps )
- SEE, I JUST KNEW IT.
- THAT IS IMPOSSIBLE.
- MAYBE, BUT THERE WAS A RIP
IN THE TIME-SPACE GRID.
IT HAPPENED RIGHT BEFORE
SHE SHOWED UP OUT OF NOWHERE.
QUITE A COINCIDENCE, HUH?
- THEN YOU MEAN SHE REALLY
DID COME FROM THE FUTURE?
- WELL, THERE'S NO PROOF YET.
I STILL HAVEN'T
QUITE FIGURED OUT
THE MOTHER'S SIDE OF HER DNA.
MAYBE IT'S ONE
OF YOU LUCKY GIRLS.
- LORD TENCHI'S WIFE--
ONE OF US GIRLS?
IT MIGHT BE ME. I CAN JUST
IMAGINE BEING HIS BRIDE.
- OH YEAH, FAT CHANCE, AYEKA.
- COULD BE ME, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I'M ALL GROWN UP.
- WOW, IT COULD BE ME TOO.
- HUH?
- COME ON, GIRLS, YOU'RE ALL
TOO YOUNG TO THINK ABOUT THAT.
- ( laughs )
- VERY FUNNY.
NOW WHICH ONE OF US
LOOKS LIKE MAYUKA?
WELL, WHAT DO
YOU THINK, MAYUKA?
HMM?
- All: WHAT?
- I KNOW WHERE SHE WENT!
- ( thinking )
A DAUGHTER FROM THE FUTURE.
TALK ABOUT CONFUSING.
I SURE DON'T FEEL LIKE A FATHER.
MAYBE THIS IS JUST
WASHU'S IDEA OF A JOKE.
ANYWAY I'M GLAD I COULD COME
HERE AND GET AWAY FROM ALL THAT.
- GUESS WHO.
- ( yelps )
( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YOU SHOULDN'T LEAVE ME
BEHIND LIKE THAT, DADDY.
IT'S SO MEAN.
I WANT TO BE HERE.
- I'M TAKING A BATH
HERE, MAYUKA.
- GOOD, I'LL TAKE ONE WITH YOU.
YOU'RE TURNING RED, DADDY.
- MAYUKA, GET OFF OF ME!
- OH.
- LISTEN TO ME.
STAY RIGHT THERE. I'M GOING TO
GET OUT AND PUT ON A TOWEL.
- DON'T GET OUT YET, DADDY!
- YEOW!
- I'LL SCRUB YOUR BACK, OKAY?
JUST LIKE I USED TO DO BEFORE.
- TENCHI!
( growls )
- ( yelps )
- RYOKO, NOW CALM DOWN.
IT'S NOW HOW IT SEEMS.
I CAN EXPLAIN.
RYOKO?
- ( roaring )
- LISTEN TO ME PLEASE!
- I'M GOING TO GET THAT
BRAZEN LITTLE HUSSY.
SHE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT SHE'S DOING!
- ( yelps )
HUH?
- THERE'S A GOOD GIRL.
NEXT TIME YOU CAN TAKE
A BATH WITH YOUR GRANDPA.
- ARE YOU TENCHI'S DADDY?
- WELL, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- OKAY, THAT'LL BE FUN!
- ( laughing )
- IS IT JUST ME
OR IS SHE WEIRD?
- ( screams )
YOU BIG FOOL!
SPOILING THINGS JUST
WHEN IT'S GETTING GOOD.
( grunts )
( screams )
- HMM, NOT A BAD HAUL.
AHH, DELICIOUS.
- HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN
MY FRIENDS AROUND HERE?
- THERE WERE THREE OF THEM.
- I TOLD THEM
I'D MEET THEM HERE,
BUT I COULDN'T SNEAK
OUT OF THE PALACE IN TIME.
HEY, I HAVE AN IDEA.
THE STARTICA FESTIVAL
IS TOMORROW.
EAT THIS AND YOUR WISH
WILL COME TRUE.
YOU'LL MEET SOMEONE YOU LOVE.
HERE.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
FROM THE PALACE.
TRY IT.
- HUH? OH.
- IT'S TENCHI'S DNA,
BUT THE CODE
ON THE MOTHER'S SIDE HAS
BEEN BLURRED ON PURPOSE
SO IT'S UNREADABLE.
SOMEONE'S TRYING
TO HIDE SOMETHING.
HMMM, WHO COULD HER MOTHER BE?
- Mayuka: NO, DON'T!
- YOU'LL CATCH COLD, MAYUKA.
YOUR HAIR'S DRIPPING WET.
- OH OUCH!
- THAT DOESN'T HURT.
- OKAY, LET ME COMB
YOUR HAIR NOW, MAYUKA.
- I WAS QUITE IMPRESSED.
YOU WERE VERY BRAVE, YOU KNOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE WAY YOU CHALLENGED RYOKO.
SHE'S A TOUGH COOKIE.
- OH.
- OKAY, LIFT UP YOUR ARMS!
- ALL RIGHT.
- HOLD STILL NOW.
- WHEW!
- ROWR.
- OHHH.
MAYUKA, YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
WOW.
- ( giggling )
I LIKE BEING PRETTY.
I KNOW!
I'LL GO SHOW DADDY.
- TENCHI'S ROOM IS
RIGHT UP THOSE STAIRS.
- THANKS!
- Mihoshi: OH.
WOW, IT'S SILVER
AND IT'S SHINY.
- Washu: WHAT'S THAT, MIHOSHI?
- OH, LOOK, WASHU.
IT'S SO PRETTY AND SILVERY.
- WHERE DID THIS HAIR COME FROM?
- I FOUND IT AFTER
I BRUSHED HER HAIR.
- ( gasps )
SO IT'S MAYUKA'S.
- ( sighs ) I NEVER DREAMT
I'D BE A FATHER AT MY AGE.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
I CAN'T BE A FATHER, NO WAY.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT, HUH?
- KEEP OUT, MAYUKA.
YOU MAY NOT ENTER TENCHI'S ROOM.
HE'S NOT FEELING VERY WELL.
- OH, I'M REALLY SORRY.
- OH, THERE YOU ARE, MAYUKA.
HOW'S TENCHI DOING?
- I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS
HE'S NOT FEELING WELL RIGHT NOW.
- OH, I'M SORRY. HEY, YOU WANT
TO PLAY A GAME WITH ME?
- HUH?
- OKAY?
- MM-HMM.
- ( crackling )
- THAT'S IT! NOW I'VE GOT
ALL THE DATA I NEED.
I JUST HAVE TO PUT IT
TOGETHER.
- FIRST FOLD IT OVER
THEN PRESS.
- FIRST OVER THEN PRESS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I DON'T THINK THAT I GET IT.
CAN YOU SHOW ME
ONE MORE TIME, SASAMI?
- OH, MIHOSHI,
YOU DID IT BACKWARDS.
- HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
- Nobuyuki: I TALKED IT OVER
WITH MY FATHER.
WE BOTH DECIDED TO LET
THE GIRL STAY HERE FOR A WHILE,
AT LEAST UNTIL WE FIND OUT
WHO HER PARENTS ARE.
SAY, WHY ARE YOU
SO HAPPY ABOUT THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST LIKE HAVING HER HERE.
EVEN THOUGH SHE
IS A BIT STRANGE.
- OH, THAT'S TRUE.
- THERE, A PRETTY CRANE.
- HEY, I GOT ONE TOO.
ISN'T IT CUTE?
WOW.
- I'M FINISHED, LOOK!
- WELL, YOU MADE SOME MEN,
NOT A CRANE, BUT IT'S GOOD.
- ( laughs )
- I'M GONNA MAKE MORE OF
THESE BIRDIES, LOTS MORE!
- GOOD, YOU CAN GIVE ONE OF THEM
TO TENCHI WHEN HE WAKES UP.
IT'LL MAKE A GREAT PRESENT.
- A PRESENT?
AH, I ALMOST FORGOT!
I'VE GOT THIS PRESENT
TO GIVE TO MY DADDY.
- WHAT IS IT?
- PRESENT?
- ( whirring )
- Mihoshi:
WOW, IT'S SO PRETTY.
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S A CHRISTMAS TREE, ISN'T IT?
- CHRISTMAS? WHAT'S THAT?
- HUH?
- THIS IS FOR STARTICA, THE
SUMMER STAR FESTIVAL IN JURAI.
IT'S SO MUCH FUN.
- Sasami: I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
WELL, IT'S KINDA LIKE
CHRISTMAS, ISN'T IT?
- Mihoshi: WHAT'S STARTICA?
- IT'S SUMMER SOLSTICE
WHERE WE COME FROM ON JURAI.
THERE'S A TREE LIKE ON CHRISTMAS
BUT WE CELEBRATE MORE LIKE THE
JAPANESE SUMMER STAR FESTIVAL.
- MMM.
- IF A GIRL SPENDS STARTICA
WITH A SPECIAL BOY
THE MYTHS AND LEGENDS
SAY WHEN THEY GROW UP
THEY'LL BE DESTINED
TO FALL IN LOVE AND GET MARRIED.
GEE, IT MUST BE THE STARTICA
SEASON RIGHT NOW IN JURAI.
- THAT'S NICE.
SEEMS SO ROMANTIC AND ALL.
- MAYUKA FELL ASLEEP.
I WONDER WHO HER MOTHER IS.
MAYUKA?
- HMMM.
- ( soft snoring )
- YEAH, GREAT GUARDS.
UH-HUH.
HMMM.
- HEY, WAKE UP, MAYUKA.
MAYUKA!
- I SHOULD WEED THE FIELD
BEFORE IT GETS DARK.
I'M WAY BEHIND.
HMM, OH?
OH! YOU CHANGED
YOUR CLOTHES, MAYUKA.
- ( giggles )
- WHAT IS IT?
- I HAVE A GOOD IDEA.
COME WITH ME.
- WAIT, WHERE ARE
WE GOING, MAYUKA?
- TENCHI?
WHERE'D HE GO?
- MAYUKA, WHERE ARE
YOU TAKING ME?
WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
( pants )
- TENCHI?
( gasps )
TENCHI!
- WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHY DID YOU BRING ME HERE?
- I LOVE YOU.
- WAH! I--
MAYUKA.
- ( gasps )
- Tenchi: NO.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S THIS?
- AHH, THAT'S THE SECOND TIME
IT'S HAPPENED TODAY!
- TENCHI, PLEASE.
LET'S BE TOGETHER NOW.
- TENCHI!
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- MAYUKA?
- UH-HUH?
UH, HUH?
WHAT?
- UH-HHHH!
WHAT HAPPENED TO US?
IT WAS LIKE SOME KIND
OF HYPNOTIC TRANCE.
- I'M NOT SURE WHAT IT WAS
AND I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
OH!
- RYOKO?
- I'M GOING TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS, TENCHI.
I'M TAKING HER WITH ME NOW!
- NO! LET ME GO!
- RYOKO!
- DADDY!
- THIS IS SO CONFUSING.
- PLEASE PUT ME DOWN.
- THEN TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO?
WHERE WERE YOU TAKING TENCHI?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WE WERE GOING FOR A WALK.
- NOW YOU'RE GOING
FOR A DROP INSTEAD.
- YOU WOULDN'T DARE!
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
- DON'T WORRY, MAYUKA. I'LL SAY
GOODBYE TO YOUR DADDY FOR YOU.
- HEY, MAYUKA,
WHERE ARE YOU?
- IT'S DINNERTIME, MAYUKA.
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI, STOP BEGGING.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
STAND BACK WHEN I'M DEEP FRYING.
- ( meows )
- HUH?
OH, RYOKO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS MAYUKA.
SHE'S MISSING.
- I WOULDN'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
- I SEE.
- Mihoshi: WE'RE BACK.
- I TAKE IT YOU DIDN'T
FIND HER THEN.
- DID YOU SEE ANYTHING AT ALL?
- SORRY, WE DIDN'T, TENCHI.
- IT'S TOO DARK NOW
TO LOOK ANYMORE.
- IT WAS VERY GOOD OF YOU GIRLS
TO SEARCH FOR HER.
GRANDFATHER'S LOOKING AS WELL.
WE'LL HOPE FOR THE BEST.
NOW WHO WANTS TO EAT?
- ( moans, gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
I FELL FROM THE SKY,
BUT I--
I'M NOT HURT.
( screams )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW DID I GET WAY UP HERE?
I'M GONNA FALL.
SOMEONE HELP ME!
- AHH, I LOST IT!
AND I WAS SO CLOSE.
SOMEONE MESSED
WITH THESE GENES.
HIDDEN DNA!
AND THEY DID A GOOD JOB OF IT.
THEY DON'T WANT ANYONE TO KNOW
WHO MAYUKA'S MOTHER IS.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- All: BON APPETIT.
- GEE, I DON'T SEE
ANY GIANT PRAWNS.
AND THERE'S NO
FISH TEMPURA EITHER.
- IT'S THE SPIRITS'
HOMECOMING DAY, REMEMBER?
WE'RE EATING SHOJIN.
- Mihoshi: WHAT
DOES SHOJIN MEAN?
- NO MEAT, NO FISH, EVERYTHING
IS STRICTLY VEGETARIAN.
- I SURE HOPE THAT MAYUKA
IS ALL RIGHT.
YOU SURE SHE WAS OKAY
WHEN YOU LEFT HER, RYOKO?
- YES. HOW MANY TIMES ARE YOU
GOING TO ASK ME THIS, TENCHI?
- GRANDFATHER'S OUT
SEARCHING FOR HER.
IF ANYONE CAN
FIND HER, HE WILL.
- HMM, MAYBE.
I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR
HER MYSELF.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU'RE WASTING TIME.
SHE'LL COME BACK HERE WHEN SHE
FEELS LIKE IT.
- HA. HOW DO YOU KNOW?
- YOU SAID SHE WAS JUST
BOTHERING YOU ANYWAY,
SO WHY ARE YOU ALL
WORRIED ABOUT HER NOW?
- BECAUSE SHE COULD
BE IN TROUBLE, RYOKO.
WHAT IF SHE'S GOTTEN LOST? DON'T
YOU FEEL A LITTLE SORRY FOR HER?
- SORRY? LOOK, SHE MAY
HAVE YOU FOOLED, TENCHI,
BUT SHE IS UP TO SOMETHING
AND I'M NOT FALLING FOR IT.
- I DON'T KNOW, RYOKO,
SHE'S STRANGE,
THERE'S SOMETHING
SWEET ABOUT HER TOO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
- Katsuhito:
TENCHI, ARE YOU THERE?
GUESS WHERE I FOUND HER.
ON TOP OF A CEDAR TREE.
SHE WAS CRYING HER EYES OUT.
IT'S OKAY, DEAR.
YOU'RE AMONG FRIENDS NOW.
- I'M GLAD YOU'RE BACK, MAYUKA.
- WELCOME HOME, MAYUKA.
- WE HAVE BEEN SO
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- ( growls )
- Tenchi: HEY WAIT,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- Sasami: HEY!
- Mihoshi: WHAT'S WRONG?
- I HATE YOUR GUTS!
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM, RYOKO?
TRYING TO GET RID OF ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT, KID.
YOU ARE IN MY WAY.
GET IT?
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NO, RYOKO!
- JUST GET LOST!
- STOP IT, RYOKO!
I SAID STOP IT!
- TENCHI, THAT GIRL
CAME HERE TO DESTROY YOU.
I'M TRYING TO PROTECT YOU
SINCE YOU'RE SO CLUELESS
WHEN IT COMES TO WOMEN.
TENCHI!
- STOP IT!
- THERE, NOW WE'RE GETTING SOME
ACTION. THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- TENCHI.
- UH.
- ( sobs )
- I'M SORRY.
LISTEN, I DON'T KNOW
THE TRUTH ABOUT MAYUKA YET.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT BROUGHT
HER HERE TO OUR HOUSE
OR WHERE SHE'S FROM,
I'M IN THE DARK LIKE YOU,
BUT I'M WILLING TO ACCEPT HER.
DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW WHY, RYOKO?
BECAUSE EVERY ONE OF YOU ARRIVED
HERE JUST THE WAY SHE DID.
- ( gasps, sighs )
- IT'S TRUE, ISN'T IT? REMEMBER?
- DADDY?
- I'M SORRY, MAYUKA.
YOU CALL ME YOUR FATHER,
BUT HOW CAN I BELIEVE THAT
WHEN THERE'S NO EVIDENCE AND YOU
DON'T HAVE CLEAR MEMORIES?
- WHAT?
- IT'S JUST A FANTASY
YOU HAVE, MAYUKA.
SO FOR ME, YOU'RE JUST LIKE ANY
OF THE OTHER GIRLS IN THE HOUSE.
- UH-HUH.
- HEY THERE,
IT MEANS YOU'RE VERY IMPORTANT
JUST LIKE THEM.
- Ryoko: YEAH.
- HUH?
- RIGHT, EXCEPT FOR RYOKO
WHO'S JUST IN THE WAY.
- HEY, RYOKO!
- HMM.
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE NOT MAKING MUCH PROGRESS
WITH TENCHI, ARE YOU?
- SHUT UP!
- OUCH!
THAT HURTS.
- RATS! WHY DID HE
HAVE TO SPOIL THINGS
WHEN THEY WERE JUST GETTING
GOOD? THAT PRINCE IS A PAIN.
THAT'S OKAY, NO WORRIES.
I'VE GOT BIG PLANS
FOR MY LITTLE MAYUKA.
- SILVER AND BLACK-- I CAN'T
FIGURE OUT THE SILVER PART OF IT
EXCEPT I KNOW
IT'S NOT FROM EARTH.
WHAT KIND OF DNA
PRODUCES REAL SILVER?
OH, BETTER EAT SOMETHING
IF I'M GONNA WORK ALL NIGHT.
- ( knocks )
- WHO'S THERE?
- IT'S ME, WASHU.
- LORD KATSUHITO, COME ON IN.
- I BROUGHT YOU A SNACK.
- WOW, THANKS!
BOY, THAT LOOKS GREAT.
I WAS STARVING!
- SO YOU DISCOVERED THIS SILVER
STRAND IN MAYUKA'S HAIR, EH?
- YEAH, DO YOU KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- BY THE WAY, AT 4:45 P.M.
THIS AFTERNOON,
THE TIME-SPACE CONTINUUM WAS
DISRUPTED FOR A SECOND TIME.
IT HAPPENED NEAR THE STEPS
OF THE MASAKI SHRINE.
THAT'S WHERE TENCHI FOUND
MAYUKA. NICE COINCIDENCE, HUH?
- COINCIDENCE? NO.
THAT IS WHY I CAME
TO SPEAK TO YOU, WASHU.
- WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
I KNOW THAT GIRL'S GOING
TO HURT TENCHI.
OR AM I JUST JEALOUS OF HER?
IT'S SO HARD TO KNOW.
- RYOKO?
- HUH?
- DO YOU MIND
IF I JOIN YOU FOR A WHILE?
- OH SURE.
- I HAVE TO ADMIT I'M JEALOUS.
IT HURTS ME SO MUCH THAT I CAN'T
EVEN BEAR TO LOOK AT TENCHI.
I THOUGHT I WAS MATURE ENOUGH
TO HANDLE SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT IF EVER
TENCHI FELL IN LOVE
WITH SOMEONE ELSE,
I'D JUST GO BACK HOME.
BACK TO MY PLANET
AND MY PALACE
AND I'D NEVER SAY
A WORD ABOUT IT.
ISN'T IT STRANGE THAT I'M
TELLING YOU ALL THIS, RYOKO?
- DON'T BE FOOLISH, AYEKA.
YOU THINK TOO MUCH.
TENCHI WOULD NEVER BREAK
YOUR HEART, AYEKA.
AND SASAMI'D LAUGH
IF SHE SAW YOU NOW.
- RYOKO, HONESTLY?
- DON'T GET ALL WEEPY NOW.
I HATE THAT.
I REFUSE TO BE
A TIMID LITTLE MAIDEN.
I WANT TO HAVE FUN, AYEKA.
( laughs )
YOU KNOW, THEY ALL
LOVE YOU SO MUCH
THEY'LL SEND A SEARCH PARTY
FOR YOU PRETTY SOON.
- Sasami: AYEKA!
- SASAMI!
- SEE, DID I CALL IT OR WHAT?
- HERE.
- FATHER'S GOING TO LET US
LIGHT FIRECRACKERS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
HAVE YOU SEEN RYOKO?
- SHE WAS JUST HERE.
I GUESS SHE WENT HOME.
- COME ON, HURRY! EVERYONE'S
ASKING ABOUT YOU, AYEKA.
- YOU AND YOUR FIRECRACKERS.
- ( giggles )
- ( pops )
- ( yelps )
- OH, DID IT BURN YOUR HAND?
LET ME SEE IT.
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
WITH FIREWORKS.
YOU MUST NEVER TOUCH THEM
ONCE THEY'RE LIT, OKAY?
- SAYS WHO?!
- WHAT?
- SORRY.
- UH, YEAH.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, MAYUKA?
- YES, I'M FINE, SASAMI.
- ( laughing )
- THIS IS FOR YOU.
- WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING!
BEAUTIFUL.
- ( laughs )
WE CAN PLAY WITH IT TOGETHER.
JUST YOU AND ME IN MY ROOM.
- HUH?
- I HAVE THINGS THAT ARE
EVEN MORE FUN THAN THIS.
LOTS MORE FUN.
- REALLY?
- YEAH, COME ON, LET'S GO.
- OKAY.
- DEPART, YOU WICKED CREATURE!
- ( screaming )
BURN IT ALL NOW, MAYUKA!
- MM-HMM.
- All: OH!
- Sasami: LOOK, IT'S SO PRETTY.
- ( cackles )
- MAYUKA, STOP IT!
WATCH OUT!
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- THERE!
- MAYUKA.
- UH...
- MAYUKA!
- MAYUKA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- CAREFUL WITH HER.
- ( groans )
MY HEAD-- AH!
- I'LL GET A BED READY FOR HER,
TENCHI. SHE NEEDS TO LIE DOWN.
YOU BRING HER IN.
- RIGHT.
WHY DON'T WE GO
INSIDE NOW, MAYUKA?
- YOU AREN'T HURT OR ANYTHING,
ARE YOU, MAYUKA?
- HMM-MM.
- HMMM.
SO YOU'RE THINKING
THE SAME THING I AM.
- RIGHT. RYOKO FELT
A DARK PRESENCE AS I DID.
SHE'S JEALOUS, BUT THAT'S
NOT THE WHOLE STORY.
THIS GIRL HAS HER SIGHTS SET.
- AND THE TARGET?
- TENCHI, I WOULD THINK.
- SO THIS GIRL IS...
- A POTENTIAL KILLER.
- SHE'S AN ASSASSIN!
- I LOVE TO RATTLE YOUR CAGE.
( laughing )
- NOT FUNNY!
NOW HOW ARE WE GONNA STOP IT?
- AH-- YOU'RE
SO SERIOUS, WASHU.
WE ARE JUST GOING TO GO ON
AS IF NOTHING HAS HAPPENED.
- HUH?
- WHOEVER PRODUCED THAT SILVER
HAIR WILL SHOW UP IN TIME.
IT'S A WAITING GAME
TILL THEN.
MMM.
( laughs )
- Mayuka: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
CAME OVER ME. I'M SORRY.
- Ayeka: IT'S OKAY.
ARE YOU FEELING BETTER NOW?
- WELL, I-- I--
I'M AFRAID OF MYSELF.
- Sasami: HUH?
- ( sighs )
- MAYUKA, IT'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
- MISS AYEKA?
- YES?
- THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME OUT.
- OH.
SURE.
- HEY, SASAMI, YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT SOMETHING
CALLED CHRISTMAS.
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
- OH YEAH, I FORGOT.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT CHRISTMAS IS, DO YOU?
- HUH-UH. IS IT
A LOT LIKE STARTICA?
- UH, WELL, STARTICA
IS IN SUMMER
AND CHRISTMAS IS IN WINTER.
HEY, I KNOW!
I COULD SHOW YOU!
THESE ARE THE CHRISTMAS PICTURES
FROM LAST YEAR.
- AH! THAT REALLY
LOOKS LIKE LOTS OF FUN.
- IT IS.
- GEE, WHAT'S THIS PICTURE?
- THAT'S THE CAKE I BAKED
WITH MY SISTER AYEKA.
IT WAS REALLY DELICIOUS.
Kiyone:
OH NO, LOOK AT THIS PICTURE.
- Sasami: FATHER'S EYES
ARE SHINY-- DANGEROUS.
- WHO'S THAT?
- RYOKO.
WHEN SHE DRINKS A LOT
SHE LOOKS LIKE THIS.
AND THIS.
- SHE'S HOPELESS.
- ( Mayuka laughs )
THEY LOOK FUNNY.
- Mihoshi: LOOK, TENCHI'S
JACKET HAS STAINS ON IT.
- Kiyone: I THINK YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SPILLED JUICE
ON IT, MIHOSHI.
- DID I DO THAT?
( giggles )
- Mayuka: HEY, THAT LOOKS LIKE
THE TREES AT STARTICA.
- Sasami: IT'S A CHRISTMAS TREE.
THEY KINDA LOOK THE
SAME, DON'T THEY?
- Mayuka: IT'S SO PRETTY.
( giggles )
IT'S NICE. EVERYONE'S SO HAPPY.
WISH I WAS A PART OF IT TOO.
- YOU DO?
- YOU CAN IF YOU WISH TO.
YOU CAN JOIN OUR FAMILY
AND BE ONE OF US.
AND WE ALWAYS CELEBRATE
CHRISTMAS TOGETHER.
- YAH!
- YIPPEE!
- THAT'S GREAT.
- YEAH, I'M ALL FOR IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- IT'S NOT UNTIL
WINTER, YOU KNOW,
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO BE
A VERY GOOD GIRL UNTIL THEN.
- OKAY!
- REMEMBER, IF YOU'RE THE
DAUGHTER OF LORD TENCHI
THEN YOU MUST ACT LIKE IT--
LIKE A PRINCESS.
- I'M SO HAPPY, I WISH I COULD
JUST STAY HERE FOREVER.
- UM, RYOKO, UH...
I SEE, SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
- DON'T COME NEAR ME.
- I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR WHAT I DID.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE FOR IT.
I WAS WRONG.
I CAN'T ABANDON HER, RYOKO.
ISN'T THAT STRANGE?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHO SHE IS
OR WHERE SHE'S FROM,
BUT I KEEP FEELING
LIKE SHE'S TRAPPED--
LIKE SHE'S CAUGHT UP
IN SOMETHING
AND SHE HERSELF DOESN'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT IT IS.
SHE'S LIKE ME IN A WAY.
I LOST MY MOTHER WHEN I
WAS A LITTLE BOY.
AND MY PAST IS FULL OF MYSTERIES
JUST LIKE HERS IS.
- TENCHI, YOU'RE IN DANGER!
- YOU DON'T NEED TO
WORRY ABOUT ME.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW I HAVE ACCESS
TO THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD
TO PROTECT ME.
COME TO THINK OF IT, RYOKO,
WHAT WAS THAT SWORD SHE USED
WHEN SHE WAS FIGHTING WITH YOU?
- IT WASN'T THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD,
I CAN SURE TELL YOU THAT!
OH YEAH, I SUPPOSE
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT IF SHE REALLY DID
TURN OUT TO BE MY DAUGHTER?
- I SAID YOU'RE IN DANGER
AND YOU'RE LAUGHING?!
- SORRY.
- I'M FRIGHTENED FOR YOU.
IF YOU EVER...
- IF I EVER WHAT?
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
I NEVER KNEW YOU WERE
SUCH A WORRIER, HUH?
EVERYTHING'S GOING
TO BE FINE, RYOKO, YOU'LL SEE.
IT'S KINDA
CHILLY UP HERE, ISN'T IT?
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK IN
AND GET SOME SLEEP, HMM?
- HUH-UH.
- PLEASE.
- ( sighs )
- ( whimpering )
- WHO TOLD YOU TO MAKE
FRIENDS WITH THEM?
THIS ISN'T A PARTY.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DO WHAT
I TELL YOU, PERIOD.
NOW YOU GET UP AND YOU
BRING THAT PRINCE TO ME!
AND BE QUICK ABOUT IT, MAYUKA,
OR I'LL DESTROY YOU!
- ( moans )
DADDY!
DADDY? I'M REALLY SCARED, DADDY.
- ( soft snores )
- ALL RIGHT, HE'S IN A TRANCE,
NOW DO IT.
- I WILL OBEY YOU.
- ( groaning )
- ( cackles )
I'VE GOT YOU NOW.
- TENCHI!
- ( gasps ) YOSHO!
- YUZUHA!
- WELL, LONG TIME NO SEE.
I'M TAKING YOUR PRINCE WITH ME.
- I CAN'T PERMIT THAT.
YAH YAH!
I MISSED!
- TENCHI!
- ( gasps )
WHAT? DADDY!
- Ryoko: WHO WAS THAT CREATURE?
- WHAT?
- I'LL ASK YOU ONE MORE TIME.
JUST WHO WAS IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- STOP THAT, RYOKO.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ( moaning )
- WHAT?
( yelps )
MAYUKA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( sobbing )
I DON'T KNOW, DADDY.
SHE GRABBED ME.
- RYOKO! AHH!
- Katsuhito: TENCHI!
YOU MUSTN'T BLAME
RYOKO FOR THIS.
- WHAT WERE YOU PLANNING
TO DO WITH OUR TENCHI?
WHERE WERE YOU TAKING HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS!
LET ME GO!
- MAYUKA!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- WAIT, TENCHI!
TENCHI, TENCHI,
YOU CAN'T LEAVE!
YOU MUSTN'T. ( sobbing )
- RYOKO?
- Ayeka: WHERE'D MAYUKA GO?
- Washu: MIHOSHI AND KIYONE
ARE OUT LOOKING FOR HER.
- THE DOMAIN
OF DARKNESS, GRANDPA?
- THAT IS CORRECT, TENCHI.
- IT'S NOT MAYUKA'S FAULT!
SHE'S UNDER A SPELL!
PLEASE, IT'S NOT FAIR!
- EVEN IF SHE IS CONTROLLED
BY SOMEONE ELSE,
SHE'S OUR ENEMY,
YOU KNOW THAT.
OUR ONLY CHOICE IS TO TAKE
HER OUT, IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
- SIMPLE YOU SAY?
IT'S NOT SIMPLE AT ALL.
SHE'S CONTROLLED FROM DEEP
WITHIN BY A DEMON NAMED YUZUHA.
MAYUKA'S FULL
OF SWEETNESS AND LIGHT,
BUT THE DEMON TWISTS IT
INTO EVIL,
LURKING IN THE DARK DOMAIN
OF AN ANCIENT NIGHTMARE.
YUZUHA HAS COMPLETE
POWER OVER HER.
- GENETICALLY SHE REALLY
IS TENCHI'S DAUGHTER,
BUT ALSO SHE IS THE CHILD
OF A MYSTERIOUS UNDERWORLD.
- UNDERWORLD? OH MY!
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
WE SHOULD DO EVERYTHING
WE CAN TO SAVE HER!
YOU'RE SO CRUEL, RYOKO!
- SASAMI!
- I PROMISED MAYUKA
THAT SHE COULD
SPEND CHRISTMAS WITH ALL OF US!
I'M GOING TO FIND HER
AND KEEP THAT PROMISE!
- STOP! WAIT, SASAMI, WAIT!
- I'LL GO FIND HER MYSELF.
- LISTEN TO ME.
- HUH?
- MAYUKA WILL COME BACK.
HER MISSION IS TO DESTROY YOU.
BE ON GUARD.
- RIGHT.
- HEY, MAYUKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- WAIT, SASAMI!
( yelps )
- HELLO, SASAMI!
AYEKA, IT'S ME!
- ( gasps )
- JUST BRING THE PRINCE TO ME
OR YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO!
- I KNOW WHAT SHE'LL DO.
SHE'LL DESTROY ME.
( moans )
I'M SCARED.
HELP ME, DADDY!
WHAT DID I DO TO YOU?
WHAT DID I DO?
( sobs )
WHY DOES IT HURT ME?
WHY DOES MY HEART ACHE SO
WHEN I THINK ABOUT YOU, DADDY?
( gasps )
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I CLONED YOU
TO CARRY OUT A MISSION,
NOT TO HAVE FEELINGS
AND EMOTIONS.
JUST FOR THAT, I'M GOING
TO ERASE YOUR MEMORY BANKS.
YAH!
- ( screams )
- MAYUKA!
YOU MUST BE YUZUHA.
YOU LEAVE MAYUKA ALONE.
HEY, WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- Ayeka: OH NO!
- AYEKA, HELP!
- ( grunting )
- ( screams )
- HANG ON, AYEKA.
- AYEKA!
- Yuzuha: PRINCE, I'M
WAITING FOR YOU.
FIND ME. ASK THE OLD MAN
FROM THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
( laughs )
- HOLD IT!
- TENCHI, HELP ME! ( screams )
- ( cackles )
- THIS FIELD IS VERY UNSTABLE.
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T
GUARANTEE YOUR WAY BACK.
- I KNOW.
- AND YOU, RYOKO?
- UNDERSTOOD.
- YOU'LL BE FIGHTING HER
ON HER OWN TURF
AND YOUR JURAI POWERS
MAY NOT WORK IN HER WORLD.
- RIGHT.
- I'M SURE BY NOW
SHE'S BROUGHT MAYUKA ALL THE WAY
INTO THE DARKNESS.
- PLEASE COME BACK TO US,
BOTH OF YOU.
- YES, BE CAREFUL.
- WE WILL, DON'T WORRY.
- PLEASE, TENCHI,
FIND SASAMI.
- WE'LL BRING HER BACK, AYEKA.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON US.
- RYOKO, IT'S TIME THAT WE WENT.
- YEAH.
- ( both grunt )
( screaming )
- Bear: OOOH!
- ( voices moaning, hooting )
- WHOA!
- ( moans )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, RYOKO?
- YEAH SURE,
I'M JUST SWELL, TENCHI.
( shouts ) WHAT KIND OF
PLACE IS THIS ANYWAY?
- A LITTLE BIZARRE. I MEAN,
THERE'S NOTHING HERE BUT TOYS.
- Bear: MERRY CHRISTMAS...
- Both: HUH?
- ...TO THE PRINCE OF JURAI
AND HIS DOUBLE PRINCESS
AND SPACE PIRATE.
WELCOME TO THE LAND
OF YUZUHA.
- HEY, THOSE TOYS ARE ALIVE!
- IT'S JUST AN ILLUSION.
HEY, WE WANT TO TALK TO YUZUHA
OR WHATEVER HER NAME IS.
- YUZUHA IS GETTING READY
FOR THE BIG CHRISTMAS PARTY.
BUT SHE ASKED US TO GIVE YOU
A SPECIAL GREETING!
- ( all laughing )
- YAH!
- TRY IT. HAH!
- DID WE SCARE YOU?
DID WE HURT YOU?
I'M SO SORRY!
- COME ON, TENCHI, WE'VE GOT
TO GET OUT OF HERE FAST!
HUH?
- ( both screaming )
- MERRY CHRISTMAS.
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- AM I CRAZY
OR WEREN'T WE JUST FALLING?
- I THINK SO.
- Mayuka: LOOK OVER HERE.
- Tenchi: SASAMI!
- Ryoko: IT'S YOU!
- DADDY, YOU CAME
TO MY CHRISTMAS PARTY.
THANK YOU.
- Tenchi: MAYUKA?
- DON'T LET HER FOOL YOU.
LOOK AT HER EYES!
HA!
- RYOKO IS THE FOOL!
- IS THAT RIGHT?
- ( grunting )
- ( yelps )
- HAD ENOUGH?
- ( gasps ) THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD!
- MAYUKA!
- WHO'S THAT?
- TAKE A GUESS. NICE TO SEE
YOU. WELCOME TO MY DOMAIN.
- Ryoko: IT'S THE DEMON!
- RIGHT. AND FORGET
YOUR LIGHT SWORD.
THAT DOESN'T WORK DOWN HERE.
I KNOW IT'S NOT THE SEASON,
BUT I HOPE YOU ENJOYED MY LITTLE
CHRISTMAS PRESENT ANYWAY.
I DID.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM US?
- OH, DON'T YOU KNOW,
MY DEAR SILLY PRINCE OF JURAI?
WHY, I JUST WANT TO PLAY
WITH YOU A BIT, THAT'S ALL.
- LISTEN, YOU LITTLE WEASEL!
WE'RE NOT YOUR PLAYTHINGS.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO US?
- I'LL NEVER TELL.
THAT'S TOO EASY.
BUT IF YOU HAPPEN TO GET LUCKY
AND MAKE IT BACK IN ONE PIECE,
ASK YOUR GRANDFATHER.
- WHAT? MY GRANDFATHER?
- ( both gasp )
- LET THE PARTY BEGIN!
- ( growls )
TENCHI!
( yelps )
- ( both yell )
( grunts )
- Tenchi: UH-OH.
- ( both groaning )
- Yuzuha: THIS IS FUN.
WE CAN PLAY AS LONG AS WE LIKE
BECAUSE THERE'S NO TIME
IN MY WORLD.
- TENCHI!
- ( screaming )
- GOTCHA!
YAHOO!
- ( roars )
- DAMN YOU!
- ARE YOU HURT?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SCRATCH.
AHHH!
- RYOKO, WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
- Ayeka: TENCHI'S POWERS WON'T
WORK IN THE NIGHTMARE WORLD?
- Katsuhito: THAT IS CORRECT.
- Ayeka: THAT MEANS THE
LIGHTHAWK SWORD IS...
- Washu: COMPLETELY USELESS,
I'M AFRAID.
- OH NO.
- Katsuhito: YUZUHA
IS THE SPIRIT
OF THE TREE OF DARKNESS. IF ONLY
WE HAD THE TREE OF LIGHT.
- TREE OF LIGHT?
- THE TREE THAT CREATED THE
JURAI ROYAL FAMILY--
"TSUNAMI."
- WAIT, WE HAVE
A ROYAL TREE RIGHT HERE.
THE TREE THAT BELONGED
TO MY BROTHER.
THAT'S THE BEST HOPE WE HAVE.
- RYOKO, HANG ON.
- ( cackles )
- PRINCE OF LIGHT,
YOU WON'T LAST LONG IN MY
WORLD OF DARKNESS.
- SHOW YOURSELF!
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR FRIEND HAS
EXHAUSTED HER POWERS.
DOESN'T IT?
- WHY DID YOU BRING US HERE?
- 'CAUSE THIS IS WHERE I CREATED
MAYUKA OUT OF YOUR BLACK HAIR
AND MY SILVER HAIR.
- SO HER LIGHTHAWK SWORD WAS...
- A FAKE, OF COURSE.
YOU FELL FOR IT NICELY.
YEAH, MAYBE I'LL JUST MELT
YOU AND RYOKO TOGETHER
LIKE I MELTED THOSE HAIRS.
RYOKO'D ENJOY THAT SINCE SHE'S
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
( cackles )
- Ryoko: AH, GO ON, DO IT!
IF IT'LL FEED YOUR PITIFUL
LITTLE EGO, GO RIGHT AHEAD.
I'D LOVE TO BE
JOINED WITH TENCHI.
- HEY, MAYUKA!
SHALL WE DESTROY
RYOKO OR SASAMI FIRST?
- NO, STOP!
LEAVE HER ALONE.
- I COULD USE MY
DISINTEGRATION TECHNIQUE,
BUT I PREFER THE PURPLE CLAW!
- LET'S MAKE A DEAL.
I'LL STAY HERE
IF YOU'LL JUST SEND RYOKO
AND SASAMI BACK TO OUR WORLD.
- I WON'T GO.
- LISTEN PLEASE,
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
- ( moaning )
- EASY, MAYUKA,
WHAT'S YOUR RUSH?
IT'S NO FUN
IF YOU KILL HIM TOO SOON.
I WANT SOME ENTERTAINMENT HERE.
- ( Tenchi screaming )
- ( gasps )
STOP IT!
- MY MY, THE LITTLE PRINCESS
FINALLY WOKE UP.
HAVE A NICE NAP?
- IS THAT MAYUKA?
- THAT'S MAYUKA. SHE'S LOST
HER HUMAN SIDE, SASAMI.
- OH, NO, WAIT!
- ( growling )
- HAVING FUN WITH YOUR DADDY?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MISS
MAYUKA? WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS!
TENCHI'S YOUR DADDY.
WE'RE YOUR FAMILY, REMEMBER?
YOU MUSTN'T HURT YOUR FAMILY,
MAYUKA. WE ALL LOVE YOU!
- DADDY?
DADDY!
- CAN'T BE!
- ( sobbing ) DADDY.
- MAYUKA?
- SORRY.
- YOU BROKE THROUGH TO HER.
MAYUKA'S COME OUT
OF THE DARKNESS INTO THE LIGHT.
- MAYUKA!
- TENCHI!
- YOU FOOL.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'LL GET
FOR YOUR FOND MEMORIES.
- ( screams )
- YOU MAY HAVE A HUMAN HEART,
BUT I CREATED YOU
AND YOU'LL FOLLOW MY COMMANDS!
ARE YOU GETTING A CHARGE
OUT OF THIS, DEARIE?
- OH, MAYUKA.
- YUZUHA'S REGAINING
CONTROL AGAIN.
- Yuzuha: THAT'S BETTER,
NOW USE THOSE CLAWS!
( gasps )
YOU DARE TO ATTACK
YOUR CREATOR?
- YUZUHA'S YUZUHA
AND MAYUKA'S MAYUKA.
I DON'T WANT STARTICA ANYMORE.
I WANT CHRISTMAS.
MY DADDY AND SASAMI
AND EVERYBODY WILL BE THERE.
I'LL BE A GOOD GIRL
AND WAIT FOR WINTER TO COME
SO I CAN HAVE CHRISTMAS
WITH MY FAMILY.
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE HERE
IN THE DARKNESS ANYMORE.
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN YOU WON'T LIVE ANYWHERE!
YOUR CODES ARE CANCELED!
- ( screaming )
- MAYUKA!
- Sasami: NO!
- DADDY?
I'M SORRY I DID THINGS
THAT I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU COULDN'T HELP IT.
- I WAS BAD.
I MADE RYOKO ANGRY.
BUT I LOVE RYOKO.
I HOPE THAT SHE
FORGIVES ME, DADDY.
- OF COURSE I DO.
HANG IN THERE.
- MAYUKA, DON'T GO AWAY!
- SASAMI, IT'S YOU.
WE'LL CELEBRATE
CHRISTMAS TOGETHER, YOU AND ME
AND DADDY
AND ALL THE ONES THAT I LOVE.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HER?
MAYUKA, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GO AWAY!
NO, MAYUKA, PLEASE!
NO, LET ME GO!
SHE'S MY FRIEND-- MAYUKA!
( sobbing )
- ( chimes )
- DID YOU ENJOY PLAYING
WITH THAT GIRL'S LIFE? DID YOU?
SHE WAS JUST A CLONE,
AN EXPERIMENT I DID
WHEN I WAS BORED.
- Tenchi: SHE WAS FULL
OF SPIRIT AND HOPE.
- SHE WAS JUST A BUNCH
OF ENCODED DNA, THAT'S ALL.
- HALF OF IT WAS
YOUR DNA, YUZUHA.
MAYUKA WAS AS MUCH YOU
AS SHE WAS ME.
- ( grunts )
- YOU KILLED PART OF
YOURSELF, YUZUHA,
AND IT WAS THE BEST PART.
- THE BEST PART OF
ME'S ALREADY DEAD.
JURAIANS!
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY DID TO ME!
( screaming )
( moans )
NO, YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
( screams )
- TENCHI!
- RYOKO, BE CAREFUL.
- WE CAN'T AFFORD TO
BE CAREFUL NOW!
- ( grunts ) I'M LOSING MY
POWER. IT'S THIS PLACE.
- WATCH IT.
- WHOA!
- ( cackling )
LOOK AT ME.
COULD ANYONE POSSIBLY
LOVE ME WHEN I LOOK THIS WAY?
I SHOULD HAVE KILLED
YOUR GRANDFATHER BACK THEN
WHEN THEY TREATED ME LIKE
SOME INFERIOR BEAST.
- MY GRANDFATHER--
- ( groans )
- Ayeka: LORD TENCHI!
BEHOLD! THIS BRANCH IS
FROM THE TREE OF LIGHT
AND LIGHT WILL
ALWAYS PREVAIL!
- ( moans )
HUH?
IT'S THE LIGHTHAWK SWORD!
- YOUR PUNY LITTLE SWORD
MAKES ME LAUGH.
YOUR GAME'S OVER!
( cackles )
- ( roaring )
- HERE. MAY WE
MEET AGAIN SOMEDAY.
( laughs )
- YOU AND GRANDFATHER.
- IMAGINE, THE DARKNESS
IN LOVE WITH THE LIGHT.
( rumbling, screaming )
- ( birds chirping )
- Ryoko: TENCHI?
- Sasami: HE'S WAKING UP.
- Ayeka: LORD TENCHI!
- WHOA.
IS EVERYONE OKAY?
- TENCHI, YOU'RE BACK!
( laughing )
- TENCHI,
YOU MADE IT BACK SAFELY.
- YES, BUT MAYUKA-- WELL--
- I SEE.
I'M SORRY FOR HER.
- ALSO THIS IS FOR YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- IT WAS YUZUHA'S.
YOU KNEW HER, RIGHT?
I THINK SHE WAS IN--
WELL...
- HMM.
HUH.
WE WERE VERY YOUNG
AND IT WAS LONG AGO.
- Tenchi: SHE'S REALLY GONE.
- YEAH, SHE WAS SO EXCITED ABOUT
SPENDING CHRISTMAS WITH US.
IT WAS CUTE.
- ( sobs )
- RYOKO CRYING?
BOY, THAT'S A NEW ONE ON ME.
- DON'T BE ABSURD.
WHY WOULD I BE CRYING?
- UH, BE POLITE.
HOW ABOUT SOME RESPECT
FOR THE GREATEST SCIENTIFIC
GENIUS IN THE UNIVERSE?
I BET YOU'RE CARRYING IT
WITH YOU, AREN'T YOU, TENCHI?
- HUH? WELL, YEAH.
- HAND IT OVER.
- HERE.
- LISTEN, EVERYONE,
SINCE THIS IS A MATTER
OF GREAT IMPORTANCE,
I'M ONLY GOING TO ASK ONE
TIME. IT'S UP TO YOU GUYS.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU DECIDE.
JUST SAY THE WORD.
- HUH?
- HERE'S THE DEAL:
IF EVEN ONE OF YOU DOES NOT WANT
THIS DONE, I WILL NOT DO IT.
- HMM.
- ( screaming )
- I WANT TO SEE HER AGAIN.
YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD, WASHU.
- OH.
- AH.
- HMM.
- ( laughs ) RYOKO!
- YEAH, I'M GONNA BE
HER PERSONAL TRAINER
AND YOU CAN BET
I'LL BE TOUGH AS HELL.
- ( whimpers )
- I GUESS RYOKO WILL BE RYOKO.
- THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I'M AFRAID OF.
- SO WHAT DO YOU SAY IN THERE?
ARE YOU READY TO GET STARTED?
- ( pop music playing )
( singing in Japanese )