- ( machine whirs )
- ( buzzer blares )
- HUH?
RED ALERT!
- ( people scream )
- ( gasping )
- Officer: HUH? WHAT THE
HELL'S GOING ON HERE?!
- THERE'S AN ANOMALY
IN THE SUBSPACE ROOM.
CONVENTIONAL
SPACE AND TIME
ARE BOTH BEING DRAWN
INTO THE CORE BLOCK.
- COMMANDER,
THINK YOU COULD--
- IT'S KAIN!
HE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO SOMETHING
SO IMPOSSIBLE!
- Woman:
DIMENSIONAL SHIELD BREACHED!
CLIMAX IS OUT OF ALIGNMENT.
SPACE-TIME'S BEGUN
MOVING INTO THE PAST.
- HE MUSTN'T GET AWAY!
- SIR, THE SUBSPACE ANOMALY
IS OUT OF CONTROL.
IF IT KEEPS GOING
AT THIS RATE,
IT'S GONNA TEAR
HEADQUARTERS
COMPLETELY TO PIECES.
- COMMANDER!
- WHAT?
- ( screams )
- ( alarm buzzes )
- ( gags )
OH, WHY DOES HEADQUARTERS
ALWAYS CALL WHEN I'M EATING?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FORGOT TO FILE A REPORT AGAIN?
- ( Man through P.A. ):
ATTENTION ALL UNITS,
INSTITUTE EMERGENCY
PROCEDURES AT ONCE.
A-1 CLASS CRIMINAL KAIN.
- HUH?
- Mihoshi: OH, KIYONE.
- HEADQUARTERS, CAN
YOU COME IN, PLEASE?
THIS IS DETECTIVE FIRST-CLASS
KIYONE IN THE SAUL SYSTEM.
PLEASE REPEAT YOUR
LAST MESSAGE, OVER.
HEADQUARTERS, COME IN!
WHAT'S HAPPENED?!
PLEASE REPEAT
YOUR LAST TRANSMISSION.
- ( screams )
- OH NO, MIHOSHI,
WHAT WAS THAT?
- Man #1: LOOK AT THAT,
THE AURORA BOREALIS.
- Man #2:
YEAH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- ( overlapping chatter )
- UH, WHAT?
( grunts )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH...
( screams )
THIS WAS THE FIRST
INDICATION I HAD
THAT I WAS GOING TO VANISH.
- Girl #1: HEY, WAIT UP.
- Boy #1: ( laughs )
- Boy #2: YOU GUYS GOT
PRACTICE LATER.
- Girl #2: YOU GUYS,
I'LL SEE YOU OVER THERE.
- Boy #3: CATCH YOU
AFTER SCHOOL, MAN.
- ( no audio )
- ( film projector clicking )
- EIGHT MILLIMETER FILM?
- YUP.
PEOPLE USED IT TO
MAKE HOME MOVIES.
- HMM.
- YEAH, MY FATHER
ALWAYS LOVED IT
WHEN HE COULD FOOL AROUND
WITH THE LATEST GADGETS.
IN FACT, THIS IS A FILM
THAT HE SHOT
QUITE SOME TIME AGO.
- Girls: OH.
- WELL, IT WAS
A PRETTY SNEAKY WAY
TO PICK UP MY MOM,
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT.
- HUH?  YOU MEAN THE GIRL
THAT WE'VE BEEN WATCHING
IS YOUR MOTHER?
- YEP.
- Girls: OH!
- SHE'S NOTHING BUT A CHILD.
- OF COURSE SHE IS.
WHEN THEY SHOT THIS FILM,
SHE WAS STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL!
- EXCUSE ME.
- SHE'S GREAT.
- OF COURSE, YOU'VE GOT
TO REMEMBER, SASAMI,
THAT TENCHI'S MOTHER
IS DESCENDED
FROM THE EMPEROR JURAI.
- HEY, THAT'S WEIRD.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU HAVE JURAI BLOOD TOO,
DIDN'T YOU?
- UH-HUH.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
- WHAT THE-- HEY!
CAN'T YOU TAKE A JOKE?
GIVE ME SOME COOKIES.
- Ayeka: THEY'RE TOO GOOD
TO WASTE ON YOU.
- Ryoko: COOKIE HOG. THEY'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE FOR ALL OF US.
- SHE LOOKS VERY GENTLE.
- SHE WAS.
- HEY!
HUH?!  AAH!
AH!  WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
( groaning )
OH!
- HE JUST WENT FLYING.
- LORD TENCHI!
- YOU BADLY HURT?
- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP THERE?
- Washu: WELL, WELL, WELL.
I CAN SEE ONCE AGAIN
I MADE IT JUST IN TIME.
THE PROBLEM'S IN THE PAST.
- ( all gasp )
- AND HERE'S THE PROOF.
CHECK THIS OUT.
- ( gasping )
- SHE'S GONE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
TENCHI'S MOTHER'S
DISAPPEARED.
- HUH?
- YES, AND HERE! AND HERE!
AND HERE!  AND HERE!
- WASHU, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasping )
- Washu:
IT IS AS I FEARED.
26 YEARS AGO,
SOMETHING TERRIBLE HAPPENED
TO LORD TENCHI'S MOTHER,
SOMETHING AWFUL.
THE MASAKI FAMILY DIED OUT.
- WHAT?!
- THAT MEANS IN THIS WORLD,
LORD TENCHI HAS
NEVER BEEN BORN.
- BUT WAIT, HOW COME
WE'RE ALL STILL HERE?
- THERE IS ONLY ONE THING
IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE
THAT STANDS BETWEEN YOU
AND OBLIVION.
THE MOST BRILLIANT MIND
IN THE GALAXY!
YOU'RE LOOKING AT HER!
I WAS WORKING IN MY
SUBSPACE LABORATORY
WHEN I SUDDENLY MONITORED
A TEMPORAL MISALIGNMENT.
SOMETHING HAS CAUSED
THE TIMELINE
REVOLVING AROUND
THE MISAKI FAMILY TO SHIFT.
IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING,
IT WON'T BE JUST TENCHI'S
HISTORY THAT CHANGES.
IT'LL BE OURS TOO.
- THIS IS TOO EXCITING.
- NO!  NO!
- COME ON, GIVE ME A COOKIE!
- NO!
- Washu: FOR NOW,
THE SHIELD I'VE PUT
AROUND LORD TENCHI
IS PROTECTING HIM
FROM THE SHIFT,
SO YOU ARE ALL PROTECTED.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN KEEP
THE TIME SHIELD UP
INDEFINITELY.
AND WHEN IT FINALLY COLLAPSES,
HE WILL DISAPPEAR.
- SO THAT MEANS...
- TENCHI.
- OH.
- OH, YOU MUST BE KIDDING.
- I WISH I WAS, RYOKO.
- THEN TELL ME,
WHAT THE HELL HAS HAPPENED
TO TENCHI'S MOTHER?!
- I'M SORRY, BUT I TOLD
YOU EVERYTHING I KNOW.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING THERE
ISN'T ANYTHING WE CAN DO
TO HELP HIM,
THAT IT?!
- WASHU, PLEASE.
- MISS WASHU.
- WELL, THERE'S ONE THING
THAT I CAN THINK OF.
- TELL ME, WASHU.
WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, TO START WITH,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TRAVEL BACK IN TIME
26 YEARS.
AND THEN OUR TASK
IS QUITE SIMPLE.
MAKE SURE NOTHING HAPPENS
TO TENCHI'S MOTHER.
- ( train whistles loudly )
- ( wheels clacking )
- ( sighs )
THAT PART-TIME JOB OF MINE
IS REALLY WEARING ME OUT.
- YOU BETTER GET TO SLEEP,
SO WE CAN GET AN EARLY START.
HUH?
- ( light snores )
- ASLEEP ALREADY.
AT LEAST THAT'S ONE THING
YOU'VE NEVER HAD
ANY TROUBLE DOING RIGHT.
- ( Mihoshi snores lightly )
- Captain: ATTENTION ALL UNITS!
INSTITUTE EMERGENCY
PROCEDURES AT ONCE!
A-1 CLASS CRIMINAL KAIN...
- HEADQUARTERS,
CAN YOU PLEASE...
I WONDER WHAT THAT
EMERGENCY SIGNAL WAS ALL ABOUT.
IT WAS SO STRANGE.
( gasps )
- GOOD EVENING.
( cackles )
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S TIME TO GO, KIYONE.
- HUH?  AHH!
- ( machine whirs )
- EVERYBODY READY?
USING MY
CHRONOMETRIC REGULATOR,
I INTEND TO SEND YOU ALL
26 YEARS INTO THE PAST.
OF COURSE THE PROCEDURE
IS STILL HIGHLY EXPERIMENTAL.
HOWEVER, IF YOU FOLLOW
MY INSTRUCTIONS,
THEN YOU'LL BE FINE.
I'M STILL COMPILING THE DATA
ON WHAT HAPPENS TO
LORD TENCHI'S MOTHER.
IT'S IMPERATIVE THAT TENCHI
NOT CONTACT HIS MOTHER
ONCE HE ARRIVES.
THAT WOULD BE DANGEROUS.
THE CHANCES OF A TIME PARADOX
ARE VERY, VERY HIGH.
- ARE YOU SURE THIS
IS GOING TO WORK?
- NOTHING VENTURED,
NOTHING GAINED, RIGHT?
- I REALLY HATE TO
PUT YOU THROUGH ALL THIS.
- THAT'S GREAT,
BUT WHY DO WE ALL
HAVE TO GET
MIXED UP IN THIS MESS?
- ( snoring )
- I'M GETTING REALLY DIZZY.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU GET BACK THERE,
YOU DON'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
DON'T THROW HISTORY OFF
ANY MORE THAN IT ALREADY IS.
- OKAY, WE HEARD IT
THE FIRST TIME.
- Washu: THAT GOES DOUBLE
FOR YOU, RYOKO.
IT'S TIME TO ACCELERATE.
- Ayeka: WHAT?
- Tenchi: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- Ryoko: HOLD IT, WASHU, WAIT!
- Sasami: I'M GONNA THROW UP!
- Kiyone: STOP THIS, PLEASE!
- Washu: HERE IT GOES.
- ( all scream )
- Tenchi: AND SO OUR
JOURNEY BACK IN TIME
TO SAVE THE FUTURE BEGAN.
- TODAY WE'RE LOOKING AT
THE DEMON OF THE RASHOMON,
THE FOURTH STORY IN
THE COLLECTION OF TALES
CALLED THE UJI SHUI MONOGATARI.
THIS IS A STORY
OF A TRIANGULAR RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN A WARRIOR,
A DEMON, AND A PRINCESS.
- Noboyuki: UH, MISS.
- YES, WHAT IS IT?
- WE, UH-- WE ALREADY
DID THAT STORY.
- AHH!
OH, MY.
THAT'S THE ONLY
EARTH STORY THAT I KNOW.
WHAT'LL I DO?
- THAT IDIOT.
- ( bell rings )
- ( students chatter )
- HEY, AYEKA.
- WHAT NOW?
- LOOK OVER THERE.
THAT'S TENCHI'S OLD MAN.
IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH TENCHI
LOOKS LIKE HIM AT THIS AGE.
- HMM, WELL, THEN THIS
IS YOUR BIG OPPORTUNITY, RIGHT?
FATHER IS STILL AVAILABLE.
- NOT THAT FILTHY OLD MAN
THAT HE BECAME
LATER ON IN LIFE.
I MEAN, TENCHI'S FATHER,
STUPID, THAT WE SEE HERE
BACK IN THE PAST.
- I'VE BEEN GIVING
OUR PROBLEM SOME THOUGHT.
YOU SEE, IF FATHER DOESN'T
END UP MARRYING MOTHER,
THEN TENCHI
WILL NEVER BE BORN.
- YOU JUST
FIGURED THAT OUT?
AND WHILE WE'RE AT IT,
WHAT'S WITH THIS "MOTHER"
AND "FATHER" THING?
SINCE WHEN DID THEY
BECOME YOUR PARENTS?
- WELL, I WAS HOPING
WHEN WE GET BACK...
- WHAT?  YOU MARRY TENCHI?!
DON'T BE STUPID.
- WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
AND WHO ARE YOU TO GO
AND CALL ME STUPID, RYOKO?
- I'LL CALL YOU WHAT I LIKE,
GOT IT, STUPID?
- ( both growl )
HUH?
( laughs )
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
NOTHING REALLY.
- ( both giggle )
HMPH!
- Coach: LET'S BEGIN.
- ( whistles )
- I GOT IT!
- ( cheering )
- HEY, OVER HERE.
- AWW, I GOT IT.
- I'M OPEN.
- HEY, OVER HERE.
- ( snickers )
WELL, IT'S DIFFERENT.
- HMM, YES, WELL,
WHAT CAN I DO, RYOKO?
AFTER ALL, I DIDN'T KNOW
THERE'D BE A CLASS LIKE THIS.
- WELL, LIKE THEY SAY,
YOU GET WHAT YOU DESERVE.
- ( growls )
AND YOU SHOULD KNOW!
AT LEAST I COULD FIT INTO
ONE OF ACHIKA'S GYM SUITS,
UNLIKE SOMEONE I KNOW
WHO HAD TO BORROW
HER GYM SUIT FROM
THE GYM TEACHER.
( giggles ) I'M NOT FAMILIAR
WITH THE WHOLE STORY,
BUT THE WORD IS THAT HE HAS
SOME SORT OF MEDICAL COMPLAINT
THAT IS PECULIAR TO MALES.
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
( sniffs )
( groans )
- ( whistles )
- UGH!
- HMM?
WHAT'S A MATTER WITH YOU?
LET'S GO!
- OH!  HE'S SCRATCHING HIMSELF!
UGH!
- AYEKA, GIVE ME
ALL YOUR CLOTHES.
- THERE'S NO WAY.
- TAKE 'EM OFF.
- ( screaming )
- RIGHT NOW.
- STOP IT!  LEAVE ME ALONE!
- COME ON.
- ( both grunting )
- HUH?
HEY-- HEY, STOP THAT,
BOTH OF YOU.
STOP, LET HER GO. YOU TWO
WANT TO STAY AFTER SCHOOL?
- ( fighting continues )
- ( sighs )
THOSE TWO NEVER STOP.
THEY'RE FIGHTING AGAIN.
- HERE.
- THANKS A LOT.
YOU'RE CUTE.
TELL ME,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
LITTLE GIRL?
- WAITING FOR MY BIG SISTER.
- OH, I SEE.
- MM-HMM.
- HUH.
- UH-OH.
- HUH?
- Female student:
ACHIKA, COME ON.
- UH, COMING.
SEE YOU.
THANKS AGAIN.
- SURE.
BYE-BYE.
HUH?
- WOW, THAT WAS CLOSE.
- YEAH, WASHU'S GONNA
BE REALLY ANGRY.
- ( gasps )
I KNEW IT WOULD BE
DANGEROUS HERE,
BUT SHE WAS
SO CLOSE THAT--
I KNOW IT SOUNDS STUPID.
I JUST HAD TO
SEE HER AGAIN.
- OF COURSE YOU DID.
- ( laughs ) SHH.
SASAMI, DON'T TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
- SURE.
- READY.
( laughs )
GOOD ONE!
- MOTHER.
- ( sighs )
MY SCHOOL'S SO FAR AWAY.
GETTING HOME JUST SEEMS
TO TAKE FOREVER.
I'M HOME!
OH, I'M SO HUNGRY.
I'LL FIX DINNER RIGHT-- HUH?
- HMM?
- YOU'RE, UH-- UH...
- HI.
- ( giggles ) I HOPE
WE'RE NOT PUTTING YOU OUT.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- AH, YES, FATHER.
I'M FINE,
JUST SURPRISED.
- WELL, I CAN
UNDERSTAND THAT.
AS IT HAPPENS,
YOUR SCHOOL CALLED TODAY.
THIS IS AYEKA AND RYOKO.
I AGREED TO LET
THEM BOARD HERE.
THEY'RE GONNA BE STAYING
WITH US FOR A WHILE.
- REALLY?  HOW EXCITING.
THEY JUST TRANSFERRED IN TODAY.
IN FACT, BOTH OF THEM
ARE IN MY CLASS.
- HUH, WELL, APPARENTLY
THEY LIVE SUCH A LONG WAY
FROM THE SCHOOL
THAT IT'S DIFFICULT FOR THEM
TO COMMUTE FROM HOME EVERY DAY.
- ( Ayeka giggles )
I'M VERY HAPPY TO BE HERE.
- SURE THING.
- IT'S MY PLEASURE.
- AH, MY, THIS IS
QUITE WONDERFUL.
MY POOR ACHIKA
HAS BEEN WITHOUT COMPANY
FAR TOO MUCH EVER SINCE
HER DEAR MOTHER PASSED AWAY.
( slurps )
- Ryoko: HEY,
I'M STARVING OVER HERE.
IS DINNER READY YET?  HUH?
- IT'S COMING UP RIGHT AWAY.
- WHY DON'T YOU HELP OUT
INSTEAD OF COMPLAINING?!
- HUH, YOU SHOULD TALK.
I DON'T SEE YOU DOING ANYTHING.
- HOW DARE YOU SPEAK
TO ME THAT WAY!
- NOW, PLEASE DON'T FIGHT.
- ( knocking )
- Both: HUH?
- Achika: WHO IS THAT?
- IT'S JUST ME.
- IT'S MISS MIHOSHI.
- I'M SORRY TO DISTURB YOU
AT THIS HOUR,
BUT I'M, UH,
CONDUCTING A HOME VISIT.
- ( both groan )
- REALLY?  HOW ODD.
- ( groans ) HOME VISITS?
WHO DOES THAT AT THIS HOUR?
- THAT FOOL.  I TOLD HER
TO GO AND TAKE A LOOK
WITHOUT MAKING
ANYONE SUSPICIOUS.
- OH, GOOD.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S MANAGED
TO GET INTO THE HOUSE, ANYWAY.
- WELL, BON APPETIT.
- Ayeka: HMM, THIS IS WONDERFUL.
- THIS IS VERY STRANGE, VERY.
- WELL, I MUST ADMIT.
YOU ALL DID A GREAT JOB
OF GETTING INTO THE HOUSE
WITHOUT AROUSING
ANY SUSPICIONS.
- I SUPPOSE.
( giggles )
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT WAS
THAT LITTLE BIT OF PERFUME
I BORROWED FROM WASHU.
- Ryoko: BEING SNEAKY
COMES NATURALLY, HMM?
- HUH?!  ALL RIGHT, RYOKO,
WHAT WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?!
- ALL RIGHT.  ALL RIGHT.
ANYWAY, WE'VE MANAGED TO
ALL GET SAFELY BACK HERE
TO 1970.
- RIGHT.
BUT HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY
TRY TO SAVE TENCHI'S MOTHER
WHEN WE DON'T KNOW
THE DANGER SHE FACES.
- ( Sasami laughs )
- ( Ryo-ohki meows )
- HERE IT IS.
I GOT A MESSAGE
FROM WASHU!
- SO IT LOOKS LIKE YOU ALL
GOT THERE SAFELY.
- OF COURSE.
WHY NOT?
- WELL, I MUST SAY
THIS TIME TRAVEL
BY FIXING THE POSITION
OF THE TIME AXIS
WAS MORE DIFFICULT
THAN I THOUGHT.
HUH, IN FACT,
TO TELL YOU GUYS THE TRUTH,
I WASN'T 100% CERTAIN
IT WAS GONNA WORK.
- ( all gasp )
- Ayeka: SO YOU MEAN TO SAY
THAT IF YOU HAD MADE
EVEN ONE FALSE MOVE,
WE COULD HAVE ENDED UP WANDERING
AROUND IN TIME FOREVER?
- Mihoshi: THAT WOULD
HAVE BEEN TERRIBLE.
- Ryoko: DAMN IT, WASHU!
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
BUT AT LEAST I GOT YOU
TO WHERE YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE,
DIDN'T I?
- ( all groan )
- WAIT UP.  UH...
MISS WASHU, I WONDER
IF YOU CAN TELL ME
EXACTLY WHEN AND WHERE
MY MOTHER'S GOING TO DISAPPEAR.
- NOT QUITE.
- HEY, ACHIKA, I'M RETURNING
THIS MAGAZINE TO YOU.
- TANAKA, I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU FOR DAYS.
SO HOW'S YOUR COLD DOING?
- Tanaka: OH, MY THROAT'S
STILL KIND OF SORE,
BUT I GOT A TEST COMING UP
SO WHAT CAN I DO?
- ACHIKA, ARE YOU
LISTENING TO ME?
- YES, YES, I'M COMING.
- THIS MAGAZINE
WAS REALLY INTERESTING.
ESPECIALLY THIS
PICTURE OF GORO.
- HMM?  REALLY,
WHICH PICTURE?
- THE FEATURE STORY
ON MICHIRU WAS GOOD TOO.
- YEAH, RIGHT,
I REMEMBER THAT.
I ALREADY READ IT
A COUPLE OF TIMES MYSELF.
- ( Washu echoes ):
ALL I CAN SAY--
ACHIKA'S POINT
OF DISAPPEARANCE...
SOMETIME WITHIN...
NEXT SEVEN DAYS.
- ( girls chatter )
- ( Washu echoes ):
KIYONE, I'VE CONFIRMED
THE DISAPPEARANCE OF
THE GALAXY POLICE HEADQUARTERS.
THEIR LAST TRANSMISSION
MENTIONED THE A-1 CLASS
CRIMINAL, KAIN...
- ( static fizzles )
- ( sighs )
- ( grunting )
- HEADS UP.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
( grunts )
- WHAT YOU DOING, AYEKA?
HAVING A DIRT SANDWICH?
( laughs )
- ( growls )
- COME AND GET ME IF YOU DARE.
- ( growls ) SHE REALLY
GETS ON MY NERVES!
- ( both laugh )
- THAT'S FUNNY.
- ( Washu echoes ): LORD TENCHI,
SHIELD ENERGY LASTS
ONLY SEVEN MORE DAYS.
BE CAREFUL.
- RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU MADE IT.
HAVE YOU TWO NOTICED
ANYTHING UNUSUAL?
- HMM.
- ANYTHING AT ALL,
NO MATTER HOW UNIMPORTANT
IT MIGHT SEEM TO YOU.
- HUH?  I HAVE SOMETHING.
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- YOU KNOW THE FRIED NOODLE DISH
THEY USUALLY SERVE AT LUNCH?
WELL, IT'S THE FIRST THING
TO BE SOLD OUT,
BUT TODAY THERE WERE...
THREE-- THERE WERE THREE
PIECES LEFT OVER.
I THINK THAT'S PRETTY WEIRD,
DON'T YOU?
- WHY ME?
- WE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER
INANE OBSERVATION.
- MM-HMM.
- SO TELL ME, EVERYONE,
ARE WE ALL STILL WILLING
TO GO ALONG
WITH THE ASSUMPTION
THAT SOMETHING HORRIBLE
IS GONNA HAPPEN
TO TENCHI'S MOTHER?
- ( grunting )
- LORD TENCHI!
- TENCHI, WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( groans )
- Ayeka: HE'S DISAPPEARING!
- Ryoko: UH-OH.
- Kiyone: I HOPE ACHIKA'S OKAY.
- ( groans )
- WAIT ONE SECOND.
IF WE'RE ALL HERE,
THEN THAT MEANS THAT...
- WHO'S WITH MOTHER?
- OH, BOY,
THIS COULD BE REALLY BAD.
ALL RIGHT, SASAMI,
YOU'D BETTER
TAKE CARE OF TENCHI.
- RIGHT.
- Kiyone: HURRY, EVERYONE.
LET'S SPLIT UP
AND LOOK FOR HER.
- ( groans )
MOTHER!
- ACHIKA!
WHERE HAVE YOU
GOTTEN TO, ACHIKA?!
- HEY, ACHIKA!
- ACHIKA?
SORRY.
ACHIKA?
YOU IN HERE?
- Kiyone:
ANSWER ME!  PLEASE!
- Ryoko:
HEY, DID YOU FIND HER?
- NO, HOW ABOUT YOU, AYEKA?
- NO, I COULDN'T
FIND HER EITHER.
LET'S CHECK ON TENCHI.
- ( sighs )
EVERYTHING SEEMS
TO BE UNDER CONTROL.
- AT LEAST FOR NOW.
- I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR ALL THIS TROUBLE.
- ( meowing )
- HEY!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- ( meowing )
- RYO-OHKI?
- I WONDER WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( meowing )
- Ayeka: YOU THINK SHE'S TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING?
- I'M NOT SURE.
MAYBE IT'S ACHIKA.
- ( gasps )
- LET'S GET GOING.
- ( leaves rustle )
- Achika: NOBOYUKI.
- HUH?  OH, ACHIKA.
- WHAT A SURPRISE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ON CLEANUP TODAY.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING WAY UP HERE?
- OH, I-- I--
- OOH, WHAT'S THAT
YOU'RE DRAWING?
- UH-- UH-- UH,
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
- AWW, PLEASE.
- WHAT?
- SHOW ME, SHOW ME.
- NO, DON'T!
- ( giggles )
OH.
WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A HOUSE.
- A HOUSE?
- YOU SEE, I LOVE--
- UH-HUH?
I LOVE ARCHITECTURE.
AND I'D REALLY LIKE TO BUILD
A HOUSE LIKE THIS SOMEDAY.
- OH.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( giggles )
OH, NOTHING AT ALL REALLY.
- CAN I HAVE THE BOOK?
- YOU KNOW, A WINDOW MIGHT
BE NICE HERE BY THE ROOF.
IT WOULD LET IN
MORE LIGHT
AND REALLY BRIGHTEN THINGS UP.
- WHAT?
YOU MEAN...
LIKE THIS?
- HMM?
MORE LIKE THAT.
- HEY, YOU SURE HAVE
EXCELLENT TASTE, ACHIKA.
- REALLY?  DO YOU THINK SO?
- YEAH.
- LISTEN, NOBOYUKI,
IF YOU EVER MANAGE
TO BUILD THIS HOUSE,
PROMISE THAT YOU'LL INVITE ME
TO COME AND SEE IT.
- HUH?!
- COME ON.
WHAT'S THE MATTER NOW?
- THE MATTER?
NOTHING AT ALL.
- ( laughs )
WHAT ABOUT ITS COLOR?
- I HAVEN'T THOUGHT
THAT FAR YET.
- I THINK IT SHOULD BE RED.
- ( meowing )
- Ryoko:
IS THIS WHERE THEY ARE?
WHAT WOULD THEY
BE DOING OUT HERE?
- ( sniffing )
- WHAT?  A RED ROOF?
- ( meowing )
- HUH?
- ( giggling )
- UH-HUH, THERE THEY ARE.
- UGH!  IGNORING THE WORLD,
ALL ALONE AND OBLIVIOUS.
- OH, HOW SWEET.  AWW.
- HUH?
- HMPH, THEY'RE
JUST HAVING FUN.  HUH?
- WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT?  NOTHING I SUPPOSE.
- HUH?
OH, MY, MY.
WELL THEN, LET ME SEE.
THE LADY ACHIKA
IS GOING TO DISAPPEAR
BECAUSE OF ONE OR ALL
OF THESE SEEMINGLY
RANDOM ELEMENTS.
NOW IF I COULD ONLY MANAGE
TO DEFINE THEM,
I'D BE ABLE TO NARROW DOWN
THE PROBABILITIES
AND ACCURATELY PREDICT
WHEN SHE WILL VANISH.
( growls )
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
- NO!
A SCHOOL STUDY TRIP!  NO!
- UH...
( coughs )
- Ryoko: WHEN?
WHEN DO WE LEAVE?
- WHEN?  WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHY, TOMORROW OF COURSE.
THAT'S WHY WE ALL
DIVIDED UP INTO GROUPS.
- Both: HUH?
- ( film clacking )
- ( chuckles )
- AAH, THIS IS GREAT.
- SO WHAT ARE
WE GONNA DO, KIYONE?
- WELL, FOR THE TIME BEING,
ALL WE CAN DO IS GO
ON THIS TRIP TOGETHER.
- I'M AFRAID I'LL GET LOST.
THERE'S JUST SO MANY PEOPLE
LIVING IN TOKYO.
- GET REAL.  DETECTIVES
IN THE GALAXY POLICE
DON'T JUST GET LOST.
- WHAT?  KIYONE.
WHERE'D YOU GO?
DID YOU FALL ASLEEP?
- ( screams )
- OH, DEAR, HAVE I CHOSEN
A BAD TIME
TO BRING YOU BACK?
- WASHU.
THE NEXT TIME THAT YOU'RE
GONNA BRING ME BACK,
I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU'D TELL ME FIRST.
- I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT OF COURSE.
ACTUALLY, THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT YOU TO CHECK FOR ME.
- I CAN HANDLE IT.
TELL ME WHAT IT IS YOU'D LIKE.
- WHEN I ANALYZED
THE ENERGY'S SIGNATURE
FROM THE POINT OF
ACHIKA'S DISAPPEARANCE,
I FOUND A CORRELATION.
IT MATCHED THE ENERGY RELEASED
WHEN THE GALAXY POLICE
HEADQUARTERS VANISHED.
- AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- IT'S QUITE SIMPLE.
BECAUSE HEADQUARTERS
DISAPPEARED RIGHT AFTER
THAT LAST KAIN TRANSMISSION
OF YOURS,
I SUSPECT THERE'S SOME
CONNECTION BETWEEN THE TWO.
- HMM.
ARE YOU ABLE TO ACCESS
YAGAMI'S COMPUTER DATABASE?
- OF COURSE I CAN.
I COULD GET THE ACCOUNT BOOKS
OF THE SCIENCE ACADEMY
IF I WANTED.
( typing )
- KAIN, KAIN?
I'M SURE I'VE SEEN THAT NAME
ON THE LIST
OF A-1 CLASS
CRIMINALS BEFORE.
( gasps )
- THERE IT IS.
LOOK AT THAT.
AGE, GENDER, HISTORY,
ORIGIN-- EVERYTHING
COMES UP UNKNOWN.
THERE ARE NO DISTINGUISHING
CHARACTERISTICS.
HOW CAN WE IDENTIFY HIM?
OFFENDER NUMBER 6-7,
CLASS A.
- "UNIVERSAL ERA 5-0-7-4-1-0.
CHARACTERISTIC ENERGY FORM
CLASSIFIED AS N.V.O.
CODE NAME: KAIN.
WANTED FOR
DESTRUCTION OF PLANETS,
SUSPICION OF MURDER.
GENERAL WARRANT ISSUED.
DESTROYED 13 FEDERATED PLANETS
AND 275,000 SPACECRAFT BEFORE
HE WAS APPREHENDED AND CONFINED
IN THE GALAXY POLICE
SUBSPACE NETWORK.
CONSIDERED
TO HAVE THE POWER
TO OVERCOME EVEN A LARGE
FORCE OF GALAXY POLICE.
HAS BEEN CONFINED
IN THE HEADQUARTERS'
SUBSPACE ROOM
FOR THE PAST 100 YEARS."
- ( growls )
- HMM, NOT AN ORDINARY
CRIMINAL, IS HE?
HE'S MORE LIKE
A BRAND-NEW SUPERNOVA.
- BUT EVEN IF HE ESCAPED
THE SUBSPACE ROOM,
HOW COULD HE GO BACK
IN TIME 26 YEARS
AND INTERFERE WITH
THE EVENTS THERE?
- HMM, TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
IF KAIN MANAGED TO
GET OUT OF SUBSPACE ,
THEN HE COULD EASILY
INFLUENCE THE PASSAGE OF TIME,
COULDN'T HE?
ANYWAY,
IF WE ASSUME
THAT KAIN
IS ON HIS WAY TO EARTH
AND FOR SOME REASON
INTENDS TO ATTACK ACHIKA,
I CAN NARROW
THE PROBABILITY LEVELS
TO 87% THAT WILL HAPPEN
BETWEEN NOVEMBER 25th
AND NOVEMBER 28th, 1970.
ACCORDING TO MY CALCULATIONS,
IT'LL BE SOMEWHERE IN--
OH MY GOD.
- Both: TOKYO.
- Tenchi: AND SO WE ALL
HEADED OFF TO TOKYO
FOR OUR SCHOOL TRIP.
- Ryoko: WELL, IF HE IS
GOING TO ATTACK US,
YOU'D THINK HE'D
HAVE THE DECENCY
NOT TO DO IT RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF A SCHOOL TRIP.
- IT'S NOT 100% CERTAIN,
BUT THE PROBABILITY
IS MUCH HIGHER
ON THESE THREE DAYS.
- THIS KAIN IS STRONG ENOUGH
TO DESTROY
THE ENTIRE HEADQUARTERS?
( shrieks )
KIYONE, I WANT TO
GO BACK HOME NOW!
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T GO HOME.
WE HAVE TO STAY HERE
TO PROTECT MOTHER.
IT'S OUR MISSION.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS TO HER,
LORD TENCHI WILL DISAPPEAR
AND WE WILL TOO.
- HUSH, AYEKA.
- SO TELL ME,
WHEN DID ACHIKA
BECOME YOUR MOTHER?  HMM?
- ( growls )
- HEY, HEY, I KNOW
JUST WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
OH, ACHIKA, JUST
LIKE ONE OF THE FAMILY.
SEE?
OH-HO-HO-HO-HO.
- I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE!
LOOK, YOU DIRT FOR BRAINS,
WE'VE ALL HEARD
ENOUGH OF YOUR INSINUATIONS!
- OH, YEAH, THE TRUTH HURTS,
DOESN'T IT?
YOU THINK I DIDN'T SEE
YOU AND ACHIKA YESTERDAY
BOTH SNEAKING OFF
TO TALK ABOUT THINGS
LIKE WHAT KIND OF BOYS
YOU BOTH PREFER?
- OH!  YOU KNOW
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
( screams )
- I'M READY.
YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
- STOP IT NOW.
AYEKA, CALM DOWN.
- THIS TIME, SHE'S GONE TOO FAR.
I SWEAR IT!
- PLEASE!
- I'M GONNA TEACH HER A LESSON!
WATCH!
- HMPH, OH, YEAH, FOR SURE.
YOU AND WHAT ARMY, AYEKA?
- ( whimpers )
- Mihoshi: NO, STOP!
- Ayeka: ACHIKA WAS...
- ( static buzzes )
- Sasami: STOP IT!
- ( train whistles )
- ( wheels clacking  )
- Announcer:
TOKYO.  TOKYO.
WE APOLOGIZE
FOR THE LONG DELAY
IN REACHING
OUR DESTINATION.
THE A.M.F. WAS TURNED ON
AS A RESULT OF THIS DELAY.
WE OFFER OUR MOST
HUMBLE APOLOGIES...
- FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE--
- I FEEL SO TIRED.
- ME TOO, ACHIKA.
WELL, AT LEAST WE GOT HERE,
EVEN IF IT IS
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
- OKAY, SENIOR CLASS,
NOW IS EVERYBODY HERE?
- YEAH.
- WE'RE ABOUT TO LEAVE.
- Male student: WE'RE HERE.
COME ON.  LET'S GO ALREADY.
- SO WHO'S GONNA
KEEP WATCH TONIGHT?
- SOMEHOW, I HAVE A FEELING
IT'S GOING TO BE US.
- ( yawns )
I FEEL SO SLEEPY.
- ( film clicking )
- HUH?
HEY, NOBOYUKI.
- ( laughs )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THAT THING?
- ( laughs )
IT'LL BE A GREAT SOUVENIR.
- OH, DID YOU SLEEP
AT ALL LAST NIGHT?
- A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
- UGH!  IT'S STILL
TOO EARLY IN THE DAY
FOR ALL OF THIS.
- YES, I AGREE.
THEY SEEM TO BE GETTING ALONG
JUST FINE, DON'T THEY?
ISN'T IT GREAT?
( yawns )
- HMPH!
- OH!  BOY, IT'S HOT.
I WISH THIS THING
WOULD GET GOING.
- WISH I HAD SOME WATER!
- ( meows )
- ( Kiyone on Microphone ):
TESTING.  TESTING.
CHECK.
UH, GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY.
HOW ARE YOU ALL TODAY?
I HOPE YOU ALL MANAGED TO GET
A RESTFUL SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
- ( groaning )
- NO!
- BE POLITE
CHILDREN NOW, PLEASE.
YOU LITTLE BRATS.
- ( film clicking )
- OH, DON'T!
THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
- ( laughs )
JUST THINK OF IT
AS A WAY OF CAPTURING
GOOD MEMORIES.
INTERVIEW TIME.
ARE YOU ENJOYING OUR
CLASS TRIP, ACHIKA?
- YEAH, I WOULD SAY I AM.
BUT, WELL,
THERE IS ONE THING
I'M A LITTLE WORRIED ABOUT.
- WHAT?
- WELL, I AM WONDERING
IF MY FATHER HAS REMEMBERED
TO EAT PROPERLY.
- EAT PROPERLY?
DON'T WORRY.
PEOPLE DON'T
STARVE TO DEATH
JUST BECAUSE THEY SKIP MEALS
FOR THREE DAYS.
- YEAH, ARE YOU
SURE ABOUT THAT?
- RELATIVELY.
- ( giggles )
- OKAY, ACHIKA, ARE YOU READY
FOR ANOTHER QUESTION?
- SURE THING.
THAT'S FINE.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO BE
WHEN YOU GROW UP?
- ( gasps )
I WANT TO BE...
A BRIDE.
- ( boys laugh )
- Ryoko: AH, I BET YOU
WEREN'T READY FOR THAT ANSWER.
WERE YOU, NOBOYUKI?
- HEY, WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
IT'S NOTHING.
- WHOO WHOO!
- THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH THE TWO OF YOU
BEING ATTRACTED TO EACH OTHER.
- WHAT?  STOP THAT.
NOBOYUKI, WHY DON'T
YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- ( boys laugh )
- Ryoko: I KNEW IT.
LOOK AT NOBOYUKI BLUSH.
HE KNOWS THAT IT'S TRUE.
- Ayeka: IT'S NOTHING.
HE'S A BIT SHY.
- WHAT ARE
THOSE IDIOTS DOING?
- YES, JUST WHEN YOUR
MOTHER AND FATHER
HAVE FINALLY GOTTEN TOGETHER.
I THINK THEY SHOULD JUST
LEAVE 'EM ALONE.
- ( meows )
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
DISAPPEARING AGAIN?!
WHEW, JUST IN TIME.
- THANKS, SASAMI.
- I'M WORRIED, TENCHI.
I WONDER IF MISS WASHU'S SHIELD
IS LOSING STRENGTH.
- YEAH.
( sighs )
IF THIS KEEPS UP,
HOW AM I EVER GOING TO
LOOK AFTER MY MOTHER?
- YOU'LL MANAGE, TENCHI.
- ( meows )
- SO THIS IS WHERE THE TWO OF
YOU HAVE BEEN HIDING YOURSELVES.
COME ON OUT.
NO ONE'S GONNA NOTICE
YOU'RE HERE WITH
ALL THESE STUDENTS AROUND.
- RYOKO.
- RYOKO, IT'S TERRIBLE.
TENCHI WAS ABOUT
TO DISAPPEAR AGAIN.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HUH?
THERE'S THAT GUY.
HE'S THE ONE!
HE'S BEEN SPYING ON US.
HEY, HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
HMM?
HE'S DISAPPEARED.
- ( crowds chatter )
- Man: KIDS,
OVER HERE WITH ME.
- PARDON ME, SIR.
I'LL HAVE ONE OF THESE
MILLET AND RICE CAKES, PLEASE.
- HEY, SOME OF THESE
SWEET BEAN PASTE CAKES.
- THIS LOVELY FAN
IS JUST WHAT
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
- ( chatter continues )
- ( both laughing )
- Noboyuki:
THIS ONE IS DELICIOUS.
( chuckles )
- ( Ryoko gasps )
- HUH?
- DID THAT GUY SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU?
- NO, NOTHING.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- HERE, GOT TO GO.
- SHE'S SO WEIRD.
I WONDER WHAT
THAT WAS ABOUT.
- YEAH.
- DAMN.  WHERE'D HE GO?
- DON'T MOVE.
- ( gasps )
- GET YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD, QUICK.
- STAY COOL.
WHAT IS THIS?
WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING
ACHIKA AROUND?
- THE SPACE PIRATE RYOKO,
I PRESUME.
A SERIOUS OFFENDER.
CASE NUMBER: 8-0-8-1-2-0-2-9
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN.
- ( gasps )
OH MY, THE GALAXY POLICE.
YOU WITH KIYONE AND MIHOSHI?
- HMPH!  YOU SEEM TO
BE GETTING ALONG WELL
WITH THOSE DETECTIVES
FIRST CLASS.
- ME, I'M A SPECIAL OPERATIVE.
I'M WITH THE GALAXY POLICE
DEALING WITH SERIOUS CRIMINALS.
THE ENERGY OF
THE CLASS-A CRIMINAL KAIN
HAS DRAWN ME BACK HERE
TO THIS ERA.
- ( screams )
- KAIN... AND JUST
WHO IS THIS GUY, ANYWAY?
AND WHAT DOES HE HAVE
TO DO WITH ACHIKA?
- KAIN'S A BEING
WHO HATES THE HOUSE OF JURAI.
100 YEARS AGO,
HE WENT ON A RAMPAGE
OF MURDER AND DESTRUCTION
ACROSS THE UNIVERSE.
- ( deep chuckle )
- THE HOUSE OF JURAI COOPERATED
WITH THE GALAXY POLICE
IN CAPTURING HIM.
- ( screams )
- THEN A WEEK AGO,
HE DESTROYED OUR HEADQUARTERS
AND VANISHED.
HE HAS COME
TO THIS WORLD AND TIME
TO TAKE REVENGE
BY SWALLOWING UP THE JURAI.
- WHAT'S THAT HAVE
TO DO WITH ACHIKA?
- A LOT.
THE CURRENT JURAI EMPEROR
HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH HIS CAPTIVITY,
BUT KAIN STILL HATES HIM.
KAIN THRIVES WHERE
THERE IS NO JURAI ENERGY.
SO HE'S HERE TO MAKE SURE
THAT NO ONE
WHO CONTROLS THAT POWER
CAN STAND IN HIS WAY.
AND SINCE YOSHO
AND LADY ACHIKA
ARE FROM
THE HOUSE OF JURAI...
- SO SHE'S NOTHING MORE
THAN AN INNOCENT BYSTANDER.
- ( grunts )
( grunts )
TAKE THIS!
BASTARD.
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE VERY GOOD, RYOKO.
I DON'T KNOW WHY ALL OF YOU
HAVE COME TO THIS ERA,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS.
KAIN WILL BE MINE!
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- WAIT.
- I'LL LET YOU
RUN FREE, RYOKO,
UNTIL I DEFEAT KAIN!
- ( gasps )
WHAT NEXT?
- Tenchi: AND WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU GET IN THE WAY
OF THEM COMING TOGETHER?
IF MY MOTHER AND FATHER
DON'T MARRY,
I DON'T GET BORN.
SO DO ME A FAVOR, YOU TWO,
AND STOP MEDDLING WITH THEM,
WILL YOU?!
- I'M SORRY.
- WE DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
HONEST, WE DIDN'T, TENCHI.
ANYWAY, I THINK I KNOW
WHAT KAIN IS AFTER.
- RYOKO, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- HUH?
- KIYONE, YOU WANT TO GO OUT?
THERE'S A SOUVENIR SHOP
ON THE FIRST FLOOR, YOU KNOW.
( gasps )
ARE ALL OF YOU COMING?
- ( all groan )
- OH NO!  MIHOSHI,
WHERE'S ACHIKA?
- All: HUH?
- WELL, LET'S SEE.
I KNOW WE WERE TOGETHER
AS FAR AS THE BATH.
- OH NO.
- EVERYBODY, JUST CALM DOWN.
AND I'LL GO FIND HER.
- SORRY.
- Ryoko: YOU ARE PROVING USELESS
TO THIS OPERATION.
- Mihoshi: I JUST CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT WITHOUT KIYONE.
- Sasami: SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WHERE IS KIYONE?
- Tenchi: GEE, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SURE I GAVE HER
THE RIGHT ROOM NUMBER.
- ( chews nosily )
- ( Mihoshi cries )
KIYONE!  WHERE IS KIYONE?
( cries )
- ( yowls )
- KIYONE!
( cries )
DON'T LEAVE ME, KIYONE.
- ( Kiyone screams )
- Tenchi: WHOA!
- WHAT WAS THAT?
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
- ( groaning )
- Tenchi: THERE YOU ARE, KIYONE.
- Ryoko: WOW, WHAT HAPPENED?
- I WISH WASHU WOULD FIND
A BETTER LANDING PLACE
FOR HER DAMN
TIME TRANSFERS.
- WASHU.
- OH, SHE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS THEN?
- UH-HUH. SHE'LL EXPLAIN
IT ALL IN DETAIL HERSELF.
- HI, SO HOW'S EVERYONE DOING?
- MISS WASHU!
- EVERYTHING GOING OKAY?
- WELL, IT'S NOT BAD SO FAR.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
THIS GUY KAIN?
- GOOD QUESTION.
WHAT ABOUT THIS GUY KAIN?
I'M SURE THE ANTI-JURAI ATTACK
ON LADY ACHIKA
WILL COME TOMORROW,
BUT I CAN'T BE SURE WHERE.
THERE IS ONE PLACE THAT
WE SHOULD LOOK OUT FOR THOUGH.
SOMEWHERE WHERE THERE'S
A VERY BIG TRANSMITTER.
- A TRANSMITTER?!
- HMM?
- TOKYO TOWER!
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE
ALL HEADING TOMORROW.
- OH, BUT NOW
I WON'T BE ABLE
TO TAKE THE PICTURE
I WANTED
FROM THEIR COOL
OBSERVATION DECK.
- PLEASE SHUT UP!
- WHAA!
- Washu: LISTEN UP.
I HAVE THE DATA
FROM WHEN KAIN WAS TAKEN
PRISONER 100 YEARS AGO.
HE WAS CAPTURED
THROUGH A COMBINATION
OF THE SUBSPACE NET
AND THE ENERGY
FROM THE EMPEROR JURAI.
- ( screaming )
- Washu:
BUT IN THIS GENERATION,
I'M AFRAID THERE IS NO ONE
CAPABLE OF WIELDING
THAT AMOUNT OF ENERGY.
MAYBE GRANDPA COULD DO IT.
- THE AMOUNT OF ENERGY
THAT'S REQUIRED
CANNOT BE GENERATED
BY LORD KATSUHITO.
AND IT WOULD BE TOO DANGEROUS
FOR HIM TO EVEN TRY.
- WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- THAT THE JURAI EMPEROR DIED.
HE WAS ABLE TO HELP
IN THE CAPTURE OF KAIN,
BUT DISPELLING
THE AMOUNT OF ENERGY NECESSARY
PROVED TO BE FATAL.
IT JUST WON'T WORK.
OKAY, LISTEN UP, TROOPS.
I'VE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS.
I'VE TAKEN ALL OF THIS
INTO ACCOUNT.
I'M SENDING YOU SOME
IMPORTANT EQUIPMENT.
MY CYE-LINK ANALYZER
IS DESIGNED
TO AMPLIFY THE CYE-WAVE
ACTIVITY OF TREES
AND CONNECTS IT DIRECTLY
TO THE SUBSPACE NET.
- FASCINATING, BUT
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW ANY OF THIS STUFF
IS SUPPOSED TO HELP US OUT.
- HEH!  IT'S ELEMENTARY.
MY EQUIPMENT WAS
MADE TO COMBINE
THE JURAI ENERGY WITH
THE SUBSPACE NET.
KIYONE, SHOW THEM!
- OKAY.
THIS IS THE MAIN BOOSTER.
NOW LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
WE PLACE THIS
ON THE TOKYO TOWER.
THE OTHERS GO ELSEWHERE.
THEY'RE ACTIVATED
BY REMOTE SWITCH.
THEY'RE DESIGNED TO GIVE US
TEN MINUTES OF POWER.
- ONLY TEN?
THAT'S NOT MUCH TIME, IS IT?
- LOOK, RYOKO,
THAT'S ALL WE'VE GOT.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT.
THIS IS AN INSTANT
JURAI ENERGY GENERATOR.
BE HAPPY THAT IT
WORKS AT ALL.
- IS IT POSSIBLE
WE CAN GENERATE
JURAI ENERGY RIGHT HERE?
ON EARTH, THAT IS.
- WELL, IT WON'T WORK
JUST ANYWHERE.
ONLY FROM THE FIVE PLACES
ON THE MAP
THAT I GAVE TO KIYONE--
NOWHERE ELSE
ON THE EARTH BUT THERE.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
IN A WAY, WE'RE LUCKY
THAT THE ATTACK IS GOING
TO HAPPEN HERE IN TOKYO.
- MEGURO, THE BLACK EYE.
MEJIRO, THE WHITE EYE.
OH, WOW, THESE ARE
THE FIVE COLOR FUDO TEMPLES.
- Sasami: THE FIVE COLOR FUDO?
- HM-HMM.
IN FEUDAL TIMES,
THEY PUT UP THESE STATUES
OF FUDO MYO-O
TO GUARD EDO CASTLE HERE.
THIS MUST BE IT.
THE OTHERS ARE THE RED EYE,
BLUE EYE, AND YELLOW EYE.
- GOOD THINKING!
THE ONLY WAY
FOR US TO ACCESS
SUCH LARGE AMOUNTS
OF ENERGY QUICKLY
IS TO USE
THE ANCIENT HOLY PLACES
AND UTILIZE THEIR ENERGY.
- SO, NOW, WE HAVE
TO DECIDE
WHO'S GONNA
TARGET EACH TEMPLE
AND WHO'S GONNA KEEP AN EYE
ON LADY ACHIKA.
- YOU CAN DECIDE ON THE REST.
I'LL WATCH MOTHER.
- IS THAT WISE?
- Tenchi: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I KNOW IT HAS
TO BE THIS WAY.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT
YOU'VE ALL BEEN CAUGHT UP
IN MY FAMILY'S PROBLEMS.
BUT NOW I HAVE
TO BE THE ONE.
WHEN THE FINAL BATTLE COMES,
I HAVE TO STAND BESIDE HER.
- WHY DON'T YOU
GO AHEAD THEN, TENCHI.
WE CAN HANDLE THE REST
OF THE DETAILS OURSELVES.
- THANK YOU, RYOKO.
( screams )
( groans )
- Kiyone: TENCHI!
- Sasami: TENCHI!
- Mihoshi: ARE YOU OKAY?
- Ryoko: GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF.
- Sasami: TENCHI!
- ( grunts, growls )
- ( moans )
- ACHIKA, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT ON EARTH HAPPENED
TO YOU?
- IT'S MY HEAD.
THERE'S SUCH SPLITTING PAIN!
- ACHIKA, WHAT IS IT?
- DON'T KNOW.
SHE GRABBED HER HEAD
AND SHE FELL OVER.
- THE POOR THING.
- ( whimpers )
- LET'S TAKE HER BACK
TO HER ROOM.
- ( moans )
- OKAY.
- ( grunting )
AHH!
- I GOT THE SHIELD.
- ( strained )
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
( growls )
( sighs )
( gasps )
( light panting )
- TENCHI.
- I'M GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I MUST BE ABLE
TO BEAR THIS MUCH PAIN
OR HOW CAN I PROTECT
MOTHER FROM DANGER?
- HMM, WELL THEN, YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
YOU BETTER GET READY.
- WASHU, HOW CAN
YOU BE SO DAMN CALM?
WHY DON'T YOU DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS?
- WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
LADY ACHIKA'S COLLAPSED,
I HATE TO SAY.
- ( all gasping )
- OH, I HOPE SHE'S NOT HURT.
- YOU CARRIED ME.
- IT WAS NOTHING.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- ( sighs )
I FEEL MUCH BETTER.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- I'M SO SORRY
TO HAVE WORRIED YOU.
- I'LL STAY TILL
YOU FALL ASLEEP.
- HEY, AYEKA.
HOW IS ACHIKA DOING?
- THEY SAY IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN ANEMIA.
- I WONDER IF KAIN
IS CAUSING ALL OF THIS.
- IT'S A REASONABLE
EXPLANATION.
WASHU DID SAY THERE'S
NO LONGER ANY DOUBT
THAT KAIN WILL MATERIALIZE
SOMETIME TOMORROW.
SO ACHIKA SHOULD BE OKAY
UNTIL THEN.
WE SHOULD USE THIS TIME
TO PLAN THE DEPLOYMENT
OF OUR EQUIPMENT
SO WE CAN DEFEAT HIM.
- MM-HMM.
- RIGHT!
- TENCHI, I KNOW YOU WANT
TO STAY CLOSE TO YOUR MOM,
SO YOU'LL GO TO
THE TOKYO TOWER WITH ACHIKA
AND TAKE
THE MAIN BOOSTER, OKAY?
- YES.
BY NEXT MORNING,
OUR PLANS HAD BEEN LAID.
KAIN WOULD APPEAR SOON,
MAKING IT A DAY
WE WOULD NEVER FORGET.
WELL, THIS IS IT.
I GUESS I'LL BE ON MY WAY
TO THE TOKYO TOWER.
- ALL RIGHT,
PLEASE REMEMBER
THE MAIN BOOSTER
HAS TO BE SET
SOMEWHERE IN THE CENTER
OF THE TOWER'S OBSERVATION DECK.
- GOT IT.
- AS SOON AS I'VE GOT
MY STUFF IN POSITION,
I'LL HEAD OVER THERE.
IF THERE ARE ANY PROBLEMS
AT ALL, USE THE TRANSCEIVER.
- RIGHT.
SEE YOU ALL LATER.
- ...LORD TENCHI.
- DAMN.
IF ONLY THIS WAS ALL
HAPPENING AT A LOCATION
THAT I'D ALREADY BEEN TO.
THEN I COULD
TELEPORT OVER THERE
AND SET THE WHOLE THING UP.
- ( laughs )
PERFECT.
JUST ANOTHER ONE OF YOUR POWERS
THAT ISN'T ANY USE.
- WHAT WAS THAT
YOU SAID, AYEKA?!
- THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU TWO.
STOP WASTING TIME.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- LET'S GO.
- Sasami: OKAY.
- ( meows )
- Ryoko: WE SHOULD TAKE
THE YAMANOTE LINE, RIGHT?
- Ayeka: I'M TAKING
THE ONE BOUND FOR SHIBUYA.
- ARE WE GOING THE
SAME WAY, SASAMI?
- YUP. BUT I HAVE TO
SWITCH TRAINS LATER.
- Kiyone: WHERE IS SHE NOW?
MIHOSHI?!  MIHOSHI!
COME ON, MIHOSHI!
- ( slurps )
( sighs )
THAT WAS GOOD.
- HEY.
( laughs )
SO THIS IS TOKYO TOWER.
( giggles )
THIS IS GREAT.
- YEAH.
- ( pants )
GREAT.
( pants )
LOOKS LIKE
I MADE IT ON TIME.
- THERE, ONE DOWN.
NOW, WE'VE GOT TO GET
OVER TO THE RED FUDO.
- EXCUSE ME.
I'M COMING IN.
- MAY YOU GUARD
TENCHI WELL.
- Women: TOKYO TOWER.
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- TAKE A PICTURE OF ME.
- ( chatter continues )
- RIGHT THERE.
WHOA!
( screams )
- ( pants )
- ( meows )
- GENERATOR IN PLACE.
RED FUDO!
- ( meows )
- ( phone rings )
- YES?
- Kiyone: TENCHI.
ALL OF THE GENERATORS
ARE IN PLACE ON THE FIVE FUDO.
HOW'S THE MAIN
BOOSTER COMING?
- NOT TOO GOOD.
I'M CAUGHT UP IN
A CROWD OF STUDENTS.
- Kiyone: OKAY,
DON'T SWITCH IT ON
UNTIL YOU'VE PUT IT IN PLACE
ON THE OBSERVATION DECK.
IF YOU DO IT BEFORE THAT,
IT'LL START TO DISCHARGE.
SO BE CAREFUL!
- RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
- IT WON'T BE LONG.
- ( elevator pings )
- ( Woman over P.A. ):
THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
PLEASE WATCH YOUR STEP.
- ( chattering )
- ( elevator dings )
- EXCUSE ME!  PARDON ME!
- HEY, MAN!
- OH!
- ( Woman on P.A. ): THANK YOU
FOR VISITING TOKYO TOWER.
IN HEIGHT: 333 METERS AND...
- WOW.
- ( grunts )
- OH!
- ACHIKA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
( groans )
- HUH?  EXCUSE ME.  PARDON ME.
- ( whimpering )
- SORRY.
- ( thunder crashes )
- OH, IT'S SHAKING.
- SOMEONE!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- ( all whimpering )
- ( grunting )
- HUSH, ACHIKA,
ARE YOU FEELING SICK?
- ( Woman on P.A. ):
PLEASE REMAIN CALM.
THE ELEVATOR WILL
RESUME ASCENT SHORTLY.
NOW PLEASE CALM DOWN.
- IT'S KAIN.
- ( rumbling )
- ( coughing )
- Kain: I CAN FEEL IT.
IT'S SO CLOSE.
THE BLOOD OF JURAI.
( chuckles )
( cackles )
( groans )
PATHETIC.
- OH.
- ( gasps )
- QUICK-- LET'S GET
TO THE STAIRS
BEFORE HE COMES BACK.
- GOOD IDEA.
- WHERE'D HE GO?!
( grunts )
( growls )
( screams )
- A SURVIVOR FROM
THE GALAXY POLICE, HMM?
WHAT MAGNIFICENT
SPIRIT YOU'VE SHOWN
IN TRACKING ME
ALL THE WAY HERE.
- KAIN, I'M GONNA GET YOU
IF IT'S THE LAST THING
I EVER DO.
- ( pants )
- HOW PITIFUL
THAT YOUR SKILL
AS AN OPERATIVE HAS HELPED
SEAL YOUR FATE.
NO ONE CAN WITHSTAND
THE POWER OF KAIN.
- ( groans )
( screams )
- ( chuckling )
- ( screaming continues )
- Washu: TENCHI, ANSWER ME.
NO, NOT GOOD.
CAN'T KEEP UP THE POWER.
THE FIVE FUDO
ARE GOING TO FAIL.
- COME ON, TENCHI.
- TENCHI.
- ( both panting )
- ( pants )
WHAT THE--
- I MUST FIND THE CENTER.
- ACHIKA?
- HUH?
- ( energy building )
- HE'S COMING.
- ( crashing, rumbling )
- ( both coughing )
- ACHIKA.
- ( both scream )
- ( chuckling )
I FEEL IT.
SOMEONE FROM
THE HOUSE OF JURAI
IS HERE.
WHICH ONE OF YOU
HOLDS THAT POWER?
- PUT THIS SOMEWHERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DECK
AND HURRY!
- WHAT?
- GO DO IT.
- BUT WHAT DOES-- HUH?
- THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANY FARTHER.
- ARE YOU OF
THE HOUSE OF JURAI?
( chuckles )
VERY INTERESTING.
WE'LL SEE HOW MUCH POWER
YOU HAVE!
( grunts )
- ( straining )
- ( chuckling )
- QUICK,
ACHIKA, LET'S GO.
- WHO'S THAT BOY?
- ACHIKA, WE GOT TO GO!
- TENCHI, I'M ALMOST THERE.
- HE SAID TO PUT IT
IN THE MIDDLE.
- ( groaning )
- HUH?
- ( pants )
- ( chuckles )
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE END
OF THE HOUSE OF JURAI.
I'LL ERADICATE YOU
AND PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR MISERY.
( chuckles )
- I WON'T LET YOU
TOUCH MY MOM!
- HUH?
ENOUGH!
THIS WILL STOP.
- WHAT?
- ACHIKA?
- YOU ARE THE ONE
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
YOU AND NO ONE ELSE.
NONE OF THE OTHERS
WERE THE SAME.
I'VE COME ALL THE WAY
TO THIS PLANET
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
TO DESTROY YOU.
- TELL ME WHO YOU ARE.
- I AM ONE WHO HAS
SUFFERED GRIEVOUSLY
FROM THE POWER THAT LIES
LATENT WITHIN YOU.
- ( pants )
PUSH THE RED BUTTON!
THEN GET HER
OUT OF HERE FAST.
- HUH?  HUH.
HUH?  COME ON.
- WHAT?  IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- ( Ryoko screams )
- ( groaning )
- ( grunting )
- ( screams )
- ACHIKA!
- ( strains )
- I CAN'T HOLD ON!
- IF I HAVE TO GO,
I WON'T GO ALONE.
- Achika: PLEASE NO!
- I'M LOSING MY GRIP.
- HANG ON, DAD!
HOLD ON TO HER!
DON'T LET HER GO!
- ( screams )
- ( all scream )
- FATHER!
MOTHER!
RYOKO!
STOP IT.
RYOKO, LET GO!
- TENCHI!
- I'VE GOT TO HELP THEM.
- TENCHI.
IT'S TOO LATE.
THEY'VE ALREADY BEEN
PULLED IN.
- LET ME GO TO THEM.
THEY NEED MY HELP!
MOTHER!
- ( wind rushes )
- HOW AWFUL,
AFTER WASHU'S EQUIPMENT
WORKED SO WELL.
- Washu: I NEVER IMAGINED
THAT WHEN WE SENT KAIN
INTO ANOTHER
SPACE-TIME CONTINUUM,
HE'D PULL LADY ACHIKA
IN WITH HIM.
- WASHU, ISN'T THERE
SOMETHING WE CAN DO
TO BRING MY MOTHER
AND FATHER BACK?
TELL ME, PLEASE.
- Washu:
I'M AFRAID NOT, TENCHI.
IT'S NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO DETERMINE
THE EXACT COORDINATES
INSIDE SUBSPACE .
SO WE HAVE NO ACCESS.
- NO ACCESS?
WASHU!
PLEASE TRY TO
BRING THEM BACK.
THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
PLEASE, WASHU,
OR THEY'LL DIE.
- ( wind rushes )
- ( gasps )
ACHIKA!
- Washu: WELL,
IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT WE CAN TRY TO TRANSFER
ACHIKA'S BRAIN WAVES
INTO TENCHI.
THEN RYOKO CAN TELEPORT
TO THOSE COORDINATES.
AND YOU CAN FOLLOW.
- Ayeka: WELL, WHAT
ARE WE WAITING FOR?
- Washu: YOU'RE FORGETTING
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING.
EVEN IF THIS DOES WORK,
YOU'LL STILL HAVE TO FACE KAIN
WHEN YOU GET THERE.
AND HE'S MORE POWERFUL
THAN ALL OF YOU COMBINED.
- ( screams )
- Ryoko: WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO DO THEN?
- ( rumbling )
- IT'S RISKY, BUT I'LL USE
THE DIMENSIONAL CANNON.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
THE DIMENSIONAL CANNON?
NOW, WAIT JUST A MINUTE,
MISS WASHU!
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
USE THAT CANNON
TO BLOW UP A WHOLE PLANET.
IT'S FOR TAKING OUT
A SMALL GALAXY.
- WE HAVE TO CONSIDER
WHO OUR OPPONENT IS.
IF WE DON'T DESTROY HIM
RIGHT NOW,
THERE'S NO TELLING WHEN
HE'LL FIND HIS WAY OUT OF
ALTERNATE SPACE-TIME AGAIN.
HEH-HEH.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE GONNA USE
AS POWERFUL
A WEAPON AS THAT.
- ( chuckling )
- Ayeka: CAN YOU PLEASE
SLOW DOWN, RYOKO?!
- OH, BE QUIET.  NORMALLY,
WE WOULDN'T EVEN NEED YOUR HELP.
TENCHI AND I COULD HANDLE
THIS ALONE, YOU KNOW.
- ALL YOU HAVE IS COMPLETELY
USELESS DESTRUCTIVE POWER.
- OH, WHAT A JOKE!
IF NOBOYUKI HADN'T BEEN
SUCKED INTO SUBSPACE ,
THEN WE WOULDN'T HAVE
NEEDED YOU AROUND ANYWAY.
- HELLO, MY LORD TENCHI,
IT'S SO WONDERFUL
TO SEE THAT YOU'RE HERE SAFE.
- MISS AYEKA,
I'M VERY SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
WHY, TO SAVE YOUR MOTHER,
I'D WALK THROUGH FIRE.
I'D SWIM THE DEEPEST OCEANS.
- ( nervous laugh )
- WHAT A BUNCH OF RUBBISH.
HEY, WASHU, WE'RE
READY TO TRANSFER.
- Washu: ROGER.
- IT'S HERE.
DIMENSIONAL CANNON IS
ARMED, AIMED, AND READY.
- OKAY, WE'RE ALL YOURS.
SO GO AHEAD, WASHU,
TAKE CONTROL.
- ROGER AND OUT.
RYOKO, GET SET.
IT'S UP TO YOU TO TELEPORT
TO THE PLACE
THAT TENCHI IMAGES
AFTER THE TRANSFER.
GOT IT?
- NO PROBLEM, WASHU.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
- THE POWER OF
THE SHIELD IS ONLY GOOD
FOR THREE MORE MINUTES.
BE SURE YOU GET EVERYTHING DONE
THAT YOU HAVE TO
WITHIN THAT TIME, OKAY?
- YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
- ( beeping )
- ( thunder crashing )
- ( static buzzes )
- ( gasps )
- ( groans )
- NOBOYUKI!
- ( chuckles )
- ( echoes )
REMEMBER, YOU PROMISED
YOU'LL COME AND SEE ME
IN THE HOUSE I BUILD.
WON'T YOU, ACHIKA?
- ( grunts )
- NOBOYUKI!
- ( coughs )
- ( strains, grunts )
NOBOYUKI!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( coughs )
- YOU AND I
WILL BUILD...
THAT BEAUTIFUL HOUSE
TOGETHER, RIGHT?
- OH, NOBOYUKI,
I KNOW WE WILL.
- ( moans )
- IT'LL BE OKAY.
THIS NIGHTMARE
WILL BE OVER SOON.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
I WILL NOT ALLOW THIS.
I WILL PAY YOU BACK!
- HUH?!  HUH?!
- BECAUSE FORGIVENESS
FOR ONE LIKE YOU
COULD NEVER BE AN OPTION.
- ( groans )
- TENCHI?
- AAH!
- WHOA.
- LORD TENCHI.
- I KNOW-- I CAN SEE HER.
SHE NEEDS MY HELP BADLY.
OH, MOTHER!
- HUH?
- ( cries )
( wails )
- TENCHI?
- YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD,
BUT NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
- ( screams )
( pants )
- ( chuckles )
IF I CAN'T DESTROY YOU,
I'LL ABSORB YOU.
( screams )
COME TO ME NOW!
- ( straining )
NOBOYUKI!
- ( laughing )
- NOBOYUKI!
NOBOYUKI!
HE'S TOO FAR AWAY.
- ( groaning )
- ( gasps )
( screaming )
- ( grunts )
- WE JUST MADE IT.
- HANG ON, NOBOYUKI.
- YOU ARE...
MY SON, TENCHI.
- Kiyone: TWO MINUTES LEFT.
AUTO-THROTTLE ON.
THE FIRST AND SECOND
SAFETY LOCKS ARE NOW OFF.
THE SHIELD IS LOSING POWER
AND FAST.
- WE'VE STILL GOT
A BIT OF POWER LEFT.
- Kiyone: AND TENCHI?
- I PRAY THAT HE CAN MAKE IT.
- ( gasps )
( growls )
( screaming )
( strains )
- Kiyone: MINUS 60 SECONDS.
OUR ENERGY LEVEL
IS AT MAXIMUM.
THE FINAL SAFETY
IS DISENGAGED,
BEGINNING FINAL COUNTDOWN.
HURRY UP, TENCHI,
AND GET BACK HERE.
- HMM.
- ( electrical charge )
- ( screams )
- ( roars )
( grunts ) OWW!
- Achika: TENCHI!
- ( laughs )
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
GO ON, RUN!
GET HER OUT OF HERE.
HURRY UP! ( screams )
- TENCHI!
- ( roaring )
- THERE'S NO TIME LEFT.
- THERE MUST BE.
- AHHH!
- ( roars )
- LADY ACHIKA?
- WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT?
SHE'S TENCHI'S MOTHER,
ALL RIGHT.
- ( growls )
- AHHH!
- WHAT IS THE SECRET
OF JURAI POWER?!
- ( sizzles )
- WHAT IS THIS?!
( grunts, groaning )
( screaming )
- ( grunts )
HYA!
( sighs )
- Ryoko: ACHIKA,
WE HAVE TO GO!
- HUH, RIGHT.
- LET'S HURRY.
- ( gasps, screams )
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?!
- THE JURAI
WILL NOT ESCAPE ME!
- KAIN'S BACK!
- INCOMING.
- ENGAGE!
- ( Kain screams )
( screaming echoes )
- KAIN'S GONE.
HE'S REALLY GONE?
- YES.
- LET'S GET GOING
AND QUICKLY.
TENCHI REALLY NEEDS HELP.
- TAKE CARE OF NOBOYUKI,
ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH.
OF COURSE.
- WHERE ARE SASAMI
AND MIHOSHI?
- WASHU TRANSFERRED
THEM BACK ALREADY.
- THE TOKYO TOWER'S A WRECK.
IS IT GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT?
- WASHU TOLD ME
THAT THE AUTHORITIES
WILL PROBABLY
CHALK THE WHOLE THING UP
AS AN UNEXPLAINED EVENT.
THE TOWER WAS DUE
FOR RENOVATION ANYWAY.
( screams )
- BOTH OF YOU PROMISE ME
YOU'LL TAKE CARE OF TENCHI.
ALL RIGHT?
- HMM?
- SO YOU KNEW?
- YES, THE POWER OF THE JURAI
OPENED MY EYES.
AND I SAW...
WHEN TENCHI
WILL NEED ME MOST,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO
BE THERE WITH HIM.
- OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
- HMM?
- ( grunts )
IT'S, UH, HERE.
- WITH KAIN GONE, THE TIME
STREAM'S RETURNED TO NORMAL.
HOWEVER, WE HAVE
TO ERASE YOUR MEMORY
OF EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
WHILE WE WERE HERE.
I'M SORRY.
- WAIT.
OH MY.
HERE.
- OH.
- I WANT YOU TO GIVE
THIS SWORD TO TENCHI.
I'M AFRAID HE'S GOING
TO NEED IT AGAIN SOMEDAY.
- LADY ACHIKA.
- TIME IS SHORT,
BUT NOBOYUKI AND I
WILL LIVE OUR LIVES
TO THE FULLEST.
I SWEAR.
THAT'S ALL THAT
REALLY MATTERS.
- TAKE CARE, LADY.
- THANK YOU ALL.
IT WAS GOOD
HAVING YOU HERE.
NOW, GOOD-BYE,
MY SON TENCHI.
- Tenchi: AND SO,
THE INCIDENT THAT OCCURRED
IN MY PARENTS' TIME
WAS RESOLVED.
MY MOTHER LOST THE POWER
THAT KAIN SO FEARED
AND 26 YEARS LATER,
IT PASSED TO ME.
THERE WAS ONLY ONE THING
ABOUT THIS AFFAIR
THAT TROUBLES ME.
THE POWER THAT MY MOTHER
DISPLAYED IN HER FIGHT WITH KAIN
WAS OBVIOUSLY THE POWER
OF THE HOUSE OF JURAI.
AND IN LOSING THAT POWER,
HER OWN LIFE MAY WELL
HAVE BEEN SHORTENED.
IRONICALLY,
THE JURAI POWER
SHE USED TO SAVE MY LIFE
WAS THE POWER THAT COULD HAVE
ENABLED HER TO LIVE LONGER.
I'M AWARE THAT THE PAST
CANNOT BE CHANGED,
BUT SOMETIMES
IT IS HARD TO ACCEPT.
- ( silent )
- Tenchi: I WISH I COULD
REACH BACK
AND UNDO WHAT
HAS BEEN DONE, BUT...
I MUST ACCEPT
WHAT I CANNOT CHANGE.
FORTUNATELY, I HAVE BEEN TOLD
THAT MY PARENTS WERE ABLE
TO SPEND THEIR
YOUNG YEARS TOGETHER,
HAPPILY DREAMING
AND PLANNING,
AND BUILDING
FOR THE FUTURE.
- ( baby cries )
- WELL, THE BABY'S FINE,
FORTUNATELY.
AND THEY SAY THAT ACHIKA
WILL BE OUT
OF THE HOSPITAL NEXT WEEK.
- HMM.
IS THAT SO?
- Noboyuki:
THE COMPANY HAS AGREED
TO LET ME
DESIGN A BUILDING.
I GUESS THEY'RE FINALLY
RECOGNIZING MY TALENTS.
- Katsuhito: IS THAT SO?
- Noboyuki: YOU KNOW, DAD,
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
REBUILDING THIS HOUSE
ONE OF THESE DAYS.
- Katsuhito: YOU DON'T SAY?
IS THAT SO?
- MY NEXT BIG PROJECT
IS TO BUILD THE DREAM HOUSE
ACHIKA AND I HAVE
ALWAYS WANTED.
BY THE WAY, DAD,
WE REALLY SHOULD THINK ABOUT
A NAME FOR THE BABY.
GOT ANY IDEAS?
- HMM?  LET ME THINK.
I NAME HIM TENCHI.
- ♪ SLEEP, SLEEP ♪
♪ SLEEP, TENCHI ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR LITTLE EYES
AND SLEEP, MY BABY ♪
♪ SLEEP, SLEEP, SLEEP. ♪
- Sasami: HEY!
- Washu: SHOVE OVER.
- Ayeka: STOP PUSHING--
- Washu: YOU SHOULD HAVE MOVED
WHEN I SAID SHOVE OVER.
- ( overlapping chatter )
- CAMERA'S READY, EVERYONE.
- Noboyuki:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.  SMILE!
- ( nervous laughter )
- ( film clicking )
- ( laughing )
- Achika: I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOUR DREAM HOUSE.
- Noboyuki: OUR DREAM IS STILL
VERY MUCH ALIVE EVEN NOW.
RIGHT, ACHIKA?
- Achika: YES.
TIME IS SHORT,
BUT NOBOYUKI AND I WILL
LIVE OUR LIVES TO THE FULLEST.
I SWEAR.
THAT'S ALL THAT
REALLY MATTERS.
- ( music plays )
- ♪ COME TO YOU
ACROSS THE DIVIDE ♪
♪ LOOKING OUT,
A WRINKLE IN TIME ♪
♪ THERE IS NOTHING LESS
I WOULD DO ♪
♪ THAN TO STAND UP
FOR TRUTH ♪
♪ IN THE COLD, DARK WAYS
OF THIS LONELY PLACE ♪
♪ I WILL WARM YOU ♪
♪ HOLD YOU ♪
♪ A GOLD SHIELD GLISTENS ♪
♪ AND YOUR
BREATH QUICKENS ♪
♪ I STAND CLOSE BY
OVER YOU ♪
♪ TWO HANDS HELD STRONG,
AND SHOW WITH ♪
♪ THE POWER OF ONE ♪
♪ REACHING OUT PAST THE WALLS
THAT CAN HOLD YOU ♪
♪ WE ARE GUARDIANS,
WARRIORS ♪
♪ COME FROM SOMEWHERE TO MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CREATES YOU AND SHAPES
THE ALCHEMY OF LOVE ♪
♪ THERE IS A CHAIN OF LIGHT ♪
♪ OUT ACROSS
THE ENDLESS SKIES ♪
♪ AND I SEE THE ENERGY ♪
♪ THAT REFLECTS
ME IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND KEEPS US BOTH ALIVE ♪
♪ EVENING AND THE SHADOWS
WILL COME ♪
♪ TO DESTROY WHAT
WE HAVE DONE ♪
♪ BUT ALWAYS WILL
THE POWER OF LOVE ♪
♪ SHINE A LIGHT
BRIGHT AS THE SUN ♪
♪ WHEN THE COLD, DARK WAVES
ON THE SHORES BREAK ♪
♪ I AM AROUND YOU ♪
♪ FOUND YOU ♪
♪ A GOLD SWORD FIRES ♪
♪ AND NIGHT EXPIRES ♪
♪ A LONG NIGHT
SURROUNDING YOU ♪
♪ TWO HANDS HELD STRONG,
AND SHOW WITH ♪
♪ THE POWER OF ONE ♪
♪ REACHING OUT PAST THE WALLS
THAT CAN HOLD YOU ♪
♪ WE ARE GUARDIANS,
WARRIORS ♪
♪ COME FROM SOMEWHERE TO MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CREATES YOU AND SHAPES
THE ALCHEMY OF LOVE ♪
♪ THERE IS A CHAIN OF LIGHT ♪
♪ OUT ACROSS
THE ENDLESS SKIES ♪
♪ AND I SEE THE ENERGY ♪
♪ THAT REFLECTS
ME IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND KEEPS US BOTH ALIVE ♪
♪ WHEN THE COLD, DARK WAVES
ON THE SHORES BREAK ♪
♪ I AM AROUND YOU ♪
♪ FOUND YOU ♪
♪ A GOLD SHIELD GLISTENS ♪
♪ AND YOUR BREATH QUICKENS ♪
♪ I STAND CLOSE BY
OVER YOU ♪
♪ TWO HANDS HELD STRONG
AND SHOW WITH ♪
♪ THE POWER OF ONE ♪
♪ REACHING OUT PAST THE WALLS
THAT CAN HOLD YOU ♪
♪ WE ARE GUARDIANS,
WARRIORS ♪
♪ COME FROM SOMEWHERE TO MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CREATES YOU AND SHAPES
THE ALCHEMY OF LOVE ♪
♪ TWO HANDS HELD STRONG
AND SHOW WITH ♪
♪ THE POWER OF ONE ♪
♪ REACHING OUT PAST THE WALLS
THAT CAN HOLD YOU ♪
♪ WE ARE GUARDIANS,
WARRIORS ♪
♪ COME FROM SOMEWHERE
TO MIND ♪
♪ WHAT CREATES YOU AND SHAPES
THE ALCHEMY OF LOVE ♪