Gah.
Man, what is up with this heat?
Come on, look at the
bright side, okay?
It could be freezing and we'd
have a bunch of dead vegetables.
Like our tomatoes and cukes.
Tomatoes and cukes
don't do well in the cold?
Nope. Low temps mess with
their growth and development.
It can cause them to
bruise super easily.
Didn't know that.
Wow. That's awful.
Do soybeans do well in the heat?
Yeah. They'll be fine.
When you were
planting them earlier,
I think I mentioned how
incredibly useful soybeans are.
But what I didn't tell you is
that they have a special power.
They do?
[KEI] Oh yeah. Hey Kousaku,
why don't you tell her
about the three
major nutrients in farming?
[KOUSAKU] Sure.
Well...
Nitrogen. Acid. And Potassium.
Of the three, nitrogen
is the most special.
[KOUSAKU] It's true. Without it,
crops won't grow properly.
Nitrogen.
Yes. The mighty power of
the super special soybean
lies in its ability to
make large quantities
of the nitrogen nutrient.
[RINGO] Hmm...
There's a lot of the stuff
just floating around in the air.
Soybeans can convert it
to usable compounds.
Or... To put it another way,
they make their own fertilizer.
Soy beans are... neato.
[KOUSAKU] It's July.
The hottest season is upon us.
Not to mention that our
agricultural lives
are heating up, too!
[MINORI] Alrighty then!
Here's to another hard day
of work out in the fields!
Whoa. What's the deal
with all this food?
[MINORI] Cucumbers, tomatoes,
eggplant, peppers, bitter melon,
okra, pumpkin,
zucchini, and corn!
We got bushels
of reject vegetables!
So we dine for free!
It's "all you can eat,"
time, you guys!
Awesome.
There are many valuable lessons
for a farming student
to learn about life. But the
most important lesson of all
is this:
[KOUSAKU] Is what?
Students must always
clean their plate!
No matter what!
Heck yeah. Think we've
got you covered there!
--[KOUSAKU] Dig in!
--[OTHERS] Bon appétit!
[GUY 3A]
What's wrong, Hata?
Minori cooked again, huh?
This looks like her handiwork.
Uh-oh. It's reject veggie
season again, isn't it?
Last year's melon festival
was a real mess, too.
Yeah! Those were the biggest
melons I'd ever seen!
Surprise, surprise,
Kousaku's blathering on
about useless nothings again!
[moos]
So big!
The biggest I've ever seen!
[KOUCHOU gasps]
[RINGO growls]
Uh. You know, I actually
sent you some nice,
juicy watermelons too, Ringo.
I made sure to pick out
the sweetest ones!
Yeah. I know, thanks.
Sure. No prob!
Wait. You know?
[MINORI] Here we are again!
At the end of a hard day
of work in the fields!
[KOUSAKU] Well, I guess being
stuck with too much food
is a first-world problem. Things
could be a lot worse, you know?
[MINORI] So true.
All the more reason we should
savor every single bite!
[ALL] Yeah!
Thank you for the grub!
[KOUSAKU] Wow! This cold
bitter melon salad is delicious!
[MINORI] Oh, you like that?
The secret ingredient
is a little chili oil
in the sesame dressing!
[RINGO] What is this stuff?
[MINORI] Pear curry!
[KOUSAKU] The crunchy texture
and mild sweetness
give this dish the
perfect one-two punch!
[KEI] Wow, this
ratatouille is richer
than a bunch of steamed veggies
have any right to be!
[RINGO] I'll have seconds!
[MINORI] Eat up, everybody!
There's plenty more
where that came from!
[KOUSAKU] Huzzah!
[RINGO] Yum, yum.
[KEI] Sweet!
Hey, what's the
matter with you?
Kei. Do you think
that we're getting fat?
I don't know.
Maybe we're just
packing on muscle
from all that harvesting.
[KOUSAKU]
That's totally what it is!
I thought I was looking a little
more filled-out than usual.
But it's probably
just my pythons!
[MINORI] Hey, you two!
Great meal. Right?
[KOUSAKU]
I was wrong! We're all fat!
So long to being trim and fit!
Say hello to obesity!
[KEI] Yep. We're chunky.
[MINORI] You're awful!
You know that's the worst thing
to say to a girl, right?
Sorry if I offended you,
maybe you'd prefer
I use a more
politically correct term
like "pleasingly plump"
or "fluffy?"
Here's the truth!
You two are fatties!
[BOTH] Huh?
He's right. You do look
a little bit rotund.
Oh yeah, well,
so do you. Fatty fat.
[gasps]
It's 'cause of those delicious
meals you make every day!
Wait just a sec!
If you don't want what I'm
cooking, then don't eat it!
Make me.
[BOTH grunt]
[KOUSAKU] Jack pot! A catfight,
every young man's
"dream come true!"
Well, at the very least, it's
a good sumo-wrestling match.
You remember that time
they mud-wrestled?
That was way cooler than this.
Seems they haven't learned
how to properly use size
to their advantage in a
hand-to-hand combat situation.
[KOUSAKU] Agreed.
[BOTH pant]
Lose weight! Right. Now!
We're skinny.
[STUDENTS cheer]
Exercise is the root of
any good weight loss plan.
Lucky for us, we have plenty of
opportunities to exercise here!
It's a good thing Miss
Kinoshita's back to normal, too.
[KEI] Well, that's a
former celeb for you.
Their freakish ability to
suddenly drop weight
puts us to shame.
Honestly, I was worried
about Minori the most.
That so? And what worried you?
Oh, don't play dumb with me.
You forget this?
Huh?
[squeals]
So, who was the
last fatty standing, huh?
[whimpers]
Tell me.
Tell me!
[MINORI] No one will marry me
'cause I look like
a marshmallow!
What am I gonna do?!
You're wrong,
guys won't want to marry you
'cause they'll assume
you're already pregnant.
[MINORI] You're so mean!
[KOUSAKU]
Has your family seen it yet?
I wonder what they would think
if someone were
to text them this?
[MINORI] No,
please don't do that.
Oops. It already sent.
[KEI gasps,
MINORU shrieks]
No! Jerk! You give that here!
I'm not joking!
You monster! You demon!
You nasty little ringworm!
[RINGO] Kousaku?
--Oh?
--Huh?
The soybeans.
There's something
really wrong with them.
This fuzzy white stuff
I've never seen
is growing near the root.
Huh. Mold, maybe?
If you give them too much
water they can get moldy.
Especially when the
weather's as hot as it's been.
[RINGO] But I've been
watering them every day.
Ah. Oh. Yikes.
It's true. I even watered
them when it rained.
Well. For future reference,
best to skip the stormy days.
But a little mold's
not that big of a deal.
We'll take care of it.
Hey. Let's go take a look
on our next break!
[KOUSAKU] Let's see.
See it?
[KOUSAKU] Whoa... No way!
Is it bad?
Ringo. Go get a teacher, please.
[gasps]
Hurry up.
[KOUSAKU] Southern blight.
Wait, I don't get it.
What is "southern blight?"
Will the plants be okay?
[KEI] Southern blight
is a terrible disease
that can sometimes
develop in soil.
Crops hit by this disease don't
survive. They just fade away.
[gasps]
[KEI] What's worse is that
blight forms sclerotia
in the ground, allowing it
to keep multiplying there.
What does that mean?
It means the disease
contaminates the soil.
[gasps]
[RINGO] How can we fix it?
[KOUSAKU] Can't be fixed.
If any of the spores remain...
...then they'll infect
next year's crop as well.
To prevent that, we have to
throw out the soil,
and the crops, too.
We burn them all.
[RINGO] That's awful.
[KOUSAKU] This whole mess is
pretty hard to believe, huh?
[KEI] It sure is.
Southern blight turned up
at another school recently.
Apparently, we both use
the same dealer.
If only we'd heard
about it earlier,
we might've been able
to do something.
Maybe... But Kei... you know
this isn't your fault. At all.
[KOUSAKU] Minori. How's Ringo?
Don't know, she said
she wanted to be alone.
[KOUSAKU] No dinner?
She said she wasn't hungry,
so I set some food aside.
Kousaku?
Huh?
[MINORI] I think
she needs your help.
Talk to her. I'm worried
she's taking this on herself.
If she'll listen to anybody,
it's you. Please.
--[KOUSAKU] I don't know.
--Well, guess what?! I do!
Because that girl is--
[gasps]
[MINORI] Just go talk to her,
please. She needs you.
Ringo. It's me.
So look. Farming
can be really fun.
It can be one of the greatest
gifts that life has to offer.
But... at the same time
it can be really brutal.
That's why so many people quit,
'cause it's too difficult.
We work so hard for so little.
It's not like we're gonna
get rich doing this.
Sometimes we don't
even get paid.
[RINGO] Then why?
If the bad outweighs the good,
then why do it at all?
[KOUSAKU] Good question.
My answer is, "I don't know".
I guess I haven't figured
that part out just yet.
[MINORI] How'd it go?
[KOUSAKU] I'm not really sure.
Oh...
Well, it's like they say,
"time is the best remedy."
[sighs]
[KEI] Kousaku?
[KOUSAKU] Hm? What's up?
I wanted her to plant those
soy beans for a reason.
It wasn't a random choice.
In the same way
they enrich the soil
and give life to new things,
I hoped those beans
might help her.
That her soul
might be enriched.
And that she
might also be born anew.
That's really thoughtful.
Yes, it's just that... if she
were to regret coming here,
I don't think I could stand it.
Kei?
Yeah, what is it?
You're nice. And I'm lucky
to have a friend like you.
Same here.
Oh yeah, this is good stuff!
A deep, forbidden friendship
reveals its true nature
in a secluded greenhouse!
We can call it--[censor beep]
I'll even put out a fan book!
What?
[KOUSAKU and KEI gasp]
If we sell one thousand
of these bad boys
at five hundred a pop,
we'll be filthy stinking rich.
Who wants to buy a yacht?
This isn't really in character
for me, but I'm here.
I had a feeling my
services might be needed
and looks like I was right.
Hello there, my darlings.
Did someone say forbidden love?
I heard that phrase
and came as fast as I could!
[KOUSAKU] Uh, what's going on?
Does somebody want to tell me
what you guys are doing here?
What are these for?
Duh. That's advance
payment for the footage.
Miso and a mountain lily?
Wait, are these for Ringo?
Uh. Yeah right!
[RINTAROU] "Ringo?
Of course they're not for Ringo,
why would they be?
It's not like we're too
embarrassed to give it to her
directly or anything!"
[RINTAROU fake cries]
Great! Now they know the truth,
you idiotic woodsman!
That was, by far, the
weirdest thing
that's ever happened
to me in my whole life.
Kei?
I actually think Ringo
will be just fine.
Don't you?
Yeah.
Kousaku. You're awake.
This is bad.
Yeah. Let's get Minori.
Ringo too.
[KEI] I called everybody
I could think of.
This is everyone who showed.
[RINGO] What happened?
What are we doing up?
We're here to pick
some tomatoes.
But it's so late.
Let's just hope
it's not too late.
Huh?
Come on.
Look.
[RINGO] They're splitting open.
It's been nothing but
hot and dry outside.
All this time, these tomatoes
have needed water.
[KOUSAKU] Now that it's raining.
The tomatoes will take in
as much water as they can.
They'll split right open.
Where am I needed?!
[KEI] Start with
that row over there!
[KOCHOU] Right away!
Focus on the ones
that haven't split yet!
[STUDENTS] Yes, sir!
[MINORI] We can still
eat the bad ones.
We'll just puree them, or make
them into jam, can them.
Keep on hustling, people!
[RINGO] I don't get it.
Why does everyone
seem okay with this?
You raised them so carefully and
waited so long for them to grow.
And now they're
completely ruined.
I don't understand why
you aren't more upset.
Hey. You got a sec?
[KOUSAKU] I like it out here.
Though you must really think
we're out in the sticks, huh?
You know....
I like it too, actually.
So much nature...
I'm glad.
[KOUSAKU] But...
There's no natural nature.
Not in anything you see
out here, anyway.
[RINGO] Hm?
[KOUSAKU] The fields, the farms.
The roads and the rivers.
People made them all,
bit-by-bit
and generation-by-generation.
Our predecessors had it hard.
There was a time when nature was
cruel and unforgiving to them.
And it's not just here.
Everywhere we humans live
is the remains of the great
struggle between us and nature.
A battleground.
[RINGO] Battleground?
Yep.
You know, there's a whole lot
that's hard about agriculture.
But at the end of the day, it's
more fun than anything else.
Just getting to watch
your crops grow.
And the same goes
for the people who made this.
It must have been joyful.
They pictured the kind of town
this was going to become.
They dreamed about us,
here in the distant future.
And with all that to look
forward to, they worked hard.
And who knows?
Maybe our vegetables
will inspire someone.
Maybe one day they'll
do something great.
And maybe they'll make
the world a better place
for us to live in.
But even if they don't...
Even if they decide to just
keep on doing their best.
Well, I think that ties into the
future of the landscape, too.
You asked why I do this?
'Cause I think we can
help people be better.
There's real power in what
we do. That's why.
I'm sorry.
That story went off the rails
pretty quick, didn't it?
[RINGO] It was you.
Huh?
The veggies. You were the
one who sent them to me.
Huh?
Back then, I was so
exhausted with my life.
It was like I didn't even
have the strength to eat.
Then someone on my staff
made me a salad
out of vegetables
a fan had sent me.
Even though I was
too tired to eat,
I figured I had to
at least try it.
But when I put it in my mouth,
what happened next
took me by surprise.
It tasted strange.
Not like what I expected.
It tasted bad?
No. Not bad. It was very earthy.
And tough in an odd way.
But somehow gentle and sweet.
Well, it wasn't that
big of a deal,
I just wanted to send you
some vegetables.
No. It was perfect.
It really was.
You'd given me
the taste of life.
You shared something I
never experienced before.
It brought me to tears.
In that moment,
I knew I'd be okay.
It was like someone was saying,
"If you trust this feeling,
and follow your heart,
everything will be fine."
Don't you see?
You helped me.
You helped me make my choice.
After that.
I happily ate every single scrap
of food you sent my way.
I looked forward to the letters
that came with them too.
From the moment we started
writing each other,
I knew beyond a
shadow of a doubt
that I wanted to come here.
It was like I could taste
how fun it was going to be.
Wait a sec.
Huh?
I... I didn't send
you any letters.
But... those vegetables
were definitely you.
Yeah, but I didn't put
my name on the box.
And no letters.
No, you... You signed them.
Those letters were
definitely from you.
And there was a picture
of everybody, too.
[KOUSAKU] A picture?
[KOUSAKU] This picture?
With a letter from me?
[KOUSAKU gasps]
The tomato tragedy is over!
I'd say it's time we had
ourselves some dinner!
--Hm?
--[KEI] Huh?
Uh... You guys...?
Dinner's a good thing,
so why do you look so stern?
Is everything alright?
There's something
I'd like you to see, Minori.
[gasps]
[KOUSAKU] Does this look
familiar? You wrote it.
How could you do
something like this, huh?!
Writing a bunch of
fake letters to Ringo?!
I mean, to Yuka Kusakabe,
pretending to be me!
[MINORI] I thought
you'd be thrilled!
Huh?
I was only trying
to help you keep
your super "creepazoid" factor
down to a minimum.
You should thank me!
But... Mm... Well.
That's thoughtful.
I guess...
Anonymously sending a girl
you don't even know
a bunch of vegetables for no
good reason,
that's a one-way ticket
to restraining order town!
[KOUSAKU] I think you're
missing the point here!
Just think how Ringo must feel
knowing all those letters
she read are actually
from you and not from me!
[MINORI] Hmm...
You've got a point.
Huh?
I am very sorry, Kinoshita.
I hate that I mislead you.
I only wanted to help.
To paint a picture of what
things are really like here.
But I see now
that I was wrong.
Okay. Stand up.
I wanted to meet you.
This whole time...
It was you...
Uh... Kinoshita?
[RINGO] All I ever wanted was
to look you in the eyes
and talk to you.
About school,
agriculture, all of it.
The way you did in your letters.
I wanted it more than
you could possibly know.
So, you're not upset?
Of course not.
[MINORI] I pretended
to be somebody else.
I lied to you.
But what you wrote
was true.
That counts for
something, right?
And besides...
If we're being real,
it's not like I was
entirely truthful either.
We're even. Truce?
What do you say?
Yeah, sure.
I guess we're all kind
of similar in some ways.
[BOTH giggle]
[KOUSAKU sighs]
[RINGO] Hey. Can I
call you "Minnopio?"
[MINORI] Sure!
I don't mind that as long as
I can call you "Ringotchi!"
[RINGO] I'd like that!
--Awesome!
--Minoppio.
I sure love you.
I like where this is headed.
Kinoshita's happy again,
mysteries have been solved,
and all's well.
Looks like a
fairy tale ending to me.
Well, I think
this is the worst!
Happily ever after, my ass!
[AKARI] Cooking Granny.