[KOUSAKU]
Summer's in full swing!
We're talking puffy white
clouds, cicada's buzzing,
the whole bit.
[chuckles] Nice!
Dressed to impress!
That's how it's done!
This doesn't make me
look dorky?
No, not at all.
[MINORI] Uh, excuse me.
Eh?
Well, do I look
adorable or what?
You definitely
look something.
Uh-huh. Say it.
I have a glow.
[KOUSAKU] Or a bun in the oven.
[MINORI sighs] Same thing.
Wow, just imagine.
The outfit might get people
thinking that you and me are--
[yelps]
Oh dear. Careful.
With a butt like that
you've got to pay attention
to your center of gravity.
Might help a little if
you didn't shove me!
Alrighty. Train's about
to leave. So, yeah.
[KOUSAKU] With Kei and Yoshida
doing their thing abroad
over the summer break, I thought
it'd fun to take Ringo along
with Minori and me for a visit
back home to the boonies.
But, oh man, was there ever
a perfect storm brewing.
Would I live to tell the tale?
Your guess is as good as mine!
[KOUSAKU]
The Nagaragawa Railway.
Naga Rail for short.
Run these days by a third-tier
public transit company,
it picks up where the old
Etsumi South Line left off.
[MINORI] Okay, this rice is
perfect for mealtime
on the rails.
[KOUSAKU] Mm. Very tasty.
So, uh, exactly how far out
is your hometown?
Oh, it's in the
middle of nowhere.
But, Minori's family's nice.
Give Ringo the rundown
on your three sisters.
Tsukasa's the oldest,
then I came along.
The two youngest are twins:
Takumi and Akin.
[RINGO] Cool.
Ah, Tsukasa. Hey, uh...
So she moved back home
not that long ago, right?
What was she doing?
Ahh... Little of this,
little of that.
You know, whatever keeps
a gal like her busy.
Heh. Guess the old crowd
didn't nickname her
"The General" for nothing.
It's weird she
came back, though.
Figured she'd still be
out there blazing a trail.
Uh-oh. Stay still!
[WAKA squeaks]
So... Some special reason
he's along for the ride?
Gee. I don't know, uh...
Little fella gets super lonely
when you're not around,
and he's got kind of a
sixth sense for where you are.
[sighs] Whatever. You're
keeping tabs on him, though.
Far as this trip's concerned,
he's your mess.
[MINORI] Mm-hmm!
In you go, love.
Make yourself at home.
[WAKA squeaks]
Uh. Okay. What the...?
[MINORI] I made a special
pouch for him in there.
Awkward. Now you
really do look preggers.
[MINORI giggles]
[ANNOUNCER A]
Attention passengers,
if you peek out your
window right now,
you'll see we're passing over
the First Nagara River Bridge.
So cool.
Check it out,
they're waving! Ha!
C'mon, you too.
Uh, okay.
[laughing
[BOY] Hello!
Hey, Kousaku?
Huh?
You know... I've been on
my share of trains and stuff,
but this one's
probably my favorite.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Next stop, Aioi.
Thank you for choosing
Nagaragawa Railway.
We hope you have a pleasant day.
[RINGO] Where's the attendant?
[KOUSAKU] Oh there isn't one.
The station's unmanned.
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[BOTH] Bubba! Sissy!
[MINORI laughs]
[TWINS] Welcome back!
[KOUSAKU] Taku and Aki!
Someone's been
eating their vegetables!
Hey! How come Sissy's
got such a big tummy?
Now, now. Don't poke.
She's carrying
precious cargo in there,
not just her usual roll of fat.
Ha! Well, well!
You just couldn't
stay away, huh?
[MINORI] Oh, hey Tsukasa!
Whoa! We're getting a ride
from The General herself?
You eat a watermelon
on the train?
Wait...
Am I crazy or is the middle
child sporting a motherly glow?
Knock if off, Sis. Jeepers.
You're going to embarrass me
in front of everybody.
Don't be so self-conscious.
You look absolutely fabulous.
Thank you. [giggles]
You've filled out a
bit, too, Kousaku.
How're things?
Finer than frog hair
split four ways.
Frog hair?
Oh, country-folk jibber-jab.
Welcome to the sticks, Ringo.
This is how we do.
No standing on ceremony.
You'll be just fine.
How do you know my name?
Ha! We're all up in
everybody's business here.
Right. Load up and climb in!
Time's wasting, fam's waiting.
Heh. Tiger gets shotgun.
Seriously?
Aunt Hisako, Uncle Kiichi.
What are we doing here again?
Exchanging engagement gifts!
Oh, yeah? Who's engaged?
Good one.
You and Minori, my boy!
[screams]
Sister. I thank you. My heart--
Miiinoooriii!!
Sorry, the jig is up! I get
why you dragged me out here!
Wakadana has a sixth sense, huh?
Oh-ho, motherly glow, eh?
You are absolutely
the worst kind of person!
[MINORI giggles] Darling,
please, save it for later!
No time like the
present for truth!
[MINORI screams]
[KIICHI] Minori!
[KIICHI yells]
[HISAKO]
What in heaven's name is that?!
[KOUSAKU]
It's a wallaby from school!
But she?
Young lady!
What is the meaning of this?
[wails] I caved
under the pressure
to give you
grandchildren, okay?!
[TSUKASA]
I see what you did there.
[TSUKASA] Let me give you
some sisterly advice, Hondo.
Next time you want us all
to think you're expecting
a visit from the stork, make
sure the proud papa-to-be
is in on the scam. You know
this is pathetic, right?
Yeah...
[WAKA squeaks]
Well, what I'd like to know
is how you all fell for it
in the first place!
I mean, how could you
possibly think me and her
were going to be parents?
How gullible can you be?
[KOUSAKU] Sorry!
Never mind about that!
The thing is, though...
What's the big rush?
--[TSUKASA] Kousaku.
--Ma'am?
Here's the deal. I'm getting
a non-profit off the ground.
This here town needs it.
Uh... Oh yeah?
We're calling it "Turn A!"
Do what now?
In city talk, coming
back to the country
is a U-turn, or,
sometimes, an I-turn.
But I'm thinking alpha.
A-turn is sort of clumsy
in practice, though.
So I "turned it around" and
there you have it:
coming back to your roots!
See, "A" also stands for Aioi!
[KOUSAKU groans]
Deal is, the town's about to put
on it's first full-fledged
Turn-A extravaganza.
I banked on you
two getting hitched
being the big draw
that brings in the crowds.
Huh? How so?
[ALL] A mixer?
You bet! Two hundred
upwardly mobile singles
mingling together over
country-fried hors d'oeuvres
right here in Aioi!
[BOTH] Hm!
And you two were
gonna be the big focus.
Young couple in love makes good
-our own farm-raised success!
Couple?
In love?
Whoaaa!
You first locked eyes in Aioi.
married in Aioi, live in Aioi,
work and play in Aioi,
and are about to be one baby
into rearing a family in Aioi.
You two'll be the ideal
PR centerpiece
for what this mixer's
meant to accomplish!
[chuckles, grunts]
I've got morning sickness.
[TSUKASA]
Here's the plan, chief:
you're going to get my sister
in a family way, pronto.
You're practically engaged as it
is, so what the hey, right?
Yes!
Come on, boy!
Think of the village!
The village!
This is crazy!
How am I supposed to just--?
Look, kid: we borrowed a lot
of dough to make this happen.
If the mixer gets called off,
we're a million in the hole.
In other words, I'd be happy to
help my community any way I can.
Yeah! Let's get
this party started!
[ALL] Yeah!
[TSUKASA]
We'll seal your engagement
at the community center!
--[KIICHI] Young couple!
--[HISAKO] Young love!
[TWINS cheer]
[MINORI]
This is gonna be great!
We're going to be
so friggin' happy!
[OLD FOLKS cooing, murmuring]
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Man, what a crazy day.
Um, where's Ringo?
I put her up in the guestroom.
Poor dear was exhausted.
I'll bet.
Guess today was a pretty
big shock to her system, too.
Don't worry, though.
I've got a bed ready for you.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah?
[HISAKO] Takes you back,
doesn't it? In you go!
Crap! [grunts]
[HISAKO] Sweet dreams,
future son-in-law!
[KOUSAKU] You locked the door?
What if I have to pee?
[MINORI giggles]
Memory lane, huh?
Remember back in the day
how you'd always wet the bed?
[KOUSAKU] Gee, thanks.
Damn. Should've known.
Towns like this...
There's nothing they
won't do to counteract
the declining birthrate!
I'm essentially breeding
stock to these people!
So, uh, you know...
I have kind of a suggestion
to make if you're open to it.
It's actually a swell idea.
Oh, yeah? Go on.
Well, uh... If you...
I mean, you and me...
Made, you know, like a baby...
My folks would get off our back.
So...?
What?
What?!
What?!!
[MINORI]
Just think about it for a sec.
They're really only rushing us
'cause there ain't
no babies around.
If we got started
making them one,
they'd change their tune
in a heartbeat, right?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah!
Not the problem! Forget it!
That is not a
viable solution, period!
Aw, c'mon, Kousaku!
You like kids, don't you?
Yeah? Don't be a grump.
Look at you.
You'd be a great dad
and you know it.
In fact, our kid'd probably
be your spitting image.
Wouldn't that be
super-duper cute?
You're... You're serious.
Of course I am.
Hey, remember when your
parents first brought you over?
We were little.
I can see it like
it was yesterday.
There you were,
hiding behind your mom and dad,
not looking up at me even once.
[KOUSAKU] What did
you expect? I was scared.
We'd just up and moved
on a whim.
I had no idea what was going on.
[MINORI] I know. It's just...
The expression on your face
always stuck with me,
kind of like you were halfway
between tears and a tantrum.
See, I knew right then that
I could never leave you alone.
--[KOUSAKU gasps]
--You need me.
Or someone, at least.
Might as well be me.
Thing is, I want
to be there for you.
Look... We... I...
[BOTH] Bubba!
--[TAKUMI] Bubba!
--[AKINA] Sissy!
We want to sleep here
with you tonight!
Uh... Sure! Why not? Eh?
Yeah! Cool beans!
We'll have a slumber party.
Just like the old days.
[TWINS] Yay!
[KOUSAKU yawns] Good morning.
[MINORI]
Good morning, my darling Koutan!
[MINORI, KOUSAKU] Back after
while, Tsukasa and me
are making arrangements
for the wedding.
[KOUSAKU] Your Loving Wife.
The-They're really going to go
through with this, aren't they?!
[RINGO] Morning.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
Oh, hey! Morning!
Did, uh, you sleep okay?
Where's the gang?
Huh? Oh. The day starts
super early on a farm.
Hey, uh.
What would you say to me
giving you a little tour?
[RINGO] Cool.
[RINGO] Everybody's so hard
at work already.
[KOUSAKU] If there's one hard
and fast rule in the country,
it's get your work in
while the weather's nice.
Uncle Kiichi lives by that.
He's always the first one up.
Also the last guy
to call it a day.
One of his prize-winning
tomatoes. Here, try a bite.
Good, right?
He uses a special technique
and everything.
Too bad he won't be able to pass
it down to future generations.
Wait. He can't?
[KOUSAKU sighs] Not a lot of
people left in rural places
like this. The old ways
have been on the down swing
for a while now.
[RINGO] I wonder...
What do you think came first,
the chicken or the egg?
Are people leaving 'cause
farming's not popular,
or is it the other way around?
Maybe farming's losing its
appeal for people
'cause so many farmers
are calling it quits?
[KOUSAKU gasps]
If there was a way to
make it all attractive again,
people would start moving back
out to the country in droves.
[KOUSAKU]
Make farming attractive.
That must be what
Tsukasa is trying to get at.
Can't really blame the girl
for trying, huh?
[MAYOR] You know
Kiichi's oldest daughter?
Well, just like that,
she's back,
stirring up all manner of
heaven only knows what.
That's the union chief
and the mayor.
[UNION CHIEF] Oh, I heard.
"The General" thinks she can
bring in a lot of new blood.
Like they won't pick up and
leave at first sign of trouble.
[MAYOR] Remember that
family came up from the city
once upon a time?
Hata, I think the name was?
[UNION CHIEF]
It'll be that all over again.
[MAYOR] What's the verdict
on Kiichi's girl?
[UNION CHIEF]
She abandoned ship once.
Stands to reason
she'll do it again.
Guarantee you her enthusiasm
won't survive the month.
Well now, if you ask me,
that's being right generous.
What did they mean
"it'll be that all over again?"
Kousaku, I want to
see your house.
I'm talking to you!
[KOUSAKU]
There's nothing to see.
[KOUSAKU] It's there,
it's just not a house anymore.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
[KOUSAKU]
Can we not go there, please?
It's not a pleasant story.
Jerk.
Uh?
Huh?
So Minori would know
what you were talking about.
But you won't
"go there" with me?
It's totally unfair.
[KOUSAKU] My parents got the
farming bug when I was little.
Thought it was the
end all be all.
One day they just up
and moved here.
Hauled stakes from the
big city with me in tow.
Only took them a
season to figure out
they'd bitten off more
than they could chew.
What happened?
In so many words...
The tomato crop they
were banking on failed.
Put 'em in so much, debt they
couldn't get out from under it.
To make ends meet,
Mom took a part-time job.
Dad was always off
somewhere away from home
trying to scare up capital.
[KOUSAKU]
That was the big irony.
The more they tried
to salvage the farm,
the less they could be here
to tend the damn thing.
When Mom buckled
under the stress
and had a nervous breakdown, Dad
travelled further and further
away from home to try to
scrounge up money
for medical bills.
Eventually I saw him
less and less, until...
Till what?
[KOUSAKU] Till the morning
Mom's poor old heart
finally gave out.
[gasps]
[KOUSAKU] That's when Dad
said to hell with the farm
and left Aioi for good.
Haven't seen him since.
Yeah, so... In come
Uncle Kiichi and Auntie Hisako,
who took me under their
wing an raised me as their own.
And Minori?
Huh?
Wha-What is she to you?
Well. I...
[TAKUMI]
Bubba! Whatcha doin'?
[KOUSAKU] Showing my pal
Ringo here the sights.
This is the best view
in the village.
[TAKUMI] I want to show you
how many exercise stamps
I've collected!
[AKINA] Me, too! Look,
I have a whole big bunch!
Good morning.
[KOUSAKU] Hm? Hey.
Come on, where are
your manners, guys?
[TAKUMI] Ah...
Are you a princess?
'Cause you...
you look like one.
[gasps] Yeah.
Seriously?
How come?
Why's a real, live princess
staying in a house like ours?
--Oh, uh--
--It's summer vacation.
Princesses get
summer vacation, too?
[RINGO] Mm-hmm.
Wait, but... What country
are you princess of?
It's, uh...
It's called Yukatania.
[TAKUMI] Where's that?
Well it's kind of in the
heart of your awesome
grown-up friend here.
[gasps] Do you have, like,
a job there and stuff?
I'm responsible for
all the cuteness.
[TWINS gasp]
Can I be the person who
carries the back of your dress
when you walk?
Me, too! Me, too!
I can't think of
anybody better.
[TWINS] Yay!
Your Highness! You have to
see something really cool!
--[AKINA] Watermelon!
--[KOUSAKU] Whoa, hold up.
[RINGO giggles]
♪
The little ones have sure
taken a shine to our guest.
--[TAKUMI] She's a princess!
--[AKINA] We're her retainers!
Is that a fact now?
Hey, uh, when you're
done with that,
I'd love to show
you a sending off.
A what?
So where are we going?
To the river.
What's there to do down there?
What's there to do?
Float paper lanterns downstream!
It's a "Sending Off" ceremony!
Let me! I want to
put one in by myself!
Me, too!
Now, now kiddos.
Careful where you step.
Don't fall in.
[MINORI]
I've got this, thank you.
Now, the important part:
Say goodbye to your ancestors.
They gotta hear you.
[TWINS] Safe journey!
Wow...
We can move to a
better spot if you want.
[KOUSAKU] I know a place
with a way better view.
Gorgeous!
[KOUSAKU] Cool.
Thought you'd like it.
[RINGO] Do the lanterns
make it to the ocean?
[KOUSAKU] Nah. There's a
big net just after the bend.
They'll collect them all
tomorrow morning.
[KOUSAKU] Sorry. Kind of
takes the magic out of it, huh?
No, not really.
[KOUSAKU] That's country life.
[KOUSAKU] The real magic
is in seeing it from far away.
Close up, sometimes it's easy
to feel like an outsider,
hard to know where you fit in.
Sorry I got all weird with you
about my folks...
I should've told you before.
I wonder.
It's tough here.
And I know farming's
not for everyone.
But... so what?
Give me this view and
the clean air any day.
The water's fresh,
the mountains are close,
and the food is delicious.
Plus any village that raised you
must be wonderful.
♪ Now that summer's here our
hearts indulge the weather ♪
♪ Quietly we sit together, ♪
♪ Our hands entwined,
the stars up above; ♪
♪ Oh, please let me
be selfish, my love. ♪
♪ Let me see desire move you ♪
♪ When you glimpse me
in my brand new ♪
♪ bathing suit, pool side ♪
♪ Instead of this
uniform--why hide? ♪
♪ This moment's
for you and me, ♪
♪ So before we say goodbye ♪
♪ Let me lay bare
what I need courage to share ♪
♪ With a special guy... ♪
♪ Timidly on my cell phone... ♪
Just so you know, that was me.
Not Yuka Kusakabe...
But the real me.
[CAST]
Everybody's No-Rin.
[WAKA squeaks]