[NATSUMI] Oh, I see...
You want to know if
the new transfer
is the girl of your dreams, eh?
Adorable.
[NATSUMI] Wait for it...
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI]
Miss Becky!
It's not so simple
as yes or no.
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI]
Please, you're killing us!
[GUY A] So, Yukatan.
That is who you are, right?
[GUY B]
You'll have to excuse him.
What he means is,
you're that singer chick, right?
Not really.
Why you slumming it
in this dive?
I don't know.
[GUY C] Uh, all-righty then.
Truth is:
The new girl was pop
sensation Yuka Kusakabe,
but now she goes by
Ringo Kinoshita.
[KOUSAKU] Called it!
--[NATSUMI] Not so fast!
--[KOUSAKU] Huh?
[NATSUMI] It's safe to
assume she enrolled here
under a new name to put the
billboard days behind her.
Ah. I get it.
So, no bringing up
her past then.
Right.
But...
Come on!
Don't translate that to mean
"avoid her altogether."
The poor dear needs
help adjusting!
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You want us to help this Ringo,
whatever-her-name is, fit in?
[NATSUMI] It'll be perfect!
She's in the same dorm
as you all.
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI] What?
Plus you have the same major
and you're in the same class.
Oh, wow. How intelligent of me!
Let me get this straight:
We'll be attached at the hip?
So, like, on the farm?
And-And in the classroom?
And where 'at the hip'
can be taken literally?!
I'm dreaming this, aren't I?
[NATSUMI] No, it's real.
[screaming]
[KOUSAKU] Nosebleed!
[KOUSAKU] Pleased to
meet you, Miss Yukata--!
Uh, sorry, I mean:
Miss Kinoshita.
Ha. I'm Kousaku
Hata, so, uh, hi.
--[WAKA squeaks]
--Right, right.
Give me a sec.
This is my friend.
Wakadanna.
Or... Young Master.
[WAKA squeaks]
Anyway.
Let me be the first to welcome
you to Tamo No-Rin,
where everyone's
a team player!
Is he talking like a
recruiter or is it just me?
Um, I think he's trying
to sound smart.
[KOUSAKU] Tour-time!
There'll be a quiz
afterwards-not really.
This is the main building.
Classes are divided up
by department.
[KOUSAKU] Here we have the gym.
[KOUSAKU] The complex of
buildings to our right
has kind of a tricky name.
We call it the Industrial
Promotion Building.
Bit of a mouthful, huh?
[KOUSAKU] There's the Green
Shop, like the sign says.
That's where we sell all
of our vegetables and stuff.
I know.
[KOUSAKU] Uh... Ah, cool.
[PEACOCK A cries]
A cat?
Uh...
No, that'd be a peacock.
[PEACOCK A caws]
[PEACOCK B cries]
[RINGO] It's so drab.
Oh. Right, I get you.
See when we think of a peacock,
we think of the males.
In nature,
it's the guys who have to
deck themselves out.
Girls are... Drab.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[KOUSAKU] Nice move,
doofus! You're losing her!
[KOUSAKU]
This is the Wallaby House.
It's where Wakadana lives.
[WAKA squeaks]
[KOUSAKU]
Heated flooring, AC...
It's actually a lot
nicer than our dorms.
[WAKA squeaks]
So, Wakadana's not a kangaroo?
Well, they are similar,
but not quite the same.
So, uh...
Yeah.
If you're interested, I could
tell you about how Wakadana
and me became buddies
back in the day.
[WAKA squeaks]
He didn't used to be
attached to us.
But then one night, actually,
it was Christmas just last year.
Either 'cause he was tired
of being cooped up
or just couldn't sleep,
the little fella got out
and wandered around in
the snow until, well,
until it got to be
too much for him.
[KOUSAKU] Luckily, I was
wandering around myself
and found him.
Took him to my room
as fast as I could.
[WAKA squeaks weakly]
[KOUSAKU] He slept cuddled
up next to me inside my...
Uh... Inside a big pillowcase.
We've been pals ever since.
When he gets bored,
he comes over to hang out
with me and the gang.
Pretty heartwarming story, huh?
[KOUSAKU whimpers]
[KOUSAKU yells]
Continuing the tour!
Feast your eyes on that!
That's what quality
poultry looks like
when it's too good
for plebeians!
The three breeds of
locally raised poultry are:
Hinai, Nagoya Cochin,
and the superlative Satsuma.
Less famous, perhaps,
but of equal merit
is the poultry raised here in
our very own Gifu prefecture
submitted for your
unqualified appraisal.
[MINORI] Very nice. Let's eat!
Well done. Thank you.
Why...
Don't speak to me as
though my self-esteem
as an animal
husbandry specialist
hinges on your approval!
Consider yourself
blessed that I deign
to let you sample
my wares at all!
She's so mean. Why?
I beg your pardon?!
If you're trying to insinuate
that I have unrequited feelings
for Kei, you're barking up
the wrong tree!
That's not to suggest I haven't
a modicum of respect
for the man.
But I regard him
primarily as a rival!
Uh, any chance
I can have some eggs?
[KOCHOU gasps]
Vulgarian...
[KOUSAKU] Let me ask you.
Between fertilized
and unfertilized,
which kind of egg is more, I
guess, you know,
better for you?
[KOCHOU] Moron!
How do you call yourself an
Ag Major and sleep at night?!
Nutritionally, there is
no difference between the two.
That said, let there be no
question that eggs produced
by caged fowl, when
compared to those produced
by the free-range variety,
are enormously less delectable.
Sorry. Thanks for explaining.
Hey.
"Unfertilized egg" means what?
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[RINGO] Look.
I'm from the city, okay? I don't
know the first thing about eggs.
Wow, that is seriously adorable!
This stuff is so... boring.
No!
Anyway...
Unfertilized, means?
Well, I, uh...
Give me a sec to explain!
Okay, I'm not going to lie:
I don't even know where
to start on this one.
What are you talking about?
You know this: just start
from the beginning.
[KOUSAKU] Look at her!
She's too delicate!
This is down and dirty stuff
she's asking about.
I can't just go there.
Oh, spare me!
It's a clinical matter.
Be clinical. The principle's
the same for plants.
Think, pistil and stamen.
[KOUSAKU] What I think is that
she ought to hear it
from another girl.
[KOCHOU] Fine!
Behold, rookie!
[RINGO] Yeah?
If you would, madam.
Your undivided attention.
[KOUSAKU] Yes!
An unfertilized egg
is essentially an egg
wearing a condom!
[NATSUMI]
The first order of business
when it comes to Agriculture
is record keeping.
That's the last time
I ask Fun Bags
to explain anything to anyone.
Sweetie, you've heard
the phrase
"putting all your eggs
in one basket," yes?
[RINGO] Fertilizing them?
No, not exactly.
What I'm getting at here
is the importance of
playing fast and loose!
[KOUSAKU screams]
[NATSUMI] What the experts say
about the same-old, same-old
is true. For example: When a
grown man practices monogamy.
Yeah, right.
His wife--
Whoa, there!
Kind of an inappropriate
example, don't you think?
[NATSUMI] What? She's a girl.
She needs to know.
You might be going off
on a tangent.
[NATSUMI] The point
I'm getting at is,
when we re-use the
same soil year after year,
eventually the crop won't take.
The concept is known
as replant failure.
Simple as that.
Huh?
Replant failure!
Simple as that!
Yes. Thank you! Awesome!
[KOUSAKU coughs]
If you'll excuse me,
I'd like to propose a toast.
As dorm leader,
it's my privilege
to welcome Miss Kinoshita
into the fold.
--We're very happy to--
--[KEI, RINGO, MINORI] Cheers!
Dang it, guys!
[MINORI] I vote
we stuff our faces! Heh.
There's really not a
whole heck of a lot to do
in a po-dunk town like this.
But, there's enough fresh grub
to feed an army!
This is way too much for me.
Oh. Well...
Is it just me, or is she
being kind of bitchy?
Come on! Give her chance.
She's probably just nervous.
Wouldn't you be?
[MINORI] Maybe, but either way,
you wouldn't be the only human
being I bothered talking to.
Heh heh! Ah...
You noticed that, huh?
Ugh. Please! Idiot.
Her attitude's not exactly
going to help her fit in.
Look, if your girlfriend
wants to cut it here,
she needs to learn
how to play ball!
Huh. Guess you have a point.
[MINORI] What you need to do is
stop fan-boying long enough
to set an example.
Quit trying to schmooze,
and get her familiar
with how things work.
[KOUSAKU] I know that, I'm
just... I'm establishing trust.
Who wants to see an impression?
Ha! Yeah!
Helium-filled sex doll.
[KOUSAKU &amp; MINORI] Woo-hoo!
[KEI coughs]
[KEI] I have daddy issues.
[KOUSAKU] Woo-hoo...
[MINORI] Yeah... Woo-hoo...
[KEI] All right, then.
Another one.
I give you "cock of the walk!"
[KOUSAKU] Nope!
[KEI grunting]
[KEI]
Overreact there much, chief?
No more impressions!
It's game time!
In fact, why don't we
let the new girl
pick what she'd like to play?
Uh...
How about "Who's the King?"
[KOUSAKU &amp; MINORI] Huh?
[ALL] Red straw's the King!
Ha-ha! The red one's mine!
[KOUSAKU] Kei's got one.
Pretty sure that signal
means Minori has three.
Yes! This is my chance!
As King, I command
whoever has Number Two
to feed me by hand!
Oh. Glad that's not weird.
[KOUSAKU grunts]
Damn it! How did you
end up with Number Two?!
I'm not any happier
about it than you are!
I was trying to signal you
that Ringo had three.
if it'd been a snake,
it would've bit you!
Your secret code is stupid!
[KEI] Quit stalling
and play the game.
The King asked to be fed.
[MINORI] Your Highness...
[KOUSAKU] Ahh...
Heh...
Glad we're not playing
spin-the-bottle, huh?
[MINORI laughs]
[RINGO] Sorry...
[ALL] Red straw's the King!
[KOUSAKU] Tee-hee.
Yes. Exactly as planned.
As king, I command Number Three
to step on my face barefoot!
Ugh. Is something wrong with you
or do you just hate me?
[KOUSAKU] No!
[KOUSAKU grunts]
I... hate my life!
If you're going to
signal me, be consistent!
Uh-uh, don't pin this
one on me!
Did you or did you not
say my secret code
was stupid last time?
Whatever, just do it!
Step on my face!
You really need to see
a therapist at some point.
Let's get this over with...
[KOUSAKU] Do it quick.
[KOUSAKU whimpers]
[quiet giggling]
[MINORI] I don't know
what this is doing for you
and I don't need to know.
Let's just agree
never to speak of this again.
[KEI] You're a good sport,
Minori. Heh.
You know what they say,
"the more you stomp it,
the bigger the barley grows."
[MINORI] Nobody says that.
Okay, that's enough!
Right. That looked bad.
But... I swear!
[cracking,
KOUSAKU gasps]
[RINGO] Sorry...
[ALL] Red straw's the King!
Looks like it's me.
Oh. Yay.
It's you.
Huh. Nice...
Uh, is something the matter?
No, I'm good.
What're you?
Huh?
[RINGO] What number do you have?
I can't just tell you!
That takes the fun out of it.
What number do you have?
Eh! Uhm... One. But
this is against the rules.
[RINGO sighs]
[RINGO] Number One has to
call me by my first name.
[KOUSAKU] You...
You'd be okay with that?
I mean, we only just met.
[RINGO] It's Ringo, by the way.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah... I-I know.
Good.
Call me that from now on.
Ringo. Nice "ring" to it. Heh.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
What the--?! Oh no!
[KOUSAKU screams]
[grunting]
[KOUSAKU sighs]
[yawning]
[KOUSAKU] Morning, Waka.
Oh, that's right: it's Sunday.
More playtime.
Man. Wait 'til you get
a load of the dream I had.
Last night, I thought Yuka
transferred here from Tokyo
and was totally putting
the moves on me
while we were
playing "Who's the Ki--".
[WAKA squeaks]
[RINGO] What?
[KOUSAKU] Nothing!
Just thinking about how
awesome Ghibli is, you know?
What are you doing?
[RINGO] Laundry.
Ah... I see.
[RINGO] What?
Uh... Nothing! Ha!
So, if you're having trouble
figuring this monster out,
and it is complicated,
I could help?
I can do it on my own,
thank you. But if you want.
Right.
Look, the first thing you need
to learn is how to ask.
[WAKA squeaks]
Nevermind.
I'll wash them in the river.
Look, I don't know
what they teach you
in the concrete jungle,
but we're rustic here,
not Neanderthal.
We'll use the washing machine!
[RINGO gasps]
[KOUSAKU] First thing we do is
separate colors from delicates.
Oohh...
[KOUSAKU] "Delicate"
means "white," basically.
Everything else is "color."
After that, we divvy
up by material.
Go on, I believe in you!
[RINGO] Here goes!
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[KOUSAKU] Wait! Are you cool
with me watching you do this?
Huh?
[KOUSAKU] It's just, you know,
I'm seeing your
underwear and all!
You embarrassed?
[KOUSAKU] Heck no!
But, I mean, aren't you?
Whatever, I'm a modern guy!
If it's fine by you,
it's fine by me.
Which pile do these go into?
Ah. Panties.
Technically, you could
go either way.
[KOUSAKU screams]
Uh... 'cause they're color!
And delicate!
What do we do?
[KOUSAKU] Hand-wash.
[RINGO] Seriously?
[KOUSAKU] Yup.
Washing machine would be
way too rough on them.
Then again, if you've never
hand-washed something before,
it can be challenging.
You think so? Really?
Oh yeah.
Fortunately for you, I'm
experienced with these things.
I'd be happy to help!
Come to daddy!
Come to daddy, my precious.
[KOUSAKU moans]
[KOUSAKU] I am so going to OD!
Step away from the
unmentionables, you pervert!
[KOUSAKU] So close...
Ugh! Leave the poor girl alone!
Like it or not,
a woman has the right
to launder her undies in peace!
[RINGO gasps]
Wait. He's not doing
anything wrong.
I just asked for his help
with my clothes.
I couldn't figure out
the washing machine, okay?
Look, take my word for it,
I know the guy:
he's a ticking time bomb.
I've earned the right
to say that
'cause I've put up with his
creeper man-games
since we were kids, alright?
You've known the perv for,
what? A whole day?
Oh, I'm sorry, I called
your man a "perv."
[RINGO growls]
What the hell is your problem?
[RINGO] Me?
[MINORI] Yes, you.
[RINGO] Oh yeah?
[MINORI] Yeah.
[KOUSAKU] Okay, okay
I like a good catfight
as much as the next guy, but
this is getting on my nerves!
Stop being a queen bee
and give her panties back!
Every second you have them
in your paws
they drop in purity by a
whole order of magnitude!
You're saying I'm impure?!
[KOUSAKU] Bravo!
Give the girl a prize!
Once upon a time,
men wrote hymns
to underwear this wholesome!
Thunder pants like yours-
they burned at the stake!
Ah... Wow. Nice one.
You really put these panties on
a pedestal, huh? Unbelievable.
[KOUSAKU] Just shut up
and hand them over!
Wait. I have a better idea.
I'll go you one better.
You... If you...
If you want them, hers
and mine are a package deal!
--Ew! Gross!
--[MINORI gasps]
[MINORI] Oh, you have
got to be kidding me!
[KOUSAKU] Don't be
such a drama queen!
[KOUSAKU] If you're going to
force me to take
your skid-marked
parachute undies,
at least hand me the
snow white pair first!
Parachute undies...?
Quit bitching and
give them here!
Ha! Over my dead body!
Nope!
If all you're going to do
is fight over them,
just give them back to me.
[ALL grunting]
[KOUSAKU gasps]
Could everyone
calm down, please?
This is stupid.
I heard everything.
You should all be ashamed!
Clearly, there's only one way
to settle this issue properly.
[MINORI &amp; KOUSAKU]
Excuse me? Like how?
[KEI] We test your expertise!
It's like looking into the sun!
[KEI] Here's the deal: pick the
highest quality pair of panties
from the selection
you see here, and you win.
Winner gets two things: my
undying respect,
and bragging rights as
the foremost authority
on ladies' undies.
[BOTH] Hmm...
These look pretty swanky.
Cute. Totally what I
would have picked.
Great minds think
alike, huh?
Right.
I'm going with these
'cause they're what I'd
choose to wear myself.
Ha! Read them and
weep, loser-boy!
I was f--king with you.
[MINORI gasps]
C'mon, that's not how
the game is played!
Us girls got to stick together!
Whatever, these are
absolutely the ones!
[KOUSAKU chuckles]
You know jack about quality.
At the end of the day, it's not
about cuteness or comfort.
Oh. Is that a fact?
[KOUSAKU] Nice try, Kei,
but your little setup here
doesn't fool me.
I... choose none!
[MINORI gasps]
Not a single pair on this
table has ever been worn!
[BOTH] Oh...? Huh?
Guys couldn't care less
about sheer fabric
or frilly little bows.
They care about
whether or not the panties
have ever gotten down
and dirty in the trenches!
Unworn pairs of
ladies' undergarments
are a dime a dozen!
Hmph!
Well, who am I to argue
the basic economics
with a man who'd give his
left nut to sniff a used pair?
In most cases, the reverse
is true, but with panties,
used versus unused can
mean the difference between
several decimal points.
But what we're
actually talking about
isn't the panties themselves.
But the sexual commodification
of the wearer!
If you would hand me the pair
you have in your hands, please.
Sure. There's no question
who's the expert.
You've, definitely earned these.
Ah-ha! Yeah!
Get ready, nose!
[RINGO growls]
[KOUSAKU whimpers]
Sorry! You've lost, pal!
I'll bet you thought those
belonged to Kinoshita.
But they're mine!
[KOUSAKU gasps]
They... They're what?!
I've had them bunched up
under my armpit
for the past five minutes.
That's right.
Nobody said anything to anyone
about them being
your dream girl's.
These, on the other hand!
[KOUSAKU] So I basically just
buried my nose in your...
Afraid so.
[KOUSAKU] How could you?
I thought you were my friend?
You've tricked me! Why?
[BOTH gasp]
[KOUSAKU] What have I done
to deserve this...?
This was all on purpose!
Bastard! You knew exactly
what you were doing!
You've turned this laundry room
into a den of lies!
[KOUSAKU sobs]
C'mon, man get a grip, already.
Let this be a lesson to you that
not all used panties
have seen the kind of trenches
you're interested in.
Then tell me....
How's a man supposed
to judge quality?
There's no surefire way.
Value is in the eye
of the beholder.
[MINORI] Why do you sound
like a guru all of a sudden?
[RINGO] I don't understand.
[KEI] Consider this:
Stop thinking in terms
of the panties themselves.
The only pair worth its weight
in gold is the pair unseen.
The one thing we're drawn
to without fail is mystery.
Once we've seen them they're
just a run-o'-the-mill fact.
What they are is nothing
compared to what they represent.
That's really deep...
So, one in the hand is...
Is worth none in the bush.
Wow, I... I was jerk.
Sorry I threw them away.
I didn't understand
their panty power.
Nah, I was the jerk.
I didn't understand
any better than you.
[KEI] There, that's the spirit.
Glad you two remember
how to be friends.
Since my work's done,
I'll be taking Kinoshita's
panties for myself.
[KOUSAKU] What?!
You dirty double-crossing--!
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[KEI] Stop belly-aching!
You already have your own!
Huh? What are you talking about?
[KEI] The ones in your heart...
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[KOUSAKU] Of course!
They've been with me
from the beginning!
Everyone carries their own
high-quality pair
of ladies' unmentionables
in their heart!
Guys! Let's hang these up like
banners and have a party!
A Spring-line Panties Party!
I'll make my special red rice!
[laughing]
Yo, sweetheart--you in
or you out?
[RINGO] You guys are all idiots!
[ALL whimper]
[KOUSAKU] And so our
Spring-Line Panties Party ended.
About five seconds
after it started.
But, man, it was fun!
[KOUSAKU] "Super Sub-Mom War:
Training Stage"