[ALEGGSIS] Moe Eggs!
Farm fresh, unfertilized
and unbelievably smooth!
Cooked or raw.
Yum! So very tasty!
[ALEGGSIS] Where else can you
get eggs likes this
but--you guessed it--Tamo
No-Rin High School?
Our eggs use condoms,
so you know they're safe!
[KOUSAKU] Sure, that last part
was bit much,
but, hey, we had an idea
and we ran with it.
None of us knew it would be
the proverbial golden goose.
[MINORI] Moe rice.
Any clue what
I'm talking about?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah, no.
Oh-ho! You've got to see it!
They've been all over the news!
Very simple concept.
Rice with a hot naked lady
on the packaging sells like wow!
Step one: Produce.
Step two: Sex.
Step three: Cash.
[KEI] It's actually real.
Wow. Really?
They hired a manga artist.
I forget his name, but he's real
popular with the otaku crowd.
He drew a bishojo chick in
a tantalizing pose and boom.
Thirty-two tons of rice sold
online in ninety days.
The company normally unloads
about fifteen tons a year,
so the new mascot
earned them eight times
their average monthly sales.
Whoa! Damn!
[MINORI]
Imagine how much we can sell
if we took the same approach?!
A little tasteful nudity and the
school would be rolling in it!
[laughter]
I smell profit.
Ah, hello my lovelies.
Heads up! We've got a Top Four!
Whenever two or more
people talk finance,
this one's ready to pounce!
Hide your 401k's!
[RINGO] Hmm...
So, she's a Top Four?
Correct! The school
has four of these types in all.
One: Fun Bags Yoshida
from Class A.
Two: Bio Suzuki from Class B.
Three: Woodman
Rintarou from Class F.
Rose Hanazono
from Class E.
And last but not least,
from Class D,
agronomic specialist and
marketing-slash-logistics guru,
Money Kanegami!
[RINGO] Hmm...
You just named five.
Never mind about that!
[KANEGAMI] So...
Rolling in it, huh?
[sighs] Something we
can help you with?
[laughs] All we've been
through together
and that's how
you say hello?
Thought I counted
for more than that.
Didn't your recent
hedge fund shenanigans
get you indefinitely suspended?
Oh, they let me back
in as of yesterday.
But let's cut to the chase.
You're cooking something up.
Mama wants in.
Good for you.
The Moe racket's
a cash cow.
I've been wanting to dip my wick
into that honey pot for ages.
Yeah, well, easier
said than done.
it's not exactly
low-hanging fruit.
He's right, you know.
We'd need a big name
artist onboard.
Anybody can slap a pic of
some spread-eagle bimbo
on the front of a rice bag
and use it to boost sales.
[laughs] You want a big-name
artiste, then here you go.
It doesn't get much bigger
than the illustrator for Kippu,
ladies ann germs.
He's available, he's interested,
and he's in my contacts.
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI] What?!
When you say Kippu,
you mean THE Kippu?!
[laughs] None other.
You mean that one guy
who does all those
light novel illustrations?!
[laughs] That's him.
The genius who draws all
the critically acclaimed
pinup girl artwork?!
[laughs] Indeed.
The same dude who fell from
grace with the art community
not long ago for manga-fying
some lameass story about
Ag students and whose family
threatened to cut him off
if he didn't rethink
his career choices?!
[laughs] Yes, I think
we all know it is.
[KEI]
And he's sincerely interested?
[KANEGAMI]
Well he is a professional.
If the price is right, I think
we should consider him sincere.
He's worth every penny,
I can assure you.
Wow. You hear that?
That's the sound of us
actually having a shot at this!
[laughs] Lend me a hand,
my lovelies,
and I just might be able to
make it worth your while.
Huh. Lend you a hand?
What do you want us to do?
Look at me.
I'm not exactly in the yearbook
as "most trustworthy," now am I?
[KANEGAMI] But if I had fine,
upstanding students
like yourselves
to vouch for me...
We could get this thing
off the ground.
Ahh... So we're your
bargaining chip.
I completely understand!
Kousaku would be more
than happy to help!
Don't volunteer me!
Look, this is simple
risk management.
If Kanegami runs afoul
of anti-trust laws
and the school
needs a scapegoat,
somebody needs to stay
behind with the shredder.
Why does it get to be you?
[KEI] Basic question:
What are we planning to sell?
I'd say damn near anything
given this guy's talent.
A drawing of his
could sell ice to Eskimos.
Now, we got to balance
supply and demand,
so think stable inventory.
Best branding in the world
isn't going to do us
a whole lot of good if there's
nothing to package, right?
[KOUSAKU] Gotcha.
The trick is to sell something
we have constant access to.
Something with a yield
we can rely on.
I've got just the thing.
Excellent choice.
Oh yeah, those!
We have a winner.
Um, okay?
[KOCHOU] Out of the question!
[KOUSAKU] C'mon,
don't be like that!
They're perfect!
Your eggs are made for the
big time and you know it!
Ugh! Disgusting!
Moe eggs! Please!
The very idea induces apoplexy!
Producers with integrity compete
on the merit of their product.
Period.
[KANEGAMI laughs] Is it lonely
up there on your high horse?
This is no different
in principle than selling them
at the Green Shop.
Look, they're still being
touted on their merits.
We're just helping those merits
reach a larger market share.
Ah! So it's you!
Why am I not surprised?
[KANEGAMI] Do we or don't we owe
it to ourselves and the school
to cast our net
as widely as possible?
And I suppose next
you'll lecture me on
laissez faire capitalism!
Don't think I don't know
what you're up to, madam!
D'aw. Please.
Why be so reactive, doll?
Take a moment to
give me a fair hearing.
Whatever I'm "up to" here,
the end game is this:
your eggs becoming
a household name.
Well...
I have to admit,
they are certainly worthy.
Just imagine...
[chuckles]
Think about it.
A carton in every
kitchen in Japan.
You know, I can't
think of another farmer
for whom that's true.
[KOCHOU] But we've
always prided ourselves
on the "locally produced" label.
Won't our regular
clientele feel betray--
Sweetheart, listen.
You've heard
the horror stories.
Feed laced with hormones
and antibiotics.
Unsanitary living conditions.
Now, haven't the corporate
farms had their shot?
Hasn't the public been subjected
to their "anything to fatten
the bottom-line"
ideology long enough?
C'mon, take your
place in the sun.
[KANEGAMI]
This isn't about money!
Oh, no. It's about
consumer rights!
Please! Do the right thing!
[KOCHOU] Y-Yes.
The system can work.
We can make it work.
I believe in us!
--I...
--[KANEGAMI] Game, set, match.
[KOUSAKU] Damn she's good.
[KOUSAKU] Okey-doke!
The product is Moe Eggs.
The mascot is Aleggsis.
We brand aggressively.
Come on! Let me hear you!
[ALL] Woo-hoo!
[KOUSAKU] So... How we doing?
Not so bad.
People seem to like the blog.
Great! Post the
four-panel manga!
How's the print media campaign?
Just bought space in
three issues of a top anime mag!
[phone rings]
Hello. Moe Eggs.
Yes. Yes.
Just one moment.
Someone wants the
figurine copyright!
Huh? Okay. That was fast.
Heh. They're falling
over themselves.
[KOUSAKU] Hmm... Now what?
[laughs] They want to
use it for an event?
I say let them have
the copyright.
We're an LLC,
so the risk is on them.
Either way, it's free exposure.
That's the ticket!
Kei! Give them the go!
[KEI] Roger.
[ALEGGSIS] Moe Eggs!
They like it when you
peel them a little rough.
So wet and slippery...
Go on... No one's looking.
You deserve the very best!
[phone ringing]
[KANEGAMI] Thank you
for calling Moe Eggs.
No, sorry.
We're not accepting any more
preorders at this time.
Yeah, that's right:
as advertised.
Order now and your shipment
will get there in 90 days.
Okay. This is
getting out of hand.
Bad news.
The school server's down.
Too many orders!
Aw, man. This is
the last thing we need!
Oh, no. They'll start
burning up the phones.
[KOUSAKU] Alright,
that settles it.
We need a phone bank
in here, STAT.
First things first.
We've got to get these
packed up and shipped!
[KOUSAKU] Right, right.
Man, we need more hands.
Got anybody we can
bring in on this?
[KOCHOU] Sell my little
porcelain orbs, sell!
[phones ringing]
[STUDENTS talking,
phones ringing]
[KOUSAKU] Look, I'm telling you:
twins are the way to go.
[KANEGAMI] Perfect choice for
branding double-yolk eggs.
I say yes.
[KOUSAKU] I'm leaning toward
"Hard-Boiled Shelly"
and "Ramona Ramekin."
[MINORI] Ooh, I like that!
Plays up their versatility!
[RINGO] Bad news. I think
We have a graphics issue.
What in the name of...?
What is that?!
[KOUSAKU] Gross!
She's old enough to be my mom!
I thought we were all
in agreement to go Lolita.
I, uh, think there's
been a misunderstanding.
[KOUSAKU]
This is not good, people!
[chuckles] Older women
have their charms.
Th-They do?
[KANEGAMI] Call her experienced.
She's a shoe-in for
the soft-boiled line.
[ALL] Ooh!
[KOUSAKU] Make it happen!
[KOCHOU] Aye-aye, sir!
[KOUSAKU] Throw up a
teaser on the website!
[MINORI] All over it!
[goat bleats]
[KEI] I want out.
[KOUSAKU] Eh? Why?
We're kicking ass!
[KEI] I'll be honest with you:
I don't like where we're headed.
Just look at us.
Don't you resent having to fall
back on cheap marketing tricks?
[gasps]
It's about exposure, man.
How else are our eggs going
to compete in a global market?
Or don't you believe in
our product?
Hah. As usual, you've put
the cart before the horse.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
Oh, I'm putting the
cart before the horse?
How about you think
outside the box?!
Hah. Whatever, man.
Have fun playing
corporate tycoon.
[gasps]
Giddyup, Jun.
[goat bleats]
[KEI] Heeyah!
Kei, wait!
[goat bleats]
Ugh. He's going to break
that poor thing's back.
[ANCHOR]
You've heard the hype,
you probably have a carton of
her eggs in your refrigerator.
Now hear first-hand from
the chicken lady herself
whose business went
from modest to Moe
in a mindboggling
matter of weeks,
whether or not there's
a correlation between
egg consumption and cup size.
Well organically produced eggs
are a good source of protein,
so it's reasonable to posit
a relationship-- Ugh!
I did not agree
to debase myself!
She sure has become a celebrity.
[chuckles] Yeah,
the camera adores her.
Did you ever think the company
would take off like this?
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, I figured
we'd do well-- Whoops.
There. Don't want
the meat to catch fire.
You want intestines a little
crispy, but not well done.
When the fat's crackling,
that's the sign to
move it off the heat.
Voila.
That's a new one to me.
Oh, nice! Absolutely perfect!
It's a good metaphor
for business.
When it's cooked
to perfection, you're done.
You've got to know
when to move on.
It's the difference between a
gourmand and a pyromaniac.
Huh.
[KOUSAKU] So what's next
on the board for Moe Eggs?
That's the point
I'm trying to make.
Moe Eggs is a thing of the past.
What? But, we...
Local farmers will
buy the trademark.
The school will make a killing.
And we move on to other things.
All for the best really.
Our business venture has
been a shot in the arm
for the local economy.
We're selling out?
Well, sort of. But we
won't reap a profit.
Students aren't legally allowed
to exploit the school
for personal gain.
You do know that, right?
Hang on--!
Easy now, Rockefeller.
Ag training's not about making
returns on the produce we grow.
It's about learning
how to make returns.
Think of it like a
financial laboratory.
Now's the time for
experimentation,
not portfolio building.
Which is great, 'cause once
we're out in the real world,
we won't have the
safety nets we have here.
We mess up, we make
bad business choices...
We're on our own.
See, kid. There'll be
plenty of time to amass
our fortunes once
we've graduated.
For the moment, the trick is to
take advantage of our freedom.
[KANEGAMI] A gourmand enjoys
a dish cooked to perfection.
A pyro just ends up
getting burned.
[KOUSAKU] Kanegami.
[KANEGAMI] Yeah?
[KOUSAKU] Well. I don't
really know how to put this.
I guess I always thought your
whole MO was making money.
[KANEGAMI laughs]
Don't get me wrong.
Money's all that
and a bag of chips, no lie.
But it's far from the
be-all-end-all, trust me.
Thing is, when push comes
to shove, I crave adventure.
Passion. Sure, money
can make that happen,
but it's not the end goal.
It's a tool. That's all.
Wow, that's deep.
[KANEGAMI] Right. So.
Eggs are old news.
But, there are plenty of
other markets to tap.
[KOUSAKU] Such as?
Heh... Clearly the next
logical step is yaoi.
[AKARI] The B in Class B
stands for Boy Love!
[KOUSAKU yells]
[KANEGAMI] Nice of you
to finally put in
an appearance, Akari.
Garcon! Warm glass of milk,
please! No ice cubes!
What's going on?
The otaku market is setting
its sights on the female dollar.
Women are dropping
more cash on sex merch
than their male counterparts.
Maybe the modern woman
has become lonesome.
Whatever the case, only a
fool would ignore the trend.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah, I get it.
But, what's our product?
Try to stay with me, chief:
you know the fungal culture
practicum from Class F?
You mean those grubby
old logs they use
to cultivate
shiitake and shimeji
and other crap like that?
Think about it, kiddo.
You're a fungi, am I right?
[gasps] What does
that even mean?
Look, I got to be honest.
Mushrooms sorta gross me out.
Oh calm down, reverend.
It's not the 'shrooms I'm after,
it's the logs those little
fellas are cultivated on.
The market's screaming for one.
Wait. Really?
[laughs] The branding
creates itself.
The hell are you?! Crazy?!
[chuckles] Try to be objective
for a moment, please.
The demand-side definitely
has an upper limit.
--It'll be a cash-grab
--[AKARI] O.M.G....
--pure and simple, you dig?
--I can't look away...
We'll adopt a
hit-and-run strategy
that'll maximize
our market impact.
I, uh... think you might be
taking things too...
Hey, Suzuki, I could use a
little help any time now.
[AKARI] You know
what'd be perfect?
A little dab of yogurt
on the tip.
I am not comfortable with this!
Cross promotion!
We could say
"apply Class B yogurt
for mushrooms bigger
than your wildest dreams!"
[chuckles menacingly]
[KANEGAMI] You know what?
That's just insane
enough to work.
This is gonna be huge.
[RINTAROU] I ought to put
an axe through your skull!
Yeah, I know, right?
What do you say
we go to the roof.
Just you and me.
'Cause I really feel like
teaching somebody how to fly.
Maybe some other time,
that's not why I'm here.
I thought you'd be
interested in showing off
Class F's mad skills.
Very funny. Good one, man.
You think we train as hard as
we do to help make pornography?
[KOUSAKU] Believe me,
I'm as uncomfortable as you.
No worries, dude.
I get it. It's too weird.
I should've seen this coming.
But could you at least
have a look at it
and tell me whether
or not it's possible?
Fine. Technically it
couldn't be easier.
You drill yourself a big enough
hole, stick in the spores,
and then there's
fungus among us.
And if the log was carved
into a crotch-shape,
it would still work?
Not on your life!
Okay, got it.
[KANEGAMI chuckles]
That's a damn shame.
And here I thought we had
the perfect storm of skill
and target audience to flood
the Forestry department
with easy women.
[RINTAROU] Huh?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
If ever there was a product
designed for fujoshi girls,
this would've been it.
That lot loves their fantasy.
Fujoshi.
Genuine fujoshi.
Yeah!
Think of all the
lonely ladies out there
who dream of you
manly forestry types!
What you do is pure sex to them:
you hunks are like the
Texas Rangers or something!
Right, Kousaku?
Huh? Oh, yeah! Absolutely!
Like I said,
it's a damn shame.
Had we been able to make this
work, there's no telling
how many free-wheeling gals
would've been falling over
themselves to join Class F.
All those hotties desperate for
attention from big, strong men.
You know, maybe I was
jumping the gun.
I should hear you out.
[chuckles]
[KOUSAKU] So here's the name.
Ugh. Brace for it, we're going
with "Yeah. Pick That Mushroom.
There You Go."
You're looking at hundreds of
years of mushroom cultivation
at its finest.
I give you the standard
shiitake mushroom
with its dark, meaty cap!
The shimeji, with its cluster
of fleshy forking tendrils.
Hungry, anybody?
Eight inches of thick,
magisterial heft.
The king trumpet!
The maitake, whose dark frills
give off an intoxicating scent.
Smell that musk!
The nameko, with it viscous coat
and suggestive skin-tone.
Careful ladies!
The lovely mukitake.
Like a gymnast's six pack.
And the oyster, fungal art
splayed like a mosaic.
This is the stuff!
Call now and we'll
include with your order
the visually alluring
fertilizer mix.
Our very special
ANaL BB Yogurt Blend!
Now, for obvious reasons,
we can't sell this stuff
through the usual networks.
Not to worry, though:
we'll be moving units through
Bio's very own fujoshi pipeline!
Packaging will be plain. The
label will say "Folk Crafts."
[chuckles] Right.
Needless to say, if anyone
catches us selling these things,
we're toast. So let's
keep everything on the DL.
[KOUSAKU] We took advantage
of our freedom, all right.
The world didn't know what
hit it when we were done.
And we were done pretty quick.
[KOUSAKU] Just as we
were starting out.
We got busted.
Oh boy. Suspension.
[KOUSAKU sighs
[NATSUMI] My, Miss Kinoshita,
that yukata looks
fabulous on you!
Think so?
[NATSUMI laughs] Why yes!
They were made for
flat-chested girls!
[RINGO growls]
[NATSUMI giggles]
Just think. Caught 'cause
one of the top clients
was a classmate's grandmother.
Yeah, well.
Guess we had it coming.
Hey, look on the bright side.
It's like three days' vacation.
You got off a lot easier
than your ring leader.
She had it much worse,
appropriately.
Repeat offenders like her get
three weeks' suspension.
And all of Class F got a formal
reprimand which, believe me,
you wouldn't have wanted.
So... what happened to them?
[KEI] The forestry teacher,
Mr. Tachikawa, beat their ass.
Yeesh.
Their summer break's
going to suck, too.
They'll spend most of it
on Mount Onake.
Oh snap. Mount Onake. No thanks.
[KANEGAMI] I'm with you on that.
[ALL] Hm?
[KOUSAKU] Oh. Hey.
Got a new business
idea brewing.
For when I get back.
What do you say?
You interested?
Huh?
[KANEGAMI] I've got
everything lined up.
I just need your...
front-man skills.
Didn't think so. Oh well.
[KANEGAMI] One more thing.
Tell me. Did you have fun?
It's a simple yes or no.
[KOUSAKU] Hmph. Yeah.
[laughs]
Then my work here is done.
[KANEGAMI] Let's see how far
we can take this mascot trend.
[AKARI] Ooh! How about
a talking prolapsed anus?
[MINORI] Some people
refuse to learn, huh?
Oh! Look at the bamboo!
Let's write wishes
for the Star Festival!
[KOUSAKU] Uhh...
What should I wish for?
[MINORI] Ah, there we go!
[RINGO] This is cool.
[NATSUMI] Too many, you think?
[KOUSAKU] Seems like
kind of a lot, yeah.
I mean, it's good
to want things, but...
[KOUSAKU gasps] You are
not hanging these up!
[NATSUMI] Oh! I almost forgot!
I want you to tie me up!
[KOUSAKU] Ugh. Who hired you?
I'm going to have a look at
what everyone else wished for.
[KOUSAKU] I like Star Festivals.
We all wish for
different things,
but the wishing
brings us together.
The deal is, none of us gets
to be happy unless we all are.
[KOUSAKU] Seems like
a good thing to me.
No, really. Makes us a family.
[RINGO] Sob Salad.