[KEI]
The Takaido Fushinari cucumbers
are coming along nicely.
The Wase Shinkuro eggplants
should be ready for
harvest soon.
I give them a few more days.
Apart from the tomato
splitting debacle.
It's been a very
successful year.
[phone rings]
Hello. Thank you for calling
Tamo-No-Rin, how can I help you?
Hello?
[MAN] Kei?
[KEI gasps] It's you...
How did you find me?!
[MAN] You didn't really think
you could escape, did you?
Come back right now.
I will not!
You and me, we're done,
do I make myself clear?!
[MAN] I'll be paying you
a visit very soon.
If I were you, I'd get ready.
[reciever clicks, tone beeps]
[KEI growls]
[KEI] One phone call...
and it all comes flooding back.
My past rears
its ugly head yet again.
[NATSUMI] Oh no!
Everyone, I have terrible news!
With an entrance that dramatic,
this better be important.
It's bad. I don't know
how else to put it
other than to say the
Principal broke.
Wait. He broke? Huh?!
[moans]
Whoa. Is this the same mighty
Principal I used to know?
The legendary warrior who killed
a bear with his own two hands?
[PRINCIPAL] What's that?
No, I'm afraid you won't be able
to speak to the bear today.
Okay.
It's clear he's completely lost
his mind, but why are we here?
Well, that's a great question.
For the eggplants!
[GROUP] The eggplants?
[PRINCIPAL] Eggplants!
He keeps rambling on
about eggplants
and I have no idea why.
Stop it!
It's not like we have a
shortage of eggplants out there.
Why don't you just
give him some already?
Yeah, that's the whole problem.
I've already given
him eggplants,
but then he started saying,
"Hey. These are not
real eggplants!"
Rrgh... Oooh, that burns me up!
Do you mind if I take
a look at them?
Maybe there's something wrong?
[NATSUMI] Knock yourself out.
They seem perfectly edible,
in my expert opinion.
Well, he disagrees.
And since these
don't fit the bill,
I figured we could use our
own eggplants instead,
which is why I brought you
all here to save the day.
[GROUP] Ahhh...
I see. Yeah.
You're hoping for
some sort of heartwarming
"after school special"
plot, aren't you?
"The sad, forlorn principal
snaps out of it
thanks to his devoted students."
Seen it before.
Geez, how unsentimental
can you get?
[KEI] The principal's
instincts are right.
[GROUP] Huh?
Those eggplants. Not a
single one of them is real.
[KEI] They're manufactured.
Wait. What makes you say that?
Yes, what exactly are you
blathering on about?
Sorry, but you're wrong,
I've tried them myself.
They're thick, fresh, firm,
and quite the mouthful.
See?
I can put the
whole thing inside.
[KEI] Listen to me.
If you let me use the
home-ec room tomorrow.
I'll show you what a
real eggplant looks like.
Oh, eggplant.
All right then, mister,
you said you'd show us
the real deal,
so bring it on!
I just hope your stuff
has what it takes, Kei.
If it disappoints,
then I'm stuck with
your itty-biddy eggplant
either way, huh?
[KEI] It's all yours.
Kei, no! Surely you
don't mean that?
I appreciate your
confidence, but let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
To begin, why don't we
take a good, hard look
at the eggplants
I've brought to the table?
Top of the line and
one hundred percent organic.
Farm to table.
Five hundred a piece!
--[MINORI gasps]
--[RINGO] That's a lot?
You gotta be kidding me!
That's, like, crazy expensive!
[giggles]
It's your move, Kamatori,
if you have one, that is.
I do. Check this out.
[ALL gasp]
[laughs] What is this,
some kind of joke?!
Even supermarket eggplants look
better than that old, lumpy,
beat-up thing!
Before you knock it,
give it a taste.
Unless you're a
"scaredy cat", of course.
It's... so... big.
Yeah, I'm shaking in my boots.
Sure does look good.
[KOUSAKU]
Yeah. Ms. Becky's eggplant
has started to let go
of its moisture.
But Kei's hasn't changed at all.
And notice the size
of those seeds.
Unlike yours truly,
Kei's dish is disappointing
inside and out!
But you guys
haven't tasted it yet.
[KOUSAKU]
All right then, here we go.
This is very delicious,
Ms. Becky!
That just might be the
best eggplant I've ever had!
Under-ripe.
Just a little, though.
And the skin's too tough.
[NATSUMI growls] Obviously, you
know nothing about eggplants,
that's how they're
supposed to be!
All right then,
time to give Kei's a try.
[PRINCIPAL] Eggplant!
Whoa. What the hell
is he doing?!
--[gasps]
--Are you okay, sir?!
[GROUP gasps]
[PRINCIPAL yells]
[ALL gasp]
[PRINCIPAL groans, yells
[NATSUMI screams]
[PRINCIPAL] Now...
That... Is... Tasty!
[PRINCIPAL]
A delicious fruit packed
with a sense of
immense accomplishment!
A scrumptious eggplant
that will boldly go
where no eggplant
has gone before!
Fresh and moist,
though not watery.
A juicy morsel exploding with
flavor so smooth, so creamy,
you'll be on your knees
begging for more!
A taste unlike any other taste
that has ever been before!
[MINORI] Sir, are you all right?
[NATSUMI] Yeah, that was insane.
[PRINCIPAL growls]
Thank you very much. That dish
was truly a delectable triumph!
Mr. Kamatori. That,
my dearest young man,
is an eggplant to rival
all other eggplants!
My friend, you have to tell me,
where in the world
did you find such a thing?
Well, as a matter of fact, I
grew it myself in my spare time.
Amazing.
But I must know, how's it so
much better than the rest?
The seeds are my
secret weapons.
I wish someone would
plant their secret weapon
in my eggplant field!
See, the thing is...
My seeds are purebred.
They might look
a little bit plain.
But with a touch of love
and the proper care,
they will always retain
their time-honored taste.
The reason those other
eggplants didn't satisfy
your craving is...
they're F1 hybrid fakes.
Wait a sec. What?
[KEI] First filial generation.
It's no big deal, just a
genetics term we plant guys use.
Bred for appearance first
and taste second,
these first generation
cultivars were created
for one reason
alone: efficiency.
Efficiency?
[KEI] This supreme focus on
efficiency over quality
leads to the liberal use of
chemical fertilizers
and pesticides on F1 products
in an environment
that's as far from
natural as you can get.
If that's not a bunch of
manufactured crap,
then I don't know what is!
[PRINCIPAL] Hmm.
You do make an excellent
point, Kamatori.
It's the truth,
plain and simple, sir.
[PRINCIPAL] We have an elite
educational summer program
that gives some of our more
exemplary students
the unique opportunity to study
global agriculture abroad.
Miss Kochou Yoshida.
Mister Kei Kamatori.
Would the two of you
care to participate?
[GROUP gasps]
Well... Shall I do it?
Perhaps it might be
worth a serious think.
Large-scale agriculture
is flourishing overseas.
But, if Kei and I journey
across the globe together,
people might mistakenly
believe we're on our honeymoon.
Oh, what a delightful,
and romantic,
comedy of errors that would be!
[laughs]
Thank you,
but I'm not interested
in overseas agriculture.
I'm here to study
small-scale, pesticide free,
organic farming based on the
"eat local" concept,
not to learn the ins and outs
of mass corporatization.
[knocking]
[MAN] Excuse me.
[gasps] You! You're here!
So are you. Well,
what fortuitous luck.
You've saved me the trouble
of having to summon you.
I do hope you've made
your preparations.
[gasps]
--What's wrong?
--You okay?
[screams] Hey, I know this guy!
You were on "Sunrise
on Gaia", weren't you?
You're President Menjou
of Hexa Techs!
Hexa... what?
Hexa Techs is a
massive company
that does everything
from growing crops
to shipping them overseas.
It's the most successful
produce company there is
and he runs it all!
[KOCHOU] So, that means
Kei Kamatori is--
[MENJOU] My unworthy son.
[KEI] No! You're not my father!
You're not anything to me!
[MENJOU] Hmph. So, you're
his teacher I take it?
Yes, and available!
Please begin the process of
transferring my son out of here!
Like, very available!
[MENJOU] Gather up your things.
You're not to waste time
wallowing in a place
like this a moment longer.
How dare you?
What do you mean a
"place like this"?
Ah. Ringo.
Answer me. What exactly
does that mean?
[RINGO] This school is the best.
In all of-- I was
going to say Japan,
but I really think
this school grows
the most delicious vegetables
in the whole world.
[MENJOU] "The most delicious
vegetables in the whole world"?
[MENJOU laughs]
[KOCHOU] Um. What is so amusing?
Well, I'll give her this much:
for a lowly ag-school student,
she does have a
strong imagination.
Like you're one to talk with
that F1 manufactured garbage
you call produce, you jerk!
[MENJOU chuckles] You've got
quite the lip on you,
but would you be willing to put
your money where your mouth is?
I'll gladly take you on
any day, old man.
[MENJOU] If that's the case,
how about a showdown?
[KEI] Bring it.
[MENJOU] I propose
a simple match:
your vegetables versus mine.
Whoever sells the
most product wins.
I do have one stipulation.
If I manage to beat you
fair and square, you'll stay
out of agriculture forever.
All right. But if you lose,
you leave this school.
And never come back!
[MENJOU] Good luck.
[KEI] I haven't shown this
to anyone yet.
But this is where I'm raising
my purebred vegetables.
[MINORI] So, this is where
you've been running off to
when you disappear
for hours on end.
[KOUSAKU] Geez, you're taking
care of all of this by yourself?
Yeah. Bringing back
heirloom vegetables
is a deep passion of mine.
Unlike my father...
The only thing he cares about
is lining his pockets.
Quality doesn't matter
to him at all!
Hey, Kei. I'm confused,
if Menjou's your real last name,
then how come
you go by Kamatori?
[KEI]
Kamatori is my aunt's name.
I asked her to adopt me,
and she did.
[RINGO]
You're adopted?
[MINORI]
But why forsake your name?
'Cause my stupid father is
a despicable human being!
[gasping]
[KEI] At the end of the day,
he's just a guy in a suit.
He has no real love
for agriculture.
All he cares about is business.
[MINORI] So, is that the real
reason why you didn't want to go
into that study abroad program,
because of your father?
[KEI] I love farming. And I'm
here because it's important,
even if it is
on a small scale.
I refuse to end up like him.
[KEI] Back home,
we tended a melon farm.
Without chemical fumigation,
melons are often prone to pests,
and let me tell you, our farm
wasn't without its share
of issues on that front.
But the problem was,
my mother was very sensitive
to these chemicals.
That didn't stop him
from using them though,
his eye always fixated on
the bottom line.
How awful.
Even after they killed
his own wife,
he still uses those chemicals.
Because when all's
said and done,
profit matters to him more than
anything else in this world.
Even his own family!
[KOUSAKU] I'm sorry. But if
that's not a prime example
of why all farms should
operate chemical-free,
then I don't know what is.
[KEI] Look,
this is a lot to ask.
And I know I shouldn't get you
involved in this showdown.
But the truth is, I really do
need your help!
We're here for you, Kei.
What do you say, you guys?
Sure! Done!
What I mean is,
from a personal stand-point,
I have no reason to care
whether Kei Kamatori
has to leave us behind.
But for the sake of Tamo-No Rin,
we cannot afford to lose him!
We'll show that old fart
of a want to-be farmer
who really runs things
around here!
What do you think
about that, Ringo?
He's going down.
We'll wipe the floor
with his dumb face!
[KEI] Thanks, everyone.
[MENJOU] Whoever sells the most
product in one hour wins,
plain and simple.
[KEI] Just to clarify, you mean
sales, not profit, correct?
Yes, that's right.
But we have the
same amount of market space.
You can try to boost sales
by selling at a loss
but it won't work.
I know that,
I'm not an imbecile.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd worry about myself.
Right. First thing we need
to do is set some prices.
Whatever his prices are,
we'll match them.
Huh?
[KEI] My vegetables are
organic and pesticide free.
Taste will win the day!
[KANEGAMI chuckles] Well,
look at what the cat dragged in.
[KOUSAKU] Whoa. What the heck
are you doing here?!
I came to help you.
Look: If you want to
sell some vegetables
and be filthy stinking rich,
then all you have to do is use
Class D's Ace Sales Technique.
You'll leave ol' daddy
dearest in the dust!
What's that sprayer for?
[KANEGAMI] Watch and learn.
[KOUSAKU] Incredible!
They look amazing!
Freshly picked, and covered top
to bottom in sweet morning dew!
[KANEGAMI chuckles]
[PA ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Visit the parking lot now
for a limited-time-only
fresh vegetable market!
All right! Let's get out there
and sell, sell, sell!
[STUDENTS] Yeah!
[WOMAN A]
It looks like it's pretty fresh.
But it does have
a very unusual shape.
And worms have been at it.
Yes, and that's proof
of its organic,
pesticide-free upbringing.
If you don't believe me,
have a taste!
[WOMAN A] Well. I suppose
that's why the bugs like it.
I'm sold!
[GIRLS] Thanks a lot for
shopping with us today!
Excellent. So far,
there hasn't been
too much action at Hexa Techs.
[chucles] Plus, I'm just
getting started over here.
Time to seal the deal!
[KANEGAMI'S HENCHMAN]
Yes, ma'am!
Hey! What the heck
are they doing?!
Relax, my friend,
have a look.
[KOUSAKU] What is this?
It's just a little trick
I call, "merchandising."
"Merchan-dising"?
Listen up.
It's midsummer, right?
And it's Friday, the start
of a relaxing weekend.
And you know what that means.
Actually, I don't.
It means lots of people
with cash to spare
want to get out there
and live it up a little.
And what's the easiest way
to accomplish that feat?
Sleep?
[KANEGAMI] Yakiniku, obviously!
Korean barbeque!
[WOMAN B] Hey, look at that,
they have yakiniku!
[WOMAN C] That's a great way
to get our veggies in!
[KANEGAMI] Merchandising
is quite simple, really.
It's all about providing
the right product.
In the perfect amount
at the exact right price.
At precisely the right moment
when people need
what you're selling.
You guys, this is too much! It's
like she's so freaking smart
my head is gonna explode!
It looks like the only extras
they have are free samples.
I really think we can win!
He's behind, isn't he?
I mean, we've had a
ton more customers.
[KANEGAMI] Still.
We can do way better.
Whoa, you mean you've got
something else up your sleeve?
Advertising, friends!
Sales promotions!
It's like they always say:
"You can sell anything
with sex."
Guys! It's boner jam time!
[GIRLS] "We like veg-gies.
They're racy. They're lacy.
They're tasty.
Don't you want to
put them in your mouth?!"
♪
[whimpers]
Hey!
Oh, come on, Lady,
you can't stay embarrassed
about this forever!
Right. Now let's get walking!
[KOCHOU whimpers]
[GROUP] Is everybody eating
their vegetables?
[NOL48] Yeah!
Their voices, youth, charm,
and undeniable attractiveness
catch the customer's eye while
subconsciously making them
more eager to spend
their money on your product.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
Plus this.
In order to attract the
ever-important male demographic,
these pretty ladies come
with Nestletix, too!
Hold on. What?
[KANEGAMI]
You can ask any girl you like
to put any veggie you want
between her breasts.
Whoa! Amazing.
That's an incredible strategy!
To compete with Hexa Techs'
sheer brand power,
"the gloves" are gonna
have to come off,
or in the case of
these ladies, "the bras."
You're so smart... So, uh...
Any girl?
[RINGO] Uh. Like this?
[giggles]
[BOYS] Oh yeah!
We hit the jackpot!
[RINTAROU, KAORU, AKARI] Now
it's our turn to have some fun!
[KOUSAKU] Holy crap,
what the heck are you doing?
Why are you here?!
We came to show that
snake in a suit
what a proper peasant
uprising is like!
Plus, I hear his
dad's a total silver fox.
[KOUSAKU] All four of them
representing in full force!
I'll help.
Anything for one of the most
talented students in school.
But sweet Kei, call me "Mom."
Please!
Go on, give it a try!
Come on, big boy, there's
nothing to be nervous about!
That's right, sugar tits,
call me your naughty mama!
Who's your naughty mama, huh?!
Who's your hot mama?!
Come on, give mommy a big, wet
smooch right on the old kisser,
preferably with tongue!
--Let's get her!
--I'm on it!
[NATSUMI, grunts, moans]
--[KOUSAKU] Stop squirming!
--[NATSUMI] Let me go!
[grunting]
Damn you! Stop it!
[NATSUMI] Let me out!
Let! Me! Out!
[NOL48] Come and eat
our veggies!
Just look at this delightfully
scrumptious eggplant
nestling between
her two gigantic fun bags!
Ugh. Marketing is so beneath me.
Whatever, it works like
a charm every time.
Hang in there, Boobs,
you'll make it through this.
"Boobs"?! Don't call me that!
[KEI] Check us out, ladies!
[LADIES] Huh?
So. Want to take a bite
of my eggplant?
Or would you like to
munch on my big cuke?
Or, my tomatoes?!
[WOMEN screaming]
[shrieks] Someone let me
outta here right now!
I have crops to harvest!
[KEI]
All that work, and in the end,
we still couldn't even
come close to competing
with the Hexa Techs brand.
So is that the reason
you beat us,
'cause people have heard of
Hexa Techs before?!
That's not it.
[KEI] What?!
[MENJOU] Give it a try.
[gasps]
[MENJOU] You too.
It tastes good.
It does. Really good.
What?! But how?!
How can that be?!
[gasps, whimpers]
You've poo-poo'd our vegetables
from the very beginning,
and even agreed on a
head-to-head showdown
without so much as even
tasting what we have to offer.
Do you know what
that makes you, Kei?
A naïve little brat!
[KEI gasps]
[MENJOU] Answer me this:
how many hours do you devote
to your vegetables every day?
One hour? Two? Five,
perhaps six at most?
We at Hexa Techs
attend to our vegetables
24 hours a day,
7 days a week.
You students, with your
little farming hobby,
could never compete with the
superiority of our product!
Fine. Spin it however you want,
but all you're really doing
is manipulating F1s
and you know it!
Hexa Techs embraces technology,
is that so abominable?
[gasps]
[MENJOU] Do you really
believe that vegetables
raised by nature alone
are somehow nobler
than those that have been
researched and improved
by scientific methods?
Tell me: do you intend
to rewrite the very history
of agriculture?
No, I just...
Look, what I'm
trying to say is--
It's vulgar. Everything you do
is for money, that's all.
The truth is, I've absolutely
no respect for you!
[MENJOU] Our product is safer.
Far less expensive!
And above all else,
tastes better!
So tell me:
Where's the vulgarity
in what I do? Eh?!
It's called progress!
[KEI gasps]
[MENJOU] You fool!
That remark of yours belittles
not only agricultural workers,
but it's also an insult
to the consumer!
[KEI] No. That's not true.
Everything I fight for is for
the good of the consumer.
You-You're dead wrong.
I keep my vegetables organic
and pesticide-free for them!
You still don't get it, do you?
You're just imposing
your own shallow,
unilateral idealism onto them.
Can you grow
delicious vegetables
without chemicals
and pesticides?
To grow truly tasty,
delectable vegetables,
you need high-level
farming techniques
and the commensurate experience.
And last I checked,
you had neither.
But at Hexa Techs
we have plenty.
So brand recognition
isn't the only reason you lost.
I've failed. It's over!
I'm a man of my word...
So take me where you will!
[ALL whimper]
No. Actually,
I've changed my mind.
You what?!
[MENJOU] I can't let my
company fail in the hands
of a successor that cares
only to grow paltry crops.
You are free to do
as you wish.
I don't understand!
[MENJOU] You want to win?
Then find a realistic method
to grow better vegetables
than your old man.
[KOUSAKU] I hope the
study abroad program
gives you what you need!
If I don't get to know my enemy,
how can I ever hope
to defeat him?
And besides, I really should see
what this world has to offer.
I'm a little worried
that you-know-who
hasn't shown up yet.
Yeah, where is Boobs?
[KOCHOU] Have no fear,
Kochou's here!
[RINGO] Oh, wow.
[MINORI] The little princess
looks like a bride
about to leave for
her honeymoon.
[KOCHOU] No, no, no, no, no,
you're wrong!
I resent the implication!
What you see here is nothing
more than proper etiquette!
You country bumpkins know
nothing of the chic world
of international travel.
Umm. Come along, Kei Kamatori.
Right.
Well, I guess it's time to go.
Yep. You guys be careful.
Woo! Bring me something awesome!
See you later, guys.
[MINORI]
Cheerful Farming Village.