[KOUSAKU] Tamo No-Rin High
School, Class 2-A Daily Journal.
Entry by Kousaku Hata.
Today was pretty
typical, actually.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Same people, same routine.
Everybody just
keeping on keeping on.
Kind of a yawn-fest, really.
[KOUSAKU] I helped check out the
cornstalks,
making sure that bugs or disease
weren't getting to them.
Ah... You need
something, Yoshida?
[gasps]
Hey, what's up? I didn't know
you were on corn duty.
Yeah. Me neither.
Not that it
particularly matters,
but I wonder what you
out-of-towners are doing
for summer break?
So far all we know
is our training schedule.
[KOCHOU] W-What about Kamatori?
Is he going home?
Sticking around?
[KOUSAKU] I don't know.
One way to find out, though.
Hey, Kei!
[KOCHOU] Ugh! Dammit!
Were you dropped on your head?!
Need something, Kousaku?
So what do you got
lined up for this summer?
Probably stay on campus
and work for a bit.
We should make a trip
down to the beach, yeah?
You want to come with?
[KOCHOU] B... B... You idiot!
How dare you invite me to
tag along all casual-like?
You've got some nerve!
So, you don't want to go
on a beach trip with Kei?
Must we hold this conversation
out in the open for all to see?
You are an evil mastermind!
Or an idiot! I can't tell which!
Shh!
I don't hear any birds.
Or the livestock.
[goat bleats]
Something's coming.
Kei, what is it?
Something... inhuman.
It's here!
[gasps]
It's a demon!
You like a boy?
Where's mine?!
Of course!
It was summoned by Yoshida's
obvious love for Kei,
which I totally didn't
mean to out, but whatever!
Huh? How's it my fault?!
Run for it, Youkul! Go!
Dude, his name's Jun...
[goat screams]
[NATSUMI snarls]
Yoshida! Get the
girls to school!
[KOCHOU] I'm on it!
Kei! Don't let the cougar-demon
touch you, or game over!
[BOYS gasp, scream]
[BOY screams]
Horny teacher!
Calm your fury!
Whatever you may be,
cougar or spinster loli,
these boys are
not yours to devour!
Yeah, she ain't
gonna like that.
Young love can suck it!
[KOUSAKU]
Are you all right, Kei?
Yeah!
She's heading for the campus!
The girls are in danger!
[GIRLS scream]
[RINGO grunts]
[MINORI] Ringo--no!
[KOCHOU] Are you okay?!
We'll never catch her!
Damn it!
Oh, Youkul!
Still not his name, bro.
[KOCHOU] Kei!
[NATSUMI growls]
Yaaah!
[NATSUMI babbles incoherently]
All right!
You saved us all!
Goodness.
She didn't go down easy.
You showed her who's boss!
Yoshida, were you hurt?
Are you okay?
Huh?! Of course I'm okay!
Why would you even ask?
That's good.
Glad to hear it.
Huh...?
[NATSUMI] Wait until your goods
start migrating south,
Tits McGee. You'll know
my suffering soon enough!
[KOUSAKU] Whatever,
Teach--you're just jelly.
[KOUSAKU] So, yeah,
corn duty was pretty dull.
And homeroom was
same old, same old.
Honestly, kind of...
...a bust.
Hey there, little lady.
So what caliber of ammo
are you smuggling?
H-cup? Or I?
Damn, they're big.
Hey! Don't give them
the third-degree!
But... I gots to know!
[KOUSAKU] That's enough
of that, fella!
"Fella?"
You think those sweater-puppies
can be kenneled in a cup-size?
That's like trying to store
the Sahara in a litter-box!
[MINORI] Huh?
That said, if you want
to think about 'em in terms
of a cup size, they are...
World Cup boobs!
World Cup boobs?
[KOUSAKU] Duh!
No one country can lay claim
to such god-tier knockers!
Those watermelons are worldwide!
[MOBUYOUMA] I'll pass!
Big boobs are nothing more than
oversized bags of bovine fat.
Really, they do nothing
but hinder a woman.
Any busty girl
will tell you so.
Yeah! A-cup forever, haters!
[KOUSAKU whimpers] Seriously?!
Hey, Boss!
You want to drop some knowledge
about the itty-bitties?
Don't call me "Boss".
Call me "Big Brother"!
What the hell?
Allow me to demolish
his worldview.
[KOUSAKU] Sure.
Men are creatures that wish
to be mothered on some level.
Nothing symbolizes that role
as well, as the breast.
Ergo, huge breasts
are the realm of the real man!
Says you.
[KEI] What?!
The desire for mothering
is a real phenomenon.
However... Any self-respecting
guy should be well
out of that phase
by high school.
As they break away
from their parents
and become men
in their own right,
a new desire starts
to rear its head!
You're overlooking a
biological directive!
What is it? Enlighten me,
tiny schoolgirl!
[RORIITA] Behold!
Paternal instinct!
[KEI gasps] Say what?
[RORIITA] As a boy
grows into a man,
he awakens to a new
paternal instinct within.
What use has he for teats?
Giving a little girl
fatherly love
is the most natural of acts
for a grown male!
Anything less is a case
of arrested development!
Yay! [giggles]
Higher, big brother!
Having fun?
[GIRL] Uh-huh!
I love you, big brother!
[KEI] I admit. Such a
scenario is appealing.
Yikes...
[laughs] So,
what size do you like?
Huh? Boob-wise?
Mmm...
You know, boobs are nice and
all, but at the end of the day,
I'm more of a foot guy, really.
[RORIITA] Huh?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah.
Like the soles of a girl who's
wearing black knee-highs.
Or maybe she's been clomping
around in shoes all day,
and now they're,
you know... musty...
--[KOUSAKU giggles]
--[KEI] Are you having fun?
--Why, yes... Yes I would!
--No, big brother's arms
--like to rub them for you!
--aren't getting tired at all!
'Sup, guys! How's it hangin'?
[NATSUMI] C'mon!
That was totes adorbs!
[STUDENTS] You're over forty!
How come you're so
mean to me? Boo-hoo!
I'm trying to be as young
and lively as possible!
You've got to respect that!
[STUDENTS] No, we don't!
You look ridiculous!
Better to be ridiculous
than dead!
[STUDENTS gasp]
My Gaia...
Burn them with moe!
[screaming]
She's so powerful! How could
a woman her age be so strong?
In a world where
couples are running amok,
she appears to punish us
for their happiness!
She fights with the force of a
thousand ignored
online-dating profiles!
She rises from the ashes
of her own wreck of a
love-life again and again!
She is the
perpetually-single Phoenix!
Run, you fools!
Get out of here!
Wrong Side of Forty.
Genma. Fist!
[baby cries]
[NATSUMI] Birth.
Kindergarten.
Elementary school.
Middle school.
High school.
College.
Work.
Suddenly, I was forty...
...and just as friggin'
lonely as ever...
Even my 13-year-old niece
has a boyfriend.
Seriously, life,
what the actual hell?
[STUDENTS] Holy crap!
Wrinkles! The wrinkles
are everywhere!
[wails] My boobs
will be down to my feet!
Going out to eat, and
every single time
it's the same thing:
"Becky, party of one!"
The future...
it really sucks!
I never knew that being
an adult was so horrible!
It's nothing but loneliness!
Day after day,
a never-ending parade of suck!
We'd all be better off dead!
[STUDENTS scream]
That took the piss
outta ya, huh?!
[screaming]
Now, who loves Becky?
[STUDENTS] Me.
[KOUSAKU] The afternoon
class was Home Ec.
"If you make something
good to eat...
...you'll have 'em lined
up down the street."
It's Kousaku's...
...and Ringo's...
...cooking show!
"Let's Go Home Ec!"
Hey, everybody,
you know what time it is.
Let's bring out our guest
instructor for the day, yeah?
[KOUSAKU] She was top of
her class in culinary school,
and won the Worldwide
Singles Cooking Contest
22 years in a row!
You know her...
You love her...
...kind of...
It's Ms. Becky!
I say 40 is the new 18!
Well, Ms. Becky, you certainly
seem glad to be here.
[phone vibrates]
Is that a phone?
Come on, you guys.
It's really distracting to hear
that in the middle of a--
Oh, my bad.
You want to answer it?
That is not a phone!
All-righty!
Today's dish is so good,
just one bite and any man
will be yours forever!
[giggles]
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Better eat up!
This feline's got needs, Hata!
Me-Meow!
Kill me.
Put something in his
mouth that he likes.
Maybe he'll return the favor!
Know what I mean?
Hata, what do you like to eat?
[coughs] I'm not really
that picky, but...
I kind of draw the line
at natto. I mean, it's so--
What the hell
do you like to eat?!
It wasn't a
hard question, was it?!
Time to shave
the tuna, you guys!
Now...
Check it out. Skipjack.
No second-rate bonito
for you guys.
Well, Ringo, how do you
think it smells?
Like tuna, because it's tuna.
[NATSUMI] Aw, geez!
Stop the tape! Cut!
We got to take that react again.
Why'd we stop filming?
Oh, come on.
Check the mannequin for a pulse,
'cause that was crappy-crap.
I don't think color commentary
is Ringo's forte.
[NATSUMI] If you think you can
coast by on your fresh face
and thousand-yard-stare, just
sit your bony ass down already!
I don't think we need
that for this recipe!
Yeah. Calm your tits.
Now, I'll show you
how to prep skipjack tuna
the Ms. Becky way!
[sniffs]
Oh, my... This thing has
such a musky odor to it.
But I... kind of like it.
Wow. There's
something on the tip!
Is that what I think it is,
you naughty skipjack--?
No, it's not!
[NATSUMI grunts] I'm sorry.
I guess I got a little
ahead of myself.
Get it? "A little head?"
[KOUSAKU sighs heavily]
Hey, Hata! Want to
be a pal and shave this down?
Aw. I'm going to be sad to
see you go, mister skipjack.
You're like a giant di--
Kousaku reporting in
for shaving duty!
Shave, shave, shave...
Faster, faster!
Don't be so rough.
Shave... Shave...
Gimme a Latin beat!
Shave, sh-sha-shave
Right, now show me your O-face!
What is your problem?!
After that, you fill up
a bowl with white rice!
[KOUSAKU sighs] Here.
Knock yourself out.
Then, you grab a
big bottle of sauce!
So what're we making
here, anyway?
What the--?
Rice bowl--voila!
Loved up and good to go!
Isn't that a bit too simple
for a cooking show?
Ah-ah-ah! There's no point
going crazy in the kitchen
when you're the only one
who's going to be eating
the final product, right?
Here's the reality.
On any given day, you just go
from your apartment to work
and then back home again.
[NATSUMI] At work,
your so-called peers
avoid you like the plague.
And they somehow forget
to invite you to their parties
every damn time.
When you get home,
you're too tired to do anything
but flop into bed and
sleep in your makeup,
'cause that's a good idea.
On your rare days off,
you spend all your time
being lazy and farting around
on the internet.
Why bother cooking for reals?
Now what do you think?
I think white rice
with toppings is okay.
On to another topic!
[BOTH sigh]
When you're cooking,
there are five seasonings
that are fundamental.
Ringo, would you care
to list them off
with that perfect little
poker face of yours?
Sugar is one of them.
Salt is, too. Vinegar also.
--And then--
--[NATSUMI] And then?!
Huh? Uh...
Ur-urrr!
Sugar, salt, vinegar,
der-der-der!
Der-der-der! Bwalala!
Enough smack-talk!
The other two are soy sauce
and miso, now aren't they?
Miso horny!
[NATSUMI grunts]
Hey wait, isn't it a
turn-on for guys
when they see a girl
cooking for them?
No way! That's just...
[giggles] You're home! Take me!
Ms. Becky, it's high time
we got down to making it, yeah?
What, a baby?
No, the food!
Okay, then! I'll get
the cutting board!
Sorry about that,
Ringo! My mistake!
Your chest is so flat,
I guess I thought it was
the cutting-board!
Goodness, I am such a bonehead!
--Maybe she'll have some boobs
--Down, Ringo!
--when she's older!
--She's not worth it!
And for dessert, we'll make
delicious strawberries
topped with condensed milk!
Wash and drain the berries,
then put them in a bowl.
Then pour on the condensed milk
and you're golden!
This stuff doesn't even
count as cooking anymore.
Oh! And there I go again!
I meant to reach for the
condensed milk,
and I went for the
condensed boobies!
I mean, just look at them!
[KOUSAKU] Go to your
happy place!
The only reason I seem
flat is because of Chubs
and the Boob Monster over there!
Don't call me "Chubs!"
What the hell?!
"Boob Monster?!"
What's the matter, Ms. Becky?
You're really letting Ringo
have it this afternoon.
'Cause I'm jealous, dammit!
Lay off the milk, okay?
[NATSUMI] Listen up, new girl!
Don't go getting full
of yourself
just 'cause you're young!
Before you got here, the boys
were all in love with me!
[KOUSAKU] What world
are you living in?
--Kiss me, gorgeous!
--I don't wanna!
[NATSUMI] So be it.
I'll just cook up
your little crush, then!
You're on the menu, missy!
Today's special is Ringo breast,
if I can find any meat!
[RINGO]
Take your best shot, Grandma.
[KOUSAKU stutters]
I don't think this is helpful!
[KEI] Stand down, ladies!
When you have a dispute in
the realm of home ec,
you settle it with a
cook-off showdown!
Chef One! Ms. Kinoshita!
Miso soup?
Soup is pretty simple.
I don't know if
this is going to do it.
Well, nobody said it
had to be flashy.
It's just tofu, right?
We all like red miso a lot,
so I'm glad she used it!
Good call there, Ringo!
Now, for the moment of truth!
[slurping]
What am I tasting?!
There's a strong fishiness
to it, like a seafood stock,
and a smell that's
making my eyes water!
The flavor is so rich,
and so powerful!
It's almost too much, but
there's something about it
that I just can't
get out of my mind!
This bowl is a chalice
given to us by the gods of miso,
and the blessed broth within
is a miracle to be cherished!
Is he nuts? I can't take
another sip of this stuff.
[MINORI] It's sour,
and kind of fishy.
It makes me feel all barfy.
[KOUSAKU] Ringo!
What perfect food did
you use to make this soup?
Old slippers.
[RINGO] You know that
brown part of the insole?
Yeah, I mostly used that.
[KOUSAKU]
You cured my foot kink!
[RINGO] It made the
soup stock really brown.
So the red miso you
tossed in just for color?
Hey, you guys.
Can we name Becky the winner
so I can go and throw up?
Yeah, no kidding.
Whatever she made,
it's got to be better than this
foot-soup Ringo hit us with.
Not a chance. We have to
try both for it to be fair.
Ms. Becky, it's your turn.
You're gonna like my dish.
I have every confidence
you'll be coming back for more!
Huh? Just rice?
So, uh, what about a side dish?
That is the side!
Here's the main course!
[screaming]
[STUDENTS scream]
That's disgusting!
Kill it with fire!
Well. Hurry up and eat.
Or else the best-by date
will pass you by
That best by date's long gone!
You are a teacher,
you nymphomaniac!
How have they not fired you yet?
Daddy's a big-shot politician.
I'm not going anywhere!
Now all the mysteries
are solved!
Come on, class!
No need to be shy!
Here. Eat Ms. Becky!
Just do it!
[NATSUMI giggles] That's a
good class. Don't worry.
There is plenty of Becky
to go around!
Huh? Uh, hold up. This is not
what I had in mind, fellas!
[STUDENTS] Heave-ho!
[screams]
[NATSUMI] Not the
going down I wanted--!
[KOUSAKU coughs] "If you make
something good to eat...
...you'll have them lined
up down the street."
[BOTH] 'Til next time.
"Let's Go Home Ec!"
[KOUSAKU] So, there you have it.
Just another ordinary,
average day like any other.
Kind of dull, actually.
Well, there was that thing
that happened on the way back
from our shopping trip, I guess.
Is this it?
[MINORI] Mm-hmm.
[KOUSAKU]
Minotamo Rock Festival, huh?
If we get up to the
stage and it looks like fun,
you guys maybe want to go up
there and give it a shot?
We've never played in a band
together before--I don't know.
Well, I think the five of us
could fake our way
through something.
She's right. If you're really
worried about how we'd sound,
then we could always go with
the visual kei route, you know.
We can even disguise Kinoshita,
if we go heavy on the make-up.
Visual kei, huh?
Yeah, sounds like fun!
We are gonna look so cool!
I'm going to
irrigate your soul!
That could be a song!
[KOUSAKU]
Nope.
That stage is pretty small.
Just the right size for
a bunch of noobs like us!
That's the spirit! Let's do it!
[ANNOUNCER] All right, folks,
our next act is called AKB40!
I thought it was 48.
[gasps] Isn't that?
Hey, guys! I missed you so much!
[GROUP] Ms. Becky?!
Now I get it!
That wasn't a mistake!
AKB40 means--!
Ancient! Teacher! Becky! Age 40!
Here comes my latest song!
"Give me a Man--Now!"
♪ You and I now share
the same last name, ♪
♪ No mistaking
it's a different game. ♪
♪ "Catch ya' later's"
just so hard to own; ♪
♪ Think I'd much prefer
you said, "Honey, I'm home." ♪
♪ I'll wait patiently for you to
shamble through the door. ♪
♪ Did I just hear
a key in the lock? ♪
♪ Can I finally take my eyes
off the clock? ♪
♪ Someone marry me!
(Be my devotee!) ♪
♪ I'm a catch, you'll see!
(How bad can it be?) ♪
♪ I'm so sick of chasing men
from sea to shining sea! ♪
♪ Bachelor's hear my plea:
(Men are what I need...) ♪
♪ Take a chance with me!
(Hotties preferably!) ♪
♪ Sweep me off my feet and
let this ponytail fly free! ♪
[NATSUMI shrieks]
Thanks, you guys!
--You're such a swell audience!
--What was that...?
That just happened, right?
[KEI] Receptions.
She's dealt with two decades
of wedding karaoke.
Howled her needs
into a mic time after time.
Think about it.
Is it so odd that she'd have a
couple of songs up her sleeve?
Not at all.
This next one is called:
"Old People Smell Funny!"
One, two, thr--!
[KOUSAKU] School Swim Trunks.