[MALE ANCHOR]
In other news, the heat is on
as the temperature soars
and the mercury rises,
though fun-seekers at Oarai
Beach will not be deterred.
[KOUSAKU] You know, when I was
kid, I couldn't say "Oarai."
So I used to think
it was pronounced
"Old Wall-Eye" Beach.
It did seem like a
weird name, though.
Huh. Your brain must
be a fascinating place.
Guys, it just dawned on me.
I haven't been to the beach
yet this summer.
[MINORI] Yeah.
I haven't been to the beach,
like, once in my entire life.
[ALL gasp]
Okay, that shouldn't
even be possible! Wow.
You-You're absolutely serious?
[MINORI] Mm-hmm...
I'm just going to come
right out and say that's sad.
Well, it's not like there's a
shoreline where we're from, so.
But don't they take you
on field trips?
Sure they do!
In grade school they
took us to Kyoto and Nara.
Then when we were older,
in middle school they
took us to Nara and Kyoto.
Sounds like the teachers
were really trying
to broaden your minds.
[RINGO] All right.
It's sand and surf time!
The schedule's flexible.
I think we ought to be able to
squeeze in some fun in the sun.
Yeah! We got a break coming up.
Let's get our feet wet!
Woo-hoo!
Nice...
Ringo in beachwear...
Something fun...
Something skimpy...
That's a fabulous idea.
Where do I sign?
[KEI] Hell yeah!
We've worked hard!
And now we play hard!
[ALL] Yeah!
[KOUSAKU] But on the big day...
Unfortunately for those
planning a day at the beach,
this category one typhoon
lost none of its strength
before making landfall.
[KOUSAKU]
Mother Nature had other ideas.
[KEI] Flash flood warning, wind
advisory, lighting advisory,
rockslide advisory. Whoa-boy.
Trifecta plus one.
In poker, this would be
a straight flush.
Are we counting high-tide
and storm-surge warnings?
'Cause, uh, if so, we're going
to need another metaphor here.
This really sucks, guys.
Wow. A category one? On top of
all the rain we've been having
the past couple of weeks?
The weather this summer
has been out of control.
[MINORI] Beach! Beach!
Beach! Beach! Beach!
[MINORI shrieks]
Hah. And speaking of
out of control.
[MINORI]
The point is to get wet, right?!
So why are we letting
a measly little typhoon
rain on our parade?!
Damn it, I want to go to beach!
This isn't fair!
Minori! Please! Look, we all
want to go to the beach,
but we can't get there if
the buses aren't running.
There's nothing stopping us from
using our bicycles,
--is there? [sobs]
--I vote we tranquilize her!
Bikes won't do a whole
lot of good under water.
No one's going anywhere
in this, all right?
The beach will still be there
when our next break comes
around. We can go then.
I'll even buy you
an ice cream cone.
Is that a promise?!
If you calm down, yes.
Cross my heart, 'kay?
Okay! But we'll have to be
good and wait thirty minutes
before getting in the water!
Forces beyond all human
understanding are at work!
Ugh. Fantastic.
Just what we need.
[KEI] What happened to you?
They cancelled practical lab
on account of the weather.
I didn't get the notification
till I was halfway here.
And with all
the buses shut down,
let's just say I've had worse
days, but not all that many.
So, have they
cancelled everything?
Yep. And it looks
like I'm stuck here
till the weather decides to
stop being a pain in the ass.
Huh. Actually,
I guess we all are.
Yeah, well.
At least we're staying dry.
[RINGO] What kind of
practical lab was it?
Oh, just
cymbidium repositioning.
Cym... bi--what now?
Cym-bidium. It's an orchid.
One that prospers in the
southeast part of Asia.
Specifically in the crisp air
of the plateau.
We haul them up the
mountain each summer
to prevent their being
blasted by seasonal winds.
[KOUSAKU] The wind's
that rough on them, huh?
Indeed, and the plants
don't develop well
--when it's too hot.
--Perfect swan dive! Woo-hoo!
If they're stunted,
then they're worthless.
--[KOUSAKU] Wow. Didn't know
--Makin' a sandcastle!
--orchids were your thing.
--Sandcastle, sandcastle...
Didn't I mention
what they go for?
[KOUSAKU] Of course.
Oh, historically, orchids
have been known to fetch
a king's ransom
on the open market.
Collectors the world over
go nuts for the little buggers.
So... Anyway,
before the storm hit
the plan was for us to haul a
batch of new cymbidiums
to market in the microbus.
Whoa. The microbus, huh?
You got to be brave
to ride in that thing.
[KANEGAMI] Truth is, with this
wind, I'm just as worried
about the greenhouse as I am
about the flowers themselves.
One good gust and
it's all she wrote.
[KOUSAKU]
Hadn't thought of that.
Hey, uh... You think we should
close the storm shutters?
I mean, better safe
than sorry, right?
Yeah. Good idea.
Ah! Can you believe this?
Kind of Humbling, isn't it?
It's like...
I know.
[KOUSAKU] An ocean.
[KEI] Right?
[MINORI grunting]
Like an ocean.
[MINORI gasps] Ocean?!
Crap.
Stop her! Don't be
afraid to use force!
[KOUSAKU grunts]
Beach boys!
[laughs] Sweet liberty!
Minori! Get back
in here right now!
The glorious ocean
has come to us!
I feel like a mermaid!
[MINORI laughs]
It's not the ocean,
it's a flood!
[MINORI laughs]
This is beyond awesome!
Look at me! I'm swimming!
Earth to Minori! You'll drown!
The current's gonna
sweep you away!
[MINORI] This is so much fun!
[growls] Idiot.
[MINORI] So. Much. Fun!
Really?
[MINORI]
I've never felt so alive!
[KOUSAKU] This is ridiculous.
Get out of there, damn it!
This isn't--!
Yah-hoo!
--Splash!
--Oh, it is totally on now!
[MINORI laughs]
I ain't afraid of you!
[BOTH laugh]
Whoo!
No having fun
without me, guys!
[ALL laughing]
[gasps]
[MINORI, RINGO laughing]
[laughing continues]
Should I feel dirty
or is this normal?
Hey, it's just mud. There's
not a thing dirty about it.
[KOUSAKU] We're just two guys
enjoying the scenery.
[KEI] Key word: enjoying.
Someone find a
beach ball right now.
I want to do like they do
in the movies!
Volleyball!
[whistle blows]
[KOUSAKU] Service!
[KOUSAKU] Good game, everybody!
[ALL] Yay!
Okay, now we have to
split a watermelon!
Who's got one?
Somebody say watermelon?!
[MINORI] Huh?
Yeah! Watermelon!
[ALL] Woo!
Right! Time for some barbeque!
[MINORI] I'm all over it!
The lighter won't cooperate.
Bring on the kerosene!
[MINORI] Aye aye, captain!
[MINORI yells]
[RINGO] Stand clear!
We've made fire!
Yeah, because we rock!
Still, either way!
[ALL] Bonfire!
I could really go
for some music.
[KOUSAKU] Music,
coming right up!
Sick summer beats, anyone?!
♪
[ALL] Party time!
[KOCHOU] Are you plebeians
out of your minds?!
You'll spook the livestock!
Yoshida, hey! Heads up,
Fun Bags at 6 o'clock!
[ALL] Yay!
What on earth is
wrong with you people?!
Aw, come on! Live at little!
Get this farm-wear off!
Proper beach party
attire only!
Take your filthy paws off me
this instant, Vulgarians!
Well, well! Lookie here!
For all your whining you
actually came prepared!
You always wear a
bikini under there?
It's not a bikini,
it's my underwear, you moron!
[ALL] Busting out!
Busting out! Busting out!
[ALL] Yay!
[BOYS] Not so fast!
[GROUP] Huh...?
[GUY A] How dare you?
This is hallowed ground!
[GUY B] Our beach is not
the place for you people
to let it all hang out!
Who are they?
[BOTH] Ha! Feast your eyes on
Tamo No-Rin's world class
beach volleyball team-ah!
[GROUP] We have a
volleyball team?!
Given that we're nowhere
near an actual beach,
isn't that sort of like
a regional hockey league
in the tropics?
Whatever you guys want,
just leave us alone!
Can't you see we're busy
stripping our friend here
down to her undies?!
Maybe we were a little
too quick to judge.
Hey!
[GUY A] Allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm the team's preppy
nice-guy captain, Hamaoka.
My comrade's name...
Butter. Ken Butter.
[KOUSAKU] Wait. Hold up.
THE Ken Butter?
[RINGO] Does this guy
have a reputation?
[KOUSAKU] I don't know.
Never heard of him in my life.
If I say he's one of Biotech's
so-called Sweet Musketeers
whose name everyone associates
with prize-winning treats,
I'm just talking outta my ass.
Want to make your
toast slick?
Try... Ken... Butter!
Shut up, please.
Care for a little
friendly competition?
Huh?
See, we're in the
middle of gearing up
for the regional tournament.
Got to get your practice on
when and where you can,
know what I mean?
[growls]
Where are they having
this tournament?
Nagano!
There's no frigging
beach in Nagano!
Um, yeah. Hello.
It's called a day trip, dude!
Where was it
last year?
Gunma.
Oh, come on!
The year before that,
they held it in Saitama.
Not to be that girl, but,
none of those places
are near the ocean.
Where exactly do you play?
Oh. Riverbeds.
Wow. Must hurt.
Look, never mind
about that, all right?!
Just play with us!
Pretty please?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure, no problem. What's up?
The fields are
taking a real beating.
Uh-oh. This is bad.
[KOUSAKU]
We've got to hurry!
The rice will be
completely submerged!
So I'm guessing that's
not a good thing?
Rice is a finicky plant,
you have to be careful.
You want the stalks under
water, but not the ears.
If that happens,
they'll start to sprout
in which case,
the yield will be nothing.
Really?
[KOUSAKU] Really!
We won't be able to eat it,
we won't be able to sell it.
We won't even be able to use it
to fertilize next year's crop.
All our hard work for nothing!
[RINGO] Oh no!
Now what? What's the plan?
I mean, what are we
--supposed to do?
--It's okay. We, uh...
We got this.
[MINORI] Oh crap!
[KEI] Look at it!
[KANEGAMI] Sorry. If only
I'd have noticed this sooner.
[KOCHOU]
Calm yourselves, Vulgarians!
What's been the purpose
of your training if not--!
[HAMAOKA] One moment, please!
[HAMAOKA] Okay. Take two--in
five, four, three, two...
--[growls] You disgust me!
--[HAMAOKA, KEN scream]
[KOCHOU] As I was saying.
Once more, from the top.
Your training has
prepared you for this!
We are nothing if not
agricultural students
and this is our moment to shine!
[ALL] Oohhh...
Kousaku, take charge!
Everyone else, follow!
From here on out,
we take all orders from you,
this includes me!
Are we agreed?
[ALL] Fun Bags!
A yes or no would suffice!
Right. First, we open the
rear drain. It's all you, Kei!
[KEI grunts, yells]
[growls, screams]
And what's a rear drain?
It's a kind of like a vent.
Regulates the water level.
[RINGO] To keep the ears
from getting submerged?
Provided the wind doesn't
blow them over, exactly.
[KEI screams]
[KEI] Come to papa!
[KEI grunting]
[RINGO] Kamatori!
Kei! Are you going
to be all right?!
[KEI] I'm good! It's just...
Just a little mud!
I'll be damned if
the drain gets clogged!
I got this!
Cool!
Now that Kei's bought us some
time, let's rope off the field!
[GIRLS] Right!
[grunting]
[KOUSAKU]
I need everyone to be careful!
Don't fall on the plants!
[KANEGAMI] Understood.
Hamaoka, run back to the school
and bring us some
more rope, STAT!
You got it!
Yoshida, your jugs are
crushing the stalks!
I'm sorry!
Minori, stop letting
your ass poke out!
Ringo, you're doing
perfect. Nice job!
Butter dude!
What the hell are you doing?
Where are you pants?
Aw, no worries.
Butter totally repels water!
[KOUSAKU] Gross, but okay.
All right, that ought
to hold her for now.
Good on us, huh?
Class D's field
shouldn't take too long.
[KOCHOU] Kousaku!
[KOUSAKU] What is it?
The rice in Class D's field
is growing way too quickly!
Huh?
[KOCHOU] The stalks are so tall
the ears are drooping.
The ropes can't support them!
The crop is done for!
Why would they grow it so fast?
Hey, what's the deal
with Class D?
I'm sorry...
We planted Koshihikari.
What in the hell would you
do a thing like that for?!
Is that bad?
Koshihikari has a reputation
for falling over so easily,
it's nickname is "Collapsikari!"
It sprouts up too tall!
[gasps]
[KOUSAKU] With the stalks
already that long...
...they don't stand a chance.
This wind will knock 'em over
like bowling pins!
[RINGO] Oh no!
Why would you guys cultivate
something so risky?!
What was I supposed to do?!
This particular variety
sells like gang-busters!
You won't be selling
much of anything
when the whole field
goes tits up!
You two, quit your bickering!
Now is not the time
for that argument!
[KOUSAKU] You're right!
There are more
important things to focus on!
Captain Aramis must
save the day! Pronto!
Just... Just give me
a minute to think.
[KOUSAKU]
There's too many stalks for us
to move them out of harm's way.
The only thing to do
is block the wind.
Except... how, exactly?
Hey, our volleyball net
is super durable.
Why don't we use that?
[KOUSAKU] Last I checked,
a net is made of holes!
We need something
that'll make a wall.
Well, sandbagging would
be the best option,
except it's a
little late for that.
Thank you, Captain Obvious!
Ah! Ah-ha! Kanegami! The keys!
[KANEGAMI] Huh?
[KOUSAKU]
To the microbus! Give me!
You had it gassed up to move
the cymbidiums, didn't you?
[KANEGAMI] Ugh. Of course.
What are you
cooking up there, chief?
[KOUSAKU] Sorry!
No time to explain!
I'll be back, just start
roping off the field!
Ha! This is gonna work...
[RINGO] Kousaku!
Ringo! The field!
The others have it
covered, it's okay.
Fun Bags didn't like you
wandering off on your own
in the storm, so she
asked me to stay with you.
Yeah, thanks. I'm a child.
Thank you, Fun Bags...
[RINGO] So what's
your big plan, exactly?
[KOUSAKU] We're gonna
improvise a wall.
[RINGO] O-kay...
It's simple: drive this upwind
and we block the gusts.
Stay with me here: Class D's
field is the furthest up, right?
Of its four sides,
three are flanked by roads.
If we drive the microbus
to the road up top,
it'll shield their
crop from the wind.
I had no idea you
even knew how to drive.
I don't, but it's a
standard diesel engine.
So, you know...
It can't be that
different from a tractor.
[engine sputters]
Okey-doke. First gear.
Release the emergency brake.
Rev the engine just enough
to get her nice and ready.
Ease up on the clutch
about halfway.
Release the clutch
once we get things a-moving.
[KOUSAKU]
And give her some juice.
Hell yeah!
Didn't even stall once!
That's incredible!
Nothing any farm boy
couldn't do, really.
Thing is...
Yeah?
[KOUSAKU] Driving without
adult supervision
is majorly against the rules.
Miss Becky's gonna be
out-of-her-mind furious.
Watch me get suspension.
You're not alone.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[RINGO] If she gets upset,
it'll be at both of us.
Let's pull this mother out!
[KOUSAKU] Whoa! Aw, damn it!
I can't see the road!
Use the windshield wipers!
The, uh, what?
Those little things that go back
and forth on the windshield!
[RINGO]
It comes with those, right?
Hello?
Yeah, I don't know.
[RINGO gasps]
[KOUSAKU] Well tractors and
combines don't come with them,
how am I supposed
to know about buses?
[whimpers]
[KOUSAKU gasps]
What are you doing?!
Don't freak.
I'm going to act as
your lookout, okay?
I need you to follow my
directions to the letter!
Uh... Okay.
[RINGO] Keep going straight!
You got it!
Start veering to the right!
We're passing the gym!
[KOUSAKU] Veering right!
All right, now
straighten the wheel!
Easy does it, easy does it.
[KEI] Kousaku!
Make a sharp right when
I give the word. Got it?
Yeah!
[RINGO] In three...
Two... One... Now!
[BOTH scream]
[grunts]
[screams]
Ringo!
[gasps]
Hold on, I've got you, okay?
And...
Yoink!
[MINORI] Diet for me, please!
[KEI] OJ, thanks.
[KOCHOU] Oh, orange juice
for me, too, please.
Yeah. Here.
[sighs]
How about it, guys?
Is the marketing teacher
awesome-sauce or what?
Hell yeah you treat the people
who saved your rice crop
to a day at the beach!
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
[chuckles] Yep.
I'm finally going to
see the ocean
for the first time in my life!
The school's not above bending
the rules every now and then.
You're a lucky man, dude.
Can't believe you got off
with a slap on the wrist.
No kidding, right?
If your little stunt
hadn't saved the field,
you'd both be suspended.
Whatever. Big whoop.
It was so totally worth it.
Hey. Kousaku.
Ha?
You, uh, might
wanna listen to this.
[MALE ANCHOR] The typhoon
prone to make landfall
any minute now is even bigger
than last week's category one.
Residents are advised
to stay indoors,
as potential wind speeds
at the storm's core
are projected to be up to
72 kilometers per hour.
[MINORI] I'm going to the beach!
--Try to stop me, I dare you!
--[KOUSAKU] Minori, no! Wait!
--[KEI] Someone restrain her!
--[RINGO] Minori, it's okay.
Focus on the sound of my voice.
--[MINORI] Beach boys!
--[KOUSAKU] You're a girl!
[KEI] Veggie Battle:
Ultimate v. Supreme