[KOUSAKU] I am so tired.
Changing outta these clothes
and grabbing some dinner
sounds awesome right about now.
[screams]
[KOUSAKU] Where are my
Yukatan posters?!
My Yukatan wall scrolls?!
My Yukatan body pillow?!
My Yukata DVD and
BluRay collection?!
My scrapbook of
Yukatan-related news articles?!
[KOUSAKU screams]
Yeah, Dumped them
in the furnace.
Don't say I never
do nothing for you.
[KOUSAKU] What would possess you
to burn my posters?!
Hey! Would you feel
comfortable in a room
with pictures of you
all over the damn wall?!
I did you a favor so
your dream girl won't freak out.
She doesn't need to know
how obsessed you are.
And besides, your mom
begged me to do something.
I promised her I'd watch
your back out here,
so get used to it.
Well. You could've asked.
[MINORI] Don't read too much
into it 'cause just so you know
I'm going to do everything
in my power to make sure
you never hook up
with that little slut.
Believe me,
I know why she's here.
And if Little Miss Pop Sensation
thinks this is the place
to stink up her
would-be green thumb,
she's got another thing coming!
--That doesn't even make sense.
--Oh, doesn't it?!
Whatever, who cares?!
Her first time working the farm
is supposed to be
tomorrow morning, correct?
I think so.
Well, Her Highness is
due for a trial by fire!
Hmph!
Alrighty then.
Does that mean
what I think it does?!
'Cause if the girl I've known
since we were playing doctor
has it in for the girl
who made my gonads drop...
Not that I'm proud of this,
but the whole thing might be
a little too hot
for me to handle.
[MINORI] Huh. I give her credit
for even bothering to show up.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah?
Well if she knew you were
planning to put her
through her paces,
she probably wouldn't have.
[sighs] Of all the
days for Kei to be out
on a welding gig for
shop class. This is balls.
I will own this whore!
Why do I always end up having to
deal with this crap by myself?
That didn't take long.
Don't be shy.
C'mon down and show us all
how you look in the uniform.
Sure thing.
[screams]
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
She looks like... She looks
like a tentacle magnet!
Huh.
Must've given her
the wrong outfit.
In what way exactly
does that suit
of comic-shop stripper-pole
armor look anything
like one of our work uniforms?!
I know what you're up to
and it's just wrong!
Ugh. What I'm up to
is for her own good. Hmph.
She can't work in that!
She'd better learn how quick,
'cause the first test she's got
is coping with distraction!
If she wants to work the earth,
she's got to get over
caring how she looks!
All the more reason
not to stuff her into
something out of
an online fan fic!
This whole thing is ridiculous,
I'm putting my foot down!
I'm okay.
See? She's down with this.
Now then.
Just to show you
I'm a good sport...
[screams]
Yup. Say hi-di-ho to girl power!
Hyah!
Hey!
--Wha--?!
--Whoa-whoa!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
I... can't... take it!
[screams]
Whoa. This is so hot!
Yeah, no. Rein it
in there a bit, tiger.
Huh? Wait. No!
That just came out!
[KOUSAKU whimpers]
[RINGO] Hmph.
Heh! You know,
Miss Kinoshita,
if you're self-conscious
you can back out now.
Like hell.
[KEI] Of course.
[KOUSAKU] Holy crap,
it's a Paladin!
Or just Kei. Seriously, dude?
A suit of armor?
I thought you were
supposed to be out welding.
[KEI] I felt a disturbance
in the force.
And I like to watch.
[MINORI]
Welcome to the Cucumber House.
Hey, Yukatan.
Can I get an autograph?
Screw her, man,
look at this one!
Now that's some produce!
The First job's a cinch.
All you have to do is check
the leaves for diseases
and what not.
See any bugs having a party,
you pick 'em off. Understood?
I'll play nice and
give you the row on the left.
One on the right's mine.
Battle starts
when Kousaku says go.
If he can do it
without drooling.
[KOUSAKU] Wait, why me?
[MINORI] Go on. It's the easiest
job in the world, I promise.
Okay fine, whatever.
Just do it.
And they're off!
In full cosplay!
[KEI] Minori's a sneaky one
when she wants to be.
Huh?
[KEI] Don't get me wrong,
cucumber's a beginner plant,
sure. We all know that,
it's just...
If you're not ready for the
prickly bits on the leaves
and stems, that stuff
can sting like a mother.
[KOUSAKU] Are you saying
Minori put her in bikini armor
on purpose to get her pricked?!
[KEI] Minori knows her cucumber;
she's used to it.
City gal like Ringo, though.
I'd say she's in
for a rude awakening.
[KOUSAKU] Wow. Look at her go!
She's a demon!
[STUDENTS laughing, cheering]
[KEI] Game over, man.
Wait. No. Not yet.
Not until Minori
wipes the floor with her.
Ahh... Oh, right.
I totally forgot.
Yuka may be naturally immune
to the prickly bits.
But what about the caterpillars?
[KEI] Bingo.
Those things make even
a seasoned cumcumber-er's
skin crawl.
[screaming]
And now we see
what she's made of.
No! She's too wet
behind the ears for this!
Get an eyeful of those
cute little buggy-wuggies
and bawl yourself sick.
"Um. Bye, everybody:
I'm going back to the Big City
where the only insects I
have to worry about are flies!"
[STUDENTS] Whooa!
[GUY 3B] Oh snap. Keinez
the Catalyst goes Oratorio!
That's what you call the power
of bikini armor, guys!
[KEI] Of course! Ringo's never
seen a caterpillar before!
How would she know
to be grossed out by one?!
She's too innocent and pure
to realize how vile they are!
Oh my glob, this is amazing!
[KOUSAKU] Whoa! She's closing
the distance between them
--like nobody's business!
--Nice try, sister,
but I didn'tt sign on to be the
laughing stock of my peers!
[MINORI growls]
Clear! Clear!
Clear-clear-clear-clear-clear-
clear-clear-clear-clear...!
[gasping]
Clear!
Photo finish!
Nuh-uh, dude:
Nakazawa won by a nose!
[screams]
Bag, please.
Heh! Yeah, well don't rest
on your laurels just yet.
This battle is far from over.
[MINORI] Next up,
we have the Hen House!
[KEI] Alongside rice farming,
cleaning the chicken coops
is the most important part of a
freshman Ag student's training.
If you can handle what's on
the other side of that door,
you can handle anything.
Good luck in there!
[KEI] Hens are a barnyard
predator's dream.
If we didn't
keep them penned up,
we'd have nothing but bones
and feathers come morning.
The coops are great,
but the downside is they're
humid and, well, cooped.
First one of us to
make the floor shine
without losing her lunch
takes home the gold!
Feathers got to go.
Food scraps got to go.
Poop's got to go.
And if feathers, food scraps,
and poop are too much for you,
you've got to go.
[MINORI laughs]
[GUY 3D] Whoa!
It's nothing to her.
She's acclimated to the smell!
[GUY 3E] Don't call it yet!
We're still just
getting started!
That's right.
The putrid aroma is only the
beginning of her season in hell!
[KEI] The smell you deal with.
The heat you deal with.
But then...
Abandon all hope
ye who enter here!
Oh. Hey, hon?
I love the energy,
but I think you might've
overlooked something important.
Can't forget about
the feed stall, can we?
--[buzzing]
--[KOUSAKU] Aah!
--Whoa!
--[buzzing]
--Aaagh!
[BOTH scream]
It's like a cockroach Armageddon
every time we open that door!
Just think about it, man:
Darkness, humidity, an
all-you-can eat poop buffet.
This is paradise for them!
[laughs] That's right!
Dealing with cockroaches
is part of the job!
Admit defeat and I'll help you
clean them out.
[GUYS screaming]
[GIRLS screaming]
[GUY 3D] Ewww!
She's stepping on them!
[GUY 3E] I'm going to say
what we're all thinking
and call this beyond gross.
Disqualification! Y-You're
supposed to be freaking out!
Sorry.
So, is that it?
[gasping]
[KEI] And the winner is,
Ringo Kinoshita!
Huh?!
Nice.
No! Not yet!
She isn't done!
Minori, please.
Give it up.
We still have to test her
most basic agricultural skill!
Trial by Rice Field!
Rice field?
Oh, yes!
Rice has been a vital part
of the Rising Sun experience
since the Yayoi Period!
You can't claim to know
what it is to be Japanese
until you've gotten your
feet wet! I defy you to try!
Only after you've mastered
our landscaping and
dietary epicenter will I allow
you to count yourself worthy!
[KEI] Uh. Don't oversell it.
Or, stop talking
outta your ass.
Argue all you want.
History is on my side!
But don't worry.
Back out now and I'll
spare you the embarrassment!
Bring it.
Someone's feeling feisty, huh?
[sighs]
All-righty, then.
So, meet at the rice fields
Saturday morning
dressed in clothes you don't
mind getting water-logged.
Woo-hoo.
[KOUSAKU] This field's roughly
one tenth of a hectare.
That's about a
thousand square meters.
[KEI] It takes four people
half a day to plant rice.
Hah! Prepare to watch me set
a new world record, losers!
Um. Before we get started
I'd like to clarify something.
Usually when you're
about to take the plunge.
It's a good idea to dress in
clothes appropriate to the task.
But, uh... Seriously,
you guys, this is just...
I mean, c'mon.
Sorry. Should I change?
Nah, it's okay. No worries.
You definitely rack up points
for thinking ahead.
And looking fly!
You, however!
What's wrong?
What do you mean "What's wrong?"
Have you seen yourself?!
I mean, okay, yes, technically
it is a bathing suit,
so it qualifies as appropriate
for getting wet in and all.
But, other than that,
nothing about what you
have on isn't wrong!
I can't un-see this,
man! Not cool!
[KEI chuckles]
Well you'd be the first
to want to un-see it.
Don't even! That's just...
Where do you go
that people encourage this?!
Let's just say
somewhere popular.
And sopping wet.
Mah! Never mind, dude!
Everybody loves to see
the Gaisenmon.
Whoa, highbrow!
That's like a French English
play on words, bro.
It's a combo of English for dude
and French for Arc of Triumph!
That's why Kei's a trailblazer
and we're just
a couple of followers!
I'm just happy we get to
bask in his presence!
Look, Kei.
I'm not trying to tell you
what to wear, but...
I mean we got to consider
the ladies, right?
Poor Ringo doesn't need to--
Give me a second,
I'm in the middle of something.
[GUYS] Kei is a living god!
Wait, don't encourage him!
Hey! I see you there!
That's the point, silly!
[KOUSAKU]
Has the world gone mad?
This is an Ag school,
you're a teacher here!
Why would you wear something
like that to farm in?
Oh, sweetie.
Wedding dresses
are meant to get soiled.
I'ma need you to not
elaborate on that, please!
Uh-oh. Have I crossed a line?
I'm such a naughty girl.
Somebody really needs to
teach the teacher a lesson.
Okay, you're like a hundred
years old and that's super bleh.
But the experts say
I'm at my peak.
[KOUSAKU] Stop hitting on
your students and go home!
We don't need you to supervise!
Oh stop playing hard to get:
this is every
teenage boy's fantasy.
[KOUSAKU]
I just want to plant rice!
Why is that so
difficult to let me do?!
I don't need this!
I don't deserve this!
You'll never sow your seed in
a field wetter than this MILF,
lover boy!!
[KOUSAKU screams]
How has the school board not
axed you twice-over by now?!
[GUYS] Whooaa...
You're only a MILF
if you actually have children!
Thank you. That was, uh,
that was getting kind of weird.
[MINORI] Hmm. Meh.
Minori's got your back.
Hey, Minori? What're those?
What? Bloomers.
Wait...
Did you...?
[KOUSAKU] Behold.
A deeper shade of blue than sky
on a Spring Afternoon. Wow.
Okay, I'm not trying to say
they're hideous or anything.
But what's the story
with these things?
You've read the
student handbook, right?
Girls are supposed
to wear shorts.
It's no big deal.
I had them sent to me
special for today.
No joke?!
Whoa! Historic!
I can't remember the last time
I saw a pair like these.
Didn't know they
were still a thing.
They're not new or anything.
Just a hand-me-down
from my sisters.
Damn it, Minori,
what is wrong with you?!
What?
I was adjusting the hem
to cover up a mosquito bite.
Well, it's mighty suggestive!
When you're dressed like that,
there's just
some things you can't do!
Hems have been playing
fast and loose
with men's short-term memory
since the caveman days!
The bloomers are too much!
Disqualification!
Control yourself
for five minutes
and they wouldn't be an issue.
Creep.
Whoa, whoa! Don't turn this
into a feminist rant.
You chose them!
Deal with it, pervert!
Wait. What the-- What do
you think you're doing?!
[GUYS] Yeah! Show us some of
that sweet swimsuit action!
[KEI] School swim team uniform.
Bold choice. Very "kyu-suku."
Kyu-suku?
--Now listen closely.
--[KOUSAKU yells]
Kyu-suku refers to a
popular old style swimsuit.
The distinguishing feature of
its design is the crotch area
being divided into
two discreet regions.
This ingenious shape
allowed the wearer
greater flexibility both in
and outside of the pool.
it also protected
the susceptible
female nether regions
from getting water-logged.
Form and function combined
to make a truly wonderful thing.
Yep, this beaut
was a game-changer.
Wow. You guys know water sports.
Well, either way
I'm a fan of the style.
It's just the right balance
of functional and girlie.
And I know nothing
about fashion.
I'm just shooting from the hip.
Don't look at me like that.
[gasps] My bad! I, uh...
I just think
you look great in that.
I mean it totally
suits your curves.
Kind of makes you
look like a model.
[gasps] You... pervert.
[gasps] Forgive me!
I won't look anymore promise!
Chauvinist!
Please. Ladies,
you got to stop this.
The landscape students
are gawking.
Is it too much to ask
that we all just get along?
--[BOTH] Stay out of it!
--[KOUSAKU gasps]
Okay, look, I'm only
trying to point out
that we're about to start the
whole rice-planting thing,
so it's probably best if
everyone lets bygones
be bygones.
[WAKA squeaks]
[BOTH] Ready when you are.
[KOUSAKU sighs]
[KOUSAKU] Alrighty, folks!
Let's get this show on the road
and start cultivating!
[gasps]
Pay no attention to that.
Only a little mud
between the toes.
You'll get used to it.
You might even find it
kind of pleasant.
Oh, okay.
First up: Let me show you
how to plant properly.
You're really good at this.
Huh? You... You think so?
Around here, Kousaku's the
man when it comes to rice.
His technique is legendary.
True fact: in class,
the teachers don't
hold a candle to him.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah. Back home,
they all used to call me
"the rice cultivating mad man."
No worries. It's not
as hard as it looks.
I call foul!
In case you haven't noticed,
we're trying to run a race here.
This is hardly the time
for one-on-one instruction!
Not so fast! Girl's got
a right to be taught.
I say let him.
We want a fair competition.
He can give her everything she
needs to know in a few minutes.
[MINORI] Fine then, teach her
your "legendary technique." But!
You'd better not be
stalling for time!
Yeah, yeah.
Let's see what you got.
Can you do it like I showed you?
Yes.
Not too shabby, but you got to
stick it down in the mud
a tiny bit deeper.
See, the way you've got it in
there now it'll get washed away.
So...?
Deeper.
Watch me.
You see how far I'm putting it
down in there? Bam.
We have to make sure the roots
are supported well. Yeah?
It's kind of hard to see.
Sure. Kind of.
Ugh! Come on already! Let's go!
Miss Becky could get a date
in half the time.
Just look at her!
Any longer and the poor woman
is going to shrivel up!
Take it from me: life is cruel.
Idea. Why don't you two
race as a team?
She leads, you come from behind.
Yeah, but for
that to work,
our bodies will have
to be touching--
Actually, what am I
complaining about?
This is a solid plan.
I'm excited to be a part of it.
Wait! I'm not liking this!
What is it teaching her?
Minori, give it a rest.
At the end of the day,
she's here to learn,
not worry about whether you
think she can pass the muster.
This is just too--!
Look at this thought bubble!
They're basically spooning, how
can I be comfortable with that?
Ringo. Are you okay
with touching?
--Sure.
--Seriously?!
This won't come back
to bite me in the ass?!
--Nope.
--Wait.
"Nope, not seriously" or
"nope" as in "we're" cool?
Bah! I'm in either way!
[squeals, chuckles]
'Kay, so...
Look out below,
mud's slippery! Timber!
Oh, I'm such a klutz!
Not as sure on my feet
as I thought I was.
Maybe I need some
one-on-one tutoring.
Do you charge, or what?
Uh, in case you
haven't noticed, Minori,
we're trying to run a race here.
Asshole.
All right. Since Miss Kinoshita
is the beginner,
we'll start her from there.
Miss Nakazawa, being the expert,
will start slightly behind.
The big moment
is almost upon us.
The tension in
the air is thick.
Welcome to the No-Rin
Rice Planting Cup.
Kousaku and myself
will be your hosts.
Thank you,
it's good to be here.
[KEI] We're waiting for
Miss Becky to do the honors.
[NATSUMI] Ready.
Go!!
[GUY 3B] Man, look at her go!
Nakazawa has
started strong.
But will that breakneck pace
take her to the finish line?
Bear in mind, Kei, the girl
has a reputation for stamina.
And it's clear she intends to
use it to bring the heat down
on her opponent.
[KEI] One has to question what
Kinoshita's plans are
once the two are neck and neck.
Come on!
Conserve your energy or you're
going to burn yourself out!
Yeah-yeah! Go, Ringo!
[GUY 3C] Slow and steady
wins the race!
[KEI] What the challenger
lacks in speed
she makes up for in
attention to detail.
You know, at the end of
the day, with a view like this
it doesn't even matter
who brings it home.
How does that work?
Give it a ponder, man!
For centuries men have
been in one of two camps:
You dig that ass, you're a perv.
Ta-tas and you're a mama's boy.
Brothers have been killing each
other over the difference
--since forever!
--He's right!
This competition is like
a peace treaty!
[GUYS] Whoa-ho!
[GUY 3D] Bloomers!
[GUY 3C] Swimsuit!
[GUY 3F] Bootay!
[GUY 3C] Ta-tas!
[GUY 3B] There's something
for everyone!
No longer must a man choose!
[GUYS sob]
Nakazawa is swiftly
closing the gap!
It's only a matter of moments
before she takes the lead!
Stop glaring. Just give up.
No way.
Look, deny all you want
but I'm telling you:
It's time you make peace
with the fact
you're not cut out
for this lifestyle.
Whatever you say.
Alright. That's it.
You're through!
[grunts]
Oops. Sorry.
Ha! Hey, no worries.
Accidents happen.
Occupational hazard
when you're a stupid slut!
[MINORI cackles]
[gasping]
Jackass.
Oh, that's it! I'm done
playing nice with you!
[grunts]
You stupid little hussy!
You're going down!
[RINGO] Quit being such a bitch.
[MINORI] I'll show
you bitch, bitch!
And it looks like they've
gone from rice planting
to mud wrestling!
We've got a spank fight!
I'd say so. I don't know
about you, Kei, but I'm riveted.
[KEI &amp; KOUSAKU] We should
probably stop them.
[KOUSAKU]
You've had your fun, ladies!
Stop trampling the rice field!
Damn but this is hot!
[grunting]
--[BOTH] Get away from me!
--[gasps]
[yelling]
[KEI &amp; KOUSAKU]
This was a bad idea!
[yelling]
[MINORI] That all you got,
jail bait?
[RINGO] Bring it, Bloomers!
[yelling, screaming]
Oh, boy.
You know, you're
actually pretty good.
Not as good as you.
[BOTH giggle]
[KOUSAKU] It's funny sometimes,
the things that'll make
two people want to
bury the hatchet.
That's life for you, I guess.
Oh, don't worry. I re-planted
the rice the next day.
Not with Miss Becky.
[KOUSAKU]
"The Smile You Showed Me."