[yells]
[MINORI] Thing is,
I want to be there for you.
[RINGO] Any village that
raised you must be wonderful.
[TSUKASA] Thank you for
coming ladies and germs!
How y'all doing this
lovely country morn'?
[CROWD] Finer than frog hair!
Alrighty! Now the moment
you've all been waiting for!
Let's get the first annual Aioi
village mixer up and running!
What do you say, folks?!
Who's ready to mingle and slam
headfirst into your soul mate?
[CROWD cheers]
[talking, laughing]
[KOUSAKU] Here you go, ma'am.
[sighs]
We got a live one.
I need you to get in there and
run interference for me.
Huh? What's up?
Be discreet. There's a
cougar at your 8 o'clock
liable to chase off the men.
Let her sink her claws
into you for a bit.
Eh? Okay, we must be
talking about a real piece
of work if she makes
you uncomfortable. Wow.
Deal is, no one's gonna
buy the age she put down.
Granted we all fudge the
numbers a tad
when we're looking to bag
a mate, but this is absurd.
She's just...
Well, see for yourself.
[TSUKASA] I mean... Damn...
[KOUSAKU sighs] Where is she?
[gasps]
Holy crap! You've gotta
be kidding me! Miss Becky?
What are you even doing here?!
And why do you look like
Ramses' the Great?!
--Forget it, General, I can't!
--You know this bag of bones?
[groans]
She's my teacher.
Good, so there's
no ice to break.
Go get her, chief!
You're my hero!
[sighs]
[KOUSAKU]
Miss Becky, is that you?
Almost didn't recognize you,
you look so--eh, slender...
I'm on a new anti-aging regimen.
Strict fasting.
That's the secret.
Revitalizes the cells.
Huh. That's nice. Wow. Fasting.
I bet is shaves years off--Not
that you have that many years
on your back to shave off
in the first place, of course!
But you know what'll
work even better?!
Goin' organic!
Mega refreshed!
Poo! And here I've been trying
so hard to stay disciplined!
You're a terrible influence!
[KOUSAKU whimpers] Please
stop looking at me like that.
Sorry, my love!
Old habits die hard.
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
Is this seat taken?
No. Please. Be my guest.
[giggles] Oh my, aren't we
a perfect gentleman?
A-buh-bayummm!
[WOMAN] So anyway,
so they were all up in arms
about the skirt being too short.
See, I'm in a better place
about my legs now.
Skinny jeans. That's the goal.
[KOUSAKU]
I've gotta do something!
Miss Becky's being swallowed
by the generation gap!
Hey, there! Hungry?
Made fresh by the
Aioi Wives Association!
Oh, how cute! That smell
really takes me back.
Kind of reminds me of
cafeteria food.
[NATSUMI] I know, right?
Like whale fritters!
[COUPLE] Fritters? Do what?
Just where did you go to school
that they served you whale?
My grandparents used to
eat that kind of stuff.
Miss Becky, no!
[NATSUMI] It's too late.
I've held back as long
as I could stand.
I must unleash!
Crap! Not that!
Anything but that!
Forty-ish... Dimension!
[NATSUMI] Believe it or not,
home skillets:
Life before the dot com bust was
all that and a bag of chips!
Uh... O-kay. Is it just me,
or did it get seriously 90s
up in here?
[NATSUMI] What you want,
what you really, really want!
--I'll tell you what I want..
--Wow, that's neat. Uh...
I'm going to go
get us all some refills.
[NATSUMI snarls]
No you don't, Skinny Jeans!
[laughs]
Well, that was... a thing.
Yeah. Yeah, it was.
[sighs]
So, what brings a lady like you
to a country mixer like this?
I mean, farming's
so yesterday, right?
Oh, no! Farming's
awesome! Really!
Hunky men,
working with their hands...
Girls love that
whole thing right now.
I guarantee you every woman
here's in the market
for a farm boy.
[gasps] But what's the appeal?!
It's not like there's any
money working the soil.
Just back-breaking labor
sunup to sundown.
Oh, come on. It's exotic.
At least it is when
you're from the big city.
Really? But... I mean...
I'd think the big city
would be more exotic
than a pile of dirt like this.
Right...?
This is nowheres-ville.
Are you kidding?!
You have no idea
what it's like in the city!
There's traffic congestion,
office politics,
sexual harassment suits,
dog-eat-dog corporate
takeovers...
A real farm beats a
cube-farm any day!
At least here you're not
just a cog in the machine!
Huh...
[WOMAN] Sorry.
[gasps]
[WOMAN]
But you see my point, don't you?
[squeals]
Friends of yours?
I'm his queen.
And I'm his knocked-up wife.
How's it going, folks?
We good? Y'all enjoying
yourselves or what?
[CROWD cheers]
How about a little game
to loosen things up?
Maybe spice this party
up a notch!
It's time to give our
"First Impressions!"
Here's how it goes:
I'll unveil a word from the
easel and ask,
"Who's the most-whatever the
word happens to be," okey-doke?
Then, you point to the
person in your group
you think that applies to!
Ugh.
Oh! This'll be fun!
I'm liking this.
Alright, round one: go!
Let's see now...
Who's the cutest?
[KOUSAKU groans]
Yeah, you got it.
Come on, silly. Which of us
you going to point to?
Yeah, yeah.
You gotta pick one.
Uh... Well...
I think it's pretty obvious
who I'm going to go--
Oh, that's so adorable.
My honey-baby's--SHY!!
--[KOUSAKU] Yeouch!
--Sounds like things are
really starting to heat up
out there, huh?
Moving on up to round two.
Who at your table
is the kindest?
[KOUSAKU groans]
Sweet pea,
you must be exhausted.
Why don't you let me
give you a massage?
Uh-oh. Somebody looks thirsty.
Baby wanna drink?
Uh... Sure, why not? Thank you?
--[RINGO] Hi-yaah!
--Not the face!!
Here! Bottoms up, darling!
[KOUSAKU grunting]
[NATSUMI] Tee-hee.
[KOUSAKU yells]
[RINGO, MINORI] So... Who is it?
[KOUSAKU whimpers]
--[KOUSAKU] Forfeit!
--Next up!
Who in your group
is the chubbiest?
[BOTH grunt]
Oh now, now. Be nice.
Didn't your mother
teach you not to lie?
Don't get defensive.
So you've packed on a
few pounds since coming here.
There's no shame in that.
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Ho-ho, things are
really popping now!
Shoulders back!
Who's the flattest?
[groans]
Me! Me! You could
roll dough on this chest!
Huh? Huh?!
Okay, folks! We're about to
get real up in here!
Bring your A-game,
it's the final round!
Who's...
[CROWD]
Don't keep us in suspense!
Who's the person you
most want to marry
and spend the rest
of your life with?!
[CROWD squeals]
Kousaku!
Koutan!
[BOTH] Pick one!
[whimpers] Geez, nothing like
putting me on the spot, huh?
[BOTH growl]
I choose...
[BOTH gasp]
[KOUSAKU] To run the hell away!
[RINGO, MINORI scream]
[TSUKASA] Hmph.
Someone's got cold feet.
Nice try, slick.
Son of a-- Why do you
have me all dolled up
in this monkey suit?!
Heh. You referring to the
tux or the ropes?
[sighs] Enough of this, huh?
Shouldn't I technically
be in a hakama anyway?
We had you in one of those
for the engagement ceremony.
For the wedding we want more
of an East meets West
kind of thing.
[KOUSAKU]
Are you out of your mind?!
You want to kick off
my married life
by pissing off
the local gods?!
I'm begging you here, Kousaku.
Please.
Ugh. Can I at least
ask you a question first?
Why'd you come back here?
You hated this town.
You'd been chomping at the bit
to leave since I've known you.
World's too small.
Huh?
No matter how far you
go, you always end up
back where you started,
or someplace just like it.
Wherever you run to,
there's always something
holding you down.
Always someone pissed at you.
[UNION CHIEF]
She abandoned ship once.
Stands to reason
she'll do it again.
Hell, you run long enough...
...pretty soon you find out
you're just running in place.
Deal is...
[TSUKASA] ...sometimes the only
way get where you're going
is to face where you're from.
Think about it.
You a runner?
I don't know.
[CROWD murmuring, laughing]
[TSUKASA] Attention everyone.
Attention please.
The Nakazawa-Hata
wedding ceremony beings now.
♪
Before we bid welcome
to the bride and groom,
Allow me to introduce their
friends Ringo Kinoshita
and Becky Natsumi,
our stunning bridesmaids.
Ah, and the bride's
darling little sisters,
Takumi and Akina,
who are thrilled to be
our flower girls.
Erectile dysfunction,
emotional unavailability.
Wandering eyes.
Passive aggression.
Breakdown of communication.
Backbiting in-laws.
[NATSUMI]
Welcome to matrimony!
[CROWD gasps, screams]
[clears throat] Now,
if you'd join me, let's, uh...
Let's give a warm round of
applause to our groom!
[CROWD clapping]
Next, the gorgeous,
young bride-to-be.
Escorted by one very proud papa!
Oh, wow! She looks beautiful!
They met, I presume,
like many of you here.
As children.
Kousaku moved to Aioi
with his parents,
who came to our humble
little village with big dreams
and a lot of heart.
Sadly, before the family could
realize its ambitions
of living off the land,
Kousaku's beloved
mother passed away.
Minori was a beacon
and pillar of strength
for the bereft young boy.
[KOUSAKU] She's right.
Minori was always there
for me when things got rough.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you would...
We ask, with a prayer
in our hearts,
that you give your blessing.
That you recognize and let be
fulfilled the love
these two earnest souls
have for each other;
a love that has triumphed
over grief and made them strong.
[clapping]
Please, Son, take care
of my precious little girl.
Treat her like the
best friend she is.
Hang on.
Does this mean we're not going
to be best friends anymore?
[KOUSAKU] What?
I want to be your best friend.
You can't have more than one!
Oh, sweetie, don't worry.
Nothing's really gonna change.
He's still going to love you
like he always has.
It's just that... Well,
when two people marry,
they've gotta be best friends.
That's how it works, okay?
But we're still
buddies with you.
No!
[MINORI] Taku?
[TAKUMI] I'm his best friend!
You don't have to get married!
Uh... Yeah, we kinda do.
I'm having his baby.
[growls] No you're not!
You're just saying that!
[MINORI] Huh?
[TAKUMI] I know the difference
between a baby and a kangaroo!
[MINORI shrieks]
[WAKA squeals]
[MAN A] What on earth?
[WOMAN A] Surely it's too
small to be a kangaroo?
[OLDER MAN A] Exactly what are
you people trying to pull?!
Okay, everyone,
please settle down!
We're trying to have
a wedding here.
I don't think you're trying
to have a wedding at all!
What is the meaning of this?!
What have you
tricked us all into?!
This whole thing's a lie!
But that speech! It...
It was so heartfelt!
--[MAN A] Outrageous!
--No, wait... We, uh...
[WOMAN B] I demand an
explanation immediately!
[MAN B] Do these kids
even know each other?!
Met when they were
children my foot!
[yelling]
--They--!
--[KOUSAKU] Wait.
[gasps]
[CROWD yelling]
[KOUSAKU] Forgive me!
I'm sorry! If you're looking
for someone to blame, it's me.
From beginning to end,
this whole stupid fiasco
has been my fault!
I never... It was never
meant to go this far!
What started as a dumb joke
went off the rails
and just spun completely
out of control!
I... I was scared.
My back was against the wall.
My only option was to
see it through to the end.
[MAYOR] Hooligan!
So you string us along?!
Oh, well done! Bang up job
representing your town!
I... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. Truth is...
I hated this town!
I got dragged here.
No one gave me a say.
I was a kid; my parents were
intent on becoming farmers
and I was going to be a part
of it whether I liked it or not.
[KOUSAKU] I watched as
their dreams crumbled.
As "good, clean living" chewed
'em up and spat 'em out.
We weren't even a family anymore
when it was all over.
I was left behind.
Only thing for me to do
was take up farming.
[KOUSAKU] It's hard work.
Especially when you
don't wanna do it.
All I ever thought about was the
day when I could finally leave.
But through it all, there was
one person who gave me hope.
A pop singer.
Ah!
[KOUSAKU] Her songs, her TV
shows--all of it--was magical.
The big city life
she always sang about
seemed so far away, so perfect.
I wanted to be a part of it.
Thinking about her got me
through the worst of times.
She buoyed me up.
Yeah, that's right.
I hated living in this town.
It's tiny, impoverished,
in the middle of nowhere.
[KOUSAKU]
But then... she came here.
She saw, and for some
crazy reason,
she loved everything about it.
[KOUSAKU] She opened my eyes
to the beauty of Aioi,
and suddenly, the things I
spent half my life
waiting to get away from
felt as magical as her voice.
"Give me this view
and the clean air any day.
Any village that raised you
must be wonderful."
That's what she said to me,
and for the first time...
I understood.
Country life shaped me
into who I am.
Look around you.
Warts and all,
this little backwater town
inspired me to
put myself on the line
to try and
convince you to love it.
Look, You seem like nice people
and I'm not proud
that I fooled you.
But the point
I'm trying to make is:
I've learned there's
actually a lot to love
about this little place.
That's all I wanted to say.
[clapping]
[sighs]
Kousaku?
Ringo.
Hey.
[KOUSAKU] Minori?
So, I guess...
You really prefer Ringo over me
after all, now don't you?
She was the one who
made life bearable, not me.
It's not like that.
This isn't about choosing one.
It's about finding
the middle ground.
You see?
We don't need to shun the city
for the country, or vice versa.
We just need to connect them.
The country feeds the city and
reminds people of their roots.
The city gives people
something to aspire to.
A bird needs two wings to fly,
we need each other to survive.
Why feel we have to
favor one over the other
when the whole point
is to have both?
When you stop
and think about it,
all of human history
has been building to this!
See? We need one another!
You, Minori.
And you, Ringo.
It's like I'm the bird.
And you two are my wings!
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[KOUSAKU screams]
♪
[KOUSAKU] Saying a lot
happened this summer
is an understatement.
But there's one
important thing
all the craziness
has taught me...
♪
[KOUSAKU] Yep.
If I've learned anything over
the past few months,
it's that we all still
have a lot to learn.
[MAN A] Mad cow! Mad cow!
[KOCHOU] Ageha!
[whimpers]
[BOTH scream]
[AKARI giggles]
Kousaku?
Hey.
[KOUSAKU] Huh? What's up?
--[BOTH] Go get him!
--[KOUSAKU gasps
[sighs]
[bull moos]
[KOUSAKU screams]
[KOUSAKU] Not again!
We've been through this already!
Some life, huh?
This has been Kousaku Hata,
and if you liked this, oh-ho!
Just you wait!