[CROWD cheering]
♪ At my fingertips each
heart-string catches fire, ♪
♪ Burning with
a fierce desire; ♪
♪ The world upends,
just hitting "send," ♪
♪ And though I'm preaching
to the choir, ♪
♪ I mean every word ♪
♪ Back in the day,
I obsessed ♪
♪ With where you sat,
how you dressed ♪
♪ With what shoes you wore.
Boy, I had it bad-it's true.  ♪
♪ And though for now,
things have changed ♪
♪ Your friends are new;
I'm a memory estranged ♪
♪ When Summer comes
Our love will make its debut. ♪
♪ Weak in the knees,
teacher please ♪
♪ I can't focus on
what's in front of me; ♪
♪ My grades slip,
my heart skips ♪
♪ Where is he? ♪
♪ My calls go straight to
voicemail-has he bailed? ♪
♪ All I think of is you; the day
our bond will be renewed! ♪
♪ At my fingertips each
heart-string catches fire ♪
♪ Burning with
a fierce desire; ♪
♪ The world upends,
just hitting "send," ♪
♪ My love,
how I aspire to be ♪
♪ At your fingertips,
the waiting, ♪
♪ long behind us;
time creating. ♪
♪ Space for love,
far above
♪ This life apart;
baby come home ♪
♪ That moment's for him and me,
So before we say goodbye ♪
♪ Let me lay bare what
I need courage to share ♪
♪ With that special guy ♪
♪ To be on my cell phone... ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[YUKA sighs]
[YUKA] Thank you!
Thank you so very much!
[CROWD roars]
You really know how
to make a girl feel special!
Best audience
ever-and I mean that
from the bottom of my heart!
[CROWD (chanting)]
Yuka! Yuka! Yuka! Yuka!
[CROWD cheers]
[CONCERT DUDE A]
I love you!
[CONCERT DUDE B]
You're my queen!
[cheering continues]
Before the next set,
I want to introduce you
to someone very special.
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
[YUKA] This is the man all my
songs are secretly dedicated to.
[CROWD cheers]
[cheering continues]
I love--
[KOUSAKU] I... love you...
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[rooster crows]
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[KOUSAKU] Aw, man...
[WAKA squeaks]
[MINORI] Really?
You're late 'cause you're
not married to a pop star?
Take a second to say those
words aloud to yourself.
[KEI] She has a point.
It's kind of sad.
Since we're on the
subject of wet dreams,
when are you going to
get a grip on reality
and stop fantasizing
about Tokyo?
Place will chew you up
and spit you out.
Not if I'm a trendy
farmer, it won't!
[KEI &amp; MINORI] A trendy farmer?
[goat bleats]
Hah! Yeah, let me give you
a clue there, slick.
Two weeks, you'll come crawling
back on your hands and knees.
Yokel like you'd be
lucky winding up
married to the hometown
harvest queen.
Oh, so now you
have a crystal ball?
Yukatan and me
will be together.
We'll grow rice in Harajukua,
then we're gonna-wait for it-
take Ropongi by storm with cows!
[cow moos]
You'll see!
Harvest queen will have to
find someone else.
Besides, the only
hometown girl my age is you.
Huh?!
[MINORI giggles]
Crazy coincidence, huh?
Funny how little details like
that can skip your notice.
[KEI] Kousaku, Minori. Please.
How 'bout you stop whatever
this is and, you know, work?
Sorry. My bad.
Gee, thanks.
Way to get me on
Kei's bad side today.
Hey! It takes two to tango!
--[MAN A] Mad cow! Mad cow!
--[ALL gasp]
[MAN B] Actually,
I think it's a bull!
[MAN A] Whatever!
It's out and it's pissed!
[TEACHER A screams]
[MAN C]
We've got a teacher down!
[MAN A] Medic!
[KOCHOU] Matador!
[KOUSAKU sighs]
They need better pens.
[MINORI] It was one of the
peacocks last time, right?
Nah. It was the goat.
The peacock was
the time before that.
[MINORI] Hey! Back to work!
What's not our problem?
[STUDENTS] Runaway cattle.
[KEI] Huh?
Um... Actually...
[KOUSAKU &amp; MINORI] Crap!
Whatever happens,
we can't let it ruin the crop!
And how're we
supposed to do that?
I'm on it, guys!
[yelling]
Dude! Kakizaki's insane!
[GUY B] He's got this.
He made it to nationals!
[KAKIZAKI screams]
[GUY C] No! Kakizaki--!
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[TEACHER D]
That thing is a monster!
Why do they keep it around?!
Whoa.
Kei!
Wha-What do we do?!
Just... take this
and run like hell.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[MINORI squeals]
[KOUSAKU] Aw, c'mon,
give me some slack!
I got no beef with you!
[KOUSAKU screams]
[KOUSAKU] Poor choice of words!
Sorry! Don't kill me! Sorry!
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Well, so far so good.
[squeak]
Oh, Wakadanna!
It was just awful!
No one even cared
I was almost trampled!
Kousaku.
You brought the
career survey, right?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah.
[WAKADANNA squeaks]
[KOUSAKU] You made up
your mind about college?
Nah, still kind of
on the fence about it.
Only thing I know for sure is
I want to specialize
in agriculture.
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Least that's a plan.
Look at me. Heh.
I'm just here 'cause
my family's been farmers
since, like, forever.
You telling me you
got nothing lined up?
Well, there's Tokyo.
Ah...
Wait! Seriously?!
Yeah, why?
Ugh. Bumpkin...
You really think the
"trendy farmer" thing's
going to take off?
[KOUSAKU laughs]
As a matter of fact, I already
know where I'm going to start.
Ha!
A magical place called
Furikoshi High School!
O-kay.
Just so I'm absolutely clear:
In dead earnest,
you actually listed "high
school" as a career choice?
That's dumb. Like, really dumb.
[WAKA squeaks]
Uh...
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
talking to me like I'm an idiot!
[KEI] Oh brother.
So, I guess it's safe to say
you've got it bad
for this pop star chick?
Yukatan Kusakabe is not a "pop
star chick", she's a goddess!
And what exactly
makes her a "goddess"?
Her dancing
dinner-plate eyeballs!
Her delicate, duck-face mouth!
Those rosy apple cheeks!
That angelic voice from heaven!
Her long, naturally
straight hair!
The way her eyebrows arch
as if to say, "Who, me?"
[KEI] Right. Thanks.
We get the picture.
[KOUSAKU] Oh-ho, no
you don't, my friend!
Not 'til you've heard me talk
about that one-of-kind,
ice-melting smile--
[KOUSAKU yells]
Wrap it up, lover boy!
No one here gives a crap!
The survey's about
life after school.
Okay, fine.
What'd you put on yours, then?
[MINORI] Hmm?
[MINORI chuckles]
[KOUSAKU] College or job?
Uh! Ah! Um... Well, I guess
all things considered,
Let's say, "job."
Something in an office?
Hang on! Do-Don't read it!
[KEI] If any of those things
happen in an office,
you're doing them wrong.
This is dumb. Really dumb.
Don't talk to me
like I'm an idiot!
I'm thinking long term! Ugh!
Stop running your mouths.
Vulgarians!
[KOUSAKU &amp; MINORI]
It's Fun-bags McGee!
The name is Kochou!
Say it with me, now:
Kochou Yoshida!
Got it?!
The plebes in
Cultivation are a tragedy.
Small-minded
guttersnipes, that's you.
Production Science
is wasted on you.
Why they lump Cultivators
and Animal Husbandry students
together, I'll never know.
I'm charged with the care
of animate creatures.
You all just
roll around in the dirt.
A-hem.
The students across
the hall will thank you
to keep it down to a dull roar.
Your inane chatter
is distracting.
Oh, Like your big, smelly cow
isn't putting us
all off our game?
[bull moos]
Silence, Vulgarian tramp!
You know nothing!
Sit down and be schooled!
This magnificent beast, Agehagou
by name, is a Hidaushi,
the highest of the
elite wagyu rank!
Which makes no real difference
in her market value.
Actually, her fetching
price is expected
to be stratospheric, plebe.
[KOUSAKU yells
[KOUSAKU] Give the magnificent
beast room to breathe, people!
[MINORI growls]
You can't just
switch sides on a dime.
That's not how this works!
[KOUSAKU] I pick the side
that doesn't murder me!
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[KOCHOU] Hmph. Violence
in lieu of dialogue.
I must say, you sum up
the Cultivators perfectly.
Yoshida.
[KOCHOU gasps]
How dare you address me
as though we were equals?!
[KOCHOU whimpers]
We are worlds apart!
Cows are sort of on
the skittish side, right?
They don't do all that
great around people?
Not to tell you your job, but
do you think it's a smart idea
to bring one into
a classroom
full of loud,
obnoxious "vulgarians?"
Trying to hoist me
by my own petard, eh?
Well, your attempt at a touché
is as predictable as you!
Wow. Not cool.
Following this
morning's debacle,
I realized Agehagou's reaction
could create a teachable moment.
Call this an exercise
in moron endurance.
[KEI &amp; KOUSAKU]
Moron endurance?!
[KEI] That actually makes sense.
Nice. Well done, Yoshida.
That's some cutting edge
animal psychology technique.
Don't let anyone
tell you different.
[KOCHOU gasps]
Well, so long as we're
on the same page, I suppose.
So you understand why
it's inappropriate
to confer with me on even terms.
Good! Cultivator Plebe!
[KOCHOU laughs,
bull moos]
[TEACHER] Good morning, class!
Get a load of this spectacular
weather we're having!
Not too hot, not too cold!
Makes a gal feel like
Goldilocks at the wedding altar!
[TEACHER giggles]
[CLASS groans]
Miss!
Yes, Ms. Nakazawa?
Points for calling me
"Miss," by the way.
Teacher may not look forty,
but that doesn't mean
she's not feeling her age.
[TEACHER moans]
Fun Bags-I mean- Yoshida brought
a big smelly cow
into the classroom!
Huh. How about that.
I'm assuming you have a really
good explanation. Yoshida?
[KOCHOU] Yes, ma'am.
You see, Mr. Mutsu
suffered an
unfortunate accident.
I thought it best that I
care for her while he recovers.
That's a complete one-eighty
from what you said!
Hmm. And you think you're up to
the task of babysitting a cow?
Oh, absolutely.
Hmph. You'd know better than me!
[MINORI] Aw, Miss Becky! C'mon!
This is totally ridiculous!
If she gets to bring a cow
into the classroom,
then the rest of us should be
able to bring our planters, too!
Fair is fair!
Who's with me on this?
Speak up, guys!
[GUY D] I'm with her!
It's not right!
[GUY E] Why do the Animal
Husbandry snobs
always get special treatment?
[GIRL A] Because we don't make
the school spend money
on stupid things like
fertilizer trials!
[GUY E] But why don't you share
some of that produce
you're always
taste-testing, huh?!
Everybody, stop arguing!
Now listen and listen good!
We're all in the same boat.
Focus on each other's
positive traits!
[MINORI] But Ms. Becky!
It's really unfair that
she gets to bring her cow!
[KOCHOU] What's unfair about
observing the caste system?
[GUY E] Give me a tomato!
[GUY D] Sure! I'll
throw one at you!
[NATSUMI] Ah-ha! All right.
Who wants to hear
a tale of romance?
Your favorite teacher
found herself in an upscale
five-star restaurant last
night, sipping wine
across from the most
intriguing man she'd ever met.
Rich, sophisticated, handsome.
Hanging on every teensy
little word she had to say.
A man a woman would love
not to have to make-up out
of soul-crushing loneliness.
[NATSUMI chuckles darkly]
[NATSUMI] That's right,
boys and girls.
Yours truly was on a date
with an empty seat.
[NATSUMI] Okay, then! What
do you say we get started?
[school bell chimes]
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI]
Down the hatch!
[KOUSAKU slurps]
Ahhhh...! Seconds please!
Good, right?
Alrighty then, coming right up!
[KEI, KOUSAKU, MINORI]
Thanks for the grub!
[KOUSAKU sighs loudly]
[KOUSAKU] Man, that was good!
Tempers flared today in
the House of Councilors
over the Prime Minister's
proposed tax increase.
Members of the opposing party
accuse the Minister's cabinet--
[KOUSAKU] Why are human
beings hard-wired to care
about taste when
it comes to food?
I mean, it's a blatant design
flaw when you think about it:
we want flavor.
Nutrition? Meh.
We eat what tastes good.
If we're lucky,
it's also good for us.
Why would God make us
that way? Is he even real?
Blasphemy! Of course he's real!
He just put all of his genius
into creating Yukatan!
[MINORI] Kousaku.
[KOUSAKU] She is living proof
that God loves us all
and wants us to be happy!
[MINORI] Kousaku.
[KOUSAKU] Any guy who doesn't
grovel at Yukatan's feet
isn't worthy to call
himself a man!
Earth to Kousaku! Come in!
Damn it, what do you want?!
Can't you see
I'm deep in meditation?
You seriously need to
look at the television.
Yeah, it's a pretty big deal.
What?
Like anything's a
bigger deal than my Yuka--
[REPORTER A] Excuse me!
Is it true you're retiring?
[KOUSAKU] God is dead!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[KOUSAKU] It's not true!
I refuse to accept it!
No, no, no, no, no!
It's all a vicious lie!
[various animal cries]
[MINORI] Will you come out
of there already?
We're going to be
late for class.
[KEI] Life marches on, dude.
[MINORI sighs]
Fine. I shouldn't
have to do this, but...
Time to come out
and face reality!
Why do you have to be
such a pain?
Everybody gets--
[MINORI screams]
[muffled crying]
[MINORI] What's wrong with you?!
[crying continues]
Can't believe people
actually buy those...
[MINORI sighs]
[MINORI] You're kidding me.
And here I'd been thinking you
were a semi-normal human being.
You do realize this means we
have no choice
but to take you out back
and put you down, right?
At least tell me you're
wearing a shirt under there.
[KOUSAKU yells]
[KOUSAKU] No, I am
not wearing a shirt!
Yukatan and I are of one flesh!
[KEI] Textbook PTSD.
He's like that guy who can't
wash the sheets
after his girlfriend puts the
kibosh on their relationship.
It might be too late for him.
Hey!
Stop being a freak
for two seconds
and come back to the real world!
If you don't come
to class, you'll fail.
Nobody wants that.
How else you going to
be a "trendy farmer?"
[KOUSAKU] What'd be the point?
[MINORI] Excuse me?
[KOUSAKU] I only ever grew stuff
so I could send fresh
vegetables to Yukatan.
[ANNOUNCER]
Kibo 209 to Osaka
boarding on Platform Sixteen.
Kibo 209 to Osaka...
[KEI] Let me make sure
I get this:
You send it all to her?
Everything you've grown
in class since forever
goes to feed a well-off
Japanese pop star?
[KOUSAKU] Yup.
Eggplants in particular, though.
Big, bulging eggplants.
Pretty sure that's harassment.
Congratulations,
you're a stalker.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
What are you talking about?!
If you were a girl, how would
you feel about
some complete and total
stranger shipping you a box
of produce shaped like that?
But... she lives in Tokyo! It's
a concrete jungle over there!
It's impossible
to find good veggies.
C'mon, who cares
what it's shaped like?
It's fresh!
[MINORI sighs]
Listen.
I know in your mind this is
all completely innocent.
Thanks. Knew you'd get it.
That's why you and me are bros.
[KEI] You ever send this
girl anything else?
Loads of big,
warty cucumbers.
Vice Squad!
Book this pervert, now!
I just said we're bros!
[KEI] Come on, Minori!
We've got to wash our hands
of this creep-a-zoid.
--Guilt by association!
--[KOUSAKU] Wait!
I sent a bunch of
other stuff, too!
Sweet corn, bitter gourds,
some mushrooms from
the forestry department!
Next shipment's going to
have some daikon in there!
--I try to give a little--
--Shut up!
I don't want to be an accessory!
You're so pathetic...
You really see nothing
wrong with this, huh?
There isn't!
I'm just trying to do something
nice for someone special!
Uhh... It's creepy.
All right, that does it!
School me. Now.
Explain to me exactly what
it is I'm doing wrong here.
Go on. I'm all ears.
Give me a break.
You need to be told
why it's creepy?
Apparently, yeah.
What about sending something
made with love to someone
who means the world to you
is such a huge crime?
Uh, you don't think
eggplants might've been
a little too suggestive?
Fine. Never mind the eggplants.
The real issue is you mailing
them anonymously
to someone you've
never even met.
Yeah.
No. Nuh-uh.
Don't skip over
the eggplant thing.
You're the one who
made it the hot button.
Put yourself in my shoes:
your best friends
rag on your
produce-I mean, come on,
you wouldn't
need an explanation?!
No one's ragging on
your produce.
It's just, eggplants
are... shaped funny...
[KOUSAKU] Oh, I see.
So eggplants are shaped funny.
Funny as in: dirty. Uh-huh.
Remind you of something, maybe?
Seems like a personal
problem if you ask me.
[MINORI] Hey. It's not--
Look, I don't
make the rules, okay?
[MINORI grunts]
[KOUSAKU laughs]
[KOUSAKU]
And what rules are those?
You'll have to
spell them out for me.
Describe for me what
the eggplant looks like
so I'll know for
future reference.
C'mon. It's clearly important--
What're they shaped like?
Huh?
Uh... They're-They're
shaped like a...
...pen...
Stop trying to make me
sound like a pervert!
Nice one.
You have to admit
you had that coming.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah. Guess it's
kind of hard to argue
with the logic of that
from this perspective.
[MINORI] Whatever.
She probably doesn't even open
the box you mail them in.
You ever gotten a
response from this girl?
[KOUSAKU] Never have,
never will...
[MINORI] Don't be so dramatic.
You're bound to get
something from her.
Eventually.
[KOUSAKU] I've stayed anonymous.
[MINORI] There is officially
no hope for you.
[KEI] Makes it that
much creepier.
It doesn't matter.
Just 'cause her career is over
doesn't mean you
get to skip class.
Here!
Get off your rump
and make an effort!
We're all in this together!
Pass! Life as I know it is over!
From now on if you want me...
You'll have to talk to
Yuka-tan!
Oh, she's so beautiful!
She's so sweet! So perfect!
[KOUSAKU sobs]
[MINORI growls]
Ugh. Fine.
The real one's probably
a total bitch anyway.
[KOUSAKU] Blasphemer!
Just because no man in his right
mind would give you his eggplant
doesn't mean you get to
foul-mouth my true love--
[KOUSAKU]
Goodbye, future offspring...
[KOUSAKU grunts]
[MINORI] I am not going
to say this again!
Stop being a titty baby
and grow a pair!
Our grades are on the line and
if you don't get it in gear,
I'll give the holier-than-thou's
in Animal Husbandry free reign
to mangle your
shriveled ball sack!
Now do we have an understanding,
or do I need to drill you
a little more?
[KOUSAKU] Got it...
[KOUSAKU]
Why are we doing this?!
There's no point!
[MINORI] Stop bitching!
Nobody cares what you think.
Kei, make him
focus on his work!
[KEI] Huh? Right.
[NATSUMI] So last night
was a complete wash!
Literally!
I bought this fabulously
expensive essential oil
I read about online
everyone says
makes you look
ten years younger.
Talk about incredible!
Oh, my skin was so soft,
you'd think I just
popped out of the womb!
Then I thought, "why
spend so much," right?
What's so 'essential'
about essential oils
that any old oil won't do?
So, it's into the kitchen for a
bottle extra virgin olive oil
with a sprinkle of chili powder,
'cause, you know, in for a
penny, in for a pound.
And let met tell you boys
and girls, it made me slick.
As in, like a fish. A fish!
So out comes the smart phone,
'cause we all know I'm
a bit of an over-sharer.
Selfie after selfie
posted on the web.
Good times!
Kind of pathetic actually.
A grown woman dousing herself in
olive oil to try
and grab a little attention
from the opposite sex.
That, class, is what
adults call "desperation."
You might think you understand
the meaning of the word,
trust me, you don't.
Oh. Right.
You have a new classmate.
It's not a cow, is it?
No. In fact, she's anything but.
Hey. Miss Kinoshita. Come on in!
[KOUSAKU] No way this girl's
an ordinary high school student.
She's too pretty.
I mean, look at her.
She makes that uniform look like
something out of a magazine.
She looks like a pop star.
She looks like...
My Yukatan.
My name's Ringo Kinoshita.
[KOUSAKU] Eh?
[KOUSAKU] "The King of Farmers."