[KOUSAKU] Hello again.
Our story today begins a little
while after Ringo transferred
to "Tamo No-Rin High."
[KOUSAKU] Seriously, slow down,
you're stressing me out here!
Geez. Not like we have
anywhere important to be.
[KOUSAKU] Life likes to
surprise us sometimes.
Just when we think
we're comfortable.
Bam: Game Changer.
And all we can do is stand there
and take the moment in.
We've been terrorized!
Ugh. What a nightmare.
Maybe someone should
call the police?
Had a feeling this would
happen one of these days.
[GUY 4C]
There's not even a fence,
this field's
completely vulnerable!
Did anybody here happen
to see who did this?
If so, speak!
[KOCHOU] I saw it.
Yes. The perpetrator
of this foul deed was a child.
Child?
He was wearing a grey coat
or some such thing,
running off with his arms
filled with our vegetables.
Wait. What time would you
say this happened?
I believe it was yesterday
evening on my way back home,
after I finished
feeding the cows.
I would say it was a touch
after eight o'clock.
The fiend dropped this.
It would seem
you're telling the truth.
The question is:
what are you planning to do?
If it was a child, then you have
to impartially investigate
the facts and figure
out his motives.
Yes. We have to figure out
what happened fast!
Do you think it's possible
the boy did this
'cause he's starving?
Please, sir. Please,
may I have some more?
[GUY 4D] Aah!
Don't you people get it?!
If we don't get to
the bottom of this,
these kids will keep coming
around and eating
all our vegetables, willy-nilly,
with no consequences at all!
Hey, you guys!
The adults are talking, Minori!
In case you haven't noticed,
I am attempting to prevent what
could become a major crisis!
You know. It could've
been a monkey.
[BOTH] A what?
I'm picking up a monkey
vibe, aren't you?
This has monkey
written all over it.
You're wrong!
He was walking on two legs!
Wild monkeys may not be
able to walk for miles
upright like that,
but they can do it!
That's true. I've
seen them run off
with whole watermelons before.
[KOCHOU] Wait. You've seen
this with your own two eyes?!
[KOUSAKU] Minori and I
are seriously from
the middle of nowhere, so we
saw crazy stuff all the time.
[MINORI] Dogs, monkeys,
pheasants. You name it.
What is this?
Japanese folk hour?
Oh, man. I'm just glad
there wasn't a starving orphan.
[MALE STUDENT 4B] Okay,
everyone, we're done!
What's going on?
Oh. We're just thinking we're
in for a bit of a battle here.
Let's do this.
[BOTH chuckle menacingly]
[KEI] All right.
Welcome to the first ever
"A Monkey Showed Up
and We're in a Jam,
So Now We Have To Come Up
With Some
Countermeasures" meeting.
[KOUSAKU laughs]
Now. Why don't we all
take turns making suggestions?
Oooh! Kei! Pick me first!
Back where I come from,
if we want to keep varmints
from treating our crops
like a buffet,
we build an electric fence.
Yeah, but... Couldn't the
animals get hurt?
It'll shock them,
but they won't die.
Yes! Commence
fence building at once!
[KEI] Hmm...
While the idea itself
isn't all that bad,
I'm afraid it's impractical.
[ALL] Yeah, why's that?
[KEI] We're flat broke.
[KOUSAKU] That sucks.
He's clearly hungry,
so why don't we just feed him?
[ALL] Huh?
It does seem like the
humane thing to do.
[MINORI] I get it now.
You're saying if we stuff
his belly till he can't eat
another bite, then he won't need
to mess up our fields anymore
and we can get back to
business as usual!
That is the greatest
idea of all time!
[KEI] Not bad, but there's
only one problem.
The food supply
isn't his only target.
He's been ransacking
our potted plants as well.
It seems pretty obvious to me
the beast is doing this for fun,
so I'm not so sure a
full belly will stop him.
[KOUSAKU] So much for that!
Listen up.
I've spent my whole life
battling these monkeys.
I know where
their weaknesses lie.
Sheer brute force is the only
way to stop these evil bastards.
Behold! I give you
Super Hitoshi, with thirty times
the power of the old Hitoshi,
a weapon guaranteed to blow
his monkey butt
back to the jungle!
Oh my. That's an awful
big gun you have!
[KOUSAKU] This bad boy
can launch up to
thirty fireworks simultaneously!
What the heck?
Well, that's weird.
Maybe the gunpowder's
wet or something.
Here, let me take a look.
[screams]
Kids, believe me
when I tell you this.
It's never a good idea to stare
down the barrel of a loaded gun.
[KOUSAKU] Who's idea was this?!
Poop.
Because you have all
failed miserably,
I will now unveil to you
my super secret plan!
All right then. Spill the beans.
Listen, Vulgarians.
As you know, humans and
monkeys are both primates.
If we deal with this rationally,
I think you'll see that--
[ALL] Hell no!
Uh. Whatever.
It was ingenious.
--You can't deny humans
--[KOUSAKU] Hunter?
--and monkeys are both primates.
--Yes. He's just one monkey.
It's not like a whole army.
We should be able
to dispose of it easily.
Dispose?
Uh. Kei. I know we've got
to put a stop to this,
but won't you feel bad
about having the monkey killed?
Farming is a brutal business.
Truth is...
I'm prepared to do whatever it
takes to solve this problem.
Ah. Yeah, okay...
[KEI] As a matter of fact,
I know a skilled hunter.
He's just the man for the job.
Hello. My name's Ohmori.
Wow. Guy's a total creeper.
Whoa! Keep those
thoughts to yourself!
No, she's right,
the man's a troll.
Hey! Did you not hear
what I just said?!
[KOCHOU]
Surely this isn't your man.
You claimed you knew
a skilled hunter.
I'll wager the only skill
this man possesses
is finding the nearest
box of snack cakes.
[KEI] People are only 90% looks.
Which means there's 10% of them
that'll take you by surprise.
Ohmori might be large.
But he's large and in charge.
And he's a blowgun pro!
[ALL] You got to be kidding me!
Oh no. It's no joke. It's real.
Yours truly is the founder
of the Ohmori School
of Blowgun Arts.
That's not weird.
Okay then.
If you're a master,
where are your blowguns?
[OHMORI] Right here.
[RINGO] Huh?
[KOUSAKU] Seriously?
Those are your blowguns?
[OHMORI] They're my super
stealthy sniper blowguns.
[MINORI &amp; KOUCHOU]
"Sniper blowguns?"
[KOUSAKU] Right.
Of course they are.
Didn't mean to doubt you
or anything, it's just,
when I first saw them, I kind of
thought they looked a bit
like anime wall scrolls.
Oh. Actually, that's
precisely what they are.
[KOUSAKU] Huh?
These puppies make
decent blowguns
if you remove the thumb tacks,
take them off your wall,
and roll them up.
[KOUSAKU] Uh, yeah,
I can see they do.
So, Mr. Ohmori, if you
don't mind me asking,
with your homemade blow
dart wall scroll guns,
what do you typically hunt?
[OHMORI] Just the
occasional real-lifer.
[KOUSAKU] Neat. Swell.
So, I got to ask this.
Your job?
I mean, when you're not out
there tracking down real-lifers.
Do you have a job
that pays you money?
[OHMORI] I'm unemployed!
[OHMORI] This potent
little narcotic will send
even the heartiest of
knuckle-dragging primates
on a one-way trip to "Monkey
Heaven", if you catch my drift.
It's name? Well, if I told you,
I'd have to kill you.
[OHMORI chuckles]
[KEI] Look!
I mastered my
dart gun technique
by sucking on pasta
several hours a day.
I call this specific blowing
method the "deep throat."
Cool name.
[OHMORI grunts]
[MONKEY screams]
It's the throat.
You have to keep it relaxed.
--I don't want to know!
--[KEI] Come on!
All right! Time to show this
monkey whose turf
this really is!
Yeah, spank that monkey!
Poor thing. He's hurt.
[RINGO] Kousaku?
No, Ringo, I'm sorry.
But we can't show him mercy.
He's right.
Our responsibility is
to protect these fields.
[KOUCHOU laughs]
[KOCHOU] I know not how this
vile beast was separated
from his tribe, nor do I know
why he has invaded
our grasslands,
but I do know this:
The time to consider the manner
of his disposal is upon us.
[KEI] Maybe try not to sound
so excited about it.
Oh, Kei, what a fool thou art!
I take no pleasure in killing
beasts, only in caging them!
I have a dear friend
who works at the zoo.
I've requested that a
comfortable dwelling
be prepared for him.
I'm a bit surprised.
That's very kind.
You see...
Currently, they only house
female monkeys at this zoo,
so when he joins them,
he'll be in "Monkey Heaven"
in the best way.
He'll perform husbandly duties
and live life like a king.
[KOUSAKU] Wow. What a relief!
[MINORI] This will give a whole
new meaning to the phrase,
"monkey see, monkey do!"
[KEI] Great plan. Thanks.
I owe you for this one!
[KOCHOU] Charitable deeds
done in the name of
self-gratification
or seeking attention
are not genuinely
charitable deeds!
I did what I did for the
monkey and the monkey alone!
I do not require your
"thank you", thank you.
[KOUSAKU] I was right.
[MINORI] Coming!
Hey, Kousaku, what's up?
Mind if I come in for a second?
There's something
we need to talk about.
[MINORI gasps]
Uh, come back in
one hour, please!
[KOUSAKU] Uh...
Actually now would be better.
But this is very last minute
and I have so many things
I need to get ready.
Just, uh, wait right there.
One hour?
[MINORI] All set!
Can I come in now?
[gasps]
Yes. I want you to come inside.
Did you redecorate
or something?
Yes. I did. But there's
no need to be nervous.
Would you like to
take a hot shower?
Uh. No, I'm okay.
You filthy boy.
So, you'd rather do it
down and dirty then?!
[knocking on door]
Kei. You're here!
Wait. Kei?
Yeah, I invited him
to join us. Come on in!
Thanks for having me-- Whoa!
She just redecorated her room.
[MINORI] This was our moment.
--I really thought it was...
--[KEI] Uh... Yeah. I see that.
[MINORI] So, what's up?
You wanted to talk
about something?
Oh. Right. It's
about Ringo, actually.
[growls]
[MINORI] Goodnight.
--What?
--[MINORI] Die!
Why are you freaking out?
I haven't even given you
the details yet!
[MINORI] Die in a fire
and rot in hell!
Rude. You don't even know
what I'm going to say!
Man. She's gonna stab you
one of these days.
How come?! Whatever, I'm done
trying to figure it out,
just look at this.
All right! Here we go.
Sing along with me, you guys!
Oh, cool. This is a
Yuka Kusakabe DVD.
I thought I threw
those things away,
but I guess someone
had a secret stash.
I used my allowance and
bought some replacements.
Anyway, take a
good look at Yukatan.
Notice anything strange?
♪
Well. This may seem
pretty obvious.
But she's acting so friendly.
The Kinoshita I know doesn't
have a happy bone
in her entire body.
He's right. She's so
smiley it's weird.
Bingo!
This is all about her smile.
Think about it for a minute,
the girl hasn't smiled once
since she got here.
She didn't crack a smile
in her first class.
She didn't so much as smirk
during the whole panties thing,
or during dinner.
Or during the king game,
or when she survived
the contest with Minori.
Not even when the damn
monkey's life was saved.
[MINORI] That's true.
But her happiness here could
just be part of her act, right?
You may be onto something.
But still...
There's a person living
with us who is so down
they never smile at all.
Don't you think that's sad?
Yeah. Actually, it really is.
[KOUSAKU] I know, right?
[KEI] If you need smiles.
Then have no fear.
The comedy cavalry has arrived!
Fancy running into
you here. Kinoshita.
Anyway... How would you feel
about watching me
perform a little trick?
[KEI] Dark matter!
[CROWD cheers]
And?
Looks like we're going
to have to step it up a notch!
[MINORI] Well, hello!
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle,
tickle, tickle, tickle...
Minori! Damn you for making me
jealous right now!
But keep up the good work!
[MINORI] So, tell me. How do you
like my technique?
Here, try this on for size.
Okay. How about a
little communication?
Talk to me. How else
will I know what you like?
I'm... sensitive.
[MINORI giggles]
[MINORI] The body doesn't lie.
There's no reason to hold back.
Just give yourself over
to absolute pleasure!
[KOUSAKU] I give myself, I do!
[MINORI laughs] Come on now.
Show me that smile.
Now it's my turn
to show you what I've got.
[MINORI screeches in laughter]
Stop! Don't do this! Please!
I'm drooling! Seriously,
I'm drooling all over the place!
I think I'm going to
pee my pants!
[MINORI laughs, screams]
You gonna tell me
what's going on?
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Look. I'm sorry. I really am.
It's just you always
seem so glum all the time.
I guess I'm worried life here
isn't really doing it for you.
I see.
So this whole thing was
about getting me to smile?
Dumb. I know.
We didn't mean any harm
by it, I swear. But...
We did get a little
carried away, didn't we?
I can't smile.
Huh?
[RINGO] I try.
But it doesn't work.
[RINGO] At first, they said my
expression seemed a little stiff
and that I needed to relax.
But I really didn't
think much of it.
I figured I was just tired.
[RINGO] But. Over time,
I completely lost
the ability to smile.
Eventually, I couldn't summon up
other expressions either.
The way things were,
it didn't make sense for me
to stay where I was.
So I left,
just like that monkey.
Yeah... But...
In the end, the monkey found a
safe place where he belonged.
So you can too--
That's nice. Thanks.
[RINGO] But there's no point.
How can someone
not be able to smile?
It just doesn't make any sense.
I'm guessing it's psychological.
That's the only explanation
I can come up with.
Maybe it was all
too much for her.
Maybe she got burnt out
living in the limelight
and always trying to meet
other people's expectations.
She needs rest.
That'll make her go back
to normal, won't it?
Well. One can always hope.
[KOUSAKU] I want her
to smile again.
Do you think it's selfish
of me to want that for her?
If it is, maybe I don't care.
[VOICE] Kousaku. Kousaku!
[KOUSAKU] Whoa! Who are you?
[DREAM WAKA] Do you not
recognize me? Silly.
I am Gaia.
Gaia?
[DREAM WAKA] Yes. I have come
to deliver a message.
Uh... What message?
You must remember, Kousaku.
Remember what mankind
has done to me.
Remember your ties to the soil.
Please. Whatever the future
holds. Stand firm.
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[DREAM WAKA] Gaia is always
with you, my friend.
Till the end of time.
Listen and you will hear me.
Imploring you to honor the land!
No. Don't leave me here!
Please! Gaia!
Gaia!
[KOUSAKU gasps]
[KOUSAKU]
What was all that? Wacky.
[KOUSAKU] "Remember what
mankind has done to me."
Guys. I think I'm going to take
Ringo to you-know-where.
I really want to
show her that soil.
Good idea. After all,
she does have something
in common with it right now.
Yeah. That's true.
Maybe seeing that field and
hearing a positive message
would help her realize
there is always hope.
[KOUSAKU] Schools like ours
have things called
"Agricultural Clubs",
or "Ag Clubs" for short!
Well, at any rate, we're headed
to the site of a project
we inherited from some
former students.
[RINGO] A project?
[KOUSAKU] Yes.
And if you're willing,
we'd like for you to join in!
[RINGO] This is it?
[KOUSAKU] Yep!
[RINGO]
Not the tomato field over there?
[KOUSAKU] Nope. Here first.
[KOUSAKU] Try touching the soil.
[RINGO] Right now?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah.
It feels hard and dry.
[KOUSAKU] Mm-hmm.
The reason it feels that way
is 'cause the soil is dead.
It's dead?
[KOUSAKU]
It's a figure of speech.
Crops won't grow here
in its current condition.
That's so sad...
[KOUSAKU] It's replant failure.
Remember, Miss Becky
talked about it?
[RINGO] If you continue to grow
the same plant in the same soil
over and over, eventually,
it won't grow anymore.
Yes. That's exactly right.
People try to get
around this problem.
They use chemical fertilizers to
try to stimulate new growth.
But that only leads to disease
and winds up damaging
the environment.
What you're seeing is the
result of a vicious cycle.
[RINGO] Will the soil ever
go back to normal again
or is it dead forever?
The process takes time.
This field started out
with that very same soil.
It's been there
since the very beginning.
Previous Ag Clubbers
started this project
and we inherited it.
They worked for seven years.
Day in and day out.
Now it's our turn.
Seven years?
It's not fixed.
There's still a lot to do to
get this soil back to normal.
But even though this soil has
a long way to go,
this field is slowly improving,
doing her best to live
on the land she's got.
So, eventually, this
place will be reborn?
[RINGO]
Hey, those tomatoes look good.
Can I eat one?
What? Now?
[RINGO] I'd like to.
Sure. Why not?
Here.
[RINGO] It's bitter.
Yeah, that's 'cause
it's not ripe just yet.
Still, I'll eat it.
[KOUSAKU] Huh?
[RINGO] Yep, definitely bitter.
Told you.
Yeah, but...
I like it.
Whoa. You--!
What?
Wait, this one's
more ripe! Here.
It'll taste way better!
Mine is even riper than hers!
[MINORI] No, no, no,
stick with mine.
It's definitely juicier
than Kei's! Take it!
[KEI] Mine is fresher!
--[MINORI] Please!
--[KOUSAKU] Food made with love,
love of the earth, love of
people, spreads happiness.
The secret?
Reminding yourself
that it's Nature's gift.
Working the land is one the
greatest joys life has to offer.
One day, I hope...
I hope you'll experience
that joy firsthand.
[KOUSAKU]
Farming's Five Top Four!