[roosters caw]
[mooing]
[KEI] Time for the next phase
of your farm education.
Your time in the
rice paddy was instructive,
but I think you're
ready for more.
Lesson number two
is... going in dry!
[MINORI] There are tons of crops
that grow in those conditions.
What're we gonna
start her on?
[KEI] Hmph.
The soybean.
[KOUSAKU &amp; MINORI] Outta sight!
[KEI] I chose them, not only
because as novice farmers go,
they're a pretty forgiving crop,
but because the end-product
is such a Jack of all trades.
Miso, soy sauce, tofu,
natto, cooked beans,
soymilk and soy flour.
They can also be made
into bean sprouts or edamame.
Edamame is soybean, then?
You betcha!
The humble soybean.
So packed with nutrients
and carbohydrates.
some call it "the meat
of the field".
People eat it all the
time, it's fairly common,
but that's just one use
for this awesome legume.
In a bean-ocracy,
they would be king!
When will it sprout up?
Soybeans grow pretty quickly.
Tonight, then?
Wow. You are so from the city.
[KEI] Ten days' to two weeks'
time, give or take.
All right!
Show them who's boss, Ringo!
As Ringo pushed those handy
little soybeans into the soil,
we had no idea that one
of their products, miso,
would soon be leading me
down the shirtless path
of yogurty hell!
[MINORI] Aww! Guys,
we're out of miso!
Who feels like going
on a supply run?
But doesn't that mean
going up to Biotech?
[MINORI] Yeah.
What's a Biotech?
Oh. It's another class, like us.
Its full name's the
Biotechnology Department.
We also call them Class B,
which works out pretty well.
[KEI] Miso is important, but...
Biotech...
I'm not a big fan of
their class rep, to be honest.
Why's that?
He's totally weird.
He's so standoff-ish
most of the time.
And then he's staring
at you all funny-like.
Does he want to talk?
You look at him to
engage him in conversation
but he runs away for safety.
Then stares some more.
Awkward...
Mm-hmm!
Fine then, don't talk to him.
But if nobody mans up,
there won't be any
miso soup at dinner.
[KOUSAKU] I want soup, but...
[KEI] Kousaku. We can do this.
[KOUSAKU] Yeah. Okay.
[KEI] You ready?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah.
Miso!
Hell yeah!
[KOUSAKU] Little did we know...
[KOUSAKU] Up here, right?
[KEI] So they say.
You don't know, then?
[gasps, screams]
Ringo?! What the heck?!
I just wanted to know
where the room was.
Oh, right.
I forgot you've never
been up to Class B before.
We're kind of in the
same the boat--
We've never actually
gone inside.
[RINGO] Look at this stuff.
What do they do with it?
[KEI] Production's curriculum
is very different than ours.
[KOUSAKU] So they use
all these machines?
It's like a lab in here!
[GIRL] Such is the power
of science!
[ALL gasp]
[KOUSAKU] You...
You're Akari Suzuki,
a.k.a. Bio Suzuki!
In the flesh. Minori said you
might be paying me a visit.
Here at Tamo No-Rin,
the weirdest and strongest of us
are known as Farming's Top Four!
I never expected one of those
numbered students to be here!
Now, now.
Protocol dictates that
I receive the Class A rep,
his bosom friend,
and the rather much-discussed
transfer student with open arms.
If you want some miso,
take your fill, Class A!
[RINGO] Smells yummy.
As well it should.
Only soybeans that had
gone through a thorough
vetting process made it in.
Is that so?
[AKARI]
Put some onto a cucumber.
It makes for a wonderful snack
this time of year!
Hurry it up.
Will do.
I guess you're hungry, huh?
[KEI] Thanks for
this beany boon.
Not just yet.
Before you go, would you
be kind enough to help me
with a trifling matter?
"Trifling matter?"
What's up?
I require... some test subjects!
[KOUSAKU &amp; KEI] I don't want to!
[giggles]
[AKARI] Easy, boys...
We developed a
new product in Class B.
I merely need some help
with a trial run.
Really?
What exactly did you make?
A Lactobacillus!
[KEI &amp; KOUSAKU] Lactobacillus?
Y'mean like that junk in yogurt?
Very good.
It makes lactic acid,
and this latest batch,
complements of the
Biotech Department,
is of the vegetable variety.
Yeah, as if!
Yogurt is made of milk.
I didn't just fall off
of the turnip truck!
[giggles]
My poor boy, you must
have metal in your head.
Lactobacilli are in
rice bran pickles.
That miso you're holding.
You even find them floating
in the air we breathe.
We call ours--!
[BOTH] Dun dun dun!
Anal BB! You like that?!
For "All Natural Life
Science, Bio Type B".
It's the perfect acronym!
[KOUSAKU] Ho-boy.
With a name like that,
I thought it was some
kind of ointment
[KEI] Apply directly
to the anus.
Geez! Did you really
have to blurt it out?!
[KEI] I'm going
to regret asking,
but exactly what sort of trial
run did you have in mind?
[AKARI] Just testing the product
in real-world conditions.
Specifically, this yogurt
made from Anal BB.
A taste-test, huh?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
[AKARI] While I applaud your
willingness to lend me a hand.
This isn't the
kind of yogurt you eat.
Huh?!
[AKARI] No. It's the kind...
...you apply topically!
[BOTH] It's topical yogurt?
[RINGO] It's not for eating?
[AKARI] It's a fact.
Lactobacillus on crops
reduces vermin attacks.
Not to mention
the added promotion
of healthy germination.
This is common knowledge!
Even if the proof is anecdotal!
With that in mind, I thought
Anal BB might help
other things grow, too!
Well, she did hook us
up with the miso.
We're in her debt.
So what do you think?
Want to give it a shot?
[KEI] I'm game.
[KOUSAKU] Bad call, self.
So, uh, where are our shirts?
[AKARI] What, and get
Anal BB all over them?
I think not!
It's time for yogurt bukkake!
[AKARI] No need to
get involved, Kinoshita.
Your face is plenty
smooth without them
shooting all over it.
[KEI] You down for Anal BB?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah. Whatever
you're packing, give me.
Ugh!
Fill me in. What's up
with the camera?
Yeah, what's that about?
[AKARI] You troglodyte!
The answer to your question
is patently obvious!
I owe it to science
to document my results!
Now, less talkin'
and more bukkak-in'!
Dude. Really?
Ah--!
Candid shots!
[STUDENTS] Skeet!
Skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet,
skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet!
You fool! Why'd you aim
for the chest?
Hit him in the
glasses next time!
If you know
what's good for you,
you'll shoot your wad
on his lenses!
Fix his make-up!
[STUDENTS] Skeet!
Kei, this is a food
experiment, isn't it?
Please tell me we're not
in a yogurt porn.
[KEI] Perhaps it's a
little bit of both.
I'm ready for my
close-up, Miss Suzuki!
Quiet on the set, men!
You, you, Splotch-a-Bro,
scene two, action!
Aw, come on!
Don't sacrifice my dignity for a
film with a ripped-off title!
She swiped Hakusho!
Now I will show you
my power at 80 percent!
Dude, not the time
to quote it!
Uwegh!
What the hell?
You're shipping us!
His bro-gurt is your destiny!
[KOUSAKU] Hmm... That line.
Put it in the fan-fic.
You idiot!
I don't want to be a
Mary-Sue in my own slash!
What does all that
even mean?!
Huh?!
--Kei! Where're your pants?
--Bro-gurt... Bro-gurt...
--You-You don't want to do this!
--No, please!
--Bro-gurt! Bro-gurt!
[KOUSAKU screams]
Glad you got it off!
These dailies are solid.
As a sign of thanks,
I'll give you a "tip."
Say "hint", not "tip".
Even now as we speak,
F is on the move.
So watch yourself.
[gasps]
Dear God! F?!
[KOUSAKU] Go-go-go-go-go,
got to go, got to go fast!
[WAKA squeaks]
[MINORI] Kousaku!
What're you doing out here?
No! Go back!
It isn't safe out here!
But waiting got boring.
[KOUSAKU] So you
threw your lives away
because you got a little antsy?!
[MINORI] What's got you
all freaked out?
[KOUSAKU sighs]
Legend tells of a class
of great brutality.
[KEI] Brute strength is the only
law they choose to recognize!
Sowing terror among their
foes for a century now,
these dervishes of doom
formed the backbone
of our very school!
Their class is the letter...
[BOTH] F!
[crows cawwing]
F, huh?
Yes! And the F stands for--!
[BOY A] --fooling with the
Woodmen is a fatal flaw,
friend-o!
[KOUSAKU] Hey...
I know you!
You're one of
Farming's Top Four,
Class F rep
Rintarou "Woodman" Miyoumoto!
Shut up, sapling!
I'm going to take you up
to the House of Pain.
The Treehouse of Pain, that is.
How come, huh?
What'd I do wrong?
Sure, play dumb.
You and I both know.
You talk to women so easy
just to spite us!
[yelling]
The F in Class F
is for "forest".
Of all the various departments,
Forest Engineering has the
single harshest curriculum.
None of us graduate
without first surviving
rigorous mortal combat.
We live up here
six months outta twelve.
We're men!
With wood in our hearts!
An' we're going to
show you our wood!
[MINORI] This guy has no idea
what he just said, does he?
Guys like you don't do anything
but mess around in the dirt
with seeds and junk,
and you have two actual,
real-live girls
following you around?!
That's balls!
[KOUSAKU] Didn't a girl join
your class this year?
She left the next day!
You Class A twerps bogart
the knockout transfer student,
and that's bad enough, but
watching you treat Nakazawa
like chopped liver hits us
like a handsaw in the heart!
That's old-growth devotion, man!
Wait. Do you like her?
She's nice!
Cheerful!
Boobies!
Childhood friend!
Good cook!
[RINTAROU] She's got everything
we Woodmen look for in a woman!
So why are you sprung
for the new girl?!
[KOUSAKU] Huh?
Yeah! I think the tree-dude's
making some good points there!
[squeals]
Listen up, Kousaku.
And listen good.
Cause I'm only
going to say this once.
Is it true that you and Nakazawa
here used to take baths together
'til you were in
the ninth grade?
Huh?!
No, of course not!
That's crazy-talk, man!
Yeah, I should've
known better!
No guy is that kind of lucky!
It was only up until
the eighth grade!
You son-of-a-bitch!
[FOREST GUYS yelling]
[KOUSAKU] Wait! It's not
what you're thinking, okay?
[WAKA squeals]
I haven't had a mom
for years and years now,
and my dad works away
from home in the winter.
Get to the bath part!
Dad sent me to live at
Minori's house for a while.
[RINTAROU] Get to the bath part!
There were too many
kids to bathe alone
so my baths were
with all four sisters.
[RINTAROU] You're telling me...
You had four girls in the bath?!
At once?
Yup.
[RINTAROU] All right.
You're dead!
I don't want to die
just 'cause I kept up
with my personal hygene!
You didn't miss out
on anything, trust me!
There were no branches on this
trunk, if you catch my drift!
No branches, huh?!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Well it was the truth,
wasn't it?!
Maybe then!
But maybe you should check out
these redwoods I'm packing now!
If you want to keep
the tree simile afloat
they're more like bonsais.
Ah! Why're you being
such a bastard?!
You know what?!
My bonsais and I are
dragging you into the bath
for a rematch later today!
If I'm really such a zero,
it shouldn't be a
problem for you, right?!
Yeah, fine. I guess.
Not that I care either way--
That a boy!
I'm going to give your back
a good scrubbing
the way I always used to!
Nah, I'm good!
No you're not!
There're some places
we just can't get to.
You could wash my back, too.
It's only fair,
you big butthead.
After that, we could take a
crack at each other's fronts!
[FOREST GUYS scream]
[RINTAROU] Cute!
[FOREST GUYS yelling]
[RINGO] Huh. Eighth grade.
That story, is it true?
You were just joking, right?
[FOREST GUY 5D] Riny!
He looks tore up.
What the heck?
It's because love-triangles
are like poison to him!
[RINTAROU] Want to know
something, Kousaku?
[KOUSAKU] Yeah. I guess.
[RINTAROU] I.... I never got
to sit next to a girl in class
not having girls
or desks out here.
And I never will.
Not unless I take the bull
by the horns, right?
Problems are like trees.
Unless I start chopping away
at them, they won't go down.
[RINTAROU] That's it, then.
My mind's made up.
I'm going to give the Forest
Engineering Department
such a spit-shine, the ladies
will be signing up in droves.
Yeah? How you figure?
We'll court them.
Court who?
Forest Girls!
[FOREST GUYS] The F in
Class F is for Forest!
Yes, I speak of
that fashion trend
that's taking the
ladies by storm!
We'll be their
lumberjacks of love!
[FOREST GUYS cheer]
[MINORI] What? That idea
came and went, you guys.
[KEI] She's right.
They've moved on.
[KOUSAKU] You'll need
a time machine.
[FOREST GUYS] Shut up!
Can't you see how badly
we need women up in here?!
If only we could sit next to one
and then forget our textbook,
so we'd have to share?
Or both of us go to pick up a
dropped pencil at once
and our fingers touch?
And the group projects!
Think of the group projects!
The F in Class F is for Female!
It's like they were
raised on dating sims.
You know, they might actually
find the right ones yet.
While it's true that
the Forest Girl fad
didn't have quite so much
in the way of staying power,
there's a new breed of athletic,
outdoorsy women
who might just be what
you guys are looking for.
[FOREST GUYS gasp]
You mean it?
Take a knee, fellas!
I'm talking about.
Mountain Girls!
[FOREST GUYS] Mountain Girls!
They go hiking on
rock-strewn trails.
And some of them
even mountain-climb.
This growing trend could bring
them right to your doorstep!
[FOREST GUYS] The F
in Class F is for Mt. Fuji!
Back to the summit!
To await our womens!
[RINTAROU laughs]
[FOREST GUYS cheer]
I hope they're cool
with a hell of a wait.
[WAKA squeaks]
[GUY] It seems
Rintarou has lost.
[WOMAN] Of Farming's Top
Four, he is the weakest.
[AKARI] He's a disgrace
to our good name,
defeated by a mere
lack of women.
[AKARI giggles]
[GUY] It's time for a snack,
my tender morsel.
[KOUSAKU] Huh? Maybe she's just
running late or something.
Hmm... She said
she'd be here, though.
Wonder what's up?
[KOUSAKU] Well,
if she's not out here,
I don't know
where to look.
No! Her book!
[GUY] You're seventeen?
Serendipitous.
As years go, that one is
molto bellissimo.
[RINGO] Aren't you the same age?
[GUY] I am seventeen
at every age.
Numbers of its ilk
are known as prime.
They're lonely
in their indivisibility.
A loneliness I know
only too well.
[KOUSAKU] That's enough!
I knew that it was you,
Class E rep, Rose Hanazono!
Why, yes, I am!
[KOUSAKU growls]
I've got your number!
You're a student in the
Landscaping Department,
and you're one of
Farming's Top Four,
not to mention the fact you're
the hottest guy in school!
None of that gives you
the right to kidnap Ringo!
For that, your life is forfeit!
[RINGO slurps] Hey, Kousaku.
Please tell me your
virtue is still intact!
Why'd you no-show
at the library, huh?
[RINGO] He offered me
snacks, so...
[KOUSAKU] How the heck have you
even survived this long?!
And you! Did I or did I not
tell you to never ever
mess around with
Class A girls again?!
Oh yeah? So what
did he do before?
He tried putting the moves
on Minori about a year ago.
[KAORU laughs]
You still recall that?
Her too, I'll wager.
[KOUSAKU] Know what
happens when a hot guy
hits on a girl like Minori?!
She loses her damn mind,
that's what!
You're all she wanted to talk
about for the next three weeks!
[KAORU] I get what I want, my
dear boy, no matter the cost.
It's a good policy to have...
Eh?
You don't get to add her
to the list 'cause she's...
not for sale!
[WAKA squeaks]
[KAORU laughs]
That's just lip-service.
Like hell!
The Pockin knows your measure.
Face me in crunchy combat!
Where did you... get that?
The rules are few. We start
chewing at it from either side.
Whoever breaks it apart or
flinches first is the loser.
Have at you, churl!
Trial by Pockin! With Ringo
as prize to the victor!
Bring it on!
Don't fret, Ringo!
I've got this one in the bag!
[KOUSAKU] He's really going
on the offensive, huh?!
[KOUSAKU] What?!
Hanazono closed his eyes!
He's not backing off at all!
He just keeps nibbling!
My heart is pounding!
The heat from his face
is burning me up!
[KAORU chuckles]
Stop this game! It's a trap!
[sighs]
And not a single
moment to spare.
Kousaku, I need you to step away
from that man on the double!
Rose Hanazono is class rep of
the Landscaping Department,
but the landscape that
interests him most
is right in front of him!
[KEI] I was too late!
Get your mouth off of him!
That right there
is the money shot!
I have tasted the rainbow!
[KAORU] Your first kiss
wasn't Ringo! It was me, 'Zono!
You have a lot of
nerve, don't you!
Indeed.
How long I've waited
for this moment.
It was di molto bellissima!
Then... you couldn't care
less about Minori or Ringo!
Go on!
[KOUSAKU] You used them to
get to me 'cause you're--!
[KAORU] Yes! I am!
Well I am not, so slow
your roll, hot-lips!
And you guys just sat back
and let this happen?
You betcha!
Your uke hi-jinks will play out
fantastically in my doujinshi!
How come I got to
be the uke?!
There's a big gay world
waiting for you!
I'm fine right here!
It's all because he
bathed with me!
Your boobs are great, okay?!
Hey.
You need something, Ringo?
[RINGO] One, Bio Suzuki.
Two, Woodman Rintarou.
Three, Rose Hanazono.
[KOUSAKU] Mm... So?
[RINGO] Aren't there four?
[gasping]
[WAKA squeaks]
[mysterious laughter]
[KOUSAKU] Next time on No-Rin,
the last member of Farming's
Top Four will arrive!
Probably could've done all this
in one episode, but whatever!
[KOUSAKU]
Full-Moe Alchemist: Bounty.