Buddyfight
uses special cards
that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters
known as the
Hundred Demons
have come
here illegally
and plan to
destroy the planet.
It's time for
an Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on.
Let's have a
snapping good time!
I'd never let you get
your grubby mitts on me.
I cast Great
Pillar of Fire!
What?
(cough)
Crimson Fist,
Dragoblaze!
Aaah!
(sinister laughing)
Now I cast
Quiescence of Cassiade!
Now any
damage I receive
is reduced by
three whole points.
Uh, oh.
You okay?
Get a hold
of yourself, kid.
Come on,
stand up, Gao!
Count Dawn,
it's your move.
I'm going to
activate my ability.
I pay one life and revive
myself to the right.
Let twilight return.
That's right,
Count Dawn can revive
if the player
pays one life
at the beginning
of the turn.
I call Wolfman, Gutz
to the center position.
♪
Let's do it.
I'll send my double
in to attack first.
Deluxe Column!
Arrgh, arrgh!
(giggle)
This will be easier
than I thought, Bia.
I cast Check It Out.
Guess that's
last call.
That's a counter spell
that returns all
monsters in the field
to each player's hand,
and lets the
player using it
call one
to the center.
I call Mysterious
Decarabia to the center.
The buddy gift gives
her one life point.
It's time to solve
Decarabia's mystery.
My Takoscope will
give us the 411.
Mysterious Decarabia
72 Pillars attributes,
size two, 6,000 power,
3,000 defense,
and a critical of two.
And when it
appears on the field...
We're going to play
rock, paper, scissors, Bia.
Rock, paper...
Huh?
Scissors.
I win, which means
I get to destroy
one of your cards
in the field.
I underestimated
her powers, for sure.
Arrgh!
Here in the
Darkness Barrier,
things are going
from bad to worse.
Gao was forced
to choose a card
after Death Shido
cast Dangerous Fuse
and increased his
gauge by two points.
(groaning)
Buddy call Iron
Cyclops to the right.
In case you
aren't in the know,
my new pal here has
a critical of four
and a double attack.
Aargh!
You lucky viewers
are about to witness
history in the making.
Gao Mikado's about to
lose his first match ever.
He's such a hater,
hey, A‐Dog?
Uh, A‐Dog?
Hey, where you at, yo?
Iron!
Argh!
Gotcha.
‐Uh.
‐You can do this.
Now you'll see
that I, Death Shido,
am the greatest
Buddyfighter in the world!
Cyclops, finish him!
Iron!
Hang tough, Gao,
I'm on my way.
I cast Blue
Dragon Shield!
Fine, I'll just finish
you on my next turn.
To finish his turn,
Death Shido
destroys Guns Knuckle
with Fate Skeleton.
Now Gao's up.
It's not looking
good for Mikado.
No, he's only got
two life points.
And Death Shido
has 12 left.
I've never seen
anyone come back
when the gap's
been this big.
Can you do this?
Somewhere, Tasuku
is watching us.
Huh?
So no matter
how tired I am,
I won't let him see me
give a lousy fight.
I got to dig deep
and deliver!
Draw!
Charge and draw!
You're up, pal.
I buddy call
Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon
to the right!
Who needs food, I can
live on Buddyfight!
Hah, hah, arggh!
Arrgh!
Let's do this.
And now he's called up
Spin Nail Dragon.
You know what
that means, folks.
Time for the
Gao Formation!
Why'd you do that,
I mean, I still have
12 life points!
My fist will change
that, Doofus Shido.
Aah!
We're never going to win
with him as our fighter.
I couldn't agree more.
Master Ikazuchi,
what are you doing here?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm running
out of patience.
Grrr.
Death Shido's quickly
down to four life points.
You got to
hand it to Mikado,
he's now made
a game of it.
Heh, not for long.
Actually, my turn
isn't over yet.
What?
When he has a
fist item equipped,
his opponent has
four life or less,
and both players have
no monster in the center,
then the conditions
are perfect for...
Final Phase!
But I don't want
to get zapped again!
I cast...
And there it is!
The Impact card that
cost three gauge to use
and inflicts four damage
that can not be reduced.
♪
Impact!
Gigantic Crusher!
Why me?
(explosion)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
All right, now
we can get some...
You all right?
Do you need
some help?
Where's the
Hundred Demon card?
Up there.
‐Huh?
‐Uh?
‐Hah!
Yet another
disappointment.
Grrr.
I know you.
My name is Ikazuchi.
Yeah, and?
I've come to
devour Tenbu!
Did someone
call my name?
This is the creep who
stole your memories, gramps.
Is that so?
Yes, but this time
I'll do more than that.
I'm gonna eat you down
to every last bone.
Or rather my
buddy Yamigedo will.
Yamigedo,
never heard of him.
Uh!
Not that horrible beast.
Don't tell me he's
recovered enough power
to fight again.
Count Dawn has
called two monsters,
setting himself up for
a triple attack formation!
And one of his
units, Cuelebre,
has the Penetrate ability.
But Lady Suzuha
has eight life left,
and she has
three Decarabias
in position
in front of her.
I don't know if
Count Dawn's two life
can see him
through to victory.
I can't let Gao fight
that foul creature
in his current condition.
I cast Decree of Dullahan!
That spell gives all
Wydar Sarkal monsters
in the field a
double attack ability!
What a play!
Cuelebra's attack
hits its mark,
and after unloading Penetrate,
Lady Suzuha
receives two damage.
Get ready for
the second attack.
I wasn't taking this
serious enough, Bia!
Aaaah!
Prepare to be
the main course.
♪
Why not let me
be your opponent?
Asmodai?
Where's Tetsuya?
I don't need
to cramp his style
by buggin' him out
over a homey
like this, yo.
I thought you
looked familiar.
As you wish.
(gasps)
You can be
the appetizer.
♪
Don't you dare
change that channel
because another fight
is about to start.
One of the fighters
is none other than
Demon Lord, Asmodai.
When did he get there?
What does he think
he's doing out there?
A millennial kingdom where
you can play for ages.
Luminize,
Devil's Millennium!
I just had word
that Asmodai is using
Tetsuya Kurodake's deck.
Hundred Demons
working in the darkness,
destroy and rampage!
Devour the world.
Dark Luminize
Hundred Thunder Demons!
Once again, Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
I'm with Magic World.
Parade of Hundred Demons.
I have never heard
of that world.
I wonder what kind
of monsters live there?
It's not a world,
but I can call
Hundred Demons monsters
from any world I chose.
Any Hundred
Demons he wants?
He could call an army.
I'd better ask
for reinforcements.
With the first
move of the game,
Asmodai calls Fallen
Angel of Rage, Beleth
to the center,
and immediately sends
him on the offensive.
What gives, A‐Dog?
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Hundred Demons,
I summon you.
Poisonous Water
Dragon, Zazamera,
Purplish Green
Dragon, Peluda,
Rampage, Chizomegumo.
Peluda, go
and devour Beleth.
Aargh!
You're next,
Chizomegumo.
Ever dance
with a spider?
I can almost taste it.
Go, Zazamera.
That is not happening
on my shift, homes.
I cast
Solomon's Shield!
End of move.
You're wasting
both of our time.
You can not defeat me.
You're grouchy, did you
skip your pre‐game nap?
Asmodai has just called
Great Duke, Astaroth
to the center area.
♪
A size two monster,
what a joke.
(screeches)
I active Zazamera's
Thunder Mine.
Aargh!
♪
After calling a
monster on his turn,
Asmodai's the one
receiving damage.
Uh, Thunder Mine.
What is it?
When certain
conditions are met,
it's an ability
that causes one damage
to an opponent.
I must find a
way to help him.
Asmodai calls Demon
Realm Architect, Gamigin.
However, as he's
a size one monster,
Peluda's Thunder Mine
has been activated,
resulting in one damage.
Aargh!
I didn't expect
to win this fight
without getting
a few scrapes.
Asmodai sets
Solomon's Great Barrier.
That spell turns all size
two 72 Pillars monsters
in the field
into size one.
Next he calls Sky Poet,
Amon to the right.
This just might work.
Come on, Asmodai,
you can win.
Yeah, do it!
Clear the way
for progress.
We didn't forget
about you, fool.
Twice is just as nice.
♪
This is your
final verse.
I cast Hundred Demons
Sorcery, Yamitagae.
No, I have failed.
End of move.
I may have
missed my chance.
Gao?
'Sup, Zanya?
You're not
injured, are you?
I'm fine.
Do you have any idea
who that guy is
fighting against Asmodai?
Once again, Ikazuchi calls
the powerful Chizomegumo.
I equip.
Veiled in the
darkness of terror,
awake the mighty jaws
of the wicked beast
that hungers
for misery.
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
Hundred Demons
devour everything!
Show no mercy,
Zazamera.
Aah!
♪
Astaroth is
revived with Soulguard.
Once destruction
isn't enough
to keep him down.
Good thing I was
prepared for that.
I cast Hundred Demons
Sorcery, Ryubokushihai.
Aaah!
I pay one life.
Ikazuchi uses a counter
spell to destroy Astaroth
who's run out
of cards in his soul.
He's on a roll now.
Monsters, fighters,
and Hundred Demons,
I'll devour every
last one of you
if I have to.
He actually destroyed
his own monster!
Why would he do that?
Now his center
position is wide open.
By simply destroying
a monster in my center
your end approaches.
It increases
Narukami's critical.
Yo, A‐Dog.
Tatsuya.
You can't lose.
I'll consume all
of your power, too.
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
Aah!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Ikazuchi.
Devour him, Yamigedo.
♪
No!
Aaah!
Oh, no.
(gasps)
Asmodai has been...
He's been eaten alive.
(weeping)
Asmodai.
(flames roaring)
Thought I'd trained you
better than that, hey, Tets?
I thought you
were worm food!
The guy you
saw get eaten
was one of my doubles.
(growling)
Although I have
lost half my power.
♪
You don't see
that every day.
What just happened?
How'd it do that?
I don't know.
It looks
like he evolved.
♪
(roaring)
Do you think that
could be his true form?
Impressive, isn't he?
Want to know
what he's called?
Great Fiend, Yamigedo.
Stand strong, don't
let him intimidate you.
You're up next, Tenbu.
I welcome any challenge
you lay before me.
(satellite beeping)
What is that?
A Buddy Police barrier.
But who set it?
Sorry to keep
you waiting, Gao.
Huh?
Tasuku!
The Tasuku Ryuenji?
If you want
to fight someone,
fight me!
Incredible.
I don't believe it!
Tasuku's finally returned
from his lengthy
training in Dragon World!
And if this reporter
can speak candidly,
he's even dreamier and more
heroic looking than before!
Like a knight
in shining armor.
Is it really him?
Indeed, My Lady.
What happened, I
don't remember a thing.
It's horrible.
Defeating the second Omni
Demon Lord is bad enough,
but taking half
of his power...
Unite elite warriors
of the future.
Radiant Evolution, Luminize!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
Star Dragon World.
S‐S‐S‐Star Dragon World?
What is that?
Parade of
Hundred Demons.
Just seeing him again
is making me
weak in the knees,
now he's fighting for
some amazing new world?
I never
stopped believing.
I knew that he'd
come back one day.
This is what
Gao told us about.
Now we finally
get to see it.
Yeah, bro.
With the first move,
Ikazuchi calls
Peluda to the center.
And then Zazamera
to the right.
Ahh!
Blazing fire!
(Tasuku groans)
♪
End of move.
Is that all
you got, pal?
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I cast Dragonarms Factory
and discard a Dragonarms
attribute card.
Now I can draw
two new cards.
That's new, a spell
that lets you draw
regardless of
your life points?
I pay one gauge
and one life
to equip Star
Saber, Asteroid.
Rainbow Vision,
Scattershare to the left.
And I buddy call Star Guardian,
Jackknife to the right.
With a buddy gift,
he regains one life point.
Tasuku, watch out
for the Thunder Mines!
For Peluda to size one
and Zazamera a size two.
When those
monsters are called,
their Thunder Mines
are activated.
Aaah!
(cracking)
I knew what to expect.
Crush mines!
Dragonarms loaded.
Role shift,
variant form.
All devices engage.
SES active.
Load finished.
Roar!
Cavalier Sword!
'Kay, Jack, do a Penetrate
attack on the center.
10‐4!
Cavalier Sword!
And Penetrate!
♪
Shadowscare,
now it's your turn.
Yes, master.
Visionator!
I cast Hundred Demon
Sorcery, Ryubokushihai.
Ahh!
I regain one more life.
You'll need it.
Tasuku's definitely
come to play.
So this is Star
Dragon World, huh?
Ikazuchi's called monsters
with Thunder Mines ability.
And equip Thunder
Claw, Narukami.
Using Hundred Demons'
Tone of Judgment,
he's increased the number
of cards in his hand
and set reinforced
formation of Hundred Demons.
Hundred Demons, I order
you to devour them all.
(roars)
Peluda!
Aahhhh!
Zazamera!
I cast Proto Barrier!
I will just
devour you myself!
By destroying Peluda,
Narukami's critical
has increased.
I cast Earth Barrier!
Earth Barrier's ability
helps Tasuku
regain one life,
but with the
reinforced formation
of Hundred Demons that
Ikazuchi set earlier,
the Peluda in the
center has revived.
Tasuku manages to side
step the Thunder Mine
and calls Dragonarms,
Winchisker to the left.
Star Guardian,
Jackknife unleashes
another punishing
Penetrate attack.
But Ikazuchi blocks it
with a counter spell.
Ah, Tasuku,
you can't fool me.
I know you're
fighting for my honor.
Winchisker, attack
the Peluda in the center.
Aaahh!
Star Saber, Asteroid!
End of move.
Ikazuchi's down
to two life!
He'll be toast
on the next turn.
I wouldn't be so sure.
‐Hmm?
What gives, A‐Dog?
I'm afraid he still has
a card up his sleeve.
Huh?
♪
Be patient, we'll
be eating soon enough.
I buddy call
to the right,
the most powerful
demon beast
that is starving
for destruction!
Devour the Hundred Demons
and show yourself!
Great Fiend, Yamigedo!
Now I've
seen everything!
Ikazuchi's buddy
monster's been called
and he's eating
all of his team mates!
Ah, if I could
muster the courage,
I'll use my
trusty Takoscope
to check out his deeds!
Great Fiend, Yamigedo.
No way!
(roaring)
♪
(explosion)
Error, barrier down.
The Star Pulsar!
They just disappeared.
But I'm afraid
they'll be back.
Regretfully,
I must inform you
that the time to tell
you everything has come.
Are you sitting down?
It's pretty bad.
I am.
To avoid all possible
danger facing us,
you promised to
tell me everything.
Leave nothing out.
Agreed?
Agreed.
It's time
that you knew.
(wind blowing)
(roaring)
Long ago, there was a
terrifyingly evil monster
that led the
Hundred Demons
in the destruction
of countless worlds.
In an effort to
cease further sorrow,
eight beings
known as Omni Lords,
hailing from
different worlds,
united to quell the beast
and seal it on Earth forever.
Are you one of
these Omni Lords?
Indeed I am.
Well, where
are the others?
I don't know.
But if I had to guess,
I would say that
they are most likely
still on this planet
watching over the seal.
My Lady,
it may be best
if you returned
to your quarters.
Yes, you're right.
(crowd murmuring)
What is your
important announcement?
What was that monster
above the chateau?
Why was the Buddy Police
barrier activated?
Is it to do with
your big announcement?
Or is it all just
a publicity stunt?
I would never
do such a thing.
But if you must know,
I'll tell you.
It's about the danger
threatening our world.
(crowd gasping)
Now that I have
your attention,
it's about time you
knew that the Earth
is currently facing
an overwhelming threat.
A monster called Yamigedo,
who leads the
Hundred Demons army,
is trying to
destroy the planet.
And there's only
one way we'll be able
to avoid this fate.
Elicit the help
of the Omni Lords,
eight monsters
with immense power.
Omni Lords?
The Omni Lords are
believed to be living
right here on Earth.
It's possible
that some of them
have lost their memories
and don't know who they are.
They may be
living among us
and hiding the truth
about being Omni Lords.
Or even regular humans going
about their daily business
oblivious to
their past lives.
Whatever the case,
we must find them
or the Earth is doomed.
We must locate
them at any cost!
Omni Lords,
if you're out there,
our planet needs you now‐‐
It appears that
the whole world
knows about
the threat now.
Count Dawn!
What is going on?
It's just as you heard.
We need all hands
on deck right away.
All right,
we won't rest
until we find
all the Omni Lords
and the planet's safe.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna
teach you all about
the cool new ability
card, Thunder Mine.
Awesome!
It's activated by the
size of monster called,
but it always causes
one damage point.
For Peluda,
it's a size one.
For Zazamera,
a size two.
And waive a size three.
When an opponent calls
one of this size,
the abilities trigger.
No way!
With each monster
that your opponent calls,
they lose a life
point right away.
It's a very useful
ability to have.
I'm gonna have Thunder Mine
nightmares for a week!
♪
Next time, the search for
the eight Omni Lords is on!
That is if Yamigedo
doesn't get in our way.
Ikazuchi's mysterious
past is revealed
and Gao does
the unthinkable!
Next episode, "Yamigedo!
The Fiend that Devours All!
Join us for a Buddyfight!