(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the Eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them and
there's only one way we can!
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
Master Protection.
♪
This is over.
There's no defending this.
Attack the center.
Variable Typhoon.
(roars)
I'm sorry, I couldn't
squash him!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Suzaku Kenran.
♪
(whimpering)
So, I've finally
tracked you down.
I imagined my enemies
would look more formidable.
Dude, we're not
your enemies!
Yeah, we don't
even know you.
We're just
hanging out.
That's what
they all say.
Now, who wants
some nice scars?
Um, we're good.
We don't need
any scars, thanks.
Leave 'em alone, tough guy.
(wind whistling)
Huh?
♪
(gasps)
Easy, pal.
We're in the
human world now.
It's no place to be
acting all uncivilized.
♪
Ha, looks like someone wants
to be first to get sliced up.
Some people
never learn.
♪
(all gasping)
This is Takihara.
I'm arriving
at the scene now.
The situation's escalating.
Witnesses are
reporting shots fired.
Please hurry!
On it.
You boys okay?
What happened to
the illegal monster?
You mean him?
Huh?
Thanks for the
cool new scars.
Who did this?
One was wearing a bamboo hat,
and the other a black felt hat?
We're getting reports of them
showing up in town a lot lately.
Last night, they
were front and center
in a confrontation
with an illegal monster.
Bamboo hats are
what they wear
in historical Asian
dramas, right, yo?
Black felt hats are the ones
like the gangsters wore.
♪
Yeah, I guess.
Though illegal
monsters themselves,
they've been helping
humans who have been attacked
by other illegal monsters.
And also, according
to eyewitnesses,
the bigger one who
wears the felt hat,
has two big
horns on his head.
Do you think
he's an Omni Lord?
Only one way to find out.
We'll have to
track them down.
Hmm.
By the way, what is
Drum doing over there?
(groans)
When Omni Lords get
close to each other,
their emblems are
supposed to react somehow.
He's just trying
to see how it works.
(grunting)
This one!
You're wrong again.
One more time!
Best five out of nine.
No matter how many times you
try, it won't make a difference.
If he could master the ability
to sense other Omni Lords,
I'd send you out on
this assignment, Gao,
but for the time being,
Tetsuya and his
buddy will take the lead.
Represent!
We'll roll up
on those illegals
and see if one of
'em's an Omni Lord.
Ah, no fair!
I was looking
forward to this one.
Yeah, but look
on the bright side.
You can keep training.
I hate being on
the sidelines.
I want to get in
on the action.
I hear ya, kid.
Sorry, I can't get
this darn thing to work.
With Zanya and Tasuku
out on assignment,
I know I'm not
your first choice,
but I won't
let you down.
Let's go, A‐Dog.
Why so wound up, Tets?
As the future king
of Magic World,
you need to
learn to chill.
Hmm?
Hey, you all
right, A‐Dog?
Something cramping
your style?
(chuckling)
It's all good.
I was sitting so long
my leg fell asleep.
Is that all, homes?
You had me totally
twisted, yo.
Pay it no mind.
Let's go find
us an Omni Lord.
Hmm.
♪
(whimpering)
Targets confirmed.
Commencing extermination.
♪
Take a look at us!
We aren't any
threat to you!
Safety released,
ammunition loaded.
Elimination
Protocol: Engaged.
(screaming)
Why are you monsters
coming after us?
We're just hanging
out eating our lunch.
Check it, A‐Dog.
An illegal monster at 12:00.
I don't think that's the same
guy we're looking for though.
Big whoop, we still
got to get him.
Back off, buster.
♪
That's the guy.
It's the dude
from last night.
Please, you
got to save us!
Interference detected.
♪
Trying to bump me off, eh?
We could have handled
this peaceful‐like,
but now you've
insulted me, see.
You should mind
your manners.
♪
Increasing
fire power.
Obliteration Mode.
♪
Time's up, pal.
(grunts)
♪
He's got two horns, yo!
(boys yelling)
No doubt that he's the
Second Omni Demon Lord, yo.
Nah, I don't think so.
How can you
be so sure, yo?
We don't know
until we check.
‐Excuse me.
‐There's no need to check.
‐That is not an Omni Lord.
‐Uh, you there!
Oh, what suddenly
makes you the expert
on Omni Lords,
huh, homes?
I'm talking to you!
Huh?
Forgive me if I'm
mistaken, fellow,
but your name doesn't happen
to be Asmodai, does it?
Otherwise known as...
Second Omni Demon Lord?
What are you
talking about?
A‐Dog's not
an Omni Lord.
So, who told you?
No one, I was just
testing a hunch is all.
Funny, when I was
eyeballing you,
I never pegged
you for a sucker.
♪
A‐Dog's the Second
Omni Demon Lord?
♪
Is that true, Count?
Wait, if he's the one then
wouldn't your Omni Lord Emblem
have reacted or lit up
when you're around him?
Have you known
from the start?
Hmm.
♪
I have you at
a disadvantage.
Oh, how's that?
I know your name, Ace, but
you don't know what mine is.
I go by Mukuro Shigamine.
I'm a humble wanderer
on your planet
from the great Hero World
without any fixed address.
The big gorilla standing
behind me is my buddy.
He's called
Shadow Hero Schwarz.
Guten Tag.
We feel like a couple of oafs
being new to your world.
We're on the up
and up, you can be sure.
We'd like to help you
fellows out anyway we can.
Awesome, we could
use their help, huh?
I don't know.
What exactly are they
doing just wandering around?
We aim to defeat Yamigedo,
but in order to do that...
You're on, Schwarz.
♪
Nothing personal,
but I'll be needing you
to hand over your
Omni Lord Emblem.
But I thought you
wanted to help.
I do, but your buddy lost half
his body to Yamigedo, see,
and he's been as weak
as a kitten ever since.
♪
The way you are now
there's no way
you can muster the
strength to face Yamigedo,
so I figured, I'd throw
my hat in the ring
to become Omni Lord
in your place.
Oh, man, the
nerve of this guy!
But is what
he said true?
Has Asmodai really lost
most of his strength?
Yes.
He pretends that
nothing's wrong,
but his affliction is worse
than first anticipated.
The way he is now it would be
impossible to seal Yamigedo.
But isn't there
a way to fix him?
I'm afraid he's the only
one who can answer that.
Earth'll be destroyed
if we don't stop Yamigedo.
Why would Asmodai hide this
from us and put us at risk?
I don't quite understand
his logic, myself,
but he is a
demon after all.
It stings for me to
admit that my Hero World
didn't play a role in the
last go‐round with Yamigedo.
So, this is my
chance to reclaim
some long lost
honor for my people.
I feel your pain, but
taking the emblem by force
isn't cool for a hero.
Well, that's just it.
There's all kinds of
heroes in my world, kid.
We have those who protect the
weak, fighting against the bad,
and some who live on
the straight and narrow
only to rise up and come forward
when others need their help,
but there are also the
special few born into darkness
who use their powers of
evil to fight fire with fire
doing whatever's required.
Sometimes they'll even
sacrifice their own to do it.
That's who we are.
The notorious
Dark Heroes.
♪
Yeah, this place will
work just swell, Mack.
Now, as agreed, if I defeat you,
your Omni Lord Emblem is mine.
Do I have your word?
As promised.
A deal's a deal.
We're gonna win
for sure, yo.
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
you'll find me, Paruko Nanana.
Today's big match is being held
at the popular Choyoyoki Park,
and the players are Tetsuya
and his buddy Asmodai versus...
Um, I'm sorry,
but who are you?
Mukuro Shigamine.
I am but a humble
wanderer from Hero World
who has traveled to your
planet to right a wrong‐‐
She just wants
your name, yo!
Okay, Mukuro Shigamine!
I think I can
remember that.
(growls)
A millennial kingdom, yo,
where you can play for ages.
Luminize!
Devil's Millennium!
♪
Time to make my
people proud.
Blending with the
shadows to cut down evil!
The lone wolves of justice!
Luminize, Shadow Heroes!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm with Magic World!
I am here for
Hero World.
The first move
goes to Mukuro.
(shuddering)
Oh, Sofia, I hope you
get back here soon.
Charge and draw!
I cast Hyper Energy!
Right away, Mukuro increases
his gauge by four.
And I set First
Darkhero Hideout.
If I remember correctly,
that set spell allows him
to draw an extra card when
he calls a Dark Hero monster.
I'm impressed you
actually know that.
FYI, bub, I happen to be
a user of Hero World too!
Oops, I shouldn't
lose my cool.
I call Judgment Hollow,
Strydarm to the center.
Ammunition Reload: complete.
Acquiring next target.
Oh, that guy?
It's the same illegal monster
he fought at the playground.
Uh‐huh, why do
you think that is?
I knew if we kept at it,
you'd have to pop your
head out of your hole
sooner or later, Ace.
It's what you
good guys do.
I hate bamboozling, but
you see I had no choice.
It was all a setup?
Yes, it appears he duped us
by staging all of the attacks.
I can't believe he
involved innocent humans.
Let me get my
hands on this guy.
We've been outsiders for
as long as we can remember.
Think of us what you will.
It makes no difference.
Now, Strydarm.
Exterminating target.
Strydarm hits Tetsuya
with a Rapid Fire attack.
Pursue him.
Recalibrating.
He can destroy
gauge too, yo?
Mission: complete.
Strydarm sends himself
to the drop zone
when his attack is over,
so Mukuro ends his
turn with no monsters
remaining in the field.
This will be
over in no time.
I pay one gauge and cast
Nice One! and draw two cards.
Next, I cast Key of
Solomon, First Volume
and increase my
gauge by two,
and call Demon Realm Architect,
Gamigin to the left.
You called?
Please build me
Solomon's Great Barrier.
Piece of cake for me.
Here.
Tetsuya pays one gauge
and sets the spell
Solomon's Great Barrier.
This will now allow him to call
Size Two monsters as Size Ones.
I got it going on!
I call Fallen Angel of Rage,
Beleth to the center,
and Sky Poet, Amon
to the right.
I cast I Have No Business
With the Likes Of You!
(screams)
Mukuro launches
his counter spell
and wipes out all
of Tetsuya's monsters!
Talk about a major blow!
That stinks.
You should put me in, Tets.
I don't know, you sure
you're up for the heat, homes?
You got to be
kidding me, right, Tets?
He might be a Dark Hero
and all, but I'm a demon.
I could wipe the floor
with a punk like him,
even if I was down to one
tenth my power, you dig?
Okay, sorry that I asked!
In that case,
let's go A‐Dog!
Yeah!
I pay one gauge and call
Dance Asmodai to the right,
and draw one card.
Next, I call
Let's Play Asmodai to the left,
so I can regain one life.
And of course, I buddy call
my favorite buddy, Asmodai,
to the center position.
(growls)
Look at this!
Three Asmodai's in a row!
Three's better than one.
Shall we dance, demon?
Why not make it
a triple play, boys?
(grunting)
The Asmodai's deliver
a punishing attack.
Oh, yeah, he
looks fine to me!
Me too.
You sure he's really
lost his strength?
I agree it is
hard to tell.
He is a demon, after all.
You got moxie,
kid, I like it.
Quite a knock
you laid on me.
Draw, charge and draw.
I call The Scar
to the left.
This time I can give
someone a nice scar.
I activate First Darkhero
Hideout's ability,
and I'll draw one card.
So that's it,
he's using it
to make up for the
cards that he loses
during each attack phase.
Not a bad observation, kid,
but you'll soon see we have
yet to release our true power.
I pay one gauge and discard
one card from my hand,
then buddy call Shadow Hero,
Schwarz to the right.
Guten Tag.
Even as a fellow
Hero World player,
I've never heard
of this guy before.
Time for my handy
Tako scope.
Shadow Hero, Schwarz,
Dark Hero attribute.
A Size Two monster with
7,000 power, 4,000 defense
and a critical of two.
He has a unique
Dumb Strike ability
which lets him destroy one
enemy monster when called.
♪
And in that get up,
he looks totally cool.
Danke schoen.
Dumb strike.
‐No, A‐Dog!
‐The emblem is mine.
Brace yourselves.
I pay one gauge
and life to equip.
Blade of Shadow,
Burial Shadow Requiem!
The Scar's soul slayer!
I leave you scarred
down to your soul!
The Scar is destroyed
after his attack.
Looks like I need to
exorcise another demon.
You're out!
Schwarz, Hell Despot.
Ja wohl.
♪
Dance Modai's
dance card is up.
I'll be back.
No way!
Schwarz has the ability to
return to the player's hand
after finishing
his attack.
(grunts)
Once again, Mukuro
leaves himself
with no monsters in the field
at the end of his turn.
♪
But with Schwarz
back in Mukuro's hand,
that means he can be called
again on the next turn.
And every time
he comes out,
he's guaranteed to destroy
one of Tetsuya's monsters.
By disappearing into the
hand after each attack,
Tetsuya never gets a
chance to destroy him.
A powerful opponent.
Now what?
Tetsuya calls Beleth to the left
and Play Modai to the center.
He increases his life and
prepares for a counter attack.
Okay, you guys, let's do it.
Attack this guy.
How do you like that?
Spike Shoe Dunk!
‐Home run!
‐End of move.
Tetsuya caused four damage
rebounding nicely
after a slow start.
There's no telling
who will come out on top.
‐Your move.
‐I draw.
Then I charge and draw.
I call The Scar to the left
and Schwarz to the right area.
First Darkhero Hideout
lets me draw one card.
Dumb strike.
Schwarz uses his ability
to destroy Play Modai.
Scar, attack.
I'll slice up those bananas,
you little brat.
I cast Chillax!
With that counter spell,
Tetsuya regains one life point.
♪
I couldn't even touch
him with my soul slayer.
Chicago Typewriter,
Schwarz, lay it on him.
Fire!
Schwarz unloads his
machine gun attack
and true to form, back
to the hand, he goes.
Ready for your
wooden kimono?
Shadow Requiem!
(screams)
Alright, I'm still in it.
‐Now I can‐‐
‐Final Phase.
‐Say what?
‐Already?
Mukuro thinks he's
got the game in hand.
Let's see what he's got.
This is for all the marbles.
When my opponent
has four life or less
and I have no monsters
in the field,
and if I also have
a Dark Hero item equipped,
then I'm able to use
my special impact, see.
Why so glum, chum?
Now I cast
This Will Be The End!
Huh?
♪
Shigamine Infinite Sword!
(screams)
Infinity Death Crest!
(screaming)
We have a winner!
Game over.
Winner: Mukuro Shigamine.
This mysterious dark hero
appears out of nowhere
and takes out
Tetsuya Kurodake.
♪
Guess we lost, huh?
Sorry, A‐Dog.
As you promised earlier.
It's time for you to
hand over the loot, friends.
You mean this
Omni Lord Emblem?
Don't think so, Ace!
But you made a deal.
I should have figured you
weasels would double cross me.
What kind of guy breaks a
promise made in good faith?
A demon.
I mean, that's what we do.
We are natural born liars
if you didn't already know.
Why would you think
I'd hand it over
to a low level
gangster like you?
(chuckling)
(gasps)
Why deny the obvious?
With half your body devoured,
in your weakened state,
there's no way you
can seal away Yamigedo.
Give it back, yo.
Fine, you can have it.
I never really
wanted to deal
with that vicious monster,
anyway, so go ahead.
Try and use it
if you dare.
I'll do more
than try, Ace.
It seems I was overly generous
in my estimation of you.
Even with your
weakened powers.
Got to fly, slick.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Huh?
What's the deal here?
Why'd you let
him take it, huh?
Is it just me or is
anyone else panicking
over what just
went down here?
Anybody?
We need to come up
with a plan right away.
That is if anything
can be done now.
Don't you think you're
being a bit dramatic, Count?
What are you
talking about?
You gave away your
Omni Lord Emblem.
What are you
talking about?
I did no such thing,
I've got it right here.
‐Huh?
♪
The one he has is a fake.
(growls)
You had me.
Good one.
My stomach would
disagree with you.
♪
Hmm?
Hmm.
You don't seem very
surprised about it.
About what, the
emblem being a fake
or you being an
Omni Lord all this time?
Either one.
Sure, I'm surprised, but
you said it best, A‐Dog.
Demons are
nothing but liars.
(laughing)
Yeah, that's right!
Come here,
don't be mad.
I couldn't say anything
to anyone, even you!
Hang on tight!
I mean it, A‐Dog.
You and me are the
best buddies ever.
And no matter what happens,
we'll be together forever.
(chuckling)
♪
(screams)
Drum, I told you never
to open the blinds!
Oops, quick, hide me
before he comes back!
You're on your own, pal!
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'll teach you
everything you wanted to know
about Shadow
Hero, Schwarz.
Bring it!
This Dark Hero card
never misses a target
and lives in the
mystery of the shadows.
Before you can call him,
you need to discard a
Dark Hero from your hand
and pay one gauge,
but he's worth it,
because when he's called,
he can destroy any monster.
He sounds tough.
He also returns to your
hand after he attacks,
so you can call him every
turn to destroy a monster.
Man, I think
I have a new hero!
(laughs)
♪
Next time, Zanya loses to First
Omni Beast, Lord Ziun again.
That's when Jin Magatsu
shows up and persuades Zanya
to challenge Ziun
a third time.
Next episode,
"Ghoul Deity Combine!
Gojinmaru!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!