Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
but now a swarm of evil monsters
known as the Hundred Demons
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on!
Contact has failed.
Reactivating safety lock
on Ice Prison Emperor,
Cocytus Greed.
It seems that someone
has installed some form
of data protection
on this buddy card.
Who'd do that?
It's strange, this has
never happened before.
I can only guess that
there must be something
top secret hidden on it,
and whatever it is,
they're trying to
keep it from us.
Our enemy is definitely
a cunning one, that's for sure.
How pathetic, Commander.
No, it can't be.
♪
Huh?
(rumbling)
(shrieking)
(screaming)
♪
Huh?
I had to see for
myself that the rumors
about you enlisting
children were true.
Yet even this humbling fact
has brought you no closer
to ending the crisis.
If you came around more often,
you'd know that since the
Hundred Demons' arrival,
our force has been busy
dealing with visits
from many other
illegal monsters as well.
Who is that guy?
His name is Count Dawn.
He's a monster
from Legend World
and a senior member
of the Buddy Police.
Monsters can be
on the force?
Well, they can when they have
a unique skill set like he has.
You, child.
Take my advice.
You shouldn't waste your
youth on the Buddy Police.
But why?
A child cannot
fulfill the duties
of a legitimate officer.
You are, after all,
still a trainee.
Now listen here, pal.
Relax, Drum.
It's come to my attention that
our enemy is intent on acquiring
the Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu.
And yet for reasons
that escape me,
you're entrusting the
card to this neophyte.
I'm curious why it's
not under secure watch
at the Buddy Card Office.
Wait just a moment.
I'm with young Gao here because
I requested to be with him.
I happen to love a girl
in uniform, don't you know?
(giggling)
If the enemy attacks again,
and chances of this
are extremely high,
he will no doubt
try and take more
than just your memories
this time around,
and this boy will find
himself in much danger.
No worries, man.
The kid's got yours truly
watching his back.
And I won't be defeated
so easily next time.
As you can see,
I'm in good hands.
That's why Commander I agreed
to make a special exception
and let me watch over Tenbu.
What's your name?
I'm the Mighty Sun Fighter.
Name's Gao Mikado,
and I have never
been a quitter, sir.
So, you claim the name
of the sun for yourself.
Then it is clear we
will never get along.
It's a known fact
I hate the sun.
‐Huh?
Now to the real reason
for my journey, Commander I.
I'm aware you committed
a serious crime the other day.
What are you talking about?
♪
(humming)
These prices are outrageous.
Huh?
That's strange, maybe someone
forgot to take their change,
or the machine's
giving me a break
for being such
a loyal customer.
Ha‐ha, it's my lucky day!
(laughing)
♪
I observed that
you took that money
and slipped it into
your greedy pocket!
I gave that change
to accounting!
I object to your
implication, Count Dawn.
What's the deal with them?
Commander I and Count Dawn
get along like cats and dogs.
Don't worry, I have much more.
I'll teach you to
invade people's privacy.
♪
(screaming)
(gasping)
Shame on you, Commander!
Count Dawn is much more
of a night person.
I can't be sure, but I feel
as though we've met before.
No; with the state of your
memory, you're surely wrong.
Yes, I apologize,
that must be it.
Huh.
♪
Eternal forces speak to me.
You have been chosen next!
Awaken, power of darkness,
power of evil, power
of the Hundred Demons!
(howling)
(shrieking)
We are the great Twin‐Headed
Hellhound, Orthrus, woof.
What's wrong with you?
It's supposed to be
my turn to say it.
Bow‐wow!
That hurts!
Why you!
(arguing)
Better not mess up
this time, Shido.
Understand?
Yes, loud and clear, sir.
I am known as Death Shido.
I'm the greatest Buddyfighter
in the history of the world.
And when I win,
I'm taking that
Fifth Omni Dragon Lord,
Tenbu card from your deck.
I've definitely heard
that voice somewhere before.
(door opening)
What are you doing in here?
This isn't a hangout.
There's a junior high class
using the lecture hall next.
(gasping)
Hmm.
Our apologies,
President Shido,
but you know, there's a big
resemblance between you
and that Death Shido guy
Gao fought the other day.
(screaming)
Something wrong?
Say something, Shido.
Something, anything!
Of course that wasn't
me, don't be crazy!
There's no way I'd
let Gallows possess me
and then call
myself Death Shido.
(moaning)
It seems President Shido is
tired from all his hard work.
Excuse us.
♪
‐Hmm.
‐I wonder.
What's up with you guys?
President Shido is Death Shido?!
You mean, you didn't recognize
that whiny voice
of his just now?
And both of their fighting
styles were the same, bro.
‐Hmm.
‐I never noticed.
There was a lot going on.
I did.
Then why didn't
you say something?
Now we know, I'll
have to look into it.
Yeah, I'd like to help as well.
Count me in on that, too, yo.
No, I can't guarantee
you guys'll be safe, man.
I don't need no babysitter.
This is a job for
the Buddy Police.
Come on, homes!
You are still just a trainee.
Gao's right, even
though he's a trainee,
he's still
a Buddy Police officer.
So I think we'll have to
defer to him on this one.
Okay, just be super careful, yo.
Always.
Owie!
What did you do that for?
I'm gonna have
a sore neck for a week.
But do you think
they bought my story?
Da.
Looks like
somebody's having fun.
‐Ahh!
‐Let me out!
Cut it out, just stay put!
Grab another
pudding or something.
If you come out, I won't
be able to tail 'em.
We're being followed.
(screaming)
Quit squirming, stay!
Do you know what this means?
If the Buddy Police
are following us,
they think I'm Death Shido.
Wait, I think I have an idea!
Why can't you just listen?
Look, it's a monster!
(roaring)
(people screaming)
This is Gao.
There's an illegal
monster at Aibo Academy.
Could be one of
the Hundred Demons.
What should we do?
Go after him,
and pursue with caution.
Hmm.
'Kay, Drum, time for
Buddy Police Emergency Launch!
Told ya to let me out.
Decker Road, open!
♪
Decker Drum's on patrol.
Buddy Skill on.
Let's show this guy
some Earth justice!
Illegal monster going down.
Follow me!
We dodged a bullet
thanks to my quick thinking.
How do you figure?
Right, I guess my genius plan
is a little over your head.
You see, with their
attention focused on Orthrus,
they'll forget all about me.
What, not a good idea?
(Gallows chuckles)
What makes you so sure that
Orthrus will come back to us
after his rampage?
Or worse, what'll you
do if he gets captured?
Who knows what he'll say
to the Buddy Police.
(screaming)
Oh, no, if that happens,
Master Ikazuchi
is going to zap me with
his lightning bolts again!
Where could he have gotten to?
I don't know, but leave it
to one of Decker Drum's
seven secrets to track him down.
Decker Nose!
(sniffing)
♪
(siren wailing)
Illegal monster detected.
♪
(people screaming)
Some Earth tradition
I don't know about?
Miahama, Niitani,
you guys are friends!
What's gotten into you, man?
I don't really know.
All of a sudden I got
this uncontrollable urge
to fight Niitani.
Yeah, it's totally weird,
I just want to punch
him in his face.
Hey, come on,
stop it, you guys!
Bow‐wow!
Anyone who breathes
in this magical smoke
can't resist the urge to punch
someone they're friends with!
Bow‐wow!
Hold your breath!
Hang on a second.
Why are you doing all the
talking all of a sudden?
‐Woof!
‐Stop it, bow‐wow!
(groaning)
♪
Gao, I...
I...feel the same way.
All I can think about
is punching you, too.
Gao's gonna have his
hands full with Drum.
Don't you guys think we
ought to do something?
Now's the perfect time
to steal the Tenbu card.
(groaning)
Go ahead, kid.
Get a few in while I
can still hold it back.
I don't mind.
Nah, I'm good over here.
You should go first, scale face.
(groaning)
Children don't belong
in the Buddy Police.
♪
Was that really a vampire?
Yeah, I think it was, bro.
(groaning)
Pathetic.
Huh?
As you claim the
name of the sun,
I was expecting much more.
Yeah, he's right.
I am the Mighty Sun Fighter!
Those two are resilient.
No one withstands us.
(screaming)
‐Look out!
‐Do something!
(whistling)
(grumbling)
‐That hurts!
‐Make them stop!
‐He did it!
‐Yeah!
What's going on?
Where are we, bow‐wow?
You'll do as I say if you
know what's good for you.
Do you understand?
So, what are you doing
here at Aibo Academy?
I just happened to be
in the neighborhood.
Thanks a bunch, Count.
You saved our bacon.
If you didn't step
in when you did,
I might've hurt my buddy.
(gasping)
Not again.
(screaming)
(groaning)
Careful, it might not look
it, but that really stings!
We cannot risk
the Buddy Police
or anyone else discovering that
Death Shido is in fact Shido,
so I'll become Death Shido
and get Tenbu myself.
Darkness Barrier,
enshroud and confuse.
(dark laughter)
♪
‐Here we go.
‐Yup.
(screaming)
♪
Like we never left.
(whimpering)
Where are we?
It's Death Shido!
You must defeat Death Shido
if you wish to leave here.
He sound different to anybody?
You must fight her.
Fight "her"?
What am I saying?
I mean, fight him.
That's odd.
Once again, to leave here,
you must fight me.
I'd like to get my
hands on that Shido.
But President Shido's
standing right here, yo.
(laughing)
See, I told you I'm not
this crazy Death Shido guy!
Warp successful!
I'll even go to other worlds
to give my play‐by‐play.
Leave him to me and keep
back, young sun warrior.
No, wait.
I know I'm young and a trainee,
but I'm also a member
of the Buddy Police.
Aibo Academy's my school,
so let me protect it!
I can handle this guy.
See what the Mighty Sun
Fighter's capable of.
Hmm.
I will give you your chance.
Do as you wish.
'Kay, partner.
Let's go with Hero
World for this one.
Cool, I'd like
some more practice
with those awesome new powers.
Righteous, this is
gonna be super fly, yo.
I'm curious to see his
new skills in action.
All non‐fighters please move
to the side out of the way.
Thank you!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power!
Luminize!
Hundred Legend Beasts!
Emergency Launch,
on the tail of a cyclone.
Luminize!
Beaming Sunshine Guardians!
On your marks,
get set, Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
‐Time to raise the flag!
I'm with Hero World.
I am with Legend World.
Death Shido will be going first.
Death Shido's using
Legend World this time?
While here in the Skull Pit,
we're able to talk to
the fighters if we want.
And how would you
know that, bro?
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
With his first attack,
Death Shido uses
King of Forest, Zlatorog
to increase his gauge and
cause two damage points to Gao.
Now it's Gao's turn.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Let's see how he handles this.
Ready or not.
Behold, super burning speed
to round up all criminals!
Transform!
Explosive Takedown,
Rampage Sonic.
Amazingly, Gao has
transformed himself!
Transform is an ability
that's unique to Hero World.
You can actually equip
a monster like an item
and go into battle yourself.
This is awkward.
I can't move in this.
(grunting)
That's better, this'll
be more than enough.
I call Cyber Police,
Assault Leader to the left,
and now I Buddy Call
to the right
Buddy Police, Decker Drum.
Oh yeah!
(grunting)
Cyber Police, Assault.
I'm armed and dangerous.
Follow me.
I'm not sure, but I think
that's the Gao formation.
If it ain't broke,
don't fix it,
no matter what world
we're fighting for.
I cast Hyper Energy!
Off the chain.
His gauge just
increased by four.
I activate Decker
Drum's ability.
Take care of Zlatorog for me.
Love to.
Whenever the kid
here pays two gauge,
I can destroy one of
our opponent's monsters.
They've got some really cool
new abilities, haven't they?
Locking on to Zlatorog.
Break.
Assault Leader,
attack Death Shido!
Roger that!
(gunfire)
Back him up, Drum.
(grunting)
Crash!
Cyclone Bunker!
♪
Last but not least.
I cast the Holy Grail.
No!
End of move.
What a play!
Death Shido
neutralized Gao's attack
with an expertly‐timed
counter spell.
Your move.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Waweldrache to the left,
and I Buddy Call Twin‐Headed
Hellhound, Orthrus to the right.
Time to play.
We'll crush you!
Once again, we can use
the Takosuke Hyper Scope,
or Takoscope for short,
to check out all the details
on Death Shido's
extraordinary buddy.
Twin‐Headed Hellhound,
Orthrus is a Size 2 monster.
Attributes are
Wydar Sarkal and Olympus,
with a power of 5,000,
defense of 3,000,
and a critical of 2.
It also has an ability
that activates
when inflicting damage.
I equip Famous Sword, Hrunting.
I cast...
Decree of Dullahan.
That spell sounds harsh, yo.
It gives all monsters with
the Wydar Sarkal attribute
the double attack ability.
Waweldrache, I invite you
to do a link attack with me.
Let's go!
The link attack gives
Death Shido 8,000 power.
He'll blow past
Gao's 3,000 defense
like a bowling ball
through wet paper!
(grunting)
(groaning)
♪
And just like that,
Death Shido's dropped Gao
down to five life points.
Come on, Gao, it's time to
pick it up a little, huh?
Come, Orthrus, attack the
fighter with all you've got.
(growling)
This old dog does
know a few new tricks.
We can destroy a monster
or an item, bow‐wow!
I cast Justice Will Prevail!
I think now I understand
why Gao transformed himself
into Rampage Sonic,
because he can use
a counter spell
to increase his
power and defense
while also gaining
a counter attack.
(grunting)
Bad dog!
Rampage Kick!
That hurts, arf!
Suck it up, you big baby.
Fine, let's just see
how you like it.
Okay, Waweldrache,
go and attack
the Assault Leader.
End of move.
Your move.
I draw.
And charge and draw.
I activate
Decker Drum's ability.
Destroy Waweldrache.
Right.
Locking on to Waweldrache.
Break!
All right, Decker Drum.
Move on to attack Death Shido.
I cast the Holy Grail.
Death Shido has just
blocked another attack!
He has no cards
left in his hand!
Take him out!
'Kay.
Rampage Kick!
Whoa!
But I have a feeling there's
more to Gao's move this time.
Final Phase!
There it is!
But I have no idea how
he's made this possible.
When he's transformed
into Rampage Sonic
and his opponent has
three life or less,
he can pay two gauge
and activate his Impact.
(grumbling)
This doesn't look good.
♪
Watch and learn.
Now I cast...
Impact, Rampage Blaster!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Oh, yeah, Hero World
does it again.
'Kay, lunch is on you
after that, kid.
Huh?
That dog was one of
the Hundred Demons, too.
Uh, so I guess I'll be
getting back to work now.
Hang on!
Accept my apology.
To be honest,
I kinda suspected
that you might
actually be Death Shido,
but I'm really glad to
find out I was wrong.
You should be sorry.
Imagine me parading
around as that weirdo.
Hmmm.
♪
You incompetent fools!
(whimpering)
I didn't lose this time!
It's not my fault!
Then whose fault is
it that I had to put
that costume on
in place of you?
I'll give you one more chance
to bring Lord Tenbu to me
or else!
♪
So, the sun doesn't affect
you when it's setting, huh?
I think that I should
make an apology as well.
Huh?
I said that a child
couldn't fulfill the duties
of a legitimate officer;
it seems I was wrong.
Please forgive me, Gao Mikado.
Or should I say,
the Mighty Sun Fighter.
Hmm!
You bet!
Hmm?
Oh, come on!
(screaming)
(gasping)
I wonder if sunscreen
would help him.
We should ask.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna tell
you all about the card
Buddy Police, Decker Drum.
All right.
It's the Hero World
version of Drum's card,
and it always gets the
monster he's fighting.
He has an ability that
destroys any monster
if you pay two gauge,
and as long as you have enough,
you can use this cool
ability every turn.
That's awesome.
Even when facing
a powerful monster,
you've nothing to fear with
Buddy Police, Decker Drum
on your side.
Decker Nose is detecting
some chocolate pudding.
My favorite.
♪
Next time, Gao's sent
to a Buddyfight event
to do some teaching,
and Death Shido tracks him down.
Meanwhile, Paruko steals Tenbu
after being possessed by
Kalavinka, Uguisukomachi.
Next episode:
Trouble at Buddy Fest!
Join us for a Buddyfight!