(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the Eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them and
there's only one way we can!
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
♪
Fire Lord Bursting Fist!
Uh‐oh.
(screams)
Penetrate!
(screaming)
Say goodnight, 100 Demon!
‐Double attack!
‐No chance!
I cast Green
Dragon Shield.
Buzz Saw blocks the attack
and regains one life point.
(snickering)
How do you like me now?
No way!
♪
It can't be!
It's not possible.
It can and it is.
Triple attack!
Who is this guy?
Now for the
final blow, ki!
He did it!
♪
You're kidding right?
You got to be,
you wouldn't do this.
It's some
kind of prank.
Are you serious?
You got to stop beating
yourself up over this.
Think about
what you're saying.
No, I've made up my mind.
I'm done.
I'm quitting
Buddyfight for good.
But what gives, yo?
At least give us
an explanation.
I'm just not
good enough.
Huh?
I can't use Dragon
decks anymore.
So what?
You could still
use Hero World decks.
I lost to Shigamine.
It's time for Final Phase.
I'm scared.
I cast!
(moaning)
I keep telling you,
you didn't lose that fight.
♪
I'm doing what you said.
Don't you remember?
Huh?
You have to
listen to me.
There are no heroes
that are going to come
to your aid when
you're in trouble.
It's time you realize
that you have to deal
with your problems
by yourself.
You're right, which is why
I'm gonna quit Buddyfighting.
I need to fix my
problems on my own.
You missed my point.
Quitting doesn't
fix anything at all.
Listen to him!
Besides, aren't you
forgetting something, kid?
What'll happen
to me if you quit?
About that.
I think you should
join Tasuku's deck.
Huh?
I bet with him you'll be able
to become a true Omni Lord.
Is that what
this is all about?
You're doing it for me?
Good luck, pal.
♪
Take good care of him.
He can be a little stubborn,
but he's as good as they come.
♪
(sighs)
I'd like to thank you for giving
me the opportunity, Count.
But in my condition, I'm
no good to the Buddy Police.
Sorry, I couldn't
have done more.
Just please find Noboru.
Yes, of course.
♪
You can't!
Sorry, pal, and
thanks for everything.
Don't cause Tasuku
any trouble now.
No wait, Gao!
Please don't leave!
♪
It just seems weird
without Drum being with us.
Yes, it's definitely
much quieter than usual.
♪
Oh, yeah!
It's amazing.
Oh, good, then I'll
have a fresh batch ready
by the time you get
home from school today.
Sweet!
So where is he then, huh?
Is he gonna be
back home tomorrow?
♪
Huh?
Hana.
You haven't finished
your vegetables.
If you must know,
I was saving them for Drum.
He usually gets hungry
an hour after we eat.
Thanks for dinner, Dad.
♪
(door opens, closes)
Hmm.
♪
So, there's still
no word from Gao.
‐I'm afraid not.
‐It's been over a week now.
Given that we don't
know Jack's whereabouts,
it may be time to consider
making Drum your official buddy.
Don't you miss him at all?
Huh?
Is he ever gonna come
and live with us again?
Gao Mikado,
is that you?
(chuckling)
Hey, it's that
little Tatsudo kid
that you taught how to
Buddyfight, big brother.
(roars)
Hey, how's it
going, Tatsudo?
Well, I'd like to get
into the Buddyfight class.
Ever since your lesson, this
little dude's been way obsessed.
Yeah, he's been
begging Ikarino,
like, practically every day
to transfer into
the Buddyfight program.
What can I say?
You changed my
life that day, Gao.
Glad I could help.
See you later.
Wait, before you go!
Would you do me the honor
of looking at my deck?
I know your schedule
must be very busy,
but I'd appreciate
your advice.
Yeah, it'll only
take you a sec.
Since you joined
the Buddy Police,
we don't see
you much at school.
It'd really
mean a lot to him.
♪
Yeah, sure.
I'll take a look,
let's see what you got.
Crimson Battler Deck.
Yes.
It's a deck
which allows me
to use the Gao Formation
that you taught me.
I also have the
same buddy as you.
See, Crimson Battler
Drum Bunker Dragon.
Huh.
Well, with a
deck like that,
you're gonna want to forget
about a Sail Sword, Dragorapter,
and use a Fist Item
like this instead.
This here's Crimson
Fist Dragoblaze.
It has 3,000 power and only
costs one gauge to equip.
Now, you're probably thinking
it doesn't sound very strong,
but don't be fooled cause
it has a critical of three.
Wow, that's
quite extraordinary.
I guess you
could say that.
What else, tell me
what other cards to use.
Okay, make sure to put enough
Dragon shields in your deck.
Using the
Gao Formation a lot,
means leaving your center
position wide open.
Always remember, the best
defense is a good offense.
You're a genius.
I'm just repeating
what Baku's told me.
Don't be modest.
Because of your
help here today,
I like Buddyfight even more.
Because you like 'em
so much, little brother,
you make me like
drawing comics even more.
♪
What did you‐‐
what did you say?
Uh, you make me like
Buddyfight even more?
Think hard, Tatsudo!
Tell me why you like to
play Buddyfight so much.
Well, I‐‐
That's easy.
Because it's the most fun
and exciting game there is.
♪
Yeah, it is.
You're so right!
♪
(screams)
How long will
he be like this?
It's been days now!
Before he took off with
Noboru, the 100 Demons guy,
Gratos said he'd be
out for quite a while.
♪
Huh?
Where do you think
you're going?
Not that it's any
of your business,
but I'm going to
give him my report.
♪
‐I'm hungry.
‐Huh?
♪
Give me food!
I need to eat.
(shuddering, screams)
(knocking)
Huh?
Hey, what are
you doing here?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I was just
in the neighborhood
and I thought you might
be looking for someone
to have a game
of Buddyfight with.
Huh?
What's that?
Your new deck?
It's yours.
Your Crimson
Dragon Fist deck.
Don't you recognize it?
Come on.
What are you afraid of?
Just a second ago
when I walked in,
you were touching your Dragon
World cards, weren't you?
Hmm.
Hey, pal.
Why don't you use that
deck and fight with me?
Or should I say,
you must fight with me.
I don't think I can.
You once asked me
to help you train, right?
♪
What if I challenged you
to a fight to help train me?
♪
There's always the risk
of something going wrong
when you luminize after a
long time away from the game.
So, let's play without
luminizing for now.
Sounds good.
Hey, what's that
deck you're using?
It's your Explosive
Dragon Fang deck.
Baku let me borrow it.
So, both of us have
Drum as our buddy?
♪
Yeah, but we'll play
without a buddy this time.
Okay, good call.
‐Rock.
‐Paper.
‐Scissors!
I get the first move.
Good luck.
‐Time to raise the flag.
‐I fight for Dragon World.
Charge and draw.
I call Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the center
and attack you with it.
♪
That's the end of my move.
Nice one.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Crimson Battler Break
Shoulder Dragon to the right
and Crimson Battler Spin
Nail Dragon to the left.
Look, Gao's playing again.
I pay one gauge and equip
Crimson Fist Dragoblaze.
♪
It's the Gao Formation!
First, I'm gonna attack
Systemic Dagger with Spin Nail.
Then, I'll attack you
with Break Shoulder.
♪
And get ready, cause here
I come again with Dragoblaze.
♪
And that's end of move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the left,
and Boomerang
Dragon to the center.
Then I pay one gauge and call
Drum Bunker Dragon to the right.
I take a card from
the top of my deck
and put it in Drum's soul,
and pay one gauge
to evolve Drum
into Super Armordragon
Drum Breaker Dragon.
♪
Now Drum has two
cards in his soul.
I pay one life and equip
Dragonblade Drum Sword.
It's the next generation
Gao Formation.
I sure wouldn't want to be on
the receiving end of that, bro.
Okay.
Boomerang
Dragon attacks.
♪
After each battle, Boomerang
returns to my held cards.
Next, I attack you with
Thousand Rapier Dragon,
and I'll cause even more
damage with Drum Breaker.
I'm gonna cast a
Green Dragon Shield
spell to neutralize
your attack.
That's good.
The Green Dragon Shield card
lets him gain one life point.
No prob, I'll just attack
you with Drum Sword.
I cast Dragonic Formation.
I move Break Shoulder
to the center
so he can take Drum Sword's
attack instead of me,
then he heads
to the drop zone.
That's end of move.
You're doing good, Gao.
I'm just getting warmed up.
Now, I draw.
Charge and draw.
Do you remember our
first Buddyfight?
I will never forget it.
♪
That was the most fun
I'd ever had doing anything.
I had no idea
what I was missing.
Thanks to you
and that fight,
I discovered how cool and
thrilling Buddyfighting was.
My life was
changed forever.
It was the same for me.
♪
Final Phase!
And through Buddyfighting with
so many different players,
I learned lots
of new things
and found out there are tons
of ways to enjoy the game.
It's the best
game in the world.
Ha ha, cast!
Shooting Cross Knives!
Right‐hand!
I call the incredible
Dragon Lord,
Duel Sieger
"Tempest Enforcer".
Anyway, I attack
Drum Breaker
with Crimson Battler
Extreme Blow Dragon.
I activate
Soul Guard.
Then I attack Thousand
Rapier with Dragoblaze.
And that's end of move.
Tasuku's putting on a clinic.
By moving Drum Breaker
to the center,
he blocked the attack and
saved getting any damage.
He's executing
the next generation
Gao Formation
to a T, bro.
I move Drum Breaker
to the right
and call Boomerang Dragon
to the left position.
Here goes.
♪
Don't you still
enjoy Buddyfighting?
Well, then, I'll
just have to pay...
Well, to be honest,
I wasn't sure anymore.
You're under a lot
of stress right now.
I mean, we all
are with the search
for the eight Omni Lords to
save the world from Yamigedo.
With all the added pressure,
the game's definitely changed
from when we used
to just play for fun.
I cast...
‐I guess, but‐‐
‐But what?
A friend and I were just
talking about Buddyfight,
and he said, well, he reminded
me of the reason why I play.
What'd he say?
♪
Because it's the most fun and
exciting game that there is.
♪
End of move.
I bet anything Tasuku's
gonna move Drum Breaker
to the center
on his next move.
Unless I can find a
way to deal with him,
the card in his soul and 5,000
defense, I'll lose for sure.
I do have Extreme Blow
in my hand,
and he's got 7,000 power,
but he's only
a Size Two monster.
Draw.
Let's see what monsters I have
in my Crimson Dragon Fist deck
that are Size One and
have at least 5,000 power.
Charge and draw.
♪
Gotcha!
Spin Nail Dragon.
♪
I call Extreme Blow to the right
and Spin Nail to the left.
I move Drum Breaker
to the center.
I attack Drum Breaker
with Spin Nail.
I activate his Soul Guard.
Now there's no
cards in his soul.
Alright, I use Extreme Blow
to attack Drum Breaker.
I just hope he doesn't have any
Dragon Shields in his hand.
♪
Now I'll finish you
off with Dragoblaze.
Hmm.
‐Thanks for a great fight.
You did well, Gao.
Thanks, Tasuku.
If I were you, I'd go and
thank that friend of yours
who you were talking to.
The one who reminded you why you
love playing Buddyfight so much.
Yeah.
Welcome back,
big brother.
(phone ringing)
Hmm, yes?
Really, how long ago?
And where is he now?
Is it really Yamigedo?
We believe he's
headed your way.
Zanya and Tetsuya
are already on route.
I want to help.
♪
Okay, Gao.
Let's get that freak!
Hey, Drum!
But before we do.
Huh?
♪
Where did he go?
Delish!
Oh, it's like a
party in my mouth.
It's been so hard
living without these.
The Count doesn't allow
junk at HQ, you know.
Only healthy food.
Sure is more fun
with him around.
Yeah.
(crashing)
‐Huh?
He's here.
Yeah.
♪
(roars)
(cackling)
I'm starving and
you're on the menu.
You ready, pal?
This guy needs
some new material.
‐I'm ready if you are.
‐Are you sure?
You're still not a
true Omni Lord yet.
This from a guy
who quit Buddyfight?
I never asked for
this Omni Lord shift.
It's a big honor and all,
but the most important
thing to me has always been
and will always be
having you as my buddy.
Thanks, Drum.
That's why we need to fight
this blowhard one more time.
Who said anything
about Buddyfighting?
I just came here to
devour you, Omni Lord.
Look out!
Drum!
Stop it!
Nice knowing you, kid.
So long, but I promised to
protect you 'til the end.
What's going on?
What's with all these cards?
We serve the Fifth
Omni Dragon Lord.
The honorable
Armored Cavalry Dragons.
They call us the Fifth
Omni Cavalry Dragons.
Maybe this Omni Lord gig's got
some sweet perks after all.
Check it out.
Your appearance,
you look so different.
Huh?
♪
(all gasping)
Hey, what's this?
♪
So, what do you want us to call
you, Fifth Omni Dragon Lord?
Just a sec!
When exactly did
I become an Omni?
At the moment Tenbu gave
you the Omni Lord Emblem.
Your selfless act
told us you were ready.
Please, tell us
your name, my lord.
So, you mean, I'm a‐‐
You did it, you're
now a true Omni Lord.
I told you!
I knew you had it in you!
Gramps Tenbu would be
mighty proud of you, pal.
(growling)
We haven't met!
I'm the Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Drum!
Huh?
I didn't mean to
vaporize the guy.
Nah.
He just teleported
to safety is all.
No!
Just who do you think you
are interfering like that?
I'm terribly
sorry, Master.
(screaming)
(screams)
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna
tell you all about
the Underling of the
Fire Lord, Ricky card.
Okey‐dokey.
It's a new card for Ricky
who supports the Fire Lord
with Burning Determination.
When you have
a Size Three
Raging Spirits monster
in your field,
you can pay two gauge to
send Ricky from the drop zone
to your hand
to call him.
He's as loyal
as they come, ki.
He also gives 5,000 power
to a Raging Spirits card
and also the
Penetrate ability.
He's just too strong, ki.
(laughs)
♪
Next time, Gao is back
and better than ever.
Now that I'm officially
an Omni Lord,
we're gonna hit
Ikazuchi's lair
and take down Yamigedo
once and for all.
Next episode, "Luminize!
Super Dragon Fifth
Omni Formation!"
Join us in a Buddyfight!