Arrggh!
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us
to find them,
and there's only
one way we can.
Let's do it,
Buddyfight!
(rain pounding)
♪
(thunder booming)
(wood splintering)
♪
(thunder booming)
This is it.
Huh?
♪
(sighs)
Uh.
Argh!
Is this because
we ate that demon?
(roaring)
I think I'm going
to enjoy this.
I apologize
for my behavior.
I understand it was
selfish of me to leave.
I know that I
don't have the right
to ask you to
take me back,
but I want
nothing more
than to work
here again.
It's part
of who I am.
The Buddy Police
is in my blood.
Please, I beg you to
give me another chance.
I'll do anything.
I request the same.
Listen, Tasuku, no
one can refute you did
monumental before as the
Buddy Police boy wonder,
but you can not
just do as you please.
You understand?
I do.
Commander I,
perhaps we might‐‐
Now then, your disciplinary
action will be as follows:
You are henceforth
relieved of your duties
as the Buddy Police boy wonder,
and reassigned
as the leader
of the newly formed
Buddy Police youth division.
Huh?
Well, Tasuku, do you
accept our conditions
for your return?
I do, thank you.
I zoned out
there for a sec,
he's gonna be
our new boss, yo?
Yeah, but it is
a big demotion for him.
With Tasuku
as our leader,
we'll have the strength
of a hundred men!
Sorry I'm late,
Commander I.
What's that?
Yeah, what's the deal
with all the flowers?
It was gramps Tenbu's idea.
You young
people have lost
the sense of
chivalry from my day.
You mean
those are for me?
How lovely.
Gramps here insisted
we give one of these
to all the girls
who've helped him
since he
arrived on Earth.
Hope you're happy.
We gave up
our lunch break
to search all over town
to find them all.
♪
Oh good, I'm glad
everyone is here.
If we don't find
the Omni Lords,
the Earth will
be forever doomed.
You have our support,
just find them.
Lady Suzuha
has offered to help
in our search
for the Omni Lords.
The Amanosuzu Group has
pledged to reward anyone
that comes forward
with useful information.
It's unorthodox to
accept financial support
from the private sector.
But under
the circumstances,
we have
little choice.
We already know
the whereabouts
of a few Omni Lords.
Yes, I am in
fact one myself.
I'm called the Seventh
Omni Earth Lord Count Dawn.
Gramps is one, too.
The Great Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu.
He told us
last night.
I lost my memory.
Yeah, we know.
Also, there's First
Omni Beast Lord, Ziun.
Really,
that guy's one?
We think most
likely he is, yes.
Most likely?
We have
nothing conclusive.
But didn't you all
work side by side
when you defeated
Yamigedo before?
Time was
of the essence.
We had to be swift.
Rushing to Earth from
our separate worlds
to quell the beast
allowed for little else.
But if we
meet in person,
our Omni Lord emblems
will identify each other
and indicate so.
Omni Lord emblems?
A special orb the
Omni Lords possess.
But not something just
anyone is able to see.
If we can't tell who's
legit by eyeballin' 'em,
then how can we help
find the Omnis, yo?
Is there no other way?
Of course.
Omni Lords can be used in
card decks from any world.
And they have horns equal
to the number in their titles.
Huh?
One, two,
three, four, five.
I get it,
grandpa's five horns
makes him the Fifth
Omni Dragon Lord!
So that's
how it works.
How could you
not know that?
But Count, there aren't
any horns on your head.
But of
course there are.
See, look closely.
Hmm?
(gasps)
Identifying
the number of horns
with absolute certainty
will be difficult.
That leaves us with
only one option.
We're gonna have to meet
with all the suspects
face to face to see if
they fit the profile.
And we need to find them
before Ikazuchi does.
So, if he's hunting
down the Omni Lords,
who do you think will
be his first target?
If I had to guess,
I think
it'll be me.
Last night I saw the rage
in that young brat's eyes.
I could tell he plans to
make me his next victim.
You're up
next, Tenbu.
What's up
with that then?
He's sent tons of
Hundred Demons after you
and each time it's
been an epic fail.
Take it from me,
youngling,
when you've lived
as many eons as I have,
you can sense when
your time has come.
Thank you.
Tenbu, then
that flower is...
If I return, I'd ask
for your hand in marriage.
Then the answer would
be absolutely no!
You think it would
take more than Ikazuchi
to stop
that old timer.
We'll need to start
working on a plan
to find the
others right away.
I'm curious, why reveal
your true identity now?
Is it possible
that you know
the true
identity of that boy
who's manipulating Yamigedo?
I can't believe
that it's him.
‐Ah!
‐What's going on?
‐(beeping)
It's Yamigedo!
♪
(roars)
How'd he get
here undetected?
Where are our scouts?
♪
The boy
is with him.
Takihara, go!
Evacuate everyone from
the vicinity immediately.
Got it.
♪
Aw, look at this.
Tenbu has a
farewell party.
I think
I'm gonna cry.
Pretty big talk
for someone so small.
If you can defeat Gao
here in a Buddyfight,
then you may have
me as your prize.
Huh, I'll indulge
you, old man,
but you're just
delaying the inevitable.
We got to win this.
How horrible‐‐the
Buddy Card Office
is under a
vicious attack
from that nasty
monster, Yamigedo.
And could it be, yes,
Buddyfighter Ikazuchi
is with him.
♪
You see that,
master is there.
What is he planning?
This is bad.
If only I could use
the Future Force.
You're on
your own, Gao.
Don't worry,
it's all good.
I can handle this.
Warp successful.
I'm Paruko Nanana,
roving reporter
and world class
commentator.
So wherever
there's a Buddyfight,
I'll be there.
Huh, what's going on
at the Buddy Card Office?
If Gao doesn't
win his fight,
I will never
see you again.
Here.
What are
you up to?
What do you mean you
might not see me again?
Will you marry me
if we meet again?
What on Earth does that
have to do with anything?
Grandpa!
I'm coming.
Give it
everything you have.
Understood.
Burning like an inferno,
with limitless spirit.
Luminize!
Crimson Dragon Fist!
Hundred Demons lurking
in the darkness.
Destroy and rampage!
Devour the world!
Dark Luminize
Hundred Thunder Demons.
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm fighting
for Dragon World.
Parade of
Hundred Demons.
That's an
amazing flag.
It lets him fight with
any Hundred Demons card
no matter what world
they come from.
Gao will go first.
Charge and draw.
I call Break Shoulder
Dragon to the center.
In battle, there is
no need for words.
Attack Ikazuchi!
Aargh!
Right off the bat,
Gao hits Ikazuchi with
three damage points.
End of move.
Your move.
I draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Vouivre
to the left.
Peluda to the center.
And Zazamera
to the right.
I equip.
Veiled in the
darkness of terror,
await the mighty jaws
of the wicked beast
that hungers for misery.
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
And I set
Reinforce Formation
of Hundred Demons!
Not one
to waste time,
Ikazuchi's prepared
for an all out attack.
My minions, go
attack without mercy.
Rar, rar, rar!
Blazing Claw!
Ah!
Once Vouivre
opened the center,
Gao is punished
with a series
of relentless attacks.
Peluda, give rise
to Thunder Claw.
Aagggh!
Narukami's ability
is activated.
Destroying Peluda
boosts Narukami's
critical by one.
Aaaah!
I cast Green
Dragon Shield!
With a timely block,
Gao fends off
further damage.
Huh?
(smashing)
That guy's
scarfing down
our entire supply
of crystals, yo.
At this rate, he'll
eat the whole building.
Come on, we've
got to do something.
Aah!
It's like some
force field.
Ikazuchi, control
your buddy down there.
We're in the middle of
a Buddyfight, you know.
Why would you
do such a thing?
How could you revive
a monster like this?
What's it to you?
You make it sound
like it's a bad thing.
You think you
can control me
like everyone
else, huh?
Reinforce Formation of
Hundred Demons activates.
Peluda has
been revived.
All my life I
was told what to do
and how to be.
I couldn't do
anything I wanted.
Couldn't even
eat what I wanted.
I was like
a caged animal
trapped inside that dark,
depressing mountain!
But one day
I was released
and finally got
a taste of freedom.
And I'll
never give it up.
I'll do what
I want, when I want,
and eat
whatever I want.
I'll eat until
there's nothing left
and no one
can stop me!
For I am the
great Ikazuchi!
(growling)
♪
(helicopter blades whirring)
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I'm gonna
pay one gauge
and equip Dragoblaze.
Let's light it up, grandpa.
I call Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu
to the right.
Now, nothing like going
out with a dragonic bang.
Taste my Thunder Mine!
Haaa!
As Tenbu is a
size three monster,
Vouivre's
Thunder Mine ability
was activated the
second he was called.
No biggie, I was
prepared for that.
Now, gramps!
Howling Fire!
Rah!
Aah, yah, ah!
It's your turn!
Tenbu's ability
drained three life points
from Ikazuchi
in one blow!
Sounds like you've had
a pretty tough life.
So just who
are you, anyway?
I told you my
name already.
All you need to know
is that I have the power
to end this world.
The great Ikazuchi.
Is it possible that
he could be a member
of the Fuchigami Clan?
The what clan, I've
never heard of them.
In order to
watch over Yamigedo
after we
sealed him away,
we entrusted a
clan of humans,
the inhabitants
of the mountain
where he was imprisoned.
They were to guard
and protect our secret.
They called
themselves Fuchigami.
Looking back, they
must have viewed us
as some sort of gods
or even demons.
This confusion
might have launched
some strict traditions
among them that may,
over time,
have been passed down
and caused their
descendents much suffering.
Then this Ikazuchi is
one of the Fuchigami Clan?
My buddy and
I are the same.
How so?
He was oppressed
and kept down like me,
even though we were
capable of so much more.
We were ordered
around and restricted
by stupid rules!
Like we could
hardly breathe!
That's why I
undid the seal.
♪
Then an amazing
thing happened.
The people who'd
been ordering me around
turned to stone.
♪
Uh.
(evil laughing)
♪
For the first time,
I had something
I never had before.
♪
The taste of freedom.
So what happened
to the people
that turned to stone?
I cast Hundred Demon
Sorcery, Yamitagae.
Who knows,
I can care less
what happened to them.
But they were your
family, weren't they?
Some family.
Uh, aargh.
Someone like you'd
never understand.
My so‐called family
was the enemy.
Don't you get it?
They manipulated me and
kept me down and oppressed.
I don't owe
them anything!
Uh.
Aaahhh!
Just because I was
born into my clan
I had to undergo brutal
training and hardships.
You couldn't cut it.
Growing up with everything
being handed to you.
I couldn't even
make simple choices
like what I
wanted to eat.
What right do
you think you have
to judge me?
When you put
it like that,
it is indeed a terrible
burden you have shouldered.
We couldn't
possibly imagine
what you went through.
And yet still, it
doesn't for one second
excuse the fact that you
released that monster
to wreak havoc
on this world.
But it's understandable.
No matter how much you
try to play the villain,
you're just
a foolish child.
Hang on a second
there, gramps.
You dare insult me!
Why, you, you're nothing
but a feeble old man.
I'll take down this chump
and devour you in one bite!
I call Rampage,
Chizomegumo
to the left position.
And use Hundred Demons'
Tome of Judgment,
which lets me
draw three cards.
And I call Demonic
Descend Ninja, Zeon
to the right.
Now I activate
Zeon's ability.
As you wish, master.
Demonic Descend
Ninja Arts,
return from
the underworld.
He revived him!
When Zeon's called,
he can revive a size
one or smaller monster
with the Thunder
Mine ability
from the drop zone.
It's incredible‐‐in a
dramatic change of events,
Ikazuchi's fielded a
full team of monsters,
after losing them
all just moments ago.
Ever danced
with a spider?
‐Raaaaa!
‐I cast Dragonic Formation!
Come on!
Tenbu moved from
the right to the center
to block
Peluda's attack.
You're nothing but
a walking corpse!
Haa!
Aw!
What a play!
Ikazuchi did a
link attack with Zeon.
Grandpa!
Oh, no!
My fate lies in
your hands now.
With the Reinforced
Formation of Hundred Demons,
Peluda has
revived once again!
That Ikazuchi never
runs out of monsters.
Well, old fool, have you
finally learned your lesson?
Your move.
Let's get him.
We owe it to gramps.
This guy's
ticking me off.
I call Burn Guts
striking to the left!
Gao's zapped with
another Thunder Mine,
this time from Peluda
in the center.
I need you, pal.
I buddy call
to the right!
Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon!
Time to let my fists
do the talking.
(shouts)
Okay, partner,
go and attack Peluda!
Consider this
payback for gramps!
I cast Hundred Demons
Sorcery, Yamitagae.
Aahh!
Sorry, kid.
Your turn,
Burn Guts,
open up that center!
Super Guts Combo Punch!
The center
position is open!
Crimson Fist,
Dragoblaze!
Aargh!
End of move.
Ikazuchi is down
to one life point
And Gao still
has five left.
So it goes
without saying,
that unless we
witness a miracle,
it's clear who
the winner will be.
Question is, does
Ikazuchi have it in him
to turn the tables?
♪
Time for dessert.
I buddy call
to the right,
the most
powerful demon beast
that is starving
for destruction.
Devour the Hundred Demons
and show yourself!
Aaaah!
Great Fiend, Yamigedo!
Whoop, there it is,
Ikazuchi's finally
called his buddy.
I'll try to
use my Takoscope
to check his
deets again.
Great Fiend, Yamigedo
Hundred Demons attributes.
Size three,
7,000 power‐‐what the?
I guess I should have bought
the extended warranty.
Ah, ah!
♪
It's like
fighting a mountain.
He must have Thunder
Mine ability, too.
But as long as I
don't call a monster,
then there's no way
I can get hit.
I call Vouivre
to the left.
Lunch is served.
Yah!
Burn Guts,
move to the center!
No one's getting
through me, boss.
Gao survives
Vouivre's attack,
but he's not out
of the woods yet.
Watch out!
Yamigedo, go and eat
to your heart's content!
(massive roar)
You've got to
do something, Gao!
‐Aah!
‐Gao!
Ikazuchi's monster Narukami
has a critical of two.
So if Gao can protect
his remaining three life,
then he'll win.
You're pretty
tough, kid.
But uh, my Yamigedo
has double attack!
I cast Blue
Dragon Shield!
♪
It worked,
I blocked the attack!
Activate Yamigedo's
Thunder Mine.
Aaah!
How'd he do that?
Yeah, Gao didn't even
call a monster, yo.
Okay, I think I understand
what just happened.
Yamigedo's Thunder
Mine ability
is a little different
from other monsters
in that
it's activated
when an attack
is neutralized.
You're kidding me.
That means...
You should
never assume.
Your tactical error
was in thinking
that it only activates
when you call a monster.
Uh!
Thunder Claw,
Narukami!
Aaah!
Game over.
Winner, Ikazuchi.
Gao!
I don't believe it.
Gao lost.
But he never loses.
Uh.
I lost.
I, too,
never anticipated
his Thunder Mine
to hit you like that.
I failed you,
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize
for destiny.
At last, Yamigedo,
you can now devour Tenbu!
Aagh!
If you wish to
devour me, then do so.
But no matter
what advantage
you think you have,
I am the mighty Tenbu.
I will never surrender
without a fight.
Grandpa!
♪
(growls)
(roars)
♪
Ah, no, grandpa!
If I have any regrets,
it's that I have
left no successor.
But I still have
time to rectify that!
Huh?
What the heck is this?
That is the Omni
Lord emblem.
Young Armordragon,
you are now the next
Fifth Omni Dragon Lord.
But gramps!
(roaring)
♪
(whimpering)
Uh, no, grandpa.
Tenbu!
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today we're
gonna learn all about
the Great Fiend,
Yamigedo card.
‐Wicked!
‐When called,
you can put as many
Hundred Demons cards
from the field into
his soul as you like.
This card has been revived
after countless years.
Oh, and his Thunder Mine
ability is activated
when one of your
attacks is nullified
by your opponent.
How can you
compete with that?
The destructive power
of his double attack
and his Thunder Mine
make this the star of the
Parade of Hundred Demons.
Yamigedo‐‐more like
yami get out of here.
♪
Next time, Gao and I
are given special leave
as we deal with
the loss of gramps,
Zanya looks for
the Omni Lords,
and a new buddy from
Katana World appears.
Next episode,
"Nanomachine Ninja Showdown!
Byakuya versus Tsukikage!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!