Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the Hundred Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on!
(whooshing)
Ah, it's not my
fault, I tell you!
Please, give me
another chance!
Maybe I should eat all
of you as well, huh?
No, please, I don't
think I taste very good!
(crying)
I'm so hungry,
I can't stand it.
‐Hungry!
‐Huh?
Looks like I'm not
the only one here
who's dying for a meal.
This guy is up next.
Awaken, power of darkness,
power of evil, power
of the Hundred Demons!
I'm Rage Thirst Emperor,
Grand Wilderness.
Feed me, I thirst for more.
Ah.
What do you want?
Well, you look
good enough to eat.
I'm not on the menu!
Master, do something!
Hungry.
Enough.
(crying)
Use this monster, and bring
me Tenbu for sure this time.
Either way, I'll be dining
on one of you tonight.
Where's A‐Dog's magic
when I need it, yo?
Hmm.
(grunting)
Am I like a ninja or what?
I'd say, "Or what."
You do realize you snuck
into the wrong class again.
Did not, I looked.
Gao's not in this class.
Commander I called him away
right after homeroom.
He's off chasing
illegal monsters again.
Huh?
Hm?
Down there!
Get him, Drum!
Decker handcuffs!
(shouting)
(grunting)
How about when we're
done here, lunch break?
Oh, yeah.
But not the usual.
How about meatball subs?
Mmm.
♪
There's no mark.
It's not one of
the Hundred Demons.
Really, just a plain,
old illegal monster, huh?
This is Gao,
mission accomplished.
‐I'll head back.
‐No, wait.
We just had a sighting of
another illegal monster
near your location.
Could you go over
and check it out?
Huh, you got it.
(groaning)
So much for our lunch break.
This is no time
to be whining.
Takihara's working
way more than we are.
Stella's putting in overtime
and hasn't been home in days.
And even Count Dawn's
burning himself up
out there to get
the job done.
We can't slough off
while everyone else works.
(siren wailing)
Hey, wait, you two.
You forgot about me!
(roaring and yawning)
Today, we'll continue
with counter spells,
specifically, their
unique timing during a game
and their varied effects.
I wonder what Gao's
doing right now.
Now, if you come down to
receive your cards for‐‐uh?
I'm sorry.
I got back here as soon as
I could, Mr. Neginoyama.
Hm, just take your
seat as always.
Yes, sir.
(grunting)
Keeping you pretty busy, huh?
Glad you could join us, bro.
I just can't register it, yo.
So many illegal
monsters out there.
Well, believe it.
I'm just glad I made it
to Buddyfight class.
I really hate
missing this one, man.
(snoring)
Goodnight.
I think it best just
to let him sleep.
‐Huh?
The poor boy needs his rest.
Now, everybody come down
and get your cards
so I can begin
today's lecture.
‐Okay.
(snoring)
I'm sorry, Commander I!
It won't happen again, sir!
You're having work
nightmares, yo.
We thought you
could use a siesta.
But don't worry.
Mr. Neginoyama left
you your homework.
Thanks, man.
I don't know when I'll
find time to do it.
(stomach grumbling)
(groaning)
Sounds like your stomach's
screaming for eats.
I got a banana if you want.
I got so busy, I didn't
get lunch today.
I totally feel your pain, yo.
Hey, I know.
Why don't you come
hang at my place?
My grandma will
make us a real feast.
Sounds fly.
Your grandma's food
is off the chain.
Count me way in.
I can taste it now.
Explain it to me again, aight?
You're saying 'cause
you're a trainee
they won't let
you take no break?
Not exactly.
But with the Hundred
Demons on Earth,
the Buddy Police
are crazy busy.
The truth is, I can't
ask them to go easy
just 'cause I'm a trainee.
(cell phone ringing)
Gao, it's Stella.
Come to HQ ASAP.
We've got trouble.
On my way.
Sorry to cancel on ya,
but they've just
called me back to work.
Eh.
It can't be helped.
Gotta take care of business.
Wake up, Drum.
We've gotta work.
(yawning)
Okay, Father.
‐I'm coming.
‐Oh, no!
The big oaf's
sleepwalking again!
Peace out, and watch
your back, aight?
♪
Grandma's cooking
would've been for real.
Hey, A‐Dog,
how could I become
a Buddy Police
Officer like Gao?
Hm?
Don't trip, I'm just
thinking it'd be nice
to help out, ya dig?
Gao's bugging out
from all that work.
I'd like to ease his pain.
I hear what you're saying
loud and clear, Tets,
but you don't
want to do that.
I mean, you're not exactly
Buddy Police material.
No, I guess not.
If you really want to
help your friend out,
there must be another
way that you can do it.
Nothing springs to mind, yo.
Hm, I got it!
Let's head over and
talk to Gao's grandma!
Yeah, we can think about it
over her delicious grub.
You want me to teach
you how to cook?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐Mm‐hmm!
All of your best recipes.
What gives?
We'd be happy to make
something for you.
It's not for me.
‐It's for Gao.
‐Huh?
He and Drum are drained
from catching all
those illegal monsters,
and I thought it'd be
cool to make 'em a feast
of all their faves to
give 'em a major boost.
‐Aw.
What a sweet boy.
Let's surprise them, I'll help!
Cool, thanks a
mil, you guys.
♪
It looks super awesome, yo.
(sighs)
I'm sure when Gao
and Drum get home,
they'll be jazzed
about what you've done.
Yeah.
I hope so.
But they might not get back
for a really long time.
(sighs)
You've earned a few
Z's, little chef.
(grunting)
(meowing)
I want more.
I'll take more.
I need food!
(birds chirping)
Ugh, can't believe
it's morning already.
And as soon as we're
done with breakfast,
it's straight
back to school.
I could sleep for a week.
(groaning)
Huh?
Tetsuya?
I think I might
be hallucinating.
(groaning)
Gao, I've been
waiting for hours.
I made this for you.
‐Hm, made what?
We're not in the
mood for jokes.
Huh?
Ah!
It's all gone!
Tell me this isn't happening!
What are you
whining about now?
Someone took my
sushi, boneface!
What else would I
be talking about?
And everything's
missing from my fridge!
It doesn't take a major
braniac to figure out
that either you or
Sofia must have taken it!
You're the only
ones who even know
I'm living down here!
I would never
do such a thing.
Mm?
Then that means...
Uh, ah, ah!
Look at this.
Ah!
What's the big idea?
‐Hm?
‐This is who ate your lunch.
Eat more.
So hungry.
I need to eat!
Hm, that's Grand Wilderness,
the new Hundred Demons card
Master Ikazuchi gave me.
More, I need more!
I guess he was so s‐starving
that he came out of
the card on his own.
(grunts)
He could ruin everything.
We must find him right away!
Strange reports of
food disappearing
from local restaurants
and convenience stores
are sweeping across the city.
With me now is the
manager of Munchy Time,
recent victim of
this bizarre trend.
Grand Wilderness has to
be behind all of this.
He must still be
somewhere nearby.
Maybe this will draw him out.
Huh, where did you get that?
It's my secret stash
of canned sushi.
Oh, I missed breakfast.
It smells so good.
(screaming)
Still hungry.
Give that food to me!
Ah!
Ah, this just in.
It appears that
an illegal monster
has been stealing
all the food.
Yeah, he must have
lifted the wicked spread
I made for you, yo.
(cell phone ringing)
Gao, we have an emergency.
You mean that illegal
monster on the news?
Yes, you must
capture it right away.
If he's not contained soon,
he'll eat all the
food in Cho‐Tokyo.
I'm on it.
You can count on
me, Commander I.
(stomach grumbling)
Oh.
Oh, man, I'll just have
to ignore the hunger
and get on with it!
Drum, let's go.
Decker Road, open!
♪
Decker Drum's on patrol.
Let's show this guy
some Earth justice!
Illegal monster...
What's going on?
I don't think I can move
unless I eat something.
Are you kidding me?
Huh?
Good morning, humans.
It's time for hip‐hop class
with Demon Lord, Asmodai.
My bet is every
professional dancer knows
it's hard to bust a move
when you haven't had
anything to eat in awhile.
Gao and Drum need help.
If I help you out, you must
promise that Tets here
stays out of trouble, agreed?
Uh, yeah, no problem.
(groaning)
This is so embarrassing.
It's not flashy, but
it does the job, yo.
Maybe I should rethink
the flying banana.
Hm, what's that?
You say something, A‐Dog?
The deal was that
I'm only taking you
to the illegal monster and
Tets doesn't get involved.
Yeah, we get it.
Hmph!
Ah!
I want to eat!
‐An illegal monster!
‐I'm starving.
I need food!
‐There it is!
‐Hang on.
(grunting)
This is terrible.
Master will zap me again
if he's captured by
the Buddy Police.
I'll have to use
Black Skull's power
to activate a
Darkness Barrier.
Enshroud and confuse!
♪
(roaring)
Huh?
♪
Warp successful.
Wherever there's
a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana
will be calling it.
Get ready for another
exciting live broadcast
from inside the
Darkness Barrier.
It looks like
they're about to start.
‐Oh, no!
‐Hmm?
What gives, you guys?
Something cramping
your style, yo?
(whirring)
They are exhausted beyond
their limit, body and soul.
What'll we do?
Well, they can't fight.
They're sleep deprived and
hungry from all that work.
It's amazing they've
even lasted this long.
I'm afraid a Buddyfight now
is out of the question.
What a dramatic
turn of events!
It seems Gao will
be unable to fight!
(laughing)
That means I win by default.
I'll take that
Tenbu card now.
Not so fast, yo!
I'm gonna fight in his place.
You are?
No, you're not
the Buddy Police.
Don't get involved.
It's not your fight.
If I'm the future
king of Magic World,
I need to represent.
I've never been someone who
leaves his friends hanging
when they need him, and
no king would do that, yo.
I hate to admit it...
...but you do
make a good point.
That food‐stealing demon
doesn't stand a
chance against us.
Magic World to the rescue.
I don't believe
what I'm hearing!
In a surprising move,
Tetsuya Kurodake will be
fighting in Gao's place!
The dancing fool will
be a piece of cake.
No, he can't,
it's too dangerous.
We don't have
any other choice.
(grunting)
A millennial kingdom, yo,
where you can play for ages.
Luminize Devil's Millennium.
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power.
Luminize Hundred
Ancient Warriors!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm with Magic World.
I fight for Ancient World.
Death Shido has first move.
I call Blade Dragon Emperor,
Vorpal Spartar to the center!
Go attack the player!
♪
The blade of an emperor!
(shouting)
Ah!
End of move.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
I call Street Racer,
Eligos to the left!
I call Demon Realm
Warrior, Zepar to the right!
And I call Demon Realm Death
Metal, Valefar to the center!
♪
Now go attack 'em, yo.
Tetsuya destroys
the opponent's monster
and causes four damage‐‐
You can do it, Tetsuya!
Come on, Asmodai!
Not bad, but even
those bananas know
you're no match for me.
Demonic Fairy Dragon,
Sorciere to the center.
I call Island Dragon
of the Origin,
Little Land Mu to the left!
And I buddy call to the right
Rage Thirst Emperor,
Grand Wilderness.
I'm getting angry.
So hungry!
I wonder what the 4‐1‐1 is
on Death Shido's
buddy monster today.
Let's check it out
with my handy Takoscope.
Locking onto Rage Thirst
Emperor, Grand Wilderness.
Dragon Lord
attribute, size two.
Power is 5,000.
Defense, also 5,000.
A critical of two.
He has one ability,
but no Lifelink.
I thirst for more.
Give me something to eat!
Ah!
Oh, watch out,
I have quite a kick!
When Grand Wilderness
destroys an opponent's monster,
the player regains two life.
So the more monsters he eats,
the more life I get back.
A penetrating charge!
Sorciere gains Double Attack
when destroying an
opponent's monster.
You'll never guess.
Paruko's doing
another live broadcast.
No way, Tetsuya's
fighting instead of Gao?
Little Land deals
a powerful blow.
And here comes
Sorciere's second attack.
End of move.
Agree to hand over Tenbu now,
and I'd be willing to
let you out of this place.
Tetsuya,
or whatever your name is,
you must make the
exchange and hand me over.
There's no shame in
surrendering, Tets.
He's only interested
in Tenbu, after all.
You just need
to hand him over,
and we can all
get out of here.
(groaning)
Well, what do
you think, Tets?
Well, if I give up Tenbu,
Gao will be super sad, yo.
Bumming out a friend's
something I could never do.
Besides, we're just
getting started.
Come on!
It's time to serve this
demon the main course.
I was hoping
you'd say that.
First, I'm gonna
cast Nice One.
He's increased the
cards in his hand.
Then set the spell
Solomon's Great Barrier,
and call Fallen Angel of
Rage, Beleth to the center.
Now I get to hit someone.
Next, I call Sky Poet,
Amon to the right.
To fight or not to fight.
The Great Barrier makes size
two monsters into size one,
enabling an all‐out
attack formation.
(laughing)
Hey there, Sorciere.
Do you need a
ride to the fair?
I'm gonna hit you hard!
I cast the Dragon
Prudent spell!
But I wanted to hit him.
Forgive me, but
I must attack.
(grunting)
End of move.
Amon ends the attack by
causing three damage!
Let's see how Death
Shido will respond.
Ah, well, even a broken
claw can break twice a day.
Once again I call Demon
Fairy Dragon, Sorciere
to the center!
No matter how many life
points you take from me,
I'll keep getting them back.
Grand Wilderness,
go and attack Amon!
I've never been so underfed.
I'll eat everything I see.
I knew you were
gonna do that, yo.
I cast Magical Goodbye.
Not before the appetizer!
Back to the
cards in his hand.
That's so not fair!
But Death Shido's
remaining monsters
attack Tetsuya in
rapid succession,
leaving him with
just one life point.
It doesn't look good
for the young fighter.
Could this be the
end of the line?
Uh.
So, what do you think
we should do now,
oh, future king?
When I'm king, I'll
build a new country,
one that's got
music and dancing
coming out of its ears, yo.
But just song
and dance alone
can't fill an
empty stomach, Tets.
I know, but nothing
energizes you
like the hippest,
hoppenest beats.
Do I sense some
freestyling coming on?
How about groovin' on
some backup, A‐Dog?
I'm down with that.
Back by popular demand,
I buddy call Demon Lord,
Asmodai to the center.
Let's bust some moves.
It's showtime!
Dangerous backdrop!
Thanks for clearing
out the center.
Now I'll send in Amon
to attack the fighter.
Yo, yo, yo!
I cast Dragon Prudent spell!
Uh‐oh.
He blocked the attack
with a counter spell.
(laughing)
Oh!
Demon drop kick!
I've got you exactly
where I want you.
In your dreams.
My turn isn't over yet.
Final phase!
Hey, Gao!
Is that Tetsuya?
Welcome back to the party.
Now you can check
out my impact.
No, don't tell me this
is happening again!
I cast...
(grunting)
Huh?
...Diabolical Hardcore!
No, why me?
Game over.
Winner, Tetsuya Kurodake.
Huh?
He was one of the
Hundred Demons.
Thanks a lot, Tetsuya.
‐You saved us.
‐Oh, I just did
what any good
friend would do, yo.
(cell phone ringing)
Hi, Gao, come to
HQ right away,
and bring Tetsuya with you.
Uh...
With the recent increase
in illegal monster
activity on Earth,
the Buddy Police doesn't have
enough officers to keep up,
so I have a favor
to ask of you.
In light of your
recent victory,
would you be interested
in coming to work for us
as a Buddy Police
trainee just like Gao?
For real, yo?
Yes, for real.
Your fight today was
absolutely brilliant.
I believe you're more
than qualified to join us.
Congrats, man!
Actually, I've been
trying to find a way
to ease the pain on Gao here,
so this is totally off
the hook, Commander I.
I'd be stoked to
become a trainee, yo.
Excellent.
You start right away.
(laughing)
Hm, well, I guess
it can't be helped.
‐Excuse me?
‐Hm?
I could swear that we've
met somewhere before.
Yeah, yeah, your memory.
You said the same
thing to Count Dawn.
I bet you've probably
seen me on TV.
I'm a big celebrity with the
number one hip‐hop dance show.
Mm, yes, maybe that was it.
Mm.
Ahh!
Sorry, Master!
You're a bunch
of useless fools!
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'll teach you about
Rage Thirst Emperor,
Grand Wilderness.
‐Cool!
‐This Hundred Demon
eats other monsters
and converts them
into life points.
When he destroys
an enemy monster,
the player using the
card regains two life.
So the more he destroys,
the more your points increase.
That's amazing!
Using Grand Wilderness to attack
just proves what they say,
"The best defense
is a good offense."
They also say to let us
out of class early
to go practice.
(laughs)
Next time, Akatsuki
thinks Zanya would make
a great Buddy Police trainee.
When an escaped criminal
Buddyfighter shows up
with a Hundred
Demon as a buddy,
the brothers are
forced into action.
Next episode,
"Brothers in Arms!
The Battle of
Dragon Brainbaltes!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!