Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the Hundred Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on!
(whooshing)
♪
All right, I opened
the Blue Dragon Shield!
Whoa, that's awesome!
Those are hard to find.
So what?
It's not like
it's a Super Rare.
Okay, so what did
you get then, huh?
I don't know,
I'm not really sure.
It's okay, we all have
to start somewhere.
Just read the cards and
tell us what they say.
I know how to play.
I just never
opened cards before.
Let me just take
a look at one.
What, no way!
Come on, unreal.
Beginner's luck.
Uh, you mean I
drew a good card?
Good, it's the same
one as Gao's buddy.
You're not in the
special Buddyfight class,
but you and Gao do
have homeroom together.
You must have heard
about Drum by now.
That's a great card, seriously.
Hm.
The same card as Gao's buddy.
Excellent.
How long do you
expect me to wait, huh?
I'm sorry, but
the last failure
wasn't my fault, Master.
Sophia and Gallows over there
are the ones that lost
to Gao Mikado this time.
Hey.
So if you want to punish
someone, punish them!
‐Enough!
‐Ah!
I'm sorry, please
don't hurt me!
(laughing)
I'm growing tired of
your sniveling excuses.
This is your last chance
to redeem yourself.
Awaken, power of darkness,
power of evil, power
of the Hundred Demons!
Pleased to meet you.
My name's Kalavinka
Uguisukomachi, chirp.
This Hundred Demon doesn't
look nearly as strong
as the last two.
Use this monster
to bring Tenbu to me
so I can devour him.
Yes, as you wish, Master!
Well, what are
you waiting for?
Be gone!
You're joking!
That is a long time
without a day off.
It's very troubling.
No matter how busy,
our officers need
sufficient rest.
Your superior
sounds incompetent.
With people like
this running things,
the Buddy Police's future
looks very dark indeed.
(grunts)
‐Gao.
‐Huh?
Go take three days off.
We can manage things here.
Are you sure?
Sometimes resting your body
is an important mission too.
(laughs)
You heard him.
Now, you should get going
and spend time being
a kid for a change.
Now what do we do?
I'm not used to
having any free time.
After grabbing some za,
why don't we check
out the Buddy Fest?
Oh, is that today?
(roaring)
(indistinct chatter)
♪
Hey, kids!
Thanks for comin'!
Are ya pumped up?
Yeah!
Our next event is for all you
Buddyfight newbies out there.
If you've ever wanted
to know how to play,
well, now's your chance to
learn from a bona fide pro.
Your wildest dream of becoming
a Buddyfighter can come true!
Learn the ropes
while participating
in a real Buddyfight!
(laughing)
It's exactly what
I've always wanted.
This place is jam‐packed, wow.
Okay, so all of you who
want your chance to play,
‐raise your hand.
‐What is this I'm hearing?
Buddyfighting takes
time to perfect.
‐It's a skill.
‐What do you think
you're doing, Gramps?
You can't just pop out
whenever you want.
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
(sighing)
That's the Lord Tenbu
card right under my nose.
We should take advantage of
this unexpected opportunity.
You're not the one
in charge here.
Hang on, I think we have a
celebrity here with us today.
Don't look now, but it's the
famous Buddy Police trainee,
Gao Mikado!
Takochu!
(indistinct chattering)
Gao, it's me, Hana!
Hey!
This is awesome, dude.
Would you like, you know,
wanna help us train
‐some of these guys?
‐Uh, I don't know.
Sure he would.
What are you doing?
It'll be a good time.
Besides, what else
ya got goin' on?
Yeah, you're right.
Okay then, I'm in.
So what do I do?
Wow, who would
like to challenge
the Castle Store Manager?
Gao's agreed to be
in your corner
for a hands‐on
Buddyfight training match.
Hey, go for it.
You'll never get another
chance like this, Tatsuto.
Uh, I can look up
the rules on my own
if I want to, thanks.
Aw, come on!
You can use your new
Crimson Battler, Drum.
What, no way.
Yeah, so what?
Who are you, what do you care?
Hey, Gao, you'll never guess!
This guy beside me has a
Crimson Battler, Drum card!
Cool, hey, Tatsuto.
Oh, hey there, Gao.
How are you?
We found our challenger!
I won't be much
of a challenge.
You'll be just fine.
We both start out with ten
life points, little dude.
Okay, let's get
started already!
Ah, but I haven't
had a chance
to learn the
rules yet, ma'am.
Relax, don't worry about it.
It's way easier
to learn the rules
when you're playing anyway.
Okay, everyone,
say it with me now!
Buddy...
Fight!
Time to raise the flag.
I'm fighting for Hero World.
Uh, what do I do now?
Flip this.
We're fighting
for Dragon World.
Normally, we place our
buddy cards right here,
but since this is
a training game,
we won't be using
buddies today.
Why don't we play
Rock, Paper, Scissors
to see who goes first?
Rock, paper...
‐Scissors.
Scissors cuts paper.
That means we go first.
To start, choose any
monster you'd like to play
from the cards in your hand.
Mm, how about this one?
That's the Hammer Ball Dragon.
Awesome choice!
So, where do you
want to put him?
I think center.
This guy has a
critical of two,
which means he'll do two
damage to your opponent.
Ah‐ha‐ha, covering
your center, huh?
Pretty good strategy, dude.
Now, just turn
the card sideways
and announce your attack.
Mm, okay.
I use Hammer Ball Dragon to
attack Castle Store Manager.
Ah!
Oh, no, you just took
two of my life points.
The player who goes first
can only attack once.
At the end of each turn,
we say, "End of move."
Cool, that makes it my go.
Now, to begin each
turn, we draw a card.
That means I take the card
that's on top of my deck
and then add it to
the cards in my hand.
After that, I take one
card that I don't need
and add it to my gauge.
This lets me draw
from my deck again.
You can do this during
your first turn, too.
And we call it
"charge and draw."
Okay, what's gauge exactly?
When you play stronger cards,
you gotta pay a cost.
We use the gauge
to make payments.
Here I go.
I call Rescue
Dragon, Crossbuster
to the right position.
And then I call Cyber
Police, Hyper Rescue
to the center area.
He called two at once.
Yeah, you see, monsters
have different sizes.
If the total they add
up to is three or less,
you can call as
many as you like.
And even if you have a size
three out in the field,
you're allowed to call
a size zero monster.
Now, attack!
These monsters have
criticals of three and one
which means that I'll
receive four damage.
Nah, don't forget,
on your first turn,
you put a monster in
the center, right?
So as long as he stays there,
you won't receive any damage.
He'll protect you.
That's right, Gao,
which is why I'm gonna
use my Hyper Rescue
to attack your
Hammer Ball Dragon.
Ha‐ha!
Oh no, what do I do now?
When monsters
fight each other,
you gotta check out their
power and defense stats
'cause if your
monster's defense
is lower than your
opponent's monster's power,
your monster
will be destroyed.
Now that there's
no one protecting you,
my attacks will
reach you directly.
Za‐zing!
I'm gonna use Crossbuster
to attack the fighter.
With no monster
in the center,
Tatsuto receives
three damage.
Takochu.
And with that,
it's end of move.
Your turn, Tatsuto.
Draw.
And I charge and draw.
Whoa, Assail Sword,
Dragoraptor.
But it's not a monster,
so what do I do with it?
It's an item card which means
that you yourself can fight.
You're expecting me to fight
in my very first game?
Sure, just pay two gauge
and put the card right here.
Okay, I equip Assail
Sword, Dragoraptor.
And items aren't
limited by size,
so you can call
another monster.
Then I call three
size one monsters.
Hang on, man.
If you do that, you can't use
the Dragoraptor
you just equipped
'cause when you've
got a monster
in the center position,
you aren't able to attack.
He's kind of blocking you in.
Think about it, you
don't want to attack
your own monster
in the back, do ya?
Then I'll leave
the center open
and call Hammer Ball
Dragon to the right
and I call Starting Dragon
to the left position.
Hey, you just set up
the Gao Formation.
I did, what's that?
Why don't we leave
that for another time?
Ha‐ha, it looks good,
but you won't be able to
break through my center.
Don't forget, my Hyper
Rescue has 6,000 defense.
Hammer Ball has 5,000 power
Starting and Dragoraptor
have only 4,000 each.
It's impossible.
There's always a link attack.
You'll have to explain that.
If you make two attacks
at the same time,
you can unite their
power together.
How much do you get if
you add up Hammer Ball
and Starting's
combined power?
Nine thousand power.
Then we can defeat
Hyper Rescue.
(crying)
Hyper Rescue's
been destroyed.
Now I'll attack store
manager with Dragoraptor.
Take that!
‐Ah!
‐That's three more damage
to the Castle Store Manager!
For a first‐timer,
Tatsuto's running the show.
I'll get Uguisukomachi to
possess Paruko and steal Tenbu.
♪
Ah.
I understand.
‐Huh?
Hm.
Are you okay?
Takochu?
Is this part of the game?
I'm feeling better
than ever, actually.
I just thought our
young friend here
could use a breather.
Chirp, chirp.
Something is quite
different about you,
but for the life of me
I just can't put
my claw on it.
Give me a break.
You can't just keep
popping out like this.
Right, you know
how my memory is.
Since we're taking
a little break,
can I have a look at
that Tenbu card of yours?
You're a Hundred Demon.
What's that?
No, I'm not a
Hundred Demon, chirp.
Paruko would never do that,
put down her
microphone during a fight
to try and look at
someone's cards.
Why, you, you leave
me no choice.
I'll have to
take it by force.
Secret Arts, Uguisukomachi's
Valley Crossing.
(shouting)
Oh, what am I gonna do now?
My best chance is to put
up a Darkness Barrier.
Everyone, please,
quickly evacuate the store!
♪
Now, hand over that
Tenbu card, or else.
(gasping)
♪
The place is growing on me.
It looks so scary on TV.
If you ever hope to
leave the confines
of the Darkness Barrier,
you must defeat me, chirp,
the most beautiful
Skull Warrior
among the Hundred Demons,
Kalavinka Uguisukomachi.
Ooh, I think I
heard about her.
The most beautiful
monster there is.
Easy, Gramps, I hate
to break it to ya,
but that's actually a guy.
‐Huh?
‐That's true.
They say only the
male of the species
makes that
distinctive bird call.
How dare you reveal
my dark secret?
I'm going to
annihilate you for that!
Above all, monsters must
have honor and be truthful,
even evil ones.
That's it, I'm
fighting with you.
We will use your
Dragon World deck,
Crimson Dragon Fist.
All right.
Burning like an inferno
with limitless spirit,
Luminize Crimson Dragon Fist!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power.
Luminize Hundred
Ancient Katana Warriors!
Takochu!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Dragon World.
We're with Katana
World, chirp.
Katana World, huh?
Not Paruko's usual deck.
I think it might be the
Hundred Demon's own deck.
Anyone going to tell
me what's going on?
Sorry you got dragged
into this, man.
I don't really know
what's going on either,
but it's clear I gotta win
if we want to go home.
Well, I'll just stand over
here and cheer you on.
Thanks, I might need it.
'Kay, hurry this up.
We want to get
back to Castle.
If you think you can beat me,
you're a hundred
years too soon.
I must say, it's
much more relaxing
to be watching
from the Skull Pit.
Charge and draw.
I call Crimson Battler, Guns
Knuckle Dragon to the center.
I'm gonna pump
you full of lead.
Attack the fighter!
My pickle's in a barrel!
Chirp, chirp!
End of move.
So this is a Buddyfight.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Blood Knife,
Kimensai to the left
and Sea‐splitting Irukamaru
to the center, chirp.
(laughing)
And now I buddy call
myself to the right,
regaining one life point.
Takochu.
You don't need the Takoscope.
I'll tell you
about it myself.
I'm a size one monster
with 3,000 power,
5,000 defense, and
a critical of one.
And my ability is
elegant Double Attack.
And you're actually a dude.
You talk too much!
Kimensai, destroy
Mr. Knuckles in the center.
Ha‐ha, sword of
devilish delight!
Ah!
(laughing)
Penetrate!
(grunting)
Called from the icy depths,
sword of the thrashing seas!
Take this Flaming
Arrow Bushfire Blitz.
(grunting)
I'm not done yet!
Say bye‐bye to one
more life point.
(grunting)
End of move.
Thanks to my Double Attack,
your life points have been
cut down to half, chirp.
On my next turn,
I'll end this battle.
(chirping)
She's making my
dragon blood boil.
When I'm called, I'll
sweep you into oblivion
with my howling fire.
That Uguisukomachi's
actually not half bad.
Maybe for once you'll get
something right, Sh‐Shids.
Master Ikazuchi
will be so happy
he won't zap me this time.
Well, you didn't actually do
anything, did you, ka‐sha?
Zip those bony lips.
My underling's success
counts as my success.
Time for the Gao Formation.
Isn't that...
Yeah, better start
taking notes, kid.
Monster under fire!
Ah!
‐Penetrate.
‐Chirp, chirp!
Crimson Fist!
I cast Demon Way,
Oborogenbu.
Ugh, dang!
Your attack's
been neutralized.
Yeah, then I'll get Spin
Nail to attack the right.
Spinning pass!
I must fly away for now!
End of move.
Gao figured out early this
game isn't just about power.
It's about staying positive.
Even when things
look hopeless,
Gao always keeps battling
till he figures
out a way to win.
Set spell Return
to the Underworld,
and I choose to
activate it now
and call myself to
the center, chirp.
As a size one Skull Warrior,
I can use this spell
to resurrect myself.
I call Tempest
Garo‐oh to the right
and I activate his ability.
(shouting)
Go take a bite
out of the fighter.
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
No problem.
Garo‐oh, again!
My Garo Slash!
Gao, isn't it my
turn to fight yet?
I'll engulf those monsters
and peck them out for good.
Like a Katana candle, I'll
light them up on both ends!
End of move.
All Gao's monsters
have been destroyed.
Stay calm, kid.
This is where the
fight gets real.
Now who's the teacher, huh?
Let's do this, partner.
What am I, chopped liver?
I draw!
Charge and draw!
Time to send this
bird back to the nest.
Buddy call Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon
to the right.
Sculpting my body
with red‐hot flame,
carving out a new path
with my own two fists.
Crimson Battler, Drum Bunker
Dragon is reporting for duty.
Why did he call
him to the right?
Gao only has
four life points.
Shouldn't he be called to
the center to protect them?
I mean, he could be defeated
on Uguisukomachi's next turn.
Thrill Ram Break!
Chirp, chirp!
And a side order of Penetrate!
Don't cut my wings, ah!
They both have
four life points
and no monster in the
center position, gah.
Wait, that means...
Oh, no, not again!
Final phase!
What, final phase?
I cast!
♪
(slamming)
Impact!
Gigantic...
Crusher!
Looks like I'm
grounded for good!
(screaming)
♪
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
Thanks.
And the lesson is over.
But I never got to fight.
♪
What happened?
Were we on commercial break?
Takochu.
‐Takochu.
‐Takosuke, what's wrong?
They really want this.
Weird our pal Death
Shido didn't show up
today though, huh?
Yeah.
♪
You failed me again?
No, the one who failed
is that Uguisukomachi
you wanted me to use.
This is in no way
my fault at all!
I told you this was
your last chance.
There's no excuse!
No!
Why does this keep
happening to me?
That'll teach him to
try and take credit
for someone else's
work, ka‐cha!
You can do it, Tatsuto!
Yeah, let him have it!
Luminize.
My buddy is Crimson
Fighter, Drum Bunker Dragon.
You're using the same
one as Gao Mikado, huh?
What are you trying to say?
Copying a lucky
fighter like him
doesn't mean
you'll be like him.
Either way, it won't
help you against me,
the great Buddyfighter
Kenta Zakoyama.
Ha, even I know
that Gao isn't lucky.
Gao and his buddy
taught me something.
This great game isn't
just about power.
The key is staying positive.
Even when it looks hopeless,
you must battle on until
you find a way to win.
Whoa, Tatsuto's pretty cool.
Kid's right.
Being positive
is where it's at,
not just for this game, but
for life in general, dudes.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Hey, look, isn't that Tatsuto?
Ha, whatever.
Stop your blabbing
and call a monster
to the center already.
You're gonna need
protection, rookie.
I equip Assail
Sword, Dragoraptor!
And, now, I buddy call...
...Crimson Battler, Drum
Bunker Dragon to the right!
‐Come on!
‐That's it.
Huh?
Gao speaking.
Gao, another illegal monster
has been reported in the city.
He was last seen
around the Sky Tower.
I'm sorry to bother
you on your day off,
but could you head to
the scene right away?
No problem.
Drum, Buddy Police
Emergency Launch.
So much for our
day off, huh?
Fine with me.
Decker Road, open!
♪
Decker Drums on patrol.
Let's show this guy
some Earth justice!
Time to go to work.
(siren wailing)
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna
teach you about
Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon.
‐Cool!
‐This is Drum so souped up,
he can destroy a monster with
a single blow of his fist.
And if you happen to have
a Fist item equipped,
he gains the ability
to Penetrate,
so you can cause
damage to the fighter
while keeping
your center open.
That's my kind of card.
He also has Soulguard,
so destroying him once
won't keep him down.
He's a really
powerful monster.
Let me out early so I
can go try and open one.
(laughing)
♪
Next time, Rage Thirst
Emperor, Grand Wilderness
is eating up all
the food in the city,
but Gao's so
exhausted from work,
he doesn't have
enough energy to fight.
Wait, is that
Tetsuya to the rescue?
Next episode, "The Life of
a Buddy Police Trainee!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!