Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth,
to become Buddies with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters
known as The Hundred Demons
have come here illegally
and plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy Skill, on!
(crashing)
It looks like the
Quartet Five is in trouble.
Unlike registered monsters,
illegal monsters don't
have their power suppressed,
making them very
difficult to contain.
Should we send in backup?
‐That won't be necessary.
‐It's Takihara.
I'm on the scene;
I'll help the Quartet Five.
Go to work!
(screaming)
Another one rounded up.
(rhythmic vocalizing)
I'll get it, Ki.
Thanks, guys, we'll take this
Hundred Demons
card off your hands.
Catch you later!
Lookie here, chief, I think
it's just some regular
illegal monster, Ki.
You sure?
Ki.
Thattaway!
♪
Nuts, it took off.
What're we gonna do now?
You should know the answer
to that, little Ricky.
With a blazing fury,
I'm gonna track
down every last one
of these evil Hundred Demons,
and demolish them with my fists.
That's why they call me the
Great Hundred Demons Hunter.
♪
That's who showed up
and took the card.
It's the same guy.
We met him before.
The one from your report?
It's clear that
he's some vigilante
rounding up these Hundred
Demons cards any way he can.
He must be stopped.
Yeah, well, no matter
what kind of reason he has,
being violent to a girl is
definitely out of the question.
I totally agree.
But why is he going after them,
and why is he calling himself
the Hundred Demons Hunter?
Only time will tell;
I just really hope
he doesn't compromise
any future investigations.
If he shows his face again, make
sure you report it immediately.
♪
The Hundred Demons Hunter?
Da.
He rode in on his motorcycle
and simply snatched the card
away from the Buddy Police.
I was thinking that
we could make Igniel
possess this hunter guy, and get
him to steal Tenbu for us.
And if you mess up this
time, you know what I'll do.
That won't happen.
He'll mess up for sure!
Keep your comments to yourself!
You and I will make a great
team, won't we, Igniel?
Leave it to me.
That's the team spirit!
Stop breathing fire!
So, Chief, your Hundred Demons
radar picking up any action?
Nope, I'm getting nada.
Sounds like you need some eats.
Sounds good to me, Ki.
Ban, ban.
Ban.
Ban, ban, ban, ban, ban, ban.
What's with you?
You've been grumping
and groaning all day.
It's that Hundred
Demons Hunter guy.
Didn't you notice
the motorcycle handlebars
that were growing
out of his head?
It's just totally
been bugging me,
you know what I mean?
I never noticed.
Ban, ban, ban, ban, ban, ban,
ban, ban, ban,
ban, ban, ban, ban‐‐
Hey!
That's him!
Let's get him!
This really hits the spot.
(eating noisily)
Is it just me, or are those guys
taking forever
getting our drinks, Ki?
(moaning)
I need to report this to HQ.
Sorry it took so long, Chief!
Hey.
You guys again.
I'm Wicked Dragon Emperor!
Billion Knuckle!
I'm Bass Dragon Emperor,
Champion Lord!
And I'm the Serial
Overlord, Gang The King!
Don't forget me,
Dragon Kid Ricky.
♪
And we are the Raging Spirits!
Don't just stand
there, say something!
Long time no see, trainee.
What do you think you're doing,
sneaking around in those bushes,
spying on us, Ki?
Well, I...
The Buddy Police want
me out of the way,
to take credit for my captures.
Why, that little‐‐
It's time he got a lesson
from Dragon Kid Ricky, Ki.
Okay, make it quick,
there are demons out there.
No prob.
Take this, and that,
and some more!
You'll wish you were never born!
I'll teach you to mess with us!
I'll be merciful and let you
off easy this time, Junior.
(laughter)
Listen, I gotta know,
why are you hunting for
Hundred Demons cards?
If you want to know that,
you'll have to fight me.
Sorry, that's not my style.
But I'd be happy to accept
a challenge to a Buddyfight.
That could work for me,
but only if you agree
to my one condition.
That if you lose, you've
gotta become my errand boy.
Hey, trainee, go
grab me a large pizza!
You got it, right away, chief!
And don't forget
the anchovies this time!
Don't worry, I'll be
back before you know it.
That Buddy Cop as
Chief's errand boy!
That's a bashing idea.
This I gotta see!
So, what's it gonna be?
Are you gonna accept
Chief's challenge, Ki?
You bet, sounds like a blast.
Oh, it will be.
Hey, you think I can
touch those handlebars
that are growing
out of your head?
Do you have a death wish
or something, Armor Dragon?
(screaming)
Chief's a little bit
sensitive about them.
No one's allowed to touch them!
Hundred Demon detected, Ki!
That way, let's go, Ricky!
Hold on, you can't leave!
What about our Buddyfight, huh?
I wanted to touch 'em.
Ban, ban, ban, ban, ban, ban!
Time for an emergency launch!
Oh yeah!
Decker Road, open!
♪
Decker Drums, on patrol!
Buddy Skill, on!
Let's go to work!
♪
They tricked us good.
What are you talking about, Ki?
This isn't a Hundred
Demon card, take a look,
the mark on the top right's
a totally different shape.
This is the symbol for Soul, Ki.
This is the character
that we're looking for.
All right, I timed it perfectly!
What did you do?
Now you're a puppet
of the Hundred Demons!
Do it, Chief.
No, no, daddy‐o.
No way!
I never thought a human could
reject the Hundred Demons card!
How in the world could that be?
Thanks for the Hundred Demons
card, now step off, little man!
It's been a slice!
Well, didn't see
that one coming.
What happened to
the Hundred Demons card?
(screaming)
What do we have here?
A demon in need of
an attitude adjustment.
Bring it.
(screaming)
I don't think so!
(siren wails)
Illegal monster detected
close to here, come on!
♪
There's no escape!
There it is!
End of the line.
You might want to
behave yourself.
You don't want to test us.
That guy belongs to me!
Leave him to Ethereal
Overlord, Gang The King!
Go take him out.
You got it!
Imperial Rear Barrett Twister!
What incredible strength.
I'm receiving the data
on him now‐‐big surprise.
That monster's unregistered.
They pose a great risk
compared to the declared
monsters we regulate
by having their
power suppressed.
The monsters fighting with
the Hundred Demons Hunter
have no limits.
That's why they're so strong.
♪
This is the Cho‐Tokyo
Fire Department,
we have a major emergency!
There's a fire in
the warehouse district
close to a shipment of liquid
explosives inside a hangar.
We need your help to
avoid a massive explosion!
Rescue Dragon, Mach Braver!
♪
Leave everything
to me, Mach Vacuum!
♪
I won't go so easily.
(screaming)
(concerned chatter)
Now you can't get me.
Possessing a human
won't save you.
Let me help you out of there!
Stop it!
No chance, trainee!
Blast him.
He's making a run for it, Ki.
Don't sweat it, it's all good.
You had me worried, if that
demon didn't leave her body,
what were you gonna do to her?
Chillax, I'm a lot of things,
but I ain't no doofus who's
going to hit a woman, kid.
Okay, but, that's
not what I meant.
Man or woman, you can't
go around hitting people.
It's just not right.
You can't use your
strength to threaten others,
or force them to
do what you want.
It's the responsibility
of guys like us
to help those who
can't help themselves.
♪
See, I told you
I'd get him back.
I've got you now.
Oh, so you decided to bring
some backup this time, huh?
Save yourself the trouble, punk.
Just hand over the card.
That's not happening.
You don't want to make me
angry, do you understand?
You can have it, but
only if you can beat
Death Shido here
in a Buddyfight.
If you lose, you'll have
to do whatever we say.
Yeah, good thinking, because
the Hundred Demons card
can't possess him,
we have to change our plan.
So, if I lose,
I'm your errand boy?
You, go get me
a bowl of borscht!
Yes ma'am, right away!
And don't forget
the rye bread this time.
I won't, I promise not
to disappoint you!
Yeah, right, that'll be the day.
Okay, I accept.
You sure, chief?
Then I activate
the Darkness Barrier!
What's happening, Ki?
♪
Warp successful!
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana will be there!
Once again, it's our old
friend, Death Shido and‐‐
Oh, it's you, we met before!
Hey, yeah, it's weird,
but I still don't know
where I know you from.
Really?
How can anyone
not know who I am?
Unless you want me to
call you "the other guy,"
can you tell me your
name for the broadcast?
Sure, doll.
I am the Hundred Demons Hunter!
Now, will both
fighters please Luminize?
It's all the rage with
boppers who are totally hip.
Luminize!
Enma Alliance,
nice to meet you.
Ravenous beings
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power.
Luminize, Hundred Ancient!
Let's Buddyfight!
Time to raise the flag.
We fight for
Ancient World, Ki.
I'm fighting for
Ancient World, as well.
Another major disaster avoided.
Thanks for your
help, Mach Braver.
Mission complete.
We're grateful for the
Buddy Police's cooperation.
Oh, believe me, my dear,
the pleasure's all ours.
After all, you're
the ones out here
risking your lives
each day, helping others.
You're not supposed
to be out of the deck.
Now back inside so we
can go find those guys!
End of move.
Death Shido's attack is over.
Now the Hundred Demons
Hunter gets a turn.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I pay two gauge, and call Wicked
Dragon Emperor, Billion Knuckle,
to the left position.
Whoever wants a good
beating, step out right now!
I equip Skysplitting
Armor Masurau.
Billion Knuckle, hit him hard!
♪
Here I come, Death Shido!
(screaming)
Hundred Demons Hunter is
going for a direct attack.
♪
Skysplitting Armor Masurau!
Why me?
End of move.
For those just tuning in to the
fight, after the first round,
Death Shido and the Hundred
Demons Hunter are even
at eight life points each.
Want to tell me why
Death Shido's fighting this guy?
Vorpal Spartar,
go attack the fighter!
The blade of an emperor!
You want to axe the chief,
you gotta go through me first.
Billion Knuckle just protected
the Hundred Demons Hunter!
But, how is such
a thing possible?
Would somebody explain it to me?
We have the ability
to redirect an attack
meant for the chief and take
it ourselves, and we call it...
Risking your own safety
for the sake of your friends
is pretty impressive,
don't you think, kid?
Hm.
What is it, Grandpa?
Are you starting to
remember something?
In a surprising twist,
Vorpal Spartar was wiped out.
With his soul guard, Billion
Knuckle turned the tables
and delivered a
harsh counterattack.
I'm glad I wasn't on
the other end of that one.
That's it, let's get
him with a link attack!
Victory is in your
hands now, chief.
Billion Knuckle!
When my guys bite the dust,
I get damaged, too.
That's what this
lifelink is all about.
Through good or bad,
we share our fate,
that's the bond
between me and my crew.
(sobbing)
Oh, chief.
Through good or bad,
they share their fate.
Heavy stuff.
I pay two gauge
and call to the left,
Bass Dragon Emperor,
Champion Lord!
I'm feeling very, very fine.
Buddy Call Dragon Kid Ricky
to the right position!
♪
Good things come
in small packages!
Okay, Ricky, target Little
Land Mu, and hit him hard!
(screaming)
How do you like me now?
Yes, now the center's wide open.
Champion Lord, hit that
Death Shido where it hurts!
All right, all right, all right!
Wait, there's more,
my double attack!
Who is this guy?
This is for getting in my way!
Hundred Demons Hunter
is coming in full force!
He's gonna attack
the fighter personally!
I cast Dragon Prudent!
(yelling)
Death Shido slipped out of that
one with a timely counterspell.
Hm, no mistaking it.
I knew it, you do
remember something.
Those things growing out of
that grumpy hoodlum's head
are motorcycle handlebars!
That's what's been
bugging you all this time?
They're driving me crazy
too, what are they for?
Little Land Mu and Sorciere, do
a link attack on Champion Lord!
All right, I'm gonna cast.
Gathering of The Armed Dragons,
which boosts the power and
defense of one Raging Spirits
monster in the field by 3,000.
You gotta be kidding me!
And it gives that monster
a counterattack, too.
♪
Oh, yeah!
Time to let off some steam!
(screaming)
Now, Igniel!
Leave it to me.
Let's use my Takoscope
to check out the deets
on this fierce‐looking dragon.
Red Dragon Igniel, size 2,
Wild Dragon attribute,
6,000 power, 2,000 defense,
a critical of 2.
When called, his ability causes
one damage to the opponent.
♪
Come on.
No, Champion!
Very, very bad.
♪
Now his lifelink will
activate and be his downfall.
Looks like defeat is in
Hundred Demon Hunter's future.
Ricky!
Link cut!
I don't believe this.
His buddy Ricky has an ability
that nullifies a lifelink!
He's got the link cut?
Who knew he had
such great ability?
The fight is really heating up,
and Hundred Demons
Hunter has the stage.
I pay three gauge and call
to the left Ethereal Overlord,
Gang the King.
I won't disappoint you, chief.
Let's do this, dudes.
Oh, yeah.
Gang the King, hit Igniel in
the center with all you've got.
Imperial Gale Force Twister!
♪
Penetrate!
I've never seen
anything like it!
Gang The King has caused
an amazing five damage!
For real?
I really need to get a life!
And this will be
the finishing blow!
Skysplitting Armor!
Masurao!
Why me?
♪
Game over, winner,
Hundred Demons Hunter.
We caught your fight.
Nice moves, man.
You again?
You took the Hundred
Demons card I defeated.
(yelling)
(snickers)
It's Ban Enma.
What?
Well, my name of course.
My name is Gao, the mighty
Sunfighter, Gao Mikado.
But chief.
You actually told him your name.
What's the big deal about that?
It's unusual, is all.
Chief never tells
anyone his real name, Ki.
I guess he trusts Gao,
and thinks of him
as a true friend, huh?
How about that?
Gao has a way with folks.
I was wrong about you; you're
a pretty cool dude after all.
And these handlebars are
about as cool as it gets!
Drum, drum, drum...
I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
No one touches my
handlebars, ever!
Now I'm angry!
Flame of fury!
No one gets away with that!
You okay?
I'm glad I didn't touch them.
Calm down, chief!
Ban!
Ban, ban, ban, ban...
I don't get it, why's he so mad?
We told you guys before!
Told us what?
Only I'm allowed to touch the
handlebars growing on his head.
Whenever someone else
touches them or even teases him
about them, he goes
all crazy like that, Ki.
Wait for us, chief!
Ban, ban, ban, ban, ban...
It seems there is one out
there who is able to reject
the Hundred Demons.
(screaming)
And this is most troubling.
I did warn you
this would happen!
Prepare yourself!
I'm sorry, but
it wasn't my fault!
There's only one thing to do.
You will learn obedience!
(screaming)
I don't get it,
why'd he go so crazy?
Next time we see ol' handlebars
head, we'll give him what for,
am I right, kid?
In a Buddyfight, you mean.
Yeah, of course, what else?
♪
Ban Enma.
Ban, ban, ban, ban,
ban, ban, ban, ban, ban!
Gao Mikado, huh?
Looks like I missed my chance
to Buddyfight that trainee.
Yeah, I suppose so.
Where are we going, Ki?
We're going wherever
the Hundred Demons guide us,
and until we hunt them all
down, our journey has no end.
That's my sworn promise.
I, the Hundred Demons Hunter.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm going to tell you
all about Ethereal Overlord,
‐Gang the King.
‐Cool!
This is a powerful monster card
that can blow away his
enemies with incredible force.
With a critical of 5
and penetrate ability,
he can cut your opponent's
life in half in just one move.
And he can also take an attack
that was meant for you.
Seriously?
He does have lifelink,
but if you have Dragon
Kid Ricky in your deck,
that can be nullified.
I wish all my homework
could be nullified, too.
♪
Next time, we meet
the Hundred Demons monster,
Mysterious Dekarabia,
and Gao gets engaged
to Suzuha Amanosuzu?
And as part of his
bridegroom training,
he has to fight a robot!
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!