Buddyfight uses
special cards that act
as portals to bring monsters
from other worlds to Earth
to become buddies
with humans, but now
a swarm of evil monsters,
known as the Hundred Demons
have come here illegally
and plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for
an Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on!
Back by popular demand,
I Buddy Call Demon Lord, Asmodai
to the center!
Let's bust some moves!
It's show time!
Dangerous Back‐drop!
Thanks for clearing
out the center;
now I'll send in Amon
to attack the fighter!
Yo, yo, yo!
I cast Dragon Prudent spell!
Uh‐oh!
He blocked the attack
with a counter spell!
(laughs)
♪
Demon Dropkick!
I've got you exactly
where I want you.
In your dreams,
my turn isn't over yet.
Final phase!
Hey, Gao!
Is that Tetsuya?
Welcome back to the party!
Now you can check out my impact.
Oh, no, don't tell me
this is happening again!
I cast...
Yah!
Diabolical Hardcore!
No, why me?!
(grunting)
I think I've made up my mind.
I wanna be like Gao
and Tetsuya and become
a Buddy Police officer.
I will live for justice.
(sirens)
(grunting)
I knew I shouldn't have let
you drive the truck, gibba!
Don't give up so soon, brother.
There's still a chance
we could get out of this.
Hey, 5‐0!
Catch!
Ah, look out!
There's another one.
My brothers,
I promise to rescue you!
Gibba!
(sirens)
♪
(panting)
I think I lost 'em, gibba.
Looks like you
could use a hand.
Who are you, gibba?
♪
I'll help you on one condition.
Okay, gibba.
You're getting him
to steal Tenbu?
It's the perfect plan.
I get it, by making Kurooni
here do your work for you,
you'll think you'll avoid
punishment if he fails.
Master Ikazuchi won't
let you off so easy.
What, no, don't be silly.
That never even crossed my mind,
but now that you mention it,
you still think
Master would zap me?
What's she mean
punishment, gibba?
Oh, nothing that you
need to worry about.
We won't fail because I have
the right man for the job.
You know what they say,
if you need something bad done,
get a real criminal on the job.
That's right, I owe you one
for getting me out of
that sticky situation
with the fuzz back there,
so you can count on me
to snatch you that Tenbu
or whatever, gibba.
(munching)
Couldn't agree more.
This time, as a special favor,
I'm gonna let you use two
of the Hundred Demons.
Power of darkness,
power of evil,
power of the Hundred Demons!
(zap)
Sibling Dragon Foonbaltus!
♪
Sibling Dragon Kibaltes!
And, as you can tell
by our names‐‐
Foonbaltes and I are brothers.
(grunting)
How nice.
These guys remind me a lot
of my two brothers, gibba.
I've been looking
for you all over school.
There's something I need
to say to you, Gao.
Go ahead, shoot;
you seem upset, Akatsuki.
Did Zanya hide your crayons?
This isn't funny.
You know there's nobody better
suited for the Buddy Police
than my big brother,
so maybe you can tell me
why no one's bothered
to try and recruit him yet.
I dunno.
It makes no sense!
I mean, how could someone
like Tetsuya become
a Buddy Police
officer before Big Z?
I'm right here.
I happen to agree
with you, little guy.
A job like that really doesn't
gel with Tets here, am I right?
Just whose side
are you on, A‐Dog?
Yeah, you know we're homies.
Come on, let's bust a move!
Catch ya later, homies.
Have you talked
to Zanya about this?
Uh.
Did he actually tell you
that he wants to join
the Buddy Police?
No, not exactly.
‐Akatsuki!
‐Huh?
Agh, what did I do?
Ow, stop, that hurts!
Hey, cut the kid
some slack, Zanya!
I'm sorry for my brother
running his mouth off earlier.
It's unacceptable.
Z, why are you so mad?
It's what you want, isn't it?
I overheard you
talking to yourself.
We will discuss this at home.
But I was just doing it
for your own good!
Anyone who betrays my trust
is no brother of mine.
Don't say that!
Take it easy, man.
That's a little harsh,
don't you think?
(sobbing)
♪
I want you to tell me how you
plan on getting Tenbu for us.
I'm interested in
seeing your technique.
There's something
I need to do first.
Hmm?
Akatsuki, Akatsuki!
Where could he
have gotten to?
I guess I was being too
hard on him just now.
He is just a kid.
Huh?
What have I done?
You okay?
Leave me alone.
Let me take you home.
I've nothing to say to you!
Wait, come back!
Huh?
(screaming)
(grunting)
Excellent work, my brother!
♪
My name is Kurooni Konmae,
and unless you want to see
your city destroyed,
you'd better release
my brothers immediately, gibba!
Call it in,
we need reinforcements.
‐I'm on it!
‐Good.
What's it gonna be?
Do you think I'm a fool?
We had a deal and now
you're abandoning the mission.
I'm not abandoning
anything, gibba.
This is the first
part of the plan
for getting you your Tenbu card.
In order to tackle
a big job like this,
we need the skills of all three
brothers working together.
I don't know if
I can trust you.
You are a criminal, after all,
but I guess I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt.
On the bright side, you'll
certainly cause some chaos.
Leave it to me, gibba.
Officers in the field
believe these illegal monsters
may be Hundred Demons.
Dispatch all agents
nearby to provide backup.
The only one in
range is Gao Mikado.
(groans)
So, he's to be sent out
on another mission?
Huh?
Just yesterday, he was unable
to perform his duties due
to exhaustion from overwork.
The time's come to increase
the number of officers on
the forces I have proposed.
I already have my own
ideas regarding that.
I see.
Will you be sharing those ideas?
I will in good time,
now order Gao to do
an Emergency Launch.
Come on, there's another
illegal monster on the loose!
Go time!
Buddy Police, Emergency Launch!
Decker Road, Open!
♪
Decker Drum's on patrol!
Buddy Skill on.
Let's show this guy
some Earth justice!
Illegal monster going down!
(siren)
♪
(thumping)
That's as far as you go!
♪
Your days of
destruction are over!
♪
What's Z doing?
Taking on illegal monsters
alone is too dangerous!
♪
Who is that young man?
His name is Zanya Kisaragi.
His father is Police
Commissioner Kisaragi.
Huh?
You look familiar, gibba.
Oh, yeah, I remember now!
Your the Police
Commissioner's kid, right?
That's right, punk!
Justice runs deep
in my family,
and you're under arrest!
Don't make me laugh, small fry!
After I beat you,
you'll make a great prize
to trade for my brothers.
So, you refuse to
come peacefully, then?
Ha, I accept your challenge!
Just remember, I tried to
give you the easy way out.
Let's see what you've got!
Huh, I'm sensing some danger.
(squealing)
Darkness Barrier,
enshroud and confuse!
♪
Live from the Darkness Barrier,
we have an exciting game between
criminal fighter,
Kurooni Konmae,
and Zanya Kisaragi!
Where am I?
Somehow I need to choose
one of you as my buddy.
Stink test.
Okay, brace yourself, test.
I'll do my best.
(explosive fart)
♪
This guy is smellier.
Foonbaltes, you win.
You'll be my buddy, gibba.
Yeah!
Well, that's one way
to choose your buddy.
Being a lady, I was too shocked
to remember to use my Takoscope!
What we do know is that
he's big and he smells.
Anyway, the fighters
appear to be ready.
I do this for you, my brothers.
To your freedom.
Let's Buddyfight!
Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Danger World!
I'm with Katana World!
Flip the script!
Zanya's fighting him, yo.
I'm guessing this must
be Death Shido's doing.
(grunts)
♪
On the opening move of the game,
Kurooni caused three damage
to Zanya using Gaelcorga
from his center position.
Now it's Zanya's turn.
I can't wait to see
the look on Master's face
when we win!
Here I go.
I call to the right
Electron Ninja, Shiden!
Activate cyber analyze ability!
If he wants, he can discard
a Ninja Arts card from his hand
and draw two cards.
I call Stealth Ninja,
Kirikakure Saizo
to the left position!
And I buddy call Nanomachine
Ninja, Tsukikage to the center!
♪
Zanya's chosen
a close combat formation
with three size one monsters.
First, I'll attack
Gaelcorga with Shiden!
Destructo Blade!
(grunts)
Saizo, Tsukikage,
attack Kurooni!
Ensnare the warrior!
Mutation Sword!
Gibba!
Final phase.
Say what?
I pay one gauge and set
Super Lethal Formation!
There it is,
Zanya's famous impact
that can't be used right away.
It requires him to take
a secret sword card
from his deck
and wait patiently
for his opponent
to fall into his trap.
It's a Counterattack impact!
Set.
Plus, all ninja monsters
in the field get an extra
1,000 attack and defense.
End of move.
Don't scare me
like that, gibba.
If it doesn't
activate right away,
I'm not worried.
I draw, charge and draw!
I buddy call to the right,
Sibling Dragon, Foonbaltes!
I call Blood Wind Dragon,
Elyrseagar to the center
and Sibling Dragon,
Kibaltes to the left!
Kibaltes attacks Tsukikage!
I'll do my bestest with
my Mortal Scrap Hands!
(crash)
Nanomachine Body Replacement!
♪
Elyrseagar attack
Tsukikage, gibba!
Nanomachine Body Replacement!
You can't do that forever.
Foonbaltes, attack Tsukikage!
Better brace yourself
for my Thrashing Tail!
Nanomachine Body Replacement!
If Tsukikage is destroyed,
he can be revived by discarding
a non‐Monster Card
from your hand.
Once we reveal Cyber
Ninja Arts' dominance,
we've surpassed
the human intellect.
I attack Elyrseagar with Shiden!
Destructo Slam!
Tsukikage, Saizo,
attack the fighter!
(grunting)
Gibba!
End of move.
Like a surgeon,
Zanya's cut away
three more of his
opponents' points!
What are you messing
around for out there?
If you lose this fight,
you'll never see
your brothers again!
Like I don't know that.
Time to bring out
the big guns!
Catch me if you can, gibba!
You always were too
slow for us, gibba.
Wait for me, gibba!
Brothers...
when we join forces,
nothing can stand in our way!
Now, combine!
As...
One!
Brainbaltes!
(zapping)
I call to the center, gibba,
Super Combidragon, Brainbaltes!
Oh, my, I didn't
see this coming!
The two monsters have fused
into one colossal monster.
It's out of this world!
This is the true form
of the sibling dragons.
It looks like you should leave
the police work to your dad.
(roars)
Locking on with my Takoscope.
Let's see what he's all about.
He's a size three monster,
attribute is a dual dragon.
He's got 8,000 power,
a defense of 7,000,
and a critical of 3.
He has four different abilities,
but no life length.
Go and attack Tsukikage, gibba!
Baltes charging brute!
And now, Penetrate!
(grunting)
Big Z!
Nanomachine Body Replacement!
This is getting old, kid.
Protect your buddy
all you want,
but your life points
keep dropping.
He's actually right.
I don't get what Z keeps
bringing back Tsukikage.
Draw, charge and draw!
Shiden, Saizo, Link Attack!
(grunting)
I'll just revive him
with Soulguard!
And I Counterattack on Shiden!
(grunting)
If Z loses, that criminal's
going to hold him ransom!
I just drew the perfect
card to put you away.
I equip Boulder‐Piercing Spear,
and that's not all.
Brainbaltes, move to the right!
(grunts)
♪
Penetrate,
Counterattack, Soulguard,
and the Move ability, too?
Zanya's looking dazed
and confused out there,
and who can blame him?
He wasn't planning on facing
off against Brainbaltes!
If he doesn't do
something fast, he's doomed!
There's no way
Kurooni can lose now!
Overconfidence
merely invites defeat.
Once should never lose focus
until the fight is over.
A warrior's prepared
for all outcomes.
It is the only guarantee
for certain victory.
Here, look at this.
Oh, no!
When I released
the Darkness Barrier,
they must have been closer
to our radius than I thought!
They may prove useful.
We can use them
to distract his focus.
(yelps)
How did they get in here?!
Gibba?
(nervous tittering)
Oh, no!
What kind of magic is this?
Our of nowhere, two
girls have just appeared
in front of Zanya!
Are they monsters
or is someone playing
a dirty trick on
the Katana fighter?
What's going on out there?
What happened to the days
when Buddyfighters had honor?
Those days are over, gramps.
Baltes charging!
(grunting)
I gotta try and help Z!
Anyone who betrays my trust
is no brother of mine.
I know he didn't really mean it.
We brothers
gotta stick together.
(growling)
Akatsuki?
Looks like you need some help.
♪
Akatsuki, I‐‐
Yeah, yeah, save it for later.
Part of being brothers
is forgiving each other
when we mess up.
Anyway, you've got a fight
to win and a criminal
to take down!
Thanks, bro.
One other thing, Z;
you really gotta get over this.
Girls are actually
pretty cool, you know?
My little brother
giving me advice.
(gasps)
I owe you one.
Go, Z!
It worked like a charm,
we've got him now!
Finish him.
Now I can free my brothers!
It's all over.
If the attack does damage,
Zanya's done for, yo.
Where'd he go, gibba?
You should have come peacefully.
Who said that?
You've fallen
right into my trap.
Although you didn't have
an item card in your hand
to start with, I figured
that you'd use it as soon
as you drew one.
What's going on?
Don't tell me we'll lose!
He played to Danger World's
weakness perfectly.
I pay three gauge to activate
Super Lethal Formation!
Secret Sword, Shooting Star!
Gibba!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Zanya Kisaragi.
Shoulda jumped in
a lot sooner, huh?
Yeah, I couldn't have done it
without you, Akatsuki.
Ah?
Oh, I just realized something.
Why'd you use Nanomachine
Body Replacement so much?
During a fight, even one's
own weakness can become a trap
for the enemy.
Sure, you say that now.
Admit it was just
a little lucky.
I mean, if your opponent
didn't draw an item card,
you'd have been done, yo.
It's just a risk you
wouldn't be willing to take.
Hey, I can bring it
when I need to.
In any case, it was
an excellent fight.
You really saved
the day, Akatsuki!
Well, Z did all the work.
(screaming)
It's not my fault!
It was that dishonest criminal!
Ask him yourself!
Where is he?!
You numbskull, you really
messed up this time, gibba!
But I meant to rescue you!
Yeah, right.
Where's the love, gibba?
You have no idea
what I've been through!
(grunting)
Don't take it out on him!
How dare you, after what
I did for you, gibba!
Zanya Kisaragi,
on the behalf of
the Buddy Police,
we would like to officially
offer you a position
in our ranks as a trainee.
We need you.
Thank you, sir,
it would be an honor.
Hmm.
♪
That's awesome,
way to go, Zanya!
Thanks, Gao.
Welcome to the team.
We are starting a new division.
Beginning today,
you will be known
as the Buddy Police Youth.
The Buddy Police Uth?
Did you say "youth"
as in meaning a young person?
That's exactly right.
I think it has a better
ring to it than trainee.
And I, Count Dawn,
will be your leader.
(growls)
I can't believe
he got this approved
without consulting me.
Don't take this personally, sir.
I'm sure you would
have recruited Zanya
had you seen his fight today.
I've had my eye on him
for a while now, Stella.
His father and I have
been friends for years,
as I'm sure you know.
Hmm.
Do us proud, young recruits,
and always work together!
Huh?
♪
(screams)
He seems unreliable for
a leader, if you ask me.
At least we know how
to get out of trouble.
(laughter)
♪
Huh?
I'm so proud to have
a brother like you.
Congrats.
Thanks.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna
tell you all about
Super Combidragon Brainbaltes.
It's a really powerful
Hundred Demons card
that's created when two
sibling dragons combine.
It's formed by placing
Sibling Dragon Foonbaltes
and Sibling Dragon
Kibaltes in the Soul.
Once joined, they become
a Size Three monster.
That's huge!
It has Soulguard,
Counterattack,
Penetrate, and Move:
a whole lot of
powerful abilities.
I'll have to tell Drum
to start working harder.
(laughs)
♪
Next time,
it's a Buddy Police Youth
Emergency Launch.
But the monster in question
isn't a Hundred Demon,
and it says it has something
important to do, but what?
Next episode...
Join us for a Buddyfight!