(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster
Yamigedo has been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power of
the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them,
and there's only one way we can!
We've gotta Buddyfight!
♪
It's just as Tasuku said it was.
If that's the case,
then I fear that
Gao may be unable
to use Dragon
World decks anymore.
Until it's resolved,
I'm forced to suspend
your Buddy Police
status indefinitely.
♪
This is totally crazy.
I've never felt better!
Tasuku and Count
Dawn worry too much.
♪
Ahh!
(growling)
It's not crazy!
Something's up with you,
and we'd better find out what!
You used Dragon World
when you fought Ikazuchi‐‐
the same fight,
I'm sorry to say,
in which we lost our
dear friend Lord Tenbu.
It's greatly affected you.
According to our
Buddy Police physicians,
this painful loss has left
you emotionally scarred
and in deep despair.
As a result, they explain
that you're subconsciously
rejecting Dragon World.
The heart is very complex.
Even if you think you've
gotten over something,
the wounds don't
always heal as quickly
or as completely as
we tend to believe.
I know this is difficult
for you to grasp,
especially for one so young.
No, they're wrong!
I'm fine‐‐let me prove it!
(gasping)
This is no time to be tough.
The first step to healing
is acceptance, Gao.
If you fail to do that,
you can never move on.
You know all too well
how long it can take
to recover from such a loss
having been faced with
unfathomable tragedy
in your Budding
life once before.
Don't worry, I'll write
more Sun Fighter stories.
Anything for my little bro!
♪
You do not need to rush things.
Before you know it, you'll
be wielding Dragon World
even better than before.
Thanks, Count.
♪
Acceptance is most difficult,
even for someone like me.
It's easy to give
such advice to others,
but should I be preachy
considering that,
after all this time,
I am still unable
to do it myself?
I wonder what you would say if
you were still here, my Buddy.
(birds chirping)
I wonder when you'll be able
to start using Dragon
World cards again.
Hard to say‐‐
nothing I've tried
has been able to
help him at all!
I feel good about this one.
Okay, I'm ready, lay it on me!
♪
I hope this works.
(grunting)
♪
Ahh!
Well, at least we can
rule out another one!
You're the brainiac‐‐
got any ideas?
This is beyond my skill set.
Reversing damage
received in a match
calls for another Buddyfight.
Don't be consumed
by negative thinking,
you've just gotta relax
and have fun out there,
and I'm sure you'll
get your mojo back
and be able to use
your Dragon World deck.
That's all it'll take?
Now who can we find
you to Buddyfight with?
Let me think‐‐what
good fighters do we know
who aren't hung up
on winning or losing?
Hmm.
I think I've got it,
and it's someone who enjoys
having fun Buddyfights!
(birds chirping)
You'd really be
proud of me, Dad.
Any day now, I'm gonna
make my 100th friend!
Come on, Kazane,
we'd better be going!
‐Okay.
‐So, where should we go
‐for lunch?
‐I feel like Italian!
So, how are things
going at school?
It's great‐‐I
really like it there.
(beeping)
Oh, this'll just
take a second, Mom.
Hey, Kuguru!
Yeah, how have you been?
Really?
Gao really wants to have
a Buddyfight with me?
Thanks for coming down, Kazane.
Yeah, no pressure.
You're just saving Gao is all.
I'm glad I could help!
Though I'd like to know
what you're so worried about.
How ill‐mannered!
Well, that would
defeat the purpose!
(groaning)
And actually the
sooner we get started,
‐the better!
‐Okay!
What's that
creepy‐looking thing?
You okay, Gao?
Look at that‐‐something's
hovering up there
and watching us.
Hundred Demons?
One way to find out.
Let's do it.
Buddy Skill: On.
Come back!
♪
Just as I thought.
Why you‐‐what's
the meaning of this?
Explain yourself!
Yeah, why are you sneaking
around and spying on us, huh?
I, uh‐‐it's really
not what it looks like.
I was merely ensuring the safety
of the young Miss
Kazane Fujimiya.
Why would you do that?
Is she in some kind of danger?
I owe you no
explanations, Mr. Mikado.
What's more, if you
value your position,
you must never, ever reveal
my existence to Kazane.
Are we clear?
♪
I warn you, don't
ever defy this order.
♪
And here I thought
things couldn't possibly
‐get any worse for us!
‐Hmm.
It's not like you to
skip out on a Buddyfight
and stress out over
other people's problems.
I know, but I'm curious!
I've gotta know what's
going on with the Count.
You know all too
well of such things
having been faced with
tragedy once before.
It takes time to recover
from a painful loss.
There must be some history
between Count Dawn and Kazane,
and I'm gonna
find out what it is!
Yes, that does seem
a little strange.
Now that you mention it,
I believe today
is the anniversary
of Officer Fujimiya's death.
Wait, "Officer"?
Yes, Daichi Fujimiya.
He was Kazane's father.
‐What?
Got outta town‐‐Kazane's old
man was with the Buddy Police?
So Count Dawn was‐‐
I mean, was he‐‐
That's right, Gao,
a long time ago.
Count Dawn was
Officer Fujimiya's Buddy.
The two of them were
considered the best suited
and most capable team
on the entire force.
But then, four years ago,
on the day of the
terrible disaster...
♪
Hang on, Daichi, we'll be
back at headquarters soon.
Then we can treat your wounds!
I'll save you no matter what.
♪
Not now, I just need
a few more minutes!
If I don't get under cover soon,
my Buddy will...
(grunting)
‐Thank you, Count.
‐Huh?
You're the best Buddy
a stubborn guy like me
could ever ask for.
Daichi, be strong.
Don't talk like that!
Tell my wife I love her
and that she made me the
happiest man in the world.
And tell Kazane that...
(screaming)
Officer Fujimiya was lost
while performing his duties,
and after that day, Count
Dawn left active service.
And, as you observed earlier,
Count Dawn has secretly
watched over the
Fujimiya family ever since.
For some reason, he doesn't
wish to meet young Kazane
or let her know he exists.
What a guy‐‐telling
us to get over Tenbu
when he hasn't even
dealt with this?
And if he wants
to protect Kazane,
why doesn't he just
meet her in person?
♪
Count, I have a
favor to ask you.
Just this once, I was wondering
if you would be part of my deck.
I need your help in my
Buddyfight with Kazane.
So you know.
I see what you're doing.
I wasn't born
yesterday, Mr. Mikado.
You're just like the rest.
Why is everyone so determined
to have me meet with Kazane?
I can only tell you
why I think you should.
Until we accept our past, we
can never move on, never heal.
I'm sure you're just
dying to meet her.
You owe it to your Buddy!
And if you join Gao's deck, you
can see her during the fight!
What you tell her is up to you!
I'm going to surprise Kazane
with her favorite
Cobb salad for dinner.
Huh?
Dawny?
In just a few short minutes,
Gao Mikado and Kazane Fujimiya
will be squaring
off in a Buddyfight
at our very own Aibo
Academy Fighting Stage!
‐Here it is, bro.
‐Thanks, man.
Sorry to ask for
such a big favor.
Don't sweat it‐‐I'm
getting used to you
asking for the impossible.
Come on, you know it's
the deck builder's job
to support the fighter.
Yeah, I guess.
‐Let's do this.
‐Oh, yeah.
Have fun, you two,
and best of luck!
We'd better head
to the Buddy pit.
‐Hey, look.
‐Look at what?
That lady over there,
she looks exactly like Kazane!
Hi, how are you?
Will the fighters
please Luminize?
Emergency Launch, from
the eye of the storm!
Luminize!
Beaming Sunshine Guardians!
A kaleidoscope of
excitement and adventure!
Luminize, Kaleido Labyrinth!
You know what to do!
Say it with me now!
Buddy...
‐Fight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Hero World!
And I'm with Dungeon World.
Hey, Kazane is always
raving about the Buddy pit.
It is really neat!
Yeah, bro.
You'll have a bird's
eye view of her match
from inside this choice perch.
I've never seen you at
one of her fights before.
No, normally I don't
come, but this time Dawny‐‐
I just felt it
was time, you know.
That's it, Gummy Slime!
Attack the fighter!
(squeaking)
End of move.
That's the way!
How unseemly!
Look how happy she is up there!
It warms my heart.
Only Buddyfighting
makes her smile like that.
When I think of
how she used to be,
it's like a dream come true.
‐Huh?
Gao's called out
the Cyber Police Army
with an intimidating
Triple Formation!
Permission to use force, Chief.
You bet!
Attack that Gummy
Slime in the center!
‐10‐4.
‐I cast!
Huh?
Hidden Crossbow!
♪
That spell can
destroy any monster
with 3,000 defense or less!
I've gotta hand
it to you, Kazane,
you are strong!
After her father passed,
it was pretty tough
going for a while.
She wouldn't eat and barely
cracked a smile at anything.
There were days
when she wouldn't even
come out of her room.
Listen to me going on‐‐you kids
don't wanna hear me rambling
all about my crazy problems!
(laughing)
Why is she laughing, bro?
I don't think it's very funny.
Yeah, it's hard to
know how to react.
Dungeons are swarming
with dangerous traps.
Draw‐‐charge and draw!
I pay two gauge and call a size
three monster to the center.
Ready or not!
Here comes Guardian Dragon
of the Shrine, Lumiere!
Most don't last
long in my company!
Check his ability!
Activate Holy Blast!
Lumiere can take out
one of his opponent's
size one or lesser monsters
both when he appears
and also when he's destroyed!
Perfect, now keep going
and attack the fighter!
Fear my holy claw!
And his Double Attack!
End of move.
Lumiere's Double Attack
comes as a shocking surprise!
Down to just four life points,
Gao quickly finds
himself on the ropes.
Whenever you're in trouble
is when a hero arrives
to save the day.
Let's take things up a notch.
Draw!
(yelling)
Charge and draw!
I call Heroic Blader to
the right and left areas!
Blade of Justice, Heroic Blader!
The Judge and Jury,
Heroic Blader!
Here I go.
Time to turn up the heat.
I pay one gauge and transform!
Fiery Inspector,
Prominence Burst!
Look at that‐‐how cool is he?
Then one day, everything
just suddenly changed.
I'd never seen anything like it.
She received a letter
from a certain someone.
Whatever was in it
really hit home with her.
When she finished reading it,
she said the most
surprising thing.
Mom, I know what to do now.
I want to try and
make 100 friends!
Prominence Buster Knuckle!
(yelling)
I'm curious‐‐what exactly
did the letter say?
I don't know‐‐it was a
letter addressed to Kazane
from her father.
Double Attack on the fighter!
Raptor Blade!
(groaning)
But how can that be‐‐
who wrote the letter?
That's just the thing,
it was sent by her
father's Buddy monster.
And now I hear
he's an instructor
‐with the Buddy Police.
‐Your move.
I activate Seventh Omni Earth
Lord, Count Dawn's ability!
I pay one life, and revive him
from the Drop Zone to the left!
The Twilight Returner.
This is an unexpected surprise!
Gao's Buddy Police boss,
the distinguished Count Dawn,
has now joined the fight!
Just what in the
world is going on?
♪
"Dearest Kazie,
Though I'm gone,
I will always be
with you in spirit.
Please continue living in the
cheerful way you always have.
My wish for you is a happy
life surrounded by 100 friends.
Keep smiling, my little girl.
Love you always, Daddy."
Hey, Mister, are you
one of the Omni Lords?
Huh‐‐why yes, I am.
Oh, wow, I get to fight
against an Omni Lord‐‐awesome!
Okay, let's end this.
I'm gonna pay one gauge
and Buddy Call my pal,
Rescue Dragon, Justice Drum
over to the right position!
Justice is served
to crush all evil,
because I, the invincible hero,
Rescue Dragon, Justice Drum
am here to save the day!
♪
Now go attack Dragonblade,
Wielding Sheila Vanna!
Okay!
Justice Break!
And each time I
destroy a monster,
I get to have an extra attack!
Break!
Not done yet‐‐break!
Farewell!
Oh, no, not Blade!
Justice Ram Bunker!
(crying)
Some info on Gao's
Prominence Burst,
it gains one critical when
a hero attribute monster
beats an opponent's monster.
As it stands right now,
his critical is at five!
Kazane may as well
say her goodbyes now!
♪
Is that even possible?
Prominence Burst!
Okay, Boss, I'm
leaving the rest to you!
Understood.
Might be my adrenaline talking,
but try and cut
Gao some slack, huh?
I will.
And I'll start by
giving him the victory.
Deela Column!
♪
Huh‐‐is this some
kind of attack?
Oh, it feels so warm!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Yeah, just an everyday hero.
(cheering)
That was fun, huh?
It was a total blast!
Thanks for doing this, Kazane.
Hey, Mr. Omni Lord!
What is it?
Well, I was hoping
that we could be friends!
Friends with me?
Sure‐‐please say yes!
If you do, I'll have
exactly 100 friends!
Come on, what do you say?
(whimpering)
Yes, of course.
If you think me worthy,
I would be very honored indeed
to become your 100th friend.
All right, thank you!
This is most unladylike!
No, I'm the one who should
be thanking you, my dear.
In all my sadness,
I never thought this
day would ever come.
‐Kazane!
‐Mom?
I didn't know you were here!
Did you catch my fight?
I sure did!
I really enjoyed it!
I'm so proud of you, honey.
Buddyfight is as
good as I said, right?
And the best part is
that you can make friends
with just about anyone!
Sure seems that way.
Do you think that
maybe I could do it?
Sure, I'll teach you
everything I know!
Come on, let's hurry home.
Oh, wait‐‐thanks, you guys!
See ya later!
You too, Mr. Omni Lord!
♪
I was afraid for so long!
It's strange how
things finally work out.
My biggest fear of
meeting her in person
was that one day she might
get around to asking me
exactly what
happened to her father.
And after working so
hard to get it back,
I didn't want to be
the reason why she lost
that beautiful
smile of hers again.
But she is much
stronger than I thought.
She has surpassed my
expectations in every way
and has moved on with
her life quite admirably.
I am sure that her father
would be very pleased.
I don't need to be
afraid any longer.
I can finally accept
the way things are.
It feels so strange,
like a weight has been
lifted from my heart.
I know it's difficult, Gao,
but you need to move on as well.
You're right.
♪
Pretty emotional day, huh, kid?
Sure was, but I
learned a lot, too.
I promise I'll be able to
use a Dragon deck again!
I believe you.
If Kazane and Count Dawn
can do it, so can I.
No matter how painful the past,
you can always
rise to overcome it.
You did it‐‐you picked 'em up!
You see‐‐I'm all better now.
I never doubted
you for a second.
Thanks for the
support, pal, you rock!
(yelling)
Are you okay?
But I thought...
Why‐‐why is this
happening to me?
What does this mean?
Will I ever be able to
use my Dragon deck again?
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna
teach you all about
the monster card
Captain Answer Final Mode.
‐Wicked!
‐By releasing all
of its hidden power,
it's a very useful card.
You guess whether the top card
is a monster or a spell.
If you're right, he
can destroy one monster,
and he can also
do a Double Attack.
The amazing Captain Answer!
Victory hinges on his ability.
Used correctly, it
gives the final answer.
Speaking of answers, give
me number 15 on the quiz?
♪
Next time, Jack's in trouble,
and Suzaku Kenran blackmails
Tasuku to throw a Buddyfight
in order to spare Jack's life!
What will Tasuku do?
Next episode, Farewell
Star Guardian Jackknife!
Join us for a Buddyfight!