Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies
with humans.
But now a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the 100 Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy skill on!
I'm beat.
(yawning)
(alarm blaring)
Emergency, there's an
illegal monster at Castle!
Report there right away.
♪
Meow, meow, meow!
‐Huh?
I can't believe this
is happening to me!
Meow!
‐"Meow?"
I don't understand
why I keep losing.
I'll accept your
challenge now!
No way, I lost
another game, meow!
You're up next.
At this rate,
I'll never win, meow!
Next.
♪
(groans)
I lost again, meow.
(groaning)
This for real?
That's the illegal monster
you called about?
Yeah, he's been
here a while
and no one will admit
to being his buddy.
Well, would you, if
you had a buddy like that?
I don't know.
Hey, you, I'm with
the Buddy Police
and you're
coming with me!
Police?
You're too slow for me!
I told you to stop!
Don't mess with us, pal!
(breathing heavily)
(yells)
He's the cutest thing!
(panting)
Here kitty, kitty, kitty.
♪
(moaning)
Meow!
(grunting)
Thanks, Kuguru,
I'll take it from here.
No problem,
glad I could help.
Do you actually carry that
thing around in your purse?
Why not?
I just happen
to love kitties.
I am not a cat, meow!
You're in the presence
of none other than
the great Cait Sith in Boots
from Legend World!
Whiskers, fluffy tail?
You look exactly
like a cat to me.
Why does nobody believe me?
I am not a cat!
Hey, you're a
buddy monster, right?
Of course, I was
losing so much
because I was fighting
against chumps
who didn't even have
their own buddy monster.
That settles it!
You two front and center for
a Buddyfight on the double.
I think he's been overdoing
it on the catnip.
You think?
We can use that
stage right over there.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm fighting
for Hero World!
And I'm fighting
for Legend World.
So, the monster
himself is the fighter?
At least,
Death Shido's not here
making us fight in
that Darkness Barrier.
Charge and draw.
My first move is to buddy
call Cait Sith in Boots
to the center, meow.
Meow, meow.
Go ahead, attack
the fighter!
Meow!
(grunting)
End of move.
I know it's just the game's
opening move and all, bro,
but he only
caused one damage.
Isn't he adorable?
I buddy call Buddy Police
Decker Drum to the center.
Lock and load.
(grunting)
And I activate
Decker Drum's ability.
Now, go take out the
Cait Sith in the center.
Here kitty, kitty.
I move, yeah, and also dodge
the Cait Sith in the center
to the right position.
Huh?
Springing into action.
(grunting)
I don't understand.
What did I do wrong?
First of all, fluffy, you
don't have the move ability,
and even if you did,
you couldn't use it
to avoid my ability
to destroy a monster.
The little runt doesn't even
know how to play the game, bro.
Give him a break.
‐He's so cute!
‐Huh?
You asked for it.
I call Knights of the Round
Table, Percival to the right
and Iron Dragon
Tarasque to the left.
Meow!
Are you for real?
Meow?
Percival and Tarasque
are both Size Two monsters.
You can't call them
at the same time.
Oh, well,
I didn't know that.
This is a joke.
He doesn't even
know how size works.
I want to take him home.
Get a grip.
I lost again, meow!
Check it out, Drum,
he lost the fight,
but he's not
turning back into a card.
He's just a plain
old illegal monster.
Spill it, feline.
Why'd you come
to Earth anyway?
Well, you see,
I wanted to...
Whoa, what's
that thing over there?
Does kitty want a
little brushy‐brush?
(contented purring)
(yells)
You're making
my fur staticky!
Relax, fuzz ball.
I hear it's all the rage
back in Legend World
where you're going.
No, I don't want to!
I can't go yet!
Please, don't
send me back!
You don't understand
the reason I'm here.
There's something I must do
in this world first, meow!
What do you mean
"something you have to do"?
Don't leave me hanging.
If you didn't know,
we of the Cait Sith clan
are responsible for
making the weapons, armor,
and shields for all the monsters
in Legend World, meow.
The thing is...
♪
(metal clinking)
I can't take it anymore!
If I have to make
one more sword or hat
or hammer out one more
helmet, I'll lose it!
I'm out of here.
I want to go have
some fun for a change!
Wait, so you
only came here
because you wanted to have
some fun Buddyfighting?
Precisely, meow.
‐Hmm.
(growling)
"Something
you must do?"
Give me a break!
Don't try
and trick us.
You got sick of your job
and decided to run away.
What's worse is you don't even
know the rules of the game.
No, that's not true.
I understand how
to play, meow.
My opponent starts
with 10 life
and if I reduce
them to zero, I win!
Be honest, Cait Sith,
and it's okay if you don't,
but do you know about
power, defense and size?
(groans)
I guess there's a lot more to
the game than you thought, huh?
Let's just
send him back!
Give him a
chance, Drum.
I promise to teach
you all about the game
if you show
me your card.
What do you say?
♪
You've got a deal.
It's in here.
Okay, this red number
on the left is your power
and the blue one's
your defense.
Wow, 2,000 power!
I'm amazing!
Well, 2,000 isn't
actually that high.
Drum has 5,000
power in defense.
Meow?
This number in the
middle is your critical,
and the one in the upper
left corner, your size.
So, I have a critical
of one and my size is zero?
I know I haven't
grasped the rules yet,
but I sound like
a pretty weak card.
Yeah, you're about as
feeble as they come, cat.
Meow!
Guess that explains
why I keep losing.
♪
(crying)
Hey?
So what if you're
weaker than dirt.
It doesn't mean
you can't win!
It's not all
about power.
Isn't that right, Baku?
Huh? Oh yeah, sure.
It's like
Drum says, bro.
Like every monster,
you have a special role
that only you can
play in the game,
and if you can
do your job well‐‐
Then I can win, meow?
Will you teach me?
Please, please
tell me what my role is!
Do you think you could throw
a deck together for him?
I guess, but
I'll need some time.
What do you say?
Can we hold off on sending
this guy back a while?
(grunts)
Okay, but not
for too long.
That's the spirit, kid!
Alright, then I guess
I'd better get on it.
Looks like you're gonna
have some fun after all.
Thank you, you guys
are the greatest, meow!
♪
Awaken, power of Darkness!
Power of evil!
Power of the 100 Demons!
I'm none other than
Systemic Dagger Black Edge!
(roars)
Shido, do I need
to remind you
what I'll do to you
if you fail me again?
I couldn't forget that,
Master, but don't worry.
Everything's under
control this time.
I've prepared the
greatest plan in history
with zero chance
for error.
(whimpers)
Now, what,
I don't have a plan.
But I couldn't tell Master
that or he'd zap me again.
You'll never
learn, will you?
Wait, you can't
leave me alone with this!
Just watch me.
Oh, come on!
Please, you have to help me
think up a terrific plan
that will get
Master his card.
I'm really starting to
think that all this zapping
is having
long term effects.
I don't think so.
But I can't come up
with a plan on my own.
I beg you,
don't do this to me!
Oh, alright.
Come out, Gallows.
What is it?
Help him think of
a plan to get Tenbu.
Not this again.
(screams)
Here, we're
all finished.
Wow, I don't
believe it!
My first deck made by
a deck builder, meow.
(laughing)
Hey, where do you
think you're going?
Get back here!
(yowls)
‐Huh?
‐Death Shido?
(grunting)
Now that I've
found you again,
I challenge you to another fight
with Lord Tenbu to the winner.
I never refuse a challenge.
But actually,
Grandpa Tenbu is...
Thank you for helping me
with those heat compressors
on my sore back.
Aching muscles are just one of
the side effects of old age.
What, so you mean you don't even
have Tenbu with you right now?
‐Nope.
‐So even if I beat him,
I won't get Tenbu.
In that case, it's
pointless to fight him now.
I'll let you
off easy today,
but prepare yourself
for our next fight.
I'll be ready.
Not so fast!
♪
Uh, and who are you?
If you really came here
looking for someone to fight,
then why leave?
Why not fight me, meow?
No thanks, I don't
mean to be rude,
but I have better things to do
than waste my valuable time
on a small fry like you.
Besides, you don't
even have a fighter.
His fighter is right here.
What are you
talking about, Drum?
Oh, what's the
big deal, kid?
Help the little guy
figure out his purpose.
I don't know, man.
Just this once!
Are you the mighty
Sun Fighter or aren't you?
♪
Okay, I'll do it.
This'll be your first,
but I'm looking forward
to it all the same.
Thanks for agreeing
to do this with me, meow.
You realize that I haven't even
agreed to fight you yet, right?
Quit your bellyaching!
Get off of me!
What are you doing?
This thing opens the
Darkness Barrier, right?
No, don't!
If you mess
around with that,
I'm going to get
in big trouble.
♪
(roaring)
Now that I have no choice,
I'll get them good.
Get out here
Systemic Dagger Black Edge.
You asked for it.
You phonies are
going to lose.
Whenever and wherever
there's a Buddyfight,
Paraku Nanana
will be there!
Warp successful,
yet again.
Alright, let's take
down Death Shido again.
To become stronger
than I was yesterday,
I will overcome
any obstacle!
Luminize!
The legend of
Fairy Blade!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path.
Witness their
awesome power.
Luminize!
Hundred Dragon!
Now, Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Legend World!
And I'm fighting
for Dragon World.
I've never seen Gao
use Legend World before.
Yeah, and he's not using
Drum as his buddy, yo.
Using a different buddy and
fighting for a different world,
Gao is just
full of surprises.
He has the first move.
I buddy call
Cait Sith to the center!
Meow!
Gao chooses to buddy call
right out of the gate.
Go get 'em,
attack the fighter!
(meowing)
End of move.
I barely even felt that.
Now, it's my turn.
Your move.
I draw.
Charge and draw.
I equip Dragonblade
Dragofearless.
I call Extreme Sword
Dragon to the right,
and I call Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the left.
Thousand Rapier,
attack Cait Sith.
Meow!
Cait Sith is destroyed
and as a result,
the two top cards from Gao's
deck are sent to the drop zone.
Next, I'll send an Extreme Sword
Dragon to attack the fighter.
And I cast
The Holy Grail spell.
I had a feeling
you'd do that.
(gasps)
Taste my Dragofearless!
(groans)
End of move.
I'm sure Gao will find a
way to use Sith's abilities.
I call Cait Sith
to the center once more.
It's like I never left.
I call Carved Stallion of
Dreams, Dalahast to the left.
(neighing)
What did you do?
Whenever Dreams
Dalahast is called,
the player must
put three cards
from the top of their
deck into the drop zone.
Now, I'll pay
one gauge and call
Dashing in the Moonlight,
Red Cap to the right area.
From this moment on,
the stage is mine.
Dalahast attack
Death Shido.
Okay, Red Cap, now you.
I cast Dragonic Formation!
And I move Extreme Sword
Dragon to the center.
You'll remember the
day you got in my way.
Evil Dispelling
Blade Silver Exorcist!
Cait Sith, go
attack Death Shido!
(meowing)
No, kitty!
That's a bad kitty!
End of move.
I did it!
Your move.
Enjoy yourself while you
still can, fluff ball.
I'm going to destroy
you soon enough.
I draw.
Charge and draw.
I pay one gauge
and buddy call
Systemic Dagger Black Edge
to the right area.
(grunting)
You're close
to the edge.
With a buddy gift,
he regains one life point.
Let's use the Tako scope
to check out the stats
on Death Shido's monster.
Systemic Dagger
Black Edge.
Armordragon
attribute: Size One.
Power and defense
are both 3,000.
A critical of two.
He has one ability,
but no life link.
Now I call Systemic Dagger
to the center!
I don't need
any help from you.
(grunting, roaring)
He destroyed
his own monster.
By destroying a Systemic
Dagger Dragon on the field,
Black Edge is free to
unleash his true power,
but before that Thousand,
send that annoying cat
over there to the pound.
‐Impero Veritas!
‐Oh, not again!
Once again, the top
two cards from Gao's deck
are sent to
the drop zone.
We meet again, Gao!
(yells)
Black Edge,
the time has come
to show these numb
skulls your true power!
I am the greatest.
All others pale
in comparison to me!
Black Dance Macabre!
(shouts)
What's happening
down there?
My Tako scope show that Black
Edge has a critical of two.
Normally he does,
but when any card
with Systemic in the name
is sent to the drop zone,
Black Edge gains one extra
critical on that turn,
so his two
becomes a three.
Wow, that's a lot!
That's not all.
When that happens,
my monster also gets
the double attack ability.
Things aren't looking
good for Gao.
If he takes this hit,
he'll drop to one life point.
Red Cap, I owe you one.
I will take
this attack for you.
What's this?
Thanks to Red Cap's ability,
Gao has survived
the double attack.
By sending Red Cap
to the drop zone,
Gao neutralized
his opponent's attack.
A smart play.
Yeah, but he spent
the entire fight
hanging on
the ropes, yo.
This isn't the Gao
I've come to know.
I call Red Cap
to the center!
See?
I told you this
was my stage.
I cast Death Summoning
Tears of the Banshee.
Huh?
That's a very useful spell
that destroys one item
on the field, but...
It can only be
used when a player
has at least six fairy attribute
cards in their drop zone.
Wait, that's it!
Then explain
it to me, yo.
Death Shido sacrificed
Dagger once again
to boost
Black Edge's ability,
and then he called
Jamadhar Dragon
and destroyed Red Cap.
♪
Don't let up now,
Black Edge!
Attack the fighter!
Black Dance Macabre!
(screams)
Gao has only
one life left.
He's like a candle
in the wind.
My double attack
will finish you.
I cast the
Holy Grail spell.
Quick thinking by Gao
to use a counter spell.
Talk about surviving
by the skin of your teeth.
Why does this keep
happening to me?
‐Your move.
‐My turn.
I draw!
Charge and draw.
Ha.
I call Cait Sith in Boots
to the right position.
Like they say,
third time's the charm!
I can't believe you keep
using that wimpy card.
I think this game
is mine this time.
I'm going to equip
Famous Sword, Hrunting.
This is where the
battle really starts.
You're pulling out
the Gao Formation
at this point
in the game?
It's too little too late.
If you haven't noticed, I
have seven life points left.
He drew it, didn't he?
Oh, yeah.
Seems the little guy's
stronger than I thought.
His power, defense and
critical are fairly low values,
but that doesn't mean
he can't become more, bro.
♪
Like every monster,
you have a special role
that only you
can play in a game.
Teach me.
Now, I know what
my special role is.
It's time for the
Gift from the Marquis!
Huh?
A gift from
the mar‐‐what?
When there are over
10 fairy attribute cards
in the drop zone,
Cait Sith gains
a unique ability.
Now, pay attention.
He's about to
show it to you.
And because
they believed in me,
I found my purpose
in this game.
Here it is, Gao!
Alright!
♪
How did your
sword get so huge?
Dalahast, attack the Jamadhar
in the center position!
Death Shido's center
is now wide open.
Uh‐oh.
This is
Cait Sith's strength.
Come again?
He increases an item's
critical by three points.
No way, how can
that be fair?
Famous Sword, Hrunting!
Why me?
Gao's whole fight was
leading up to this trap.
Totally sweet!
This is for
calling me annoying!
‐Meow!
‐Ow!
Meow!
(screams)
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Alright.
Another 100 Demon
off the streets.
Huh?
You agreed
to fight knowing
that you wouldn't
get Tenbu if you won,
and you lost
a 100 Demons card?
You swore to me
that you wouldn't fail!
That you had the
greatest plan in history!
(screaming)
I know, but this time
it was beyond my control!
(Cait Sith sighs)
So, was your first
real Buddyfight
all you thought it'd be?
Boy, was it ever!
I've decided that
from now on,
you're gonna
be my buddy, Gao!
After all
I've done for you?
What do you mean?
I don't
have a buddy,
so what's
the problem?
‐You don't wanna?
‐That's not it.
You came to this world
without getting permission,
and you have
to go back.
You can't become buddies
with me or anyone else.
Meow?
The thing you have to do
is go back to Legend World,
and one day, someone will
draw your buddy rare card,
then they will
be your buddy.
Someone, well,
who will it be?
And when, meow, huh?
If you're lucky,
it'll happen pretty soon.
Lucky?
So it's all about
random chance?
Well, not exactly.
Luck only comes to those
who are prepared for it.
Some say we
create our own luck.
‐Isn't that right?
‐Yeah.
I need to be prepared?
But what do
I have to do?
You just have to
keep living your life
and work hard everyday.
If you do that, eventually
you're bound to catch a break.
But that could
take a long time.
(gasps)
This means you can't
run away from your job
and responsibilities anymore.
Is that why you did all this and
helped me so I'd learn that?
Not at all.
That part's
just a bonus.
Thank you for
everything, meow.
(giggling)
(sighs)
I'd better get home and
start working hard.
I'll see you guys
when I get my buddy!
So long, meow!
Hey, pal, there's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Hmm?
I'm just curious why
you decided to be
so kind to Cait Sith.
Well, I can
relate to the guy.
I mean, there
were tons of times
I got sick of
training every day
and ran away
from home too.
So, you're saying
that he reminded you
of your younger self?
Don't even go there.
But thanks to having a
father who set me straight
and helped me understand the
right way of doing things,
like working hard and
continuing my training,
I was able to meet
a great buddy like Gao.
Cait Sith, I'm sure you'll
meet a terrific buddy as well.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna teach you
about the Legend World card,
‐Cait Sith in Boots.
‐Cool!
It's a monster card that when
used under the right conditions
can unleash amazing power.
It may look weak, but
if you have ten or more
fairy attribute cards
in the drop zone,
it will increase
the critical of any item
you've equipped by three.
That's amazing!
So, basically, with
Cait Sith's ability,
any item can become as
powerful as an impact.
Let's add it to our
decks ASAP, meow!
Meow.
♪
Next time, Baku and
Kuguru are possessed
by a 100 Demons monster named
Dekalfar Demon Swordsman, Heim.
He takes them hostage and
demands Tenbu in ransom.
Next episode, "The Demon
Swordsman Draws Closer!
Tenbu Abducted!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!