Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters
from other worlds to Earth
to become Buddies
with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters
known as the Hundred Demons
have come here illegally
and plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
Emergency Launch.
Buddy Skill on!
♪
What?
You can't really
be hungry already.
Okay, then give me more,
more of your glorious power.
With the Hundred Demons
under my control,
I'll devour this entire world
and its pathetic
future along with it.
♪
(sinister chuckling)
Oh, great Yamigedo,
leave it to me.
So as not to alarm people,
we've asked Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu
to take on a mini form.
It's okay, you're safe
with us at the Sky Tower.
Just close your eyes,
try to relax,
and think about
what it was
you wanted to warn us about.
Hmm, okay.
Can you remember
any of the details?
I don't know,
it's all so hazy.
Hmm.
We're stimulating
localized areas
of his reptile brain
to try and help him
recover his long‐term memory.
But so far, it's
proving unsuccessful.
You spoke of an overwhelming
threat to our planet.
Do you remember?
No, sorry.
I can't recall anything.
How did that lightning guy take
Grandpa Tenbu's memories anyway?
Good question.
We're using all of our resources
to find his whereabouts
but as of yet,
we have no leads
and we still don't
know what happened
to those Hundred monsters
that entered
the Earth illegally.
Ah, if only I could
recover my memory.
Until I do,
I'll be no help at all.
I wish there was
more I could do.
Don't worry, maybe it'll
come back to you at some point.
At least you tried your best.
‐Hi, Grandpa Tenbu.
‐Do you remember us?
Just a minute, so do you give me
medical clearance for card play?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, I could kiss you.
I kinda feel sorry
for the old guy.
Maybe we could help
him out, ya know?
Now listen here, you two.
Since we are unable
to access my memories,
at least let me feel useful
by contributing to
the cause somehow.
I insist you use me
in your deck, Gao.
Huh?
That's so awesome,
I'd totally be honored!
Huh, look at the time.
Gao, you don't wanna be
late for school now.
(gasps)
Not again!
Teacher's gonna kill me!
♪
Oh no!
This is not good.
First class has started already.
Hey, you up there!
The bell rang five minutes ago!
I'm sorry, sir,
but I've got a really good
reason for being late.
You know you're supposed to
enter through the front gate.
Flying is a violation
of school rules!
But I do it all the time!
Huh?
Everybody knows that, mister.
Keep being late and you might
lose your training status.
(whimpers)
You know the agreement.
You can only be in the
Buddy Police trainee program
if it doesn't
interfere with school.
Keep breaking the
rules or being late
and it'll all be over.
‐Okay.
‐Uh, actually,
now that I think about it,
Commander I left
specific instructions
if such a thing were to happen.
Yeah, and what were they?
That if you missed a lesson
or were late due to official
Buddy Police business,
you made up the
time after school.
How's that sound to ya?
Great.
(groans)
Man, this stinks!
What's the matter,
lose your crayons?
Huh?
Good afternoon, Buddy Police
Youth Trainee, Gao Mikado.
I'm sure you recognize her.
Sofia Sakharov
has returned
‐to be our vice president.
‐Da.
Turn around and go back
the way you came.
We come in peace,
I assure you.
We just have a
question, that's all.
I was wondering about
that monster, Tenbu,
you fought at the Sky Tower.
Do you happen to
know where he is now?
Even if we did,
why would we tell you?
‐Listen here, you little‐‐
‐Shido.
(grunts)
Any true Buddyfighter
would be very interested,
don't you think?
Sounds a little
suspicious to me, kid.
Nah, I think it's okay.
Actually, I've got
Grandpa Tenbu in my deck.
That's great.
Enjoy the rest
of your day, guys.
Hm.
What was that all about?
I don't know.
I never expected
Gao to have him.
It's gonna make things
more difficult.
‐Shido, wait.
‐You have a plan?
No, he wants us.
(exclaims)
(yells)
(gargling)
Is it too much to ask
for a little warning
when you do that?
Still a little wet behind
the ears, Sh‐Sh‐Shido?
Zip it or I'll end
our Buddy Pact.
Wait for me, Sofia!
(snarling, chewing)
♪
I trust you bring good news
about where Tenbu is hiding.
Yes, Gao Mikado has him.
So he says.
Well, what would you
like us to do now?
Yeah, what sh‐sh‐should we do?
The three of you
will be working for me.
And I want you to use this.
♪
Awaken!
Power of Darkness!
Power of Evil!
Power of the Hundred Demons!
Ice Prison Emperor, Cocytus
Greed at your service.
What's yours is mine
and what's mine is mine.
As for everything else,
it now belongs to us.
Yes, if you say so.
Snatch Tenbu out from
under Gao Mikado's nose.
I can't get that
flavor out of my mind.
I just have to taste it again.
Now, go at once!
♪
(chuckling)
You boorish humans
will be dancing on a string
for now you are one of
the Hundred Demons' puppets.
(hisses)
♪
Yes, I understand.
What's mine is mine.
But everything else
now belongs to us.
Listen to this.
Armordragon.
Power: 6,000,
Defense: 6,000,
and a Critical of 3.
Wow!
This Fifth Omni Dragon
Lord, Tenbu rocks.
Sure does, I want him in my
Crimson Fist dragon deck.
Think you can do it?
Funny that you should ask, bro.
All I've thought about
since I first saw it
was finding a way
that I'd be able
to squeeze him into your deck.
That's why you're the best.
I'm counting on you.
Huh?
'Kay, Drum, class
is starting up.
Back in your card.
Yeah, yeah, I know the drill.
It's time for my nap anyway.
Huh?
(chatter)
What's goin' on down there?
Hey, Gao, do you happen
to know where your deck is?
Of course.
I've got it right here.
Well, that's good,
at least for you.
Tell us what's
going on, you guys.
Everyone who left a deck
in their desk during lunch
came back to find that
it had been stolen.
You gotta be kidding!
I always make it a habit
of keeping my deck with me
so I avoided being one
of the unlucky victims.
Not me, yo!
Mine was lifted
and A‐Dawg along with it.
Stealing one deck's
unforgiveable,
let alone a bunch of 'em!
Don't worry about
a thing, you guys.
As a Buddy Police Youth Officer,
I will find the thief.
You can't just go
around accusing people
without evidence.
First I want all of you
to go do a thorough search
for your decks.
Meanwhile, I'll
check whether or not
there have been any victims
at the junior high.
But Mr. Neginoyama...
What's the matter, Maihama?
Huh?
Niitani hasn't shown up.
I know he's at school today
and he'd never miss
a Buddyfight lesson.
Maybe he went to report
his deck missing.
I guess that's possible.
But I'm going to look for him.
(panting)
Huh?
That's weird.
How did all these
flowers get frozen?
That's cold!
Huh?
(devious chuckling)
‐Niitani!
‐Huh?
Where did you get
all those decks?
Wait, don't tell me
you're the one
who stole them all!
All of these decks
belong to us now!
(exclaiming)
(whimpers)
Huh?
Are you okay?
No.
All of these decks
belong to us now!
Niitani?
So then he's the thief.
Want 'em, come get 'em!
Greetings, my name is Ice
Prison Emperor, Cocytus Greed.
All of your Buddyfight
decks are now my decks
and so is everything else.
You possess nothing now.
♪
Gao reporting.
We just had an illegal
monster here at Aibo Academy.
Awaiting orders, sir.
‐At your school?
‐Go after him!
And pursue with caution.
He's fast.
We can't let him get away.
It's time for Buddy Police
Emergency Launch!
Decker Road Open!
♪
Decker Drum's on patrol.
I haven't seen that before.
You mean Drum's a Buddy
Police officer too, yo?
He sure is.
Just one of the new
powers he picked up
during his training
in Hero World.
♪
Buddy Skill on.
Let's show this guy
some Earth justice!
Time to go to work!
♪
‐There he is.
‐Leave it to me.
Gives me a chance to try
out one of Decker Drum's
Seven Secrets.
Decker Handcuffs!
♪
(grunts)
What?!
You didn't really think
you'd get away that easily.
You fools!
You're out of your league!
Agree to return all
those decks right now!
Out of the question!
I told you,
they belong to me now!
For an illegal monster,
you're not too bright, are you?
So much for being discreet.
What do you want
to do, Sh‐Sh‐Sh‐Shids?
I think I have
something that can help.
Master Ikazuchi gave
me this before we left.
The Black Skull.
Darkness Barrier,
enshroud and confuse!
♪
Uh‐oh.
‐What is this place?
‐I don't know,
but I'm totally creeped out.
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana
will be there!
♪
Warp successful!
A dedicated commentator will
even travel to other worlds
to give a play‐by‐play.
Uh, so where are we?
Any ideas?
We were kinda gonna
ask you the same thing.
Take it away, Shids.
It's your sh‐sh‐sh‐show.
We have to fight Gao here
in this Darkness Barrier
and take Tenbu away from him.
'Kay, and who's going
to challenge him?
Oh, well, uh...
For now, I think it's
best if you two fight,
with Cocytus Greed
as your Buddy.
Death Ruler, Gallows,
I order you to possess Shido.
Wait a sec!
(yelling)
♪
(whimpering)
(laughing)
If you want to see
the light of day again,
you'll have to defeat me!
Whatever.
Just who are you anyway?
Huh?
Oh, I'm not‐‐nobody‐‐
what's my name?
Just relax.
Tell him your name
is Death Shido.
Hey, that's
actually pretty good.
♪
I am known as Death Shido.
I'm the greatest Buddyfighter
in the history of the world!
And when I win,
I'm taking
that Fifth Omni Dragon Lord,
Tenbu card from your deck.
So that's what
this is all about.
Yeah, I wonder what they
want with Gramps Tenbu.
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path.
Witness their awesome power.
Luminize!
Hundred Ancient Warriors!
I don't care how
powerful they are,
there's no way
you're beating me
or taking any of my cards.
Drum, I'm gonna go
with Dragon World.
We couldn't have asked
for a better match
to break in our new deck
with Gramps Tenbu, huh?
You can say that again.
♪
Sculpting my body
with red‐hot flames,
carving out a new path
with my own two fists.
Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon
reporting for duty!
Burning like an inferno
with limitless spirit.
Luminize!
Crimson Dragon Fist.
On your marks,
get set, Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
I'm with Dragon World.
I fight for Ancient World.
The first move goes
to Gao Mikado.
Charge and draw!
♪
I call Crimson Battler,
Extreme Blow Dragon
to the center position.
♪
Now let's make this
a clean fight, all right?
Go attack Death Shido!
This is the part I hate.
Here's my Crimson Flurry!
(yelling)
♪
End of move.
We've lost Gao's signal.
There's no sign of him
anywhere in the world.
Look at this!
Gao's engaged in a Buddyfight
and it's being
broadcast live.
What; Put it
on the main screen.
It's Death Shido's
turn to attack.
He's called Demonic Fairy
Dragon, Sorciere,
Blade Dragon Emperor,
Vorpal Spartar,
and Island Dragon of
the Origin, Little Land Mu.
The three of them have
taken out Extreme Blow.
That announcer sounds
like Paruko Nanana.
How's she in an
unknown dimension?
She must have used
a special ability
of her Buddy,
Martian UFO, Takosuke
to be able to do this.
Exactly who is this
Death Shido guy?
I don't know, but his voice
sure does sound familiar.
What do you mean?
Like he's some kind
of friend of yours, yo?
No, of course not.
There's no way I'd be
friends with anybody
crazy enough to be doing this.
But I'm positive that
I know that voice.
I call Break Shoulder
Dragon to the left!
Most battles are won before
the first attack is made.
And I Buddy Call
my partner,
Crimson Battler, Drum
Bunker Dragon to the right!
Let me at this
mask‐wearing weirdo!
(grunting)
♪
Let's do this!
It doesn't matter how
many monsters you line up
that are top heavy in Critical.
With a Defense as low as yours,
you don't stand a chance.
I equip Crimson Fist,
Dragoblaze!
Okay, Drum, attack the Vorpal
Spartar in the center.
Get ready for Crimson time!
I cast Dragon Flame Cascade!
That's not good,
I've heard of that spell.
It says it's a counter spell
that destroys all monsters
with less than 2,000
Power or Defense.
Talk about cramping Gao's
style, you know what I'm saying?
(yelling)
♪
Oh, that's the ticket!
Now I'm feeling feisty.
I had no idea he was strong
enough to survive that!
♪
Penetrate!
You're kidding me!
♪
Now to put the
icing on the cake.
I'm not just gonna stand
here and do nothing.
♪
I cast Dragon Prudent!
(yells)
Incredibly, he's
blocked Gao's attack
with a timely and
powerful counter spell.
Death Shido has cast
Dragon Emperor Legend
and in doing so
has increased his gauge,
the number of cards
in his hand,
and his life points.
Now show him the power
of the Hundred Demons.
I Buddy Call Ice Prison
Emperor, Cocytus Greed
to the center!
What's yours is mine,
including your cards!
Thanks to the Buddy gift,
he regains one point.
If you're like me,
you're wondering
what kind of monster
Death Shido's Buddy is.
I think this is a situation
that calls for
my Takosuke Hyper Scope,
or Tako Scope for short.
Let's put it to work.
Now locking on to Ice Prison
Emperor, Cocytus Greed.
♪
Dragon Lord
attribute, Size 2.
Power is 4,000,
Defense also 4,000,
a Critical of 2,
and he has two abilities
and Lifelink 1.
When I am called
into the field,
one of your gauge
will become my gauge.
♪
That's kind of extreme.
Like candy from a baby.
Don't cry.
Now witness how my recent
boost in gauge will be spent.
(chuckling)
I activate Cocytus
Greed's ability!
With Blizzarding
Gale Force Winds!
(exclaims)
♪
I'll freeze you like
the dark side of the moon,
foolish monster.
All those who dare to defy me
will be frozen solid!
All I have to do
is pay three gauge
and Ice Prison Emperor,
Cocytus Greed
can destroy one card on my
opponent's playing field.
(yelling)
Drum!
You've got bigger things
to be worrying about
than the welfare
of your Buddy.
Sorciere
and Little Land Mu
are attacking Gao.
(groaning)
Cocytus Greed, go
finish off the fighter!
As promised, your life
will now be mine!
Oh no, it looks like
curtains for Trainee Mikado.
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
He didn't!
As we've come to expect,
he had a last‐minute
Dragon Shield in his hand.
End of move.
I'm in pretty good shape.
With a monster in the center
and six life points,
easy peasy lemon squeezy!
I don't know about that, pal.
I'd say this fight's
just getting started.
I draw!
Charge and draw!
♪
It's time for you
to take the stage, Grandpa!
I call to the right
Fifth Omni Dragon Lord, Tenbu!
Yes, feast your eyes on this!
When I enter the field,
beware, young man.
All of your monsters
will be destroyed.
What?
♪
Howling Fire!
(grunting)
This isn't right.
My life is my own
and yours is mine as well!
Why did I let Sofia talk me
into this in the first place?
♪
Thanks to Cocytus
Greed's Lifelink,
Death Shido only suffered
one damage point.
I just wanted to apologize
for my earlier behavior.
Now watch me as I save the day!
I cast Dragon Prudent!
♪
Don't underestimate me!
Crimson Fist, Dragoblaze!
But I thought your turn
was already over,
what am I missing?
It's far from over.
I cast Dragonic Charge.
He's increasing his gauge
now, then that means...
♪
Final phase.
Don't say that.
Why are you saying that?
I cast!
♪
Impact!
Gigantic Crusher!!
Why me?
♪
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
Thank you.
It's all in the name of justice.
Huh?
That was kinda weird, huh?
At least the deck works well.
Huh?
‐Hey, isn't that...
‐Huh.
It's that Cocytus Greed
guy we just fought.
And the stolen
decks are here too.
But where's the
Death Shido guy?
I don't know, probably ran
off crying to his mommy.
♪
Safety seal unlocked.
Confirmation.
One illegal monster
entered Earth
through unlawful methods.
Initiating contact now.
Ice Prison Emperor,
Cocytus Greed.
But why would a monster
from Ancient World do this?
Take a look at that mark.
Could he be one
of the Hundred Demons?
‐Come again, Gramps.
‐Hundred Demons?
It is clear.
The time to tell you
has finally come.
Huh?
You see, the Hundred Demons...
♪
No, wait, ah,
it's gone again.
(exclaiming)
You're gonna drive
me crazy, old timer.
Gao, don't you need to get
to your afternoon classes?
Huh‐‐oh no, school!
Detention time.
You incompetent fools!
(screaming)
Don't come back
again without Tenbu!
I can almost taste him.
(snarls)
♪
You need to make up for all
the classes you missed today
while out on your mission.
I have a feeling we're going to
be seeing a lot of each other.
Now first let's see if you
can solve this math equation.
(sighs)
The thanks I get
for saving the world.
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna
teach you about
the Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu.
It's a very powerful card
with the ability to
burn everything in sight
with its flames.
Being able to destroy
all opponent monsters
just by appearing on the field
can be especially
useful against enemies
that attack as a group.
Yeah, I'll say.
Even if your opponent
has a high Defense,
you can still try
to create an opening
to attack the player.
Sounds great!
Is it lunchtime yet?
(chuckling)
♪
Next time, Commander I's
archenemy Count Dawn
tells Gao to quit
the Buddy Police,
but Gao accepts
another challenge
from Death Shido
and finds himself
face‐to‐face
with Twin‐Headed
Hellhound, Orthrus.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!