Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies
with humans.
But now a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the 100 Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy skill on!
♪
A big welcome
to all monsters,
and a good morning
to everyone else.
So, how are you viewers
spending this lovely Sunday?
Oh, you know, fearing for
my life and going hungry.
You're such a
drama queen, Shido.
Stay with me while I ask this
monster what he's doing today.
Excuse me.
Since when does she interview
monsters in the park?
Can you tell our viewers what
you're doing in Cho‐Tokyo?
I came here hoping
to find my friends.
I went to sleep
for a little while
and when I woke up,
everyone had wandered off.
Ha!
Not too bright, that one.
(indistinct shouting)
Huh?
I brought you
some sushi.
Good, I happen
to be starving!
Here, hand it over.
♪
‐He's calling us.
‐Let me eat first.
(Shido screams)
These are rock hard!
I'll get you
for this, Gallows!
(laughing)
Only a fool like you
would fall for that trick.
If you like
eating rocks, Shido,
I've got a nice one
for you right here.
That's okay, I'm good.
Go ahead, show him.
Da.
Stars, use your
energy to guide me.
It's that monster
we just saw on TV.
Like Tenbu, this one's
incredibly powerful,
and he's probably equal
to him in flavor as well.
I'm relying on you
to bring them to me.
It's my wish to
devour both of them.
♪
(snoring)
(door opens)
Gao.
(groaning)
Gao!
(moans)
Come on, get up!
What are you
doing here?
Very funny,
now let's go.
There's no way Zanya would
be in my room right now,
which means that
I'm having a bad dream.
Okay, time to scram,
bad Zanya dream.
Huh?
I'm nobody's dream!
‐Now, get up, Gao!
‐Leave me be, Zanya.
It's my first day
off in like forever.
What's your deal?
‐Let me sleep in!
‐You're unbelievable.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
the reason why I'm here.
Answer me!
My grandma's
dumpling recipe?
(growling)
Be late for all I care!
I'm out of here.
Let's go, Tsukikage!
Nin.
Nin?
♪
(snoring)
First Omni Beast,
Lord Ziun, wake up.
Huh?
Who are you?
Let's just say an
old friend sent me.
I just knew I'd
find you, old friend!
‐Huh?
‐Ha‐ha!
(Shido screams)
I really hate to break
the news to you, old timer,
but I'm definitely not
one of your old friends.
Huh?
Yes.
Now that you mention it,
you do seem a little
different then I remember.
Of course,
I'm different.
I'm not him.
But if you truly wish to see
your dear friend so badly,
then I, the
great Death Shido,
might be persuaded
into telling you
how to find them.
You would do
that for me?
(crying)
I'm moved to tears with
gratitude, young man!
He really isn't
too bright, is he?
If I play my cards right, he
could help me steal Lord Tenbu.
Then, Master would
be so proud of me.
Alright, I'll tell you, but
first, I have one condition.
You must defeat
Gao Mikado in a Buddyfight
and take the Fifth Omni Dragon,
Lord Tenbu card from him.
Hmm.
I don't think
he's interested.
Why doesn't anyone
listen to me?
Are you still
sleeping, yo?
Leave me alone!
I finally have a day off!
Man, you must be tripping.
We got to make up for all
of our missed classes today.
"Missed classes?"
That was today?
You three, this Sunday,
we'll be running a makeup
session for all the classes
you missed this week.
So, be sure to come and join us
in Homeroom bright and early.
(groans)
We have to make up for our
classes on a Sunday morning?
This Buddy Police Youth
training is harsh.
(laughs)
You think that's bad?
Just wait 'til
they get you going
on the self‐defense
exercises.
(groaning)
What's wrong, Buddy Cop?
No doughnuts?
You're kidding.
There's no self‐defense
training, right?
No, Tetsuya.
He's just
pulling your leg.
Zanya, can I
ask you a favor?
♪
Do you think maybe
you'd be able to come over
and wake me up on Sunday?
It's against my code to
refuse a friend's request,
so I'll do it,
but be warned!
You'd better promise
that you'll get up!
Give me a break,
course, I'll get up!
Course I'll get up.
I totally forgot!
Buddy skill on.
Come on, Drum.
(grunts)
I happen to know that Gao's
coming to school today
to make up for
missed classes,
and when Ziun beats him,
that Tenbu card
will be ours.
That's not happening.
You're such a Negative Nelly!
See for yourself.
I don't think
Gao's coming.
Huh?
Stop right there.
I challenge you
to a Buddyfight.
♪
Is it a 100 Demon?
Nin!
Now it's time to luminize!
I couldn't stop this now
even if I wanted to.
Darkness Barrier,
enshroud and confuse!
♪
(roaring)
It's a Darkness Barrier.
Hurry, let's get
inside, you guys.
I'm game!
♪
Zanya!
Look who woke up.
Yeah, sorry about that.
No, it can't be.
A‐Dog, is that guy
a friend of yours?
No, I don't think so.
Warp successful!
Wherever there's
a Buddyfight,
Paraku Nanana
will be there.
I'm doing yet another
emergency live broadcast.
Come on, let's head
to the skull pit.
What's the rush?
Sacred and silent,
but you still hear
the sound of my mighty sword.
Luminize, Kisaragi
Ninja Arts Type Two!
If you think you can stop me,
you're welcome to try!
Luminize!
Disaster Charge!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
Go, Katana World!
♪
I fight for
Katana World, too!
Another Darkness
Barrier's been raised?
The first move goes to, uh,
sorry, what's your name?
I'm Ziun.
The first move
goes to Ziun.
Yes, our suspicions
were correct.
This monster's
not in our database.
Most disturbing.
We'll have to wait
'til the fight's over
to see who he really is.
♪
Welcome back!
During the break,
Ziun called
Outlander, Bokunryu
to the center.
Prepare for the cool
touch of my steel!
(grunts)
End of move.
A skull warrior with
a critical of three?
Seems pretty
pointless
considering he'll be destroyed
at the end of the turn.
Why would he waste
his special ability?
This is utterly outrageous.
It's a puzzle for sure.
Why use Bokunryu now when
his ability can destroy
an opponent's Size Two
monster when he appears?
What a major nonbo!
Zanya should
have no trouble
shredding it up
with this guy, yo!
Yeah, an easy
win for sure.
Three damage on the
first move is pretty bad.
Your move.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
I call.
To the right,
Accelerate Ninja, Hayate!
And two Kirikakure Saizo's
to the center and the left!
Both Saizo's,
go attack the fighter!
‐Sir!
(groans)
Hayate, use your speed!
Attack the fighter.
Wind and cloud,
Flying Slash!
I cast Demon Way,
Oborogenbu.
Time for Final Phase.
I pay one gauge and set
Super Lethal Formation!
There it is!
Zanya's specialty.
The impact that's
a counter spell.
It also increases his ninja's
power and defense by 1,000.
Zanya now waits for his
opponent to step into his trap.
Your move.
I draw, charge and draw.
♪
I call Lightning Speed,
Tsukiusagi to the center,
and I call Almighty
Dokakusai to the left!
What's he playing at?
Dokakusai's another
monster that gets destroyed
at the end of the turn.
Dokakusai,
penetrate the center!
I got this by a nose!
He's got penetrate?
Scruffing swords with me?
(grunting)
Tsukiusagi,
continue the attack!
Flying Bones of
Moonlight Mist!
(groaning)
End of move.
With his turn over,
Ziun's monster,
Dokakusai is destroyed.
Your move.
Things are
heating up.
Draw, charge and draw!
I call Shiden
to the center.
What's this?
He's not using Shiden's
Cyber Analyze ability?
Or maybe he's saving his
gauge for something else!
Either way, he's going
with a three ninja attack!
Forecast!
Slash!
(groans)
With that attack, Ziun is down
to just two life points.
End of move.
Zanya's only got three
life left himself, yo.
Don't sweat it.
I'm sure he's kept some
defense cards in his hand.
Yeah, he's got
it in the bag.
(groans)
♪
He hasn't used any
of his gauge yet.
So in order to
break this deadlock,
he'll probably use
a massive amount of it
and hit me with
some kind of spell.
♪
And when he does, the
Secret Sword Star Crusher
I put into Super Lethal
Formation will activate,
wiping out all of his
remaining life points.
That means I've won.
I buddy call myself
to the center.
Well, it's about time!
Now we can find out exactly
what kind of monster Ziun is!
Let's use my trusty
Tako scope to check it out!
First Omni Beast,
Lord Ziun.
Skull warrior attribute,
Size Three with 8,000 power,
one thousand defense
and a critical of three.
First Omni Beast Lord?
Do you know him,
Grandpa Tenbu?
With my memory,
I can't be sure.
Do you or don't you?
I attack with myself.
(grunts)
I cast.
Art of Body Replacement.
You're too late.
I pay one gauge and
activate my ability.
Now hear this!
When Ziun attacks
on his own,
his ability prevents the
opponent from neutralizing
or blocking his attack.
That's totally
off the hook, yo!
(groans)
Penetrate!
(screams)
Game over.
Winner: First Omni
Beast, Lord Ziun.
Master was right,
he is pretty tough.
Even so, beating Zanya still
doesn't help us acquire Tenbu.
Yeah, you're
right, I forgot!
Nice fight, but I
have something to tell you.
About my friends?
That was our
agreement for victory.
I told you to beat
Gao Mikado, not that guy.
You mean I was
fighting the wrong human?
Yes, the one you
want to destroy
is over there
consoling the loser.
Are you okay, Zanya?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Gao Mikado, fight me!
Careful what you wish for.
I suggest that you let
me fight in this one too.
I've got a good
feeling I might be able
to remember something
useful if I fight him.
Glad to have you.
Oh, no, I'm such a goof!
I left the Crimson Dragon
Fist deck at home!
‐You serious?
Then there's no chance
Grandpa Tenbu can fight, yo!
That's not
necessarily the case.
Hey, Paruko, over here!
What is it, Asmodai?
Would you mind examining Lord
Tenbu's card for us, please?
Be glad to.
Let me grab
my Tako scope.
♪
It's always at the ready
to give the deets on monsters.
Fifth Omni Dragon,
Lord Tenbu.
Armordragon attribute.
Size Three with
6,000 power and defense.
A critical of three and he
can be used with all flags.
(both gasp)
Just remember, in a
non‐Dragon World deck,
you can only include
one of his cards.
Don't worry, I promise
I'll be very useful to you.
Now, let's go
get this guy.
Alright.
I trust you.
(roaring)
Be patient.
We'll be dining
on him soon.
(roaring)
And I can hardly wait.
Emergency Launch!
From the eye
of the storm!
Luminize!
Beaming Sunshine Guardians!
If you think you can stop me,
you're welcome to try.
Luminize!
Disaster Charge!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm fighting for Hero World!
I'm fighting
for Katana World.
The first move of the
fight will go to Gao.
I love going first.
Charge and draw.
I call Cyber Police Assault
Leader to the center!
Cyber Police Assault!
Go ahead, attack!
Roger that.
(groans)
End of move.
Now, it's Ziun's
turn to attack,
and if his bout with
Zanya was any indication,
he was practically
unstoppable.
(groans)
Sword of the
thrashing seas.
(groans)
Flying Thorns of
the Moonlight Mist!
(grunts)
End of move.
Ha, you're actually
not half bad,
but the real fight's
just beginning.
Last time I looked,
overconfidence couldn't
lower my life points.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
♪
It's your turn to
take the stage, Gramps.
I call Fifth Omni Dragon, Lord
Tenbu to the center position.
Now, feast your
eyes on my ability.
When I appear,
I destroy
all my opponent's
monsters in the field.
♪
Huh.
Howling Fire!
(screaming)
♪
Goodness, that's what I
call one incredible attack,
and by the looks of
things, he's not done yet!
Prepare, for now I come for
you‐‐ oh, wait, I forgot.
His name's First Omni Beast
Lord or something like that.
Yeah, that's right.
(grunts)
I cast.
Demon Way,
Oborogenbu.
(groans)
End of move.
Stay out of this, old timer.
Now it's my
turn, you hear?
If you want to say
something to Gao,
now's the time
to do it, Zanya.
I don't think I'm the
one to be giving him advice.
I mean, I lost to Ziun,
so what help could I be?
Don't forget what we
learned at the academy.
Buddy Police Youth officers help
each other no matter what.
Yes, of course,
you're right.
Nin.
Ziun called Irukamaru
to his center area,
then called Dokakusai
to the left
and did a punishing
penetrate attack
on Grandpa Tenbu
and Gao's center.
It's time you expire.
(groans)
This was my only chance
to shine today.
(groaning)
Irukamaru, attack
that Gao Mikado.
You can spend a
night in the deep.
Gao, don't let him take
any of your life points.
What's your plan?
The way he's set up,
he'll cause three damage
to you on your next turn.
So, you'll need to use
the Rescue Dragon
Mach Braver in your hand.
Awesome advice,
thanks, Zanya!
I activate Rescue Dragon
Mach Braver's ability!
I have the option of
calling it to the center
during my opponent's turn.
Your wicked deeds end now!
It's too dangerous for me.
‐End of move.
‐He's one lucky fellow.
Now the turn is over,
Dokakusai will be destroyed.
It's been a slice!
Now the Sunshine Guardians
Deck can show its true power!
Let's do this!
Transform!
Super burning speed,
round up all the criminals!
♪
Explosive take down!
Rampage Sonic!
Gao's finally shown
us his transformation!
(grunting)
I can't forget my pal.
I buddy call to the right,
Buddy Police Decker Drum!
Alright!
(grunts)
I move Mach Braver
to the left.
Well, this looks
mighty familiar.
It's the Gao Formation!
You're up, clear out
the center for me.
Be glad to.
(grunting)
Never bet against
a determined dragon.
The center's open.
Let's take him together!
‐Come on!
‐After you.
Mach Slash!
Rampage Roundhouse kick!
(groaning)
End of move.
That does it.
Now it's time
to get serious.
With Ziun's blocking ability,
Tenbu will finally be mine.
I buddy call myself
to the center.
Here's the mighty
Omni Beast Lord.
By the looks of things,
this is gonna end up
just like his last fight.
(grunting)
End of move.
If he'd been hit by
Irukamaru's attack earlier,
this would have
been game over for Gao.
Good thing Zanya was here
to pass on his advice, yo.
We're all on
the same team.
Come on, Gao, I know
you can do this.
Nin!
I cast Hyper Energy,
and I'm gonna activate
Decker Drum's ability.
Go take care of this monster
with 'tude, okay, partner?
Leave it to me.
When Gao pays two gauge,
I can even destroy Size Three
monsters in one hit.
He's going to blow
the center open.
Locked onto Ziun.
Break!
I admit it,
you're good.
Ha, let's hit him with
the Gao Formation again.
Just like before,
Mach Braver.
Go attack the fighter.
You got it!
Mach Slash!
(grunts)
Keep it going, Drum!
(yells)
Crash Cyclone Bunker!
(groans)
Now to finish him.
I activate Lightning Speed,
Tsukiusagi's ability.
I pay one gauge and
call her to the center.
I will not let you
pass through me!
Better luck next time.
"Next time?"
My move ain't
over yet.
That can't be.
Time for Final Phase!
No, it can't be,
not again!
♪
I cast!
Impact!
Rampage Blaster!
(groans)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Alright.
It was a total
team effort.
What, he's not
a 100 Demon?
He came to Earth
10,000 years ago
and he's been
sleeping ever since.
He has nothing to do
with the 100 Demons at all.
He was tricked by Death Shido
and used like some puppet, yo.
I'm truly sorry
for what happened.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Gramps, I thought you said
you'd remember something useful
if you fought against him.
You're right,
I did say that.
‐Hmm.
‐Nope, nothing.
(sighs)
(chuckles)
I can't believe I actually
lost to this guy.
Do you have any clues for
finding your friends?
I was asleep for so long,
I don't remember
what they look like.
(laughing)
Catch ya later!
Shouldn't we have taken him
to the Buddy Card Office?
I mean, he is an unregistered
monster and all.
No, it's okay.
We don't have to
worry about him.
If it's copacetic with A‐Dog,
it's all right, yo.
I should be
heading home too.
Yeah, I'm beat.
Why don't y'all come
over for some eats?
I'm down with that.
Mind if Akatsuki comes?
Well, duh,
of course not!
Hmm.
I feel like we've
forgotten something.
No, maybe not.
Are Gao and the others
ever going to show up?
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna
tell you all about
the First Omni
Beast Lord, Ziun.
Cool!
This is an extremely
aggressive monster
whose attack is
literally unstoppable.
Paying one gauge
triggers his ability,
preventing opponents from
nullifying his attack
and with his penetrate,
having a monster in
the way is no problem.
Sounds intense!
So when you drop your
opponent's life points,
finish them off with the
First Omni Beast Lord, Ziun.
Speaking of finishing,
can we get out early today?
(laughing)
♪
Next time that 100 Demons
hunter shows up again,
and his name is Ban Enma.
Meanwhile, Death Shido tries his
luck with Red Dragon, Igneel.
Next episode, "The Wandering
Hundred Demons Hunter!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!