(roars)
Now that the
devastating monster
Yamigedo has been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us
to find them.
And there's only
one way we can.
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
(snarling)
♪
(grunt)
What's going
on with him?
I thought eating Tenbu
was going to
fully revive him.
Maybe he had indigestion
from eating too fast.
Tenbu's power was too
much for him to process.
He'll remain in his
current state for a while.
(groaning)
(giggling)
A good time to pay
him back for all his‐‐
(scream)
They're highly unstable,
so don't get too close.
Thanks for that
timely information.
You really aren't too
bright hey, Sh‐‐shi‐‐shids?
♪
(body thumping)
Uh!
(heavy breathing)
What do you mean,
special leave?
Your duties with
the Buddy Police
Youth Division
are not required
for the immediate future.
That's what it means.
But we have to go
after Yamigedo!
He absorbed the
Fifth Omni Dragon Lord
because he's trying
to fully revive, right?
We need to find
the other Omni Lords
as soon as possible.
And I want to help!
Other officers
have been assigned
to the search team.
And besides,
we have ample time
before Yamigedo makes
another appearance.
He has to recuperate.
Huh?
The only thing
you should be
worrying about right now
is figuring out
how to turn Drum
into a true Omni Lord.
‐Huh?
‐Uh.
And you yourself need
to become a fighter
who is worthy of being
an Omni Lord's buddy.
You're dismissed.
I wasn't prepared for this.
What's required of
an Omni Lord's buddy?
♪
This is all
just so crazy.
I mean me,
an Omni Lord?
‐I don't know what
‐I'm supposed to do.
(doorbell ringing)
‐Huh?
Hey.
Hope we
aren't interrupting.
Teach asked me to drop
of your homework, bro.
Man, that's a lot.
With you on
special leave,
the school figured
it was a good time
to catch up on things.
Yeah, great.
Tell me, bro,
how you doing?
I mean, a lot of
stuff's gone down.
Yeah, with Buddy Police
headquarters being destroyed,
how are they managing?
Well, good as
can be expected.
They're making
do working out
of the satellite
Buddy Card offices
in districts
two and three.
And they're
trying to find
the remaining Omni Lords
by following
up on the leads
coming into the
Amanosuzu Group's hotline.
And the Buddy Police Youth?
Now that Tasuku's
heading things up,
they're ready to
respond to reports
all across
the entire country.
How can they manage that?
Sounds impossible.
Yeah, totally
crazy, right?
Thing is, our
new headquarters
is pretty mobile.
‐Huh?
With the great Tasuku's
recent appointment
to the leader of the
Buddy Youth division,
I wanted to lend my support
by offering this as his
temporary headquarters.
But to be honest,
I'm more than
a little perturbed
that the leader's never here.
I mean, really.
And on top of that,
they've got Gao away
on some imposed leave.
You don't care
Zanya's not here?
You don't say,
I hadn't really noticed.
What do you think
you're doing?
That's Tasuku's chair.
Get up and once.
Whoa.
Oh.
Huh?
With Tasuku
out on assignment,
I've come to share
some promising news
that may aid in our
search for the Omni Lords.
Why does Tasuku
have to be out there?
I mean, why not send
this rookie here?
You cut me
deep just now.
(thudding)
‐Huh?
Sorry, guys, I'm
still a long way
from being at
full strength.
I also came to thank you
personally, Lady Suzuha.
It's because of you
that we obtained
the helpful information
on the Omni Lords.
Oh, well you're
most welcome, Count.
You'll find once
the remaining Omni Lords
have been identified,
all of our officers
will be deeply
grateful to you, my dear.
That includes Tasuku
and Gao, of course.
Honest, do you
really mean it?
Ah.
♪
How can I ever
thank you, Suzuha?
Please let me know
how I can repay you.
Ahhh.
In that case,
I guess I can wait
a little while longer.
Now, I insist that
you join me for tea
while we wait for
Tasuku to return.
And please,
feel free to sit
in Gao's special
chair if you wish.
(giggle)
♪
Dawn!
(crowd murmuring)
(stammers)
(snorting)
That guy's got
to be an Omni Lord.
Check out the size
of his horn.
I don't think so.
What do you mean,
of course he is.
That is a rhinoceros.
I know that's
the form he's in now,
but Omni Lords could be
posing as anything, right?
And I looked it up,
rhinoceroses are supposed
to have two horns.
This guy only has one.
So I think that maybe
the First Omni Beast Lord
you're looking for
has disguised himself
as this big guy right here.
Nin.
Interesting theory, but
that's an Indian rhinoceros.
‐Huh?
‐Nin?
And they're identified
as having only one horn.
It says so
right here.
Wha?
Hey, that's true.
Tsukikage, why are
you acting so surprised?
You should know him!
You've fought the First
Omni Beast Lord once before!
Nin?
It's imperative we find
the First Omni Beast Lord,
but we just aren't
having any luck.
Hey, Big Z,
I think I found him.
Really?
♪
That's not him!
Over here!
Are you for real?
That must be him.
Akatsuki!
♪
My brother's too overeager.
He's taking us
all over the place.
It's getting so I
can't find a single lead.
I'm feeling lucky.
Next time we'll
find him for sure.
Nin, nin.
Argh, you've
done enough!
What‐‐no, wait!
I need to keep
my eyes peeled
for even the
slightest clue.
Huh, wait up!
Howdy, little dudes.
Huh?
Hey, how are you guys?
Ah, a girl!
Did you find
the Omni Lords?
You are still
looking for them, right?
Wait, what are
you doing here?
Don't tell me there's
one hiding at Castle.
(whimpers)
I can't reveal the
secrets of the operation.
Well, if you have some time,
how about we have
a Buddyfight?
Uh...ahem, sorry,
I can't today.
I'm here on
official business.
I came strictly
to buy some cards.
Oh.
Don't mind him.
That young chap's as
ill‐mannered as usual.
Don't be a stranger.
Wouldn't it be cool if
you opened up a rare card?
There's a reason they're
called rare, little brother.
No way!
♪
Commander I, I'm picking up
a Buddy Monster signal.
Really, where?
Just give me a second.
This makeshift
satellite is a little slow.
There, at a shopping
mall in Toshifuya.
Oh no, we lost the signal.
Perhaps we could relocate
to one of the
district offices?
Out of the question.
As commander, I can't
abandon HQ for any reason.
(crashing)
Help me up.
A white Tsukikage?
(clap)
Ah!
Hey, hey, hey,
it's about time
you opened me up.
Here I am
coming to you
from the far reaches
of coolio Katana World.
Put your hands together
for Zanya's Buddy.
Zanya's Buddy?
Nin!
But I already have one.
Nin.
Stop it right there,
old Buddy, old pal.
I can see the
wheels of confusion
burning rubber
in your mind.
You're thinking
that this average guy
in the black suit
is good enough.
Wrong, he's weak
and unreliable.
That's why I've come to
save you from mediocrity.
For a Nanomachine Ninja,
I'm the absolute
very best there is.
‐Nanomachine Ninja?
Nin.
Huh?
Big brother?
You got it, I'm
Nanomachine Ninja, Byakuya.
A.K.A, Tsukikage's
big brother.
All right, Junior,
now I'm here,
you can scram, capiche?
Mama needs you
back in Katana World
to clean the garage.
Nin!
Does he have to go?
It seems a little
sudden, don't you think?
Let's try and keep emotions
out of it,
shall we?
I get that
it's a shock,
really I do,
but let's face facts.
You want the best
Buddy there is, right?
Judge for yourself.
If I'm not superior
in every way,
I'll be the one
to leave, agreed?
Nin.
‐Huh?
First up,
the 100 meter dash.
On your mark,
get set...
(gun shot)
(screeching)
Faster.
Higher.
Nin!
(thumping)
Further.
‐Convinced yet?
‐Nin.
A true ninja
must be quick
at gathering and
relaying information.
So for our next event,
we'll have a speed
writing contest.
Come on, Tsukikage.
He's got this
one in the bag.
♪
I'm ten times
faster than him.
Uh!
And being ninjas,
we've just got to have
a ninja arts contest.
But not just your
run of the mill kind.
We're Nanomachine Ninjas.
So prepare
for the ultimate
Nanomachine Ninja
Arts showdown!
Nanomachine Ninja Arts,
Art of Nano Nano Ni.
Nin.
Where'd they go?
Look down there.
I only see Tsukikage.
So where's Byakuya?
The Art of
Nano Nano Ni
is devoted to
making yourself smaller
and creating numerous
duplicates of yourself, too.
Looks like I win again!
Nin.
I trust this
has enlightened you
and helped you
to see which of us
is truly worthy of being
Lord Zanya's Buddy.
‐Huh?
Tsukikage, make
your appropriate
farewells with
haste and then return
to Katana World
immediately.
We have to say
goodbye to him?
No fair,
I don't wanna!
A ninja's heart
cannot be soft.
Zanya deserves
the very best
for his Buddy.
No one must interfere.
Yeah, but we only became
Buddies with Buddy Monsters
so we can have
Buddyfights.
So shouldn't
we be testing
which one of
you is superior
through a Buddyfight?
You make a valid point.
Akatsuki, you take
Tsukikage as your Buddy,
Zanya and I will
fight against you.
Then we'll see
who's the best.
But he's all I know.
Don't worry,
it's the only way.
Whoever wins will
become your Buddy.
We shuffle.
This is all so weird,
but I guess at the very
least it will be interesting
to see what kind
of monster he is.
(cell phone ringing)
Hey, I just got
a text from Kazane.
Huh, get this.
She says that
Zanya and Akatsuki
are going to
have a Buddyfight.
Keeping it all
in the family, hey bro?
We've all got to go
and check this out.
Yeah, count me in.
Wherever there's
a Buddyfight,
you'll find me,
Paruko Nanana.
Today we have
a special treat.
A Kisaragi showdown
between brothers
Zanya and Akatsuki.
I've got to do this
for Tsukikage.
I won't lose
no matter what.
All right, Zanya,
what do you say?
Let's show that uppity
little brother of mine
what it's like playing
with the grownups,
shall we?
♪
Zanya has the first move.
Hey, guys, over here.
Good timing, it's
just about to start.
I call Yumi Ninja, Suiha
to the center area.
I have trained
for such a day.
Suiha allows any
player that calls him
to search his deck for
a size one or less ninja
and add it to his hand.
Hey, bub, it's my job
to explain that!
Art of Water Escape,
Flowing Water check.
I add Electron Ninja,
Shiden to my hand
and call him
to the right.
I'll use Cyber Analyze
and draw two cards.
There is nothing my Arrow
of Luminance cannot pierce.
(yells)
End of move.
Huh, if he loses,
he's no longer his Buddy?
That's what I heard.
And Tsukikage will also have
to go back to Katana World.
No way.
I wouldn't be
okay with that.
Are you, Zanya?
I call Stealth Ninja,
Kirikakure Saizo
to the left
and Accelerate Ninja,
Hayate to the right.
♪
I Buddy Call
Tsukikage to the center.
♪
Nin.
The Buddy Gift lets
him regain one life point.
Go and attack that Suiha!
Nin!
♪
(yells)
I cast Demon Way,
Geppakugiri.
(yells)
That was a counterspell
that unleashes an attack
when one of your
monsters is defeated.
Hide in the mist and
cut through the shadows.
Mutation Sword.
(screams)
Final Phase.
I set Lethal Formation!
Set.
Looks familiar.
I guess his deck's a lot
like his brother's.
I call Hidden Sword
Ninja, Sekitetsu
to the right.
And Japanese Blade
Ninja, Hachimonji
to the left!
Villainy is
fast to spread.
I seek honest combat.
I equip Water Slash
Sword, Murasame.
♪
I hope your
heart is in this
and you don't plan
on tricking me.
Guess you don't know me.
Hidden Sword Style,
Wild Flashing Steel!
Tsukikage!
Japanese Sword Style.
Single Sword,
vertical division.
When I draw my
treasured blade,
it shines like a jewel.
Water Slash Sword, Murasame!
Ah‐ha‐ah!
End of move.
That was fantastic.
But you are
aware that Murasame
is destined to disappear
at the end of the turn?
For the last time,
pal, that's my job!
This is it, I draw.
Charge and draw.
There's no way
I'm letting Tsukikage
get sent back
to Katana World.
‐I call to the center‐‐
‐Nin.
Akatsuki calls
Tsukikage a second time!
I call to the
right my secret weapon,
Tsukikage Blademaster Mode!
Nin!
Is it me or am
I seeing double?
Tsukikage Blademaster Mode
boosts his critical
whenever there's
a Tsukikage card
in the drop zone.
If he converts his attacks,
it'll be a major
amount of damage.
So he can just fire up
some defensive spells.
Unless Akatsuki sets
Secret Sword, Star Crusher
in the Lethal Formation.
'Kay, Big Z,
all you gotta do
is use a defensive spell.
If you do,
then I win.
Gotcha, you've fallen
into my trap, big brother.
Lethal Formation, activate!
Secret Sword,
Star Crusher!
Your counterspell's
been neutralized
and I inflict
three damage to you.
All the monsters
in my field
have a combined
critical of seven.
I've won.
Ninjas unite and
attack my brother!
With stealth.
‐Nin.
♪
Zanya's hit with
a triple attack
and receives
massive damage!
End of move.
How come you're not
defending yourself,
you dweebface?
Because your strategy
is so transparent.
Guess it was Star
Crusher after all.
So now he can't just
use any spell he wants.
Wonder what Zanya's gonna do?
I return Murasame to
the cards in my hand.
What's he doing?
He's taking Murasame
out of the drop zone!
I Buddy Call
to the center.
The wait is over,
the star player has arrived.
That's right,
it's the amazing
Nanomachine Ninja,
Byakuya in the flesh.
My trusty Takoscope
will give us his deets.
Nanomachine Ninja, Byakuya,
attribute Ninja,
a size one monster
with 5,000 power,
1,000 defense,
a critical of one,
and get this,
he has two abilities.
Tsukikage here
is blocking my center
and I've got
five life left.
So no matter how
much you try to attack,
I can defend my life points
and outlast you.
‐Nin.
‐Huh?
(exclaims)
♪
Hidden Sword Style,
Wild Flashing Steel.
(yells)
How did she get
past Tsukikage?
It's Shadow Dive.
There are monsters
from Katana World
that have Shadow
Dive ability too?
You think that's special?
Give me a break.
Everyone, look closely.
It's what I'm known for.
He's attacking the fighter
even with a monster in
the center position!
It's Shadow Dive!
I cast Art of Body Replacement!
He dodged the attack!
Oh, yeah, now I've won.
Think again,
young Kisaragi.
Come on, Zanya.
Thanks, I know.
I activate
Byakuya's ability.
I discard all the
cards in my hand.
When I'm in the field
and all the
non‐monster cards
are discarded
from Zanya's hand,
I can attack as
many times as I want.
It's called the Nanomachine
Clone Exterminate.
That's amazing.
This guy is one super
powerful Buddy, bro.
♪
Your life is now mine.
And mine and
mine, mine, too.
No, Tsukikage,
I'm so sorry!
♪
Game over.
Winner, Zanya Kisaragi.
Ah, Tsukikage!
Tsuki always was
a little sensitive.
I get that it's
hard to say goodbye,
but a promise
is a promise.
Now return to Kataka
World on the double.
‐(sobbing)
‐Nin.
The thing is, I never
made any such promise.
‐Huh?
‐Nin?
Hold the phone, muchacho,
you can't renege now.
We had a deal.
We said whoever
won the fight
would become your Buddy.
Remember the ninja code.
We are nothing
without our honor.
No, you said that without
even consulting me.
(all gasp)
That's true, Z didn't
agree to anything.
Nin.
But he went along
with the fight.
Mmm.
Even if you didn't
agree right away,
it's as clear as
the nose on your face
which of us is more
worthy of being your Buddy.
Now, let's go
start the process
for switching me
over as your Buddy.
What do you say, 'kay?
While it is true that you
are an excellent monster...
Yes, and...?
See, the thing is, you
have one glaring flaw.
That's absurd, what
are you talking about?
You talk way too much!
Ah!
‐Uh.
You make me feel
as uncomfortable
as I do around girls!
And do you know
why that is?
Because they're
chatterboxes!
Girls talk too much.
They go on and on and on
about nothing meaningful
and they never listen
to a single word you say!
I know, I hate that!
Nin.
You don't listen either!
You actually thought
that rhinoceros
was the First Omni Beast Lord!
Yeah, that wasn't
my best moment.
Those who talk too
much are not suited
for being my Buddy.
Meaning that I'll
be more troubled
if you become my Buddy.
But I'm the better,
stronger ninja!
Tsukikage's the
only Buddy for me.
Now and forever,
we share a bond.
I knew it the
moment we first met.
We were fated.
We chose each other
and have been best
friends ever since.
Nin.
Hooray, now we can
all be together!
I'm so happy
you can stay
and won't have
to leave us.
Nin!
But then why was
my card opened?
If you're interested,
I'd really like it if you'd
become part of my deck.
To be honest, I could
use your strength.
Of course, I'd do anything
to help you, Zanya.
I'd climb mountains,
swim oceans,
walk through fire,
fend off‐‐
Just try not to
talk so much, okay?
Nin.
Cool, now the two brothers
get to fight side by side!
Nin.
From now on, I'll obey
your orders, big brother,
and do everything in
my power to help us win.
Big brother?
I thought Tsukikage
was your younger brother.
I guess it can be
confusing for you humans
who are obsessed with
chronological order.
But in the world of
Nanomachine Ninjas,
the superior
ninja is always
referred to as
the big brother,
regardless of birth order.
If you must know,
I was actually born
after Tsukikage,
but by choosing him
as your preferred Buddy,
I am automatically
now the little brother.
I don't really mind,
in the end it's best
for brothers
to get along.
I couldn't agree more.
I guess we should do the same.
Yeah, we got
to work together
and stop fighting.
Come on, let's go find the
First Omni Beast Lord, Ziun!
♪
(chuckle)
It turns out that the
monster spotted in Choguma
isn't an Omni Lord after all,
just a registered monster.
It was mistakenly
reported as a possible
because of its horns.
We've got to
keep searching.
Okay, report back to base.
Why don't we take
a little detour first?
Let me guess, you want
to check in on Gao.
Yeah, Jack.
He can probably
use a friend.
I'm worried about him
after dropping
his first fight.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna
teach you all about
Nanomachine Ninja, Byakuya.
I'm all ears!
He destroys his enemies
with the skillful
Nanomachine Clone Exterminate.
Each time you discard
a non‐monster card
from your hand,
he can attack again.
And he has Shadow
Dive ability,
which lets him blow past
an opponent's center monster.
That's awesome!
He works well with
Water Slash Sword, Murasame,
which can return
from the drop zone
to your hand.
Wish I could
return home to bed.
♪
Next time, Gao's taken by
the Hundred Demons hunter
and he's forced to
compete in a Buddyfight.
I can't leave my
Buddy on his own,
so I power up
to lend a hand.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!