(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the Eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them and
there's only one way we can!
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
♪
Schwarz, hit him
with Hell Despot.
Ja wohl.
(grunting)
♪
It's like child's play.
It's time for Final Phase.
I'm scared.
I cast!
(groaning)
This will be
the end of you.
Well, look who
we have here.
‐Get him!
‐Huh?
(shouting)
Harder!
(grunting)
♪
Your lucky day, Ace.
I got to scram.
♪
Dig in, boys.
Here's to getting Ricky back.
Hey, you forgot
the sour candies.
Be happy with what
you've got, bird brain!
Can't you two stop your
squabbling long enough
to celebrate
Ricky's return?
It's like I never left.
Why'd they take our
little scrapper anyway?
That guy in the
bamboo hat said
something about
Omni Lord Emblem.
Hey, I've heard
of those guys.
Aren't they the
ones the Buddy Police
are going crazy
looking for?
How should I know?
Emblem shmemblems, it's
nothing to do with me.
Catching 100 Demons'
all I care about.
But I'll be needing
you to hand over
your Omni Lord Emblem,
hunter boy.
Do it nice
and easy now.
♪
Guess it's time.
I think I've hid
the truth from Chief
for long enough, ki.
♪
How's Gao doing?
I've never
seen him so bad.
He's locked himself
up in his room
and isn't talking
to anybody!
Poor kid.
I just wish there was
something I could do.
Maybe I was harder
on him than I thought.
(door opens)
Everything wasn't
a total loss.
Shigamine led us
to a new Omni Lord.
Take a look.
His name's
Dragon Kid, Ricky.
As you know, he's
the buddy monster
of 100 Demons Hunter,
Ban Enma.
♪
That bright light is definitely
from an Omni Lord Emblem.
You really think that little
homie's an Omni Lord?
Huh?
There must be
some mistake, ki.
I'm just little old Dragon Kid,
Ricky from Ancient World.
Someone's trying
to pull a fast one.
If he is one then
why do you think
he'd flat out
deny it, Count?
Hard to say, but I felt
like he was hiding something.
Explain, hiding
what, exactly?
That's just it,
I don't know.
♪
How about you let me
try talking to him?
Good idea, yo.
Drum has gotten to know
these guys a little.
Yeah, he can get to
the bottom of things.
Dragon to dragon.
That's exactly why
I asked you here.
I'll lift your special
leave albeit temporarily.
Emergency launch right away,
and take Ban Enma into custody.
Alright, leave
it to me, Count!
Decker Road open!
Decker Drum's
on patrol!
You want to borrow
my 100 Demons monster?
That's right.
You have one,
do you not?
What exactly are you
planning on doing?
I intend to
diminish the power
of the Omni Lords
while we still can.
Then I'll make Master
Yamigedo's revival complete.
Reducing their power?
Is such a thing
even possible?
You ask far too
many questions, boy.
‐No, what are you doing?
‐I'm taking your Black Skull.
Put me down!
Take this.
(Shido growls)
Good.
(imitating motorcycle engine)
Nothing like taking a ride
after stuffing your gut,
am I right, Ricky?
Let's drop in on Gao
and pay him a visit.
He was acting a little
weird the other day.
I'm worried.
You don't mind if we make a
little pit stop, do you?
Hmm.
Actually, Chief.
Huh, what's up?
Well, I, uh, have something
important to tell you, ki.
(waves crashing)
(buzzer)
Hmm.
‐Hey, Ricky!
‐Hmm, Drum?
I've been looking for you.
What are you
doing way out here?
Ask the chief.
We were on our
way to see Gao
when I told him I had something
important to tell him.
He wanted to hear
it by the sea.
Why are you here?
Huh?
Hey!
That what I think it is?
Yeah, it's my
Omni Lord Emblem.
But cause I'm
a rookie at this,
I can't get
it to light up.
The reason I came is to ask you
if you've got one of these too.
Uh.
Be honest, you're
an Omni Lord, right?
Well, not exactly.
It's complicated.
(whooshing)
Look out!
Who did that?
I did!
Buzz Saw Roar Dragon!
Well take your wood
cutter somewhere else!
We're in the middle of a
conversation here, pal!
I'm not going anywhere until you
hand over that Omni Lord Emblem.
Zip it, Blondie.
Thought I could smell ya!
My 100 Demons radar's
been going off like crazy.
You know who I am?
If I had to guess, I'd say
my next victim, biker scum.
Looky here, we got
a live one, boys.
Show him what
it is we do.
I'm Wicked Dragon Emperor,
Billion Knuckle.
They call me Fast Dragon
Emperor, Champion Lord.
And I'm Ethereal
Overlord, Gang, the King.
‐You scared yet?
♪
You're looking at
the 100 Demons Hunter.
Give up now if you
know what's good for you.
We'll see who'll be
begging for mercy.
♪
And just who
the heck are you?
Huh, the creepy skeleton!
That's the guy
who took out Noboru!
Chief, careful, don't
get too close to him!
Much time has passed since our
last encounter, old friend.
I'm not surprised you
don't remember who I am.
Huh?
Hey, you're‐‐
(screams)
Submit and become
Master Yamigedo's pawn!
(screaming)
Hang on!
Who is that guy?
(yelling)
(yells)
He'll pay for that.
(growling, grunts)
That's using your head.
A very bashing move.
Maybe it's just
me, you guys,
but does the chief seem
a little different to you?
On guard!
♪
What was that for?
He's lost it!
Why are you
attacking us?
I see.
He repressed his
memories to prevent me
from ever altering
them in my favor.
And the thoughts of fury, I
have just implanted within him
have caused him to
become blind with rage.
He now attacks aimlessly
without knowing friend or foe.
Interesting.
What do we do?
He's attacking
anything that moves.
Then I guess
we stay still.
Down here, Chief.
‐It's me, Ricky.
‐No, it's too dangerous.
(grunts)
Are you okay?
How fortuitous.
If I leave him like this
without lifting my spell,
his mind will crack and his
memories will be lost forever.
No, you can't!
(screaming)
We'll try and
hold him off.
You guys better get out
of here before it's too late.
No can do!
We're not about
to ditch you.
(screaming)
Where do you think
you're going?
Get back, Ricky!
Time for Scorching Sidekick
Stand of Courage, ki.
♪
What's he doing?
Look out, Ricky!
(screaming)
Come on, Chief, you
got to fight through it.
You got to try
and remember.
How you saved me
the first time we met.
Our lives depend on it!
(distant scream)
Huh?
You will become my pawn!
You don't see
this every day!
(grunts)
I've erased his memories
and given him new ones.
Now the Fourth
Omni Fire Lord
will never be able to
rise against us again.
What kind of a rat fink hits a
guy when he's not even looking?
Hundred Demons' don't
play by your rules.
I'll do whatever I must to seal
the power of an Omni Lord.
As for you,
little dragon,
you're in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
You have seen too much
and I cannot let you go.
I'm forced to alter
your memories as well.
I'm gonna go ape on you!
(grunting)
You truly are an Omni Lord
to have such power
after what I've done.
No matter, I've
achieved what I came for.
(grunts)
Are you all right?
Nuts!
It looks like that guy wasn't
jiving about my memories.
My head's getting all funky.
Try and pull
yourself together, ki.
Listen up, Daddy‐o, it's a real
drag you got caught up in this,
but I got to ask you to
do me a major solid, you dig?
Yeah?
Before I repress
my memories,
there's something
I need to give you
and you got to promise to
protect it with your life.
Don't ever give it up
or tell anyone about it.
♪
Wait, you mean‐‐
You're the‐‐
This is the
Omni Lord Emblem
that you entrusted me
with that day we met, ki.
After what happened with that
doofus Shigamine the other day,
I've been trying to
find a way to tell you
that you're an Omni Lord,
but you seemed so mad
about the whole thing,
I didn't know how to say it,
but Omni Lords are important.
You're important,
like a deity, ki.
Huh?
Truth is, I didn't
want to tell you,
cause I'd be losing you,
and I couldn't bear
saying goodbye to my pal.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Omni Lord Emblem,
I call on you!
Help the chief turn back into
the Fourth Omni Fire Lord, ki!
(screams)
♪
Ricky!
Huh?
♪
Chief, that you?
I don't understand.
It's obvious, moron,
that's the chief's true form.
♪
It seems implanting memories of
rage within him has backfired.
Greetings, I am the Fourth
Omni Fire Lord, Burn Nova!
♪
The Fourth Omni title
was given to me
in reference
to a great king
who ruled over
an ancient kingdom.
Just kidding!
Huh?
Hey, what happened?
Think about it.
How would getting my memories
back change my personality too?
It's still me,
you dipsticks.
Why you, nerd!
That wasn't funny at all!
You shouldn't play
around like that, ki.
Admit it, that
was a good one.
Hey, I need you
to do something for me.
Can I ask you to keep
holding on to this, hmm?
Yeah, of course,
I'd be happy to.
Nobody disrespects me like
that and gets away with it.
If you two are finished
with your little bro‐mance,
we've got some unfinished
business, you and me.
Excellent.
I'll leave the
rest to you, Buzz Saw.
♪
(roaring)
Oh, boy, here
we go again.
What is it, Count?
Drum's just informed us,
there's a Buddyfight
between illegal monsters
at Chamiyura Beach
and get this,
the 100 Demons Hunter's
the Fourth Omni Fire Lord.
The 100 Demons' Hunter?
‐Head over right away.
‐On it!
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana will be there!
Today's exciting
match up is between
Buzz Saw Roar Dragon and
the 100 Demons Hunter.
With the first move,
the 100 Demons Hunter
increases his
gauge and life.
Equips Sky Splitting Armor,
Masurao and attacks,
but is blocked by Blue Dragon
Shield ending the turn.
Let's watch
Buzz Saw Roar Dragon
as he gets a
chance to respond.
I draw.
And I charge and draw again.
I call
Thunder Knights,
Bastard‐Sword
Dragon to the center
and Missile Bunker
Dragon to the left.
Now, Missile Bunker,
go attack the fighter.
Missile Bunker's ability
boosts the player's gauge
and lets him return to
the deck after his attack.
You're next,
Bastard‐Sword.
Bastard‐Sword Dragon, has
the double attack ability.
Let's see how you deal
with my double strike!
Not so fast!
I cast Manliness
Spirit Shield!
Why you‐‐
End of move.
He blocked the
second attack.
It appears as though this
will be a defensive affair.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I pay two
life and cast.
Rise and Fall
of Dragons.
With that, he increases
his gauge by four.
Now, I buddy call Dragon Kid,
Ricky to the right area.
Okey‐dokey.
Next, I call Gang, the King,
to the left position.
Alright!
I've got three raging
spirits in my drop zone,
meaning Gang currently
has 13,000 power.
Go hit him hard!
Imperial Rear Barrett!
(groans)
Penetrate!
Hey, that hurts!
Now the fighter's following
up with his equipped item!
♪
Sky Splitting
Armor, Masurao!
(screams)
‐You're up, Ricky.
‐A test of courage.
I cast Dragonic Thunder!
I rule.
The 100 Demons' Hunter
loses one life with lifelink.
End of move.
(siren wailing)
Update.
There's a Darkness Barrier.
I couldn't find a way in.
And it doesn't come down
until the fight's over.
Buzz Saw looks determined
as he prepares for his turn!
I buddy call myself
to the center.
♪
I'm going to
saw you in half.
The buddy gift gives
him one life point.
I wonder what abilities
this monster has.
Time to pull out my
trusty Tako scope.
And check his deets!
Buzz Saw Roar Dragon,
armordragon attribute.
Size Three with
7,000 power, 7,000 defense
and a critical of
four, and one ability.
Go pay Gang,
the King, a royal visit!
Right, feel the sting
of my buzz saw's teeth!
(grunting)
Sorry, Chief!
Gang, the King,
has been destroyed
and the 100 Demons Hunter
is down to four life.
This isn't your lucky day.
I have another
attack and be warned,
I'm going berserk on you!
We'll see.
Destroying a monster on my first
attack triggers my ability.
Prepare for a
double attack!
(grunting)
The 100 Demons Hunter is hit
by a surprising second attack.
And with Buzz Saw's
critical of four,
this game is
all but over!
The 100 Demons Hunter
has dropped to zero life
in just one blow.
You think that zero life
means the game is over?
You're so naive.
When I'm about to hit zero,
I can use this to stay
alive with one life.
What card does that?
I pay three gauge, discard
all cards from the field
and my hand and
call to the center.
He's gonna play it.
♪
(screams)
Fourth Omni Fire Lord,
Burn Nova!
♪
I don't believe my eyes!
Reviving from an
almost certain defeat
of zero life is
amazing enough,
but what's this
guy all about?
I better use my Tako scope
to check it out!
Fourth Omni Fire
Lord, Burn Nova!
Raging Spirits
attribute, Size Three
with 9,000 power,
8,000 defense
and a critical of two.
And we've already seen
his game changing ability.
Nice to meet you.
He looks incredible.
That's our chief for ya!
Talk about cool, hmm?
♪
What's going on?
Saving himself from
the jaws of defeat,
the 100 Demons Hunter
is back on the attack.
Let's see what he does!
Draw, charge and draw!
I activate Underling of the
Fire Lord, Ricky's ability
and pay two
gauge to do so.
I call him to the right
and use his Underling's turn.
Get a load of me.
Evolved form of
Dragon Kid, Ricky!
Underling of the
Fire Lord, Ricky is here
and ready for action.
Alright, Ricky!
It's not flashy, but
it's certainly a step up.
My threads aren't the only
thing that's changed, ki.
Feast your eyes on my
outrageous new ability.
♪
Go, Chief!
Fighting Spirit, ki!
Alright!
Incredibly, Burn Nova's power
has just increased by 5,000,
and he's gained the
ability to penetrate.
This must be the new ability
the Underling of the
Fire Lord, Ricky mentioned.
♪
Fire Lord
Bursting Fist!
♪
Uh‐oh.
(screams)
Penetrate!
(screaming)
Say goodnight,
100 Demon.
Double attack!
No chance, I cast
Green Dragon Shield!
Buzz Saw blocks the attack
and regains one life point.
(snickering)
How do you
like me now?
No way!
♪
It can't be!
It's not possible.
It can and it is.
Triple attack!
Who is this guy?
Now for the
final blow, ki!
He did it!
With zero life, I've never seen
such an incredible come back!
Game over.
Winner: 100 Demons Hunter.
And that's
how it's done.
♪
Fourth Omni Fire Lord.
So we meet again.
Now to blast the
evil out of you.
(grunts)
Okay, Buzz Saw Roar Dragon,
go back to your own world.
Have a nice trip.
So you've been undoing
Yamigedo's curse
and sending monsters
back to their worlds.
I'm sorry, we had
you all wrong, didn't we?
Sure did, Buddy Cop.
Chief here was saving
cursed monsters a long time
before he lost
his memory, ki.
Please, we need to stop Yamigedo
in order to save our planet.
You just have
to come with us.
Sorry, Daddy‐o,
but I ride alone,
and that's not my scene,
but anytime you need my help,
just say the word.
I'll be sure to show up.
If you say so.
‐So, Drum.
‐Hmm?
You think Gao'd mind if
I head over to his place?
A little birdie told me he's
been a bit off his game lately.
Sure, I think he'd
like to see you guys!
You can help cheer him up.
Just wait 'til he finds out
you're actually an Omni Lord.
Isn't that a kicker?
Hey, maybe I can even help you
get your emblem to light up too.
Let's not push
it now, Chief.
(imitating motorcycle engine)
Burn Nova!
As Gao's buddy,
it's my duty
to get him back to
his old self again.
The way things are, I can't
be with the Buddy Police.
Until I deal with my problem,
I'm a burden to everyone.
So I got to quit.
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'll teach
you all about
Fourth Omni
Fire Lord, Burn Nova.
Scorchin'!
An Omni Lord card
that uses fire
to avoid being destroyed.
You can use it when
your life points
are about to
drop down to zero.
You get one life
by giving up
the cards in your hand
and in the field.
That's a lot to give up.
Nine thousand power, a critical
of two and a triple attack.
Worth it, don't you think?
Yeah, bring on Burn Nova!
(laughing)
♪
Next time, Gao's decided
to quit Buddyfighting?
You've got to be
kidding me!
As your buddy, what
am I supposed to do?
Next episode,
"Farewell Buddyfight!"
And maybe join
us for a Buddyfight?