(roars)
(zapping)
Now that the devastating
monster, Yamigedo,
has been revived, the only way
to seal him away again is with
the power of
the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them,
and there's only one way we can!
We gotta Buddyfight!
Okay, let's try another one.
If you're on a bus
that's traveling
55 kilometers an hour,
and the Buddyfight stage
is 75 kilometers
from the school,
how long will it
take to get there?
Huh?
(helicopter puttering)
Hey, it's the Buddy Police!
Hey, look, they're heading
for the junior high building.
You know anything
about this, bro?
I'm kinda outta the loop
since I've been on leave.
You should go see.
Huh, okay.
Settle down now,
we're still in
the middle of class, kids.
(engine whining down)
A big surprise, indeed.
Thank you for cooperating.
You have a visitor.
Uh.
Oh, what a pleasant surprise.
So, what brings you here?
I can't believe that our Sofia
is working with Yamigedo.
She was posing as Death Shido.
I confirmed it personally.
I always did have
a sneaking suspicion about her.
That's the desk she used
if you'd like to check it out.
Thanks, it wouldn't hurt
to have a quick look.
Do you know where she is?
When's the last time
you heard from her?
I have no idea, she
hasn't been here in days.
(phone beeps)
Hi, any news?
No, nothing here yet either.
Of course, you'll be
the first to know.
♪
Unfortunately, the search
of her home produced
nothing useful at all.
I'm really hoping
we'll have better luck
with that tablet of hers.
We'll be in touch with you.
My door is always open.
(engine roars)
You didn't want
to check in on Gao?
I figured that I'll see him
at the meeting a little later.
A master criminal like me
can outsmart those Buddy cops.
I'm going to enjoy watching
Master Ikazuchi punish Sofia.
(chuckles)
You don't really believe
that you'll escape
punishment, do you?
(yelps)
Are you nuts, the Buddy Police
were just here looking for you!
Leave, or they'll
arrest me, too!
Come with us,
we've got bigger things
to worry about.
♪
(water whooshing)
(zapping)
Uh, what am I looking at here?
Why don't you tell us?
It looks like he's
creating a new card!
(bell chiming)
Catching up on missed
classes again today?
No, apparently, Mr. Itsuke
is busy doing something else.
I think I'll do some
Aiki‐jujutsu training instead.
Later!
We should head home, too.
Aiki‐jujutsu training, huh?
Man, he used
to practice Buddyfighting
whenever he had the chance.
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
What's weird is Gao's
only using Hero decks
these days, even in class.
Hey, you're right,
now that you mention it;
that's the deck he used
against Kazane the other day.
I heard some kids talking.
He said for some reason
Gao's not able to use
Dragon World decks anymore.
I'll be back.
Huh?
By popular demand,
I've returned from the USA!
Uh...?
Well, aren't you guys
gonna welcome me home?
Come on, it's me: Noboru Kodo!
Uh, yeah, we knew
it was you, Noboru.
It's just that,
"I'll be back,"
is something people
say when they leave.
Ugh, you don't get
my American humor!
Anyway, where's Gao?
Either of you seen him around?
(chuckling)
Huh, he can't use
Dragon decks anymore?
We're talking about
Gao Mikado, right?
Man, that's totally tragic!
That's just what
I heard, ask him!
Did you hear the news
over there that Gao
lost his first fight?
Of course I did.
I was in the States,
not on Pluto.
Everyone who Buddyfights knows.
His luck finally
ran out, I guess.
He always was lucky
with this game.
Now he understands
what I went through.
At least I didn't get
all depressed, though.
Wait a second,
it sounds to me
like you came back to Japan
because you're worried
about Gao!
Nu‐uh, that's just crazy talk!
America's got a lot
of cool stuff and all,
but I got bored and wanted
to come back, that's all!
(growls)
But since I've gone
to all this trouble
to come back,
it'd be a shame
if I couldn't enjoy, uh,
I mean, get a glimpse
of his sad face.
Sofia Sakharov
has disappeared,
whereabouts unknown.
We believe she'll
show herself trying
to get close to an Omni Lord,
so we need to be on full alert
and prepared
for the unexpected.
Here's a rundown
of the Omni Lords
we've identified so far.
First, Omni Beast Lord, Ziun.
Second, Omni Demon
Lord, Asmodai.
He's sleeping, yo.
Seventh,
Omni Earth Lord, Count Dawn.
And the one who
tripped me in Cho‐Nagoya,
Sixth Omni Storm Lord,
Variable Cord.
We're still trying
to figure out how
we can track him down.
That leaves four to go, huh?
Actually, there's only three.
Yeah, yeah, I know you
guys are relying on me.
I'm trying to become
worthy of being the fifth
Omni Dragon Lord.
Maybe one day,
this'll light up?
Hey, you see that?
This is called Ninja Arts
Art of Flashlight.
Very illuminating.
Byakuya, stop
fooling around!
♪
He actually made a new card!
Hands off!
(agonized screaming)
The card belongs to me!
♪
I'm starving, feed me
some prey worthy of this card
and do it now!
(grunting)
Master, are you okay?
It would appear he's
unable to control himself
very well right now.
Find...Gao Mikado.
I'll fight him and devour
the next fifth Omni Dragon Lord.
I don't think you're
capable of fighting anyone.
Would you prefer that I
eat you fools instead?
(nervous tittering)
We will find him
as you request.
Really, Gao's
going to Buddyfight?
Hello there, I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide for the exciting
world of Buddyfight.
Today, I'm at Castle,
where Gao Mikado
is gonna fight a mysterious
challenger named Tiger!
At least, that's
what I've heard.
That's why I'm here!
Oh, here's Gao now,
let's see what he has to say!
Okay, where is this Tiger?
Over here.
♪
Hey, uh, why are you
wearing a kitten mask?
(groans)
It's a tiger!
Well, whatever
you think you are,
I'm gonna take you down
with my Hero deck.
Hold the phone,
what's with that deck, pal?
I said I wanted to have
a dragon battle with you.
I'm a little confused;
aren't you a tiger?
Now you're a dragon?
No, I fight for Dragon World!
So, then what's
with the tiger getup?
I wear it 'cause my
last name means "tiger."
Look at that,
the mysterious fighter
is none other than Noboru Kodo!
(whoosh)
Don't forget about me!
I don't believe it!
I haven't seen you
in, like, forever!
How have you been,
and why on earth
did you come back home?
To knock some sense
into you, obviously.
Huh?
Here, catch!
Leave the rest to me!
So, what'd you go
and do that for?
If you beat me,
I'll give you your deck back,
but now use
your dragon deck.
Uh‐oh.
Yeah, sure, I understand.
Hmm.
(gears whirring)
Hurry up and luminize so I
can prove I'm better than you.
It's you!
It's Sofia Sakharov!
Wait, are they
going after Gao?
Gao Mikado, Master
Ikazuchi challenges you.
Accept or suffer
the same fate as
your dear friend, Tenbu.
That's the guy who beat Gao?
Darkness Barrier, activate!
(rumbling)
(grunting)
Not this again!
What's happening?
♪
Just when you think you're out,
they pull you back in.
‐Where are we?
‐In a Darkness Barrier.
And we're stuck in here
until we manage to defeat
that Ikazuchi fellow.
Warp successful!
Wherever there are Buddyfights,
Paruko Nanana will be there!
We have another live broadcast
from the Darkness Barrier!
Hurry up already!
Gao, will you
be able to do this?
(grunts)
Game over.
Winner: Ikazuchi.
(roars)
Grandpa.
(zapping, grunts)
You okay?
We can't do this.
Giving up without a fight?
I didn't take you for
a spineless loser!
Oh, well, it's dinner time!
‐Not so fast.
‐Huh?
What kind of player brags
about defeating someone
who can't fight back?
Let me, the great Noboru Kodo,
be your opponent.
When I'm done with you,
you won't be able
to devour an ant.
Did you hear that?
Noboru's just challenged
Ikazuchi to fight him
instead of Gao!
And then the plot thickens.
Show yourself.
All in good time,
I apologize for being
a tad late to the party.
Who are you?
I am one of the Hundred Demons,
First Knight of
the Apocalypse Gratos,
to be exact.
The fight is about to begin!
Come on, hurry,
I don't wanna miss anything.
Let's kick it into top gear!
I'm glad I had that nap.
Yeah, you're fully charged
to help Gao, yo!
(motor puttering)
How can you help, Tasuku?
You don't have a buddy
or even a core gadget.
Even so, I have no choice.
Hundred Demons
lurking in the darkness,
destroy and rampage,
devour the world!
Dark Luminize
Hundred Thunder Demons!
With golden wings at my back,
I soar through the sky!
Luminize Noble Wing Knights!
Buddyfight!
Time to raise the flag!
Parade of Hundred Demons!
I'm with Dragon World.
Ikazuchi has the first move.
First, he calls Rampage
Chizomegumo to the center,
then Stranger Dilemma
to the left, and he sets
the spell star, Yamigedo.
No, Noboru, stop!
He's just too dangerous!
It's too late.
Chizomegumo,
devour the fighter!
In your dreams,
I cast Dragonic Thunder!
(screams)
Hope you can do better
than that, tough guy.
I can, Stranger Dilemma's
Thunder Mine activates!
Say what?
I despise cocky smart alecks.
Behold, my Thunder Mine!
End of move.
Yowza, what a terrifying move!
That was Stranger Dilemma's
ability, was it not?
Yes, a Thunder Mine activates
when an opponent uses a spell.
How are you holding up, my boy.
Eh, I've had a lot worse.
Step aside and let me fight!
I couldn't forgive
myself if you ended up
like gramps Tenbu.
Why do you never give me
enough credit, Gao?
What do you mean?
This guy beat you,
so if I defeat him,
it means I'm stronger
than you, right?
I'll win and prove to you
once and for all that I'm
the better Buddyfighter.
I draw, charge and draw!
Buddy Call to the right,
Dragon Knight, El Quixote!
I'll charge to
the ends of the Earth!
I call Dragon Knight,
Red Baron to the left!
(shouts)
I equip Soar Now,
Calvary Dragon, Hyperion!
There it is; Noboru's
become one with his monster
and set up a three
in a row formation!
Red Baron, go attack Dilemma.
No, wait!
I'll show them what I can do.
Helping Gao is just a bonus.
Another clipped wing
for my Red Baron.
An Assault of Glory!
(zapping)
I'm tired of him
doubting my abilities
and treating Gao like
he's some kind of hero!
(zapping)
End of move.
That boy has something special.
He could prove useful
as a sacrificial pawn
for the great Yamigedo.
I cast Hundred Demon
Sorcery, Akishoki!
With six life,
I can draw two cards.
Yeah!
He deliberately
allowed the attack
so he could cast that spell.
Increasing the cards in his hand
does not bode well for Noboru.
But he can't use it without
a Hundred Demons card
in the field.
Huh?
His set spell must have
a Hundred Demons attribute.
He's calling one Hundred Demons
monster after the other!
(zapping)
♪
Thanks to Zion's ability,
Dilemma is revived in
the center position.
I equip.
Veiled in the
darkness of terror,
awake the mighty jaws
of the wicked beast
that hungers for misery,
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
Devour him completely,
my Hundred Demons!
I move Red Baron to the center!
In thrust I trust!
Ugh, I'm hit!
Demonic Descend, Slash!
Eraser Blade!
Noboru is hit with three damage.
Serve me best by perishing!
Narukami boosts its critical
by destroying a fellow monster.
Disappear, underling!
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
He blocks and gains one life.
End of move.
Master's being too
reckless out there.
He's using all of his energy
to just stay standing.
I hate to think what he
might do if he loses the fight.
This will finish you off!
I call to the left,
Dragon Knight, Vlad Dracula!
(roaring)
Time heals all wounds, but a
true warrior never forgets.
I will not let you venture
into the unknown alone,
young dragon warrior!
Vlad Dracula's
critical increases
with each Dragon Knight card
that's in the Drop Zone.
Six?
A critical of that magnitude
is formidable, indeed.
And Ikazuchi has six life left.
Noboru could win it here.
There's no way this weirdo's
stronger than Gao,
and if I defeat him,
then Gao should return
to his old self.
There sure is a lot
riding on this.
I could get another
shot at fighting Gao,
my ultimate rival!
I have gotta win this!
Somebody's on fire.
Bloody Charge, activate!
Dragon Knight Vlad Dracula,
attack the fighter!
I will fight you with
everything in my arsenal!
I cast Gedo Shield!
I'll devour the attack!
Let's see how you
respond to that, Dragon Boy!
Amazing, Noboru
receives one damage point!
Along with blocking the attack,
that spell inflicts damage
on the opponent!
Talk about one scary card!
Ready, my boy?
Oh, yeah, Hyperion!
Assault of Glory!
End of move.
I'll finish him
on my next turn.
You won't have
a next turn, sorry.
I need to eat, feed me!
Don't look now, but I think
something's wrong with Ikazuchi!
I'm starving, must devour!
Feed me!
♪
The most powerful demon beast
that is starving
for destruction!
Devour the Hundred Demons
and show yourself,
Great Fiend, Yamigedo!
♪
Good golly, he's Buddy
called Great Fiend, Yamigedo
to the right position!
♪
(roars)
This can't be good!
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
Once again, that spell helps
him regain one life point.
It's no use, Noboru, watch out!
Yamigedo's
Thunder Mine activates!
(grunts)
What colossal power!
Noboru was able to block
Yamigedo's attack,
but he couldn't
prevent the damage
from his Thunder Mine!
At least it's better
than taking a direct hit.
I said, "Feed me,"
and I mean now!
Here comes Yamigedo's
double attack!
(screams)
Dinner is served!
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
You're not that tough.
Time I showed you
the skills I picked up
in the great old US of A!
‐Not yet!
‐Huh?
The dark and evil power
they call Demonic
and all of it
is controlled by me!
Time for Final Phase!
I cast.
Did he say, "Final Phase"?
I guess he must have
an impact card!
Now is the time
to show your power!
Unorthodox Arts,
Shoraiabare Kandachi!
I shall ride again!
To the light!
(grunts)
All his monsters and his
item have been destroyed!
What an incredible card!
But that's not all.
For each card
that was destroyed,
he inflicts damage points
to his opponent.
(grunting)
♪
(screams)
Noboru!
(grunting)
I'm not surprised.
If he's absorbed Yamigedo's
massive level of energy,
there's no way his body
will be able to handle it.
It's a miracle he's been able
to keep it together
for this long.
I always wondered what
the human threshold was
for such power.
We can't maintain
the Darkness Barrier
any longer.
♪
(whooshing)
What happened, we lost?
Don't make a move, Sofia!
You're completely surrounded!
We've got an arrest warrant
for you and Ikazuchi.
So, you better come
peacefully, ya dig?
Even in my weakened condition,
I can still prevent you from
making a getaway with that
mysterious power of yours.
I cannot allow that to happen.
Who's that?
You were defeated,
so you lose everything.
(gasping)
That is the fight code of honor.
♪
And just who are you
supposed to be?
Silence, I will deal
with you later.
What have you done?
Why you‐‐
(grunting)
I will be taking
these two with me.
You're what?
What did you expect?
He lost.
You must accept
the consequences of defeat.
Now, don't try anything.
With your Omni Lord
at reduced strength,
there's no way
to prevent the inevitable.
You wanna test that theory?
No need, I bid you all farewell!
♪
What sorcery is this?
That spooky‐looking
mystery monster
just made Ikazuchi,
Noboru, and Sofia
disappear right
before our very eyes!
What the...how
on earth did he do that?
♪
We were too late.
(ding)
♪
Huh?
Sorry, Gao.
♪
(grunting)
Poor Noboru, it should
have been me fighting!
It's not your fault.
(grunting)
Noboru!
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, we'll talk
about Unorthodox Arts,
Shoraiabare Kandachi.
I'm all ears!
The Hundred Demons impact card
uses Thunder Mine
to destroy enemies.
It destroys one opponent's card
for each Thunder Mine card
the fighter has
in the Drop Zone,
and for every destroyed card,
one damage is dealt
to the opponent.
No way!
So, load up on
Thunder Mine monsters
and seal the deal
with this impact card.
Speaking of sealing the deal,
what do you day
we get out early today?
(chuckles)
♪
Next time, we find out
Dragon Kid Ricky
is an Omni Lord,
and Mukuro Shigamine
captures him to take
his Omni Lord emblem!
But Gao and I
are on the case!
Next episode...
Join us for a Buddyfight!