♪
Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies
with humans.
But now a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the 100 Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy skill on!
♪
Because they
believed in me,
I found my
purpose in this game.
Here it is, Gao!
Alright!
♪
Dalahast, attack the Jamadhar
in the center position!
♪
Death Shido's
center is now wide open!
Uh‐oh.
This is
Cait Sith's strength!
Come again?
He increases an item's
critical by three points.
No way, how
can that be fair?
‐Famous Sword, Hrunting!
‐Why me?
This is for
calling me annoying!
Meow, meow!
(screaming)
♪
As feared, the arrival
of the 100 Demons,
that ruthless group
of illegal monsters
from various
parallel worlds
has resulted in relentless
destruction in our cities.
The Buddy Police are
overwhelmed with their task
of apprehending
these depraved creatures
who place no value
on human life.
They can be identified
by a mark on their card
displaying a
Japanese word for demon.
You like that?
Go home, 100 Demon.
You're wrong.
I keep telling you
I'm not a 100 Demon.
I'm a regular
illegal monster.
If that's true, then
you'd better prove it.
I‐‐I can,
just take a look.
♪
Hmm.
Just as I told you, ki.
No 100 Demons mark
visible on this one.
Too bad.
‐Come on, let's roll.
‐Okey‐dokey.
Go back to
your own world.
(imitating motorcycle engine)
Awaken, power
of darkness!
Power of evil,
power of the 100 Demons!
♪
Why are there
Earthlings here among us?
We'll be the ones asking
the questions, thank you.
I don't speak
with low lifes.
Easy, Dekelfar Demon.
They're our allies.
Yeah, listen to
Master Ikazuchi
and try to lose
the attitude, bub!
Heim, is it?
You're going to team up
with me to steal Tenbu and‐‐
I'd never join forces
with the likes of you.
You don't seem
to understand!
You don't
have a choice!
It's you who
doesn't understand.
Awaken,
Bronze Giant, Talos!
♪
A 100 Demons card?
But how did‐‐
Talos, silence the human.
Yes.
Sledgehammer!
Help me, Master!
♪
You were so close.
How can a 100 Demons
monster call another one?
Hmm.
That's enough, Heim.
Now, I need you to
go steal Tenbu for me.
Do whatever you
wish after that.
And you guys do
anything Heim asks!
But that's not fair.
I'm the one in charge.
♪
This is Gao Mikado.
All you require from me is to
seize Tenbu from this human?
That's right.
Do you think that
you can achieve this?
(snickering)
The Great Demon, Heim,
is capable of much
more than that.
‐Hmm?
Hey, you guys, what's up?
You feeling okay?
Hrunting.
Artemis Arrow.
‐They're serious!
‐Not again!
♪
A 100 Demon detected
in that direction, ki.
Yeah, I can smell
the stench from here.
‐Let's ride!
‐Okey‐dokey!
(imitating motorcycle engine)
(gasps)
(grunts)
I don't get it, why
are they doing this?
Hmm.
♪
They're possessed
by 100 Demons.
Hmm, that explains it.
Huh?
(grunts)
(snickering)
I'm surprised you
could detect my presence.
You must be the one who's
done this to Baku and Kuguru.
Give me Tenbu to see
them back as they were.
So this guy's
after Gramps too.
(gasps)
I won't be the reason why
these kids are put in danger.
Are you the Fifth
Omni Dragon, Lord Tenbu?
Indeed, I am.
Stew me, roast me,
I'll let you do
what you like,
but first, you must agree to
return them back to normal.
Tenbu!
What are you
doing, Gramps?
With that,
I will be leaving.
Get back here, Demon!
Drum, give me
your buddy skill.
(gasps)
Surprise, surprise.
A 100 Demon doesn't
keep his promise.
It's Gao,
there's trouble.
What, he took Tenbu?
Now, Stella,
send in some support!
All of our officers
are already on other calls.
Hmm, we'll have to send in youth
officers, Tetsuya and Zanya.
Yes, sir!
(groans)
What do you wanna do?
(grunts)
Ban!
Ban‐ban‐ban‐
ban‐ban‐ban‐ban!
The 100 Demon hunters
are on the scene, ki.
I think I'm afraid to ask.
Let's have some fun.
Flying Sparks!
Don't hide, demons!
Come out and
fight me with honor!
Yeah, stop hiding, ki.
(grunting)
♪
(groans)
‐Huh?
Don't worry,
bright eyes.
I didn't
forget about you.
Huh?
Stop it!
Hey, lay off!
What's your
problem, huh, pal?
Yeah, what's
your problem?
I'm not just gonna stand here
and watch you hurt my friends!
They aren't your friends.
Look again!
Huh?
Ha ha.
(gasps)
Hmm?
Chief, hold up.
This is the
Buddy Police boy wonder
who replaced
Tasuku Ryuenji,
or should I say the
Buddy Police trainee, ki.
Huh?
Wimping out, not letting
me attack illegals
that are
possessing humans.
That's what they're
teaching you these days?
Good thing
I'm around.
(grunts)
Sure you're
cut out for this?
I guess that's why you're
still a trainee, huh, kid?
Huh?
(screams)
(shudders)
Well, aren't you
gonna do something?
(static)
♪
Huh?
A Buddy Police barrier.
How long are you planning
on sitting on me?
Gao!
Leave this
one to us, yo.
Yeah, you should
go get Tenbu back.
Thanks a lot, guys.
♪
Decker Road, open!
Decker Drum's
on patrol!
Buddy Police,
emergency launch!
Illegal monster going down.
(siren wailing)
Now that this barrier's up,
we can't get out, ki.
That brat made
me pull a muscle.
‐Huh?
Yeah!
Wherever
there's a Buddyfight,
Paraku Nanana
will be there.
She looks familiar.
Where have we
seen her before?
You mean you
really don't know me?
I need to work
on my social media.
Zanya, you might have to
fight Kuguru and if you do,
with your fear of girls,
you'll be behind
the eight ball
before the fight
even starts.
Ha, I actually
welcome the challenge.
Huh?
You really didn't think
that I would let something
so silly effect me
forever, did you?
Please.
(groans)
Can you even see
anything like that?
I may not be able
to see like normal,
but I can see
with my mind's eye.
‐Whatever.
‐Right, okay.
Let's get to the action.
Everybody at home
say it with me now.
Buddy...
Fight!
‐Raise the flag.
I'm with Magic World!
Legend World.
I fight for
Katana World!
Legend World.
So what are we gonna do about
that 100 Demons guy, ki?
Nothing we can do.
We'll just have to wait
until the fight is over,
and enjoy being
spectators for once.
There he is up ahead!
I'm on it!
Leave it to one
of Decker Drum's
seven secrets to
bring him down.
Decker handcuffs!
(grunting)
(growls)
Darkness Barrier, activate!
(roaring)
‐Huh?
♪
What a surprise.
Welcome back, Buddy Cop.
What do you say?
Lucky for you,
I was nearby
and set up this
Darkness Barrier for you,
so how about a
little thank you, huh?
Even for a human,
you're dumb.
I've had enough
of your ignorance!
I already have Tenbu, so tell
me, He of Superior Intellect,
why should I fight them?
You make a good point.
I messed up!
Maybe we could‐‐
Just deactivate the barrier.
Once a Darkness
Barrier's been raised,
it can't be deactivated until
a Buddyfight's officially over.
You're a fool.
Hey!
You'd better return
Gramps Tenbu right away!
I'd be happy to
if you're capable
of defeating me
in a Buddyfight.
Well, let's find out.
Good.
I'm glad all of
that is settled.
Now, hurry up and
get to the Buddy area.
Dream on, you
uncultured rube!
Why me?
Burning like an inferno
with limitless spirit!
Luminize!
Crimson Dragon Fist!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path!
Witness their
awesome power.
Luminize!
Hundred Legend!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm with Dragon World!
I fight for
Legend World.
Sledgehammer!
(grunts)
Bronze Giant,
Talos hits Zanya,
stripping him of
three valuable life points.
And now the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Here's my Tako scope.
Now locking on to
Bronze Giant, Talos.
Attribute is
Olympus, Size Two.
Power is 2,000,
but defense is 6,000.
A critical of three but
no ability or life link.
Zanya's just called Accelerate
Ninja Hayate to the left,
buddy called Nanomachine
Ninja Tsukikage to the right
and he equips Five
Heavenly Swords, Onimaru.
I'll use Five Heavenly
Swords, Onimaru
to attack
Bronze Giant, Talos!
♪
And just like that,
Onimaru's 6,000 power
takes out Talos like
the morning garbage.
It looks like
Zanya wasn't kidding
about that mind's eye stuff.
Let's check in and
see how Tetsuya's doing.
I'm gonna pay one gauge and set
Solomon's Great Barrier, yo.
Now, all of the Size Two
72 Pillars monsters
can be called as
Size One monsters.
Yeah, now let's cramp
this guy's style.
I call Dance Asmodai
to the right area.
Dance is my life.
Hang with me and watch
homie get his groove on,
cause when I'm called,
you can draw one card!
Cool, look who it is!
I love this guy.
It's the great Dance Asmo‐‐
actually, that name's too long.
We'll call
him Dance Modai.
Next, I call his bro,
Let's Play Asmodai
to the left, yo.
When we bust a move
playing a sport,
our hearts pump
and give us energy.
There's nothing like
friendly competition.
When I'm called to play,
you regain one life point.
And now it's Let's Play Asmo‐‐
wait, that's too long as well.
How about we call
him Play Modai?
It should come
as no surprise
that Tetsuya's deck is
stacked full of Asmodai's.
Okay, Dance Modai, show
us some off the chain moves.
Ready to be
dipped by a demon?
Demon tango!
Fresh off the bench,
Play Modai's up.
Go give it your all.
It's a hit and a slam.
I just made a double play.
Will the real Asmodai
please stand up?
‐Your turn!
‐Okay.
Leave it up
to me, Tets.
Demon drop kick!
End of move.
Tetsuya's dominating the
fight with his Asmodai army.
Now then, in the
other match up,
Kuguru's called out
Stellar Deity, Astraeus,
Gorgon Three
Sisters, Medusa,
and Wind Fairy Sylph.
Talk about three girls with
incompatible attributes.
Meow!
If I can't see them, then it's
like they aren't really there.
Tsukikage,
attack the center!
Must defend.
I cast Berserk
Guard Spell.
It increases Medusa's
power and defense by 2,000
and lets her
counter attack.
♪
Nanomachine
Body Replacement!
I must adjust to seeing
with my mind's eye.
Ha!
Forward Saizo,
attack the fighter.
Hide in the mist and
cut through the shadows.
Mutation Sword navigates
through the unknown.
♪
End of move.
Now they're both
down to five life,
and Kuguru has a
chance to answer back.
Must attack.
Draw, charge and draw.
I equip Immortal
Sword, Durandal.
You got to be
kidding me!
She has Immortal Sword,
Durandal in her deck too?
This girl's bringing out
all the heavy hitters today.
She's definitely built a deck
with a lot of good cards,
but with a Wydar Sarkal
attribute Sylph,
a star attribute, Astraeus,
and the hero attribute,
Durandal cards,
there's absolutely no balance
or synergy to them at all.
I cast.
I discard a
card from my hand.
I cast Great Spell
Thunder of Zeus.
As ruler of the skies,
I beckon the power of thunder
and lightning
to eradicate evil.
Punish these demons!
(groaning)
Celestial forces
are something
we don't want to
be messing with, Tets!
My posse!
(screams)
Divine stallion, Pegasus,
Moon Celestial, Selene,
Bronze Giant, Talos,
attack the fighter!
(groans)
With that flurry, Tetsuya's
down to just two life.
If he's hit by Talos' attack,
it's the end of the line.
Sledgehammer!
I cast Solomon Shield!
End of move.
What a great move.
Tetsuya used a counter
spell just in time
to stop the deciding blow,
but he has no monsters
left in the field,
and to make matters worse,
he has only two cards
left in his hand.
Over in the other game, Zanya's
down to just one life point.
It's more likely
I'll grow an extra head
than see these
two win today.
♪
With my mind's eye,
I have no blind spots.
Tsukikage,
attack the fighter!
(screams)
Five Heavenly
Swords, Onimaru!
I cast!
Huh?
You've fallen
into my trap.
I pay three gauge to activate
Super Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword,
Star Crusher!
(grunts)
The master of set
spells does it again!
Zanya played it perfectly
with the patience
to see his Super Lethal
Formation through to the end.
♪
Game over.
Winner:
Zanya Kisaragi.
Huh?
Meanwhile, Tetsuya has used
Key of Solomon, First Volume
to increase
his gauge by two.
I cast.
I'm gonna pay four gauge
and sacrifice one life point
so I can cast Great Spell
Devil's Rock and Roll, yo.
I wondered when he'd bring
out his favorite great spell.
Devil's Rock and Roll
returns all player's
Size Two or smaller monsters
currently in the field
back to their
individual hands.
And then Tetsuya gets to check
the top five cards in his deck,
and if he wants, he can call up
to three 72 Pillars monsters.
‐Oh, yeah!
‐Long live rock and roll!
Let's bust it out,
Valefar and Zagan.
Go give Baku what for!
Feel the beat.
Music is my life.
This one packs a punch.
(growling)
(screams)
Big Finish!
Rock and roll forever!
♪
Yeah, I did it!
I'll be taking that
100 Demons card, ki.
What are you doing?
Don't be a hater, yo.
‐Wait!
‐Huh?
Tetsuya!
We need to get
that card back!
Huh?
There's something I got to talk
over with these 100 Demons.
Thanks for
softening 'em up.
Thanks for your
hard work, ki.
Ready to burn rubber?
Okey dokey.
(imitating motorcycle engine)
Curse you, human.
‐Double penetrate!
Crimson Fist Dragoblade!
Now, it's time to give
us back Grandpa Tenbu.
Final Phase.
No, it can't be,
not again!
I cast!
♪
(machinery whirring)
Impact!
Gigantic Crusher!
(screams)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Yeah.
All in a day's work.
Hey, why isn't the 100 Demons
card appearing as usual?
I don't know.
For all his big talk,
Heim was defeated so easily.
I guess that means the
Tenbu card was lost too.
‐No need to worry.
‐Huh?
I didn't
lose anything.
I merely let my
clone take my place
so I could hang back and
observe my opponent's skills.
Hey, come back!
Hand over that
Tenbu card right away!
Huh?
Give Grandpa Tenbu
back or else!
Now you see how it is.
‐Open a portal.
‐I think not.
It would be unwise to
refuse me, and you know it,
for I can still hurt those kids
that you care about so much.
(growls)
You demons
have no honor,
but it appears that
I have no choice.
‐Huh?
(grunting)
♪
Intense.
Yeah, but what now?
Wait, come back!
You can't leave me
behind like this.
Let's go.
Master wants you.
(screams)
I'll get that Heim.
How dare he
abandon me like this.
(growls)
The unlikelihood,
given that he used Tenbu
to open a portal and flee.
I conclude that he must be
heading to Dragon World.
Listen up, Gao,
Count Dawn believes
that Heim is currently on
his way to Dragon World.
Don't let this
guy get you down.
Tenbu's tough.
We'll get a chance to
bring him back, I know it.
Hope so.
I just can't
help thinking.
Maybe I'm not worthy of
being Tasuku's replacement.
(grunts)
Gao.
Don't beat
yourself up.
Nobody's perfect.
Especially you humans.
Now let's go to Dragon World
and get Gramps.
Alright.
♪
Are you kidding?
They left for Dragon World
without consulting us first?
Most interesting.
♪
I just hope nothing
goes wrong over there.
(metal scraping)
Huh?
(breathing heavily)
Hey, Tasu!
♪
I don't get it.
It doesn't make any sense.
How could Tasuku
be fighting against
the Purgatory Knight?
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna teach
you all about the card
‐Province Baron, Shido.
‐Alright!
He's a tricky monster
that slips past his enemy
and attacks the
fighter directly.
His Shadow Dive ability
lets him attack your opponent
even if they have a
monster in the center,
and if he causes damage,
you regain one life point.
He kinda looks like‐‐
I know, he looks a
little familiar to me too.
Huh, must be
our imagination.
I'd never imagine
someone so goofy looking.
(laughs)
♪
Next time, Gao
learns that Tasuku
must defeat the monsters
in his past to find peace,
but what is Star Guardian,
Jackknife?
Next episode "Crossnize!
Star Dragon World!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!