(wind blowing)
♪
I'm afraid
we are too late.
This marks the fourth
world he's destroyed,
and counting.
And what of the next
planet in his path?
We must protect it,
no matter the cost.
But who are we
to defy fate?
We're the Great 8, you dig?
There's no time,
let's get going.
Empowering the forces
of earth, water,
fire, and air,
we summon forth all souls
that came to Dragon,
Demon, Beast, and Deity
to safeguard
the world of humans
from this titan of terror!
♪
I just don't think
it's the one for me, man.
What else you got?
Just give me a
minute to think, bro.
What's there
to think about?
It's a blank impact card.
It can be anything you want.
Just make it the most
powerful card possible.
We can't, it's the whole
yin and yang thing.
Explain it to him, Kukuru.
In theory
you'd be right,
but with great power
comes weakness, too.
It's all about balance.
I think you should at least
give my first idea a chance.
But it's kinda your call.
Hmm.
♪
Okay, you're
the one who knows
my fighting style the best.
If you think that's
the one for me,
I trust you.
Really?
I'm just so stoked
we get to create
a new impact card.
I can't wait to
use it in a fight.
Yeah, it's gonna be choice.
Gao, come quick,
it's horrible!
Huh, what is it, Hana?
(crowd murmuring)
♪
What's going on, Tets?
I don't know,
you tell me, yo.
♪
Uh, uh, Z?
Try and focus.
Clear your mind
of distractions.
But I think you'll
want to see this.
What is it?
A giant dragon has
appeared over Chou‐Tokyo Bay.
And it appears
to be making its way
to the Sky Tower.
It's obvious this creature
is from another world,
but as of yet,
no one in the vicinity
has identified it
as their Buddy.
The fear is that
we're dealing with
a rogue, illegal monster.
What's an illegal monster, Gao?
Ah, well, it's
like that thing
right, Drum,
tell her about it.
Like that thing.
It's what they call a monster
from a parallel world
that comes to Earth
without transporting
through a Buddy Card.
You understand?
Couldn't have said
it better myself.
It was on the tip
of my tongue.
♪
Stella, status update.
The monster has not been
registered in our system,
which confirms
our suspicions
that it is in fact‐‐
Commander I, Card Burn
and I have just arrived
at the scene, sir.
And right on cue,
the Buddy Police have arrived.
Hey, isn't that‐‐
Are you getting this,
Commander I?
Yes, I am.
He's Luminized
some Buddyfight cards.
He's got six cards
in his hand
and two cards
in the gauge.
You know what to do.
Time for the
Buddy Police barrier.
♪
All right,
let's do this.
Catching outlaws
with cards of justice.
Luminize.
Fighting Card Burn.
I have no
quarrel with you.
I seek the strongest
Buddyfighter in your world.
Is he looking at me?
I think he's looking at me.
Did he say the
strongest Buddyfighter?
Hear that?
Yeah!
But if you insist,
Buddy Call!
No, wait.
(screaming)
(struggling)
(yells)
Stand down.
If you know
what's good for you,
you'll surrender now.
Your innocuous threats
are entirely
useless against me.
Now brace yourself, human.
Finishing Move.
(screaming)
Takihara, no!
This is history
in the making, folks.
For the first time ever,
the Buddy Police
has been defeated
by an illegal monster.
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
Commentator Paruko
Nanana will be there.
Paruko, what on Earth
are you doing here?
Oh, hi, Miss Haneda.
I'm just here to call the
play‐by‐play of the fight
and...ahh!
Paruko!
Tako‐chuu!
Tako‐chuu, tako‐chuu, tako‐chuu!
Takosuke,
are you okay?
You put me down
right this minute,
you big slimy bully!
There's a call coming in.
And it's from
you know who, sir.
All right,
put him through.
This is Commander I.
You think you're up for it?
Then you have
my authorization.
Buddy Skill, on.
I told you already,
I'm searching for the
strongest Buddyfighter
this planet has to offer.
Are there no worthy
fighters to be found here?
As you heard, the
unidentified monster
is demanding the world's
best Buddyfighter.
Him, are you sure?
Do you really
think he's ready?
I do.
And I need you
to back him up.
Mmm, roger that.
Well, what's our strategy?
He's sending a
Buddyfighter our way.
Probably the best we've got.
I'll hang on to you until
someone challenges me.
What?
Sorry I took so long, Paruko.
It's you?
Gao Mikado's the
best we've got?
Well, I guess he is.
After Tasuku Ryuenji went
to go train in Dragon World,
nobody else really
comes to mind.
The Aibo Academy
grade six student
has taken Tasuku's place
as the boy wonder cop
of the Buddy Police.
That is, he will once he
sheds the temporary title
of trainee.
Now let's see‐‐
I won't be a
trainee for long!
This child is the most
formidable Buddyfighter
on your planet?
Tako‐chuu, aahh!
He's here, you
can let go of me!
Temper, temper, o fiery one.
I think I'll hold on
to you as insurance
that your people
aren't trying to trick me.
Isn't this overgrown
mutant breaking
some intergalactic
law or something?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
Gramps, easy now.
You can keep
Paruko, all right?
Are you out of your
mind, lizard brain?
But the condition is
you have to defeat Gao.
Huh?
How can a mere boy be a
fitting opponent for me?
I thought you
were looking for
the world's
toughest Buddyfighter.
Between us dragons,
this guy's it.
(snickering)
It seems insolence
is a quality
even dragons have
on this planet.
Okay, I'll fight him.
My dear, just wait here.
This won't take long.
You better win, Gao!
I'm Gao Mikado,
the Mighty Sun Fighter.
Before we
start the fight,
tell me your name, old timer.
It's been many moons
since anyone has used it.
I forget the name
that I am called.
Huh?
Ha, I had you going
there, huh, kid?
Uh...
They call me Tenbu.
The Fifth Omni Dragon Lord.
Well, it's an
honor to meet you.
You ready?
Indeed I am.
But you'll have to
train a million years
before you can beat me.
My bravery will shine
brightly on this day.
Luminize, Flight Formation.
You wanted to use
your new powers.
Well, there's no time
like the present, pal.
Watch and learn.
Sculpting my body
with red hot flames,
carving out a new path
with my own two fists.
Crimson Battler,
Drum Bunker Dragon
is reporting for duty.
Wow, looks like Drum's
been working out.
He's trained in
the martial arts.
Check this out, kid,
my crimson fist
packs a punch.
Now Gao's gonna Luminize.
Wait till you see
how we feature
Drum's new abilities.
I built Gao
a sweet new deck.
I rock.
Burning like an inferno,
with limitless spirit!
Luminize, Crimson Dragon Fist!
What do you say,
we doin' this or what?
It's a monster from
a parallel world.
Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu
versus our very own Buddy
Police trainee, Gao Mikado!
Buddyfight, ha ha!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Dragon World.
I'm also fighting
for Dragon World.
And the first move
goes to Tenbu.
Charge and draw.
I call Extreme Sword
Dragon to the center.
Attack the fighter.
All right!
Ugh!
End of move.
Right off the bat,
Gao suffers three damage.
Let's see how he
answers on his move.
You better win this.
If that creep
takes me prisoner,
I'm coming for your dragon!
Come on, show some faith.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Crimson Battler,
Extreme Blow Dragon
to the right.
Who wants to make friends
with my crimson flurry?
Next I call Break Shoulder
Dragon to the left!
In battle, there is
no need for words.
And I equip Crimson
Fist, Dragoblaze!
He set up an attack with
two monsters and an item.
And each one has
a critical of three.
Oh, yeah,
it's his specialty.
The Gao formation!
All right, Extreme Blow.
Clear out the
center for me!
In with a right
and a left,
and a right!
Okay, Break Shoulder, go
and attack Grandpa Tenbu.
Will do.
Now, I cast Dragon Breath.
(roars)
(belch)
Okay, you asked for it.
Ignite, my fists of fury!
Crimson Fist,
Dragoblaze!
End of move.
That's what
I'm talkin' about!
Gao responds by causing
three damage of his own.
Gao's new deck
is off the chain,
hey, A‐dawg?
Yeah, but this
Dragon Lord is no slouch.
The match is just beginning.
Tenbu calls Boomerang
Dragon to the right,
another Extreme Sword
Dragon to the center,
and Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the left.
Boomerang, go
attack Extreme Blow.
I ain't afraid of
you, kangaroo boy.
You're going down,
you dunny rat!
Argh!
Swing and a miss.
Extreme Sword,
Systemic Dagger,
attack the boy.
(Gao yells)
End of move.
No, Gao just suffered five
damage points in one turn!
Not looking good.
He's only got
two life left.
Don't worry,
Akatsuki, remember,
Gao's fighting
with a new deck.
I'm sure he has some
strategy in mind.
Your move.
I draw, charge and draw!
I call to the
right and left,
Crimson Battler,
Spin Nail Dragon!
I attack Extreme Sword
with the Spin Nail
on the right.
You can't
fight these nails!
Spinning pierce!
And now I attack Tenbu
with the Spin Nail
on the left.
Spinning pierce!
Arrgh!
If Gao's direct
attack hits,
both players will be tied
with two life points.
Crimson Fist!
No chance, I cast
Green Dragon Shield.
End of move.
I thought you were
gonna win this, Gao!
Instead of being tied,
the Green Dragon
Shield has increased
Tenbu's life
points to six!
(snickering)
Told you‐‐draw,
charge and draw.
You're finished, rookie.
(Gao growls)
I Buddy Call.
In Systemic Dagger's place,
I Buddy Call myself
to the center.
Fifth Omni
Dragon Lord, Tenbu
is heading into battle.
What on Earth's going on?
Agh, how could old scale
face do a self Buddy Call?
Isn't that against
the rules or something?
No, it's quite legal.
I assure you, my dear.
How about a good luck kiss?
Ugh, no, how about not?
Be warned,
for when I appear,
I destroy all my opponent's
monsters in the field.
Take this‐‐
Howling Fire.
I cast..
Gao!
(shouting)
(groaning)
That ability's
bad news, bro.
I know, destroying
all of Gao's monsters
just by being called.
Is my big brother gonna lose?
Why does this has
to be the first match
Gao ever loses?
I don't want to be the prize
to that creepy old dragon!
You know, I think
we're gonna be okay.
Keep it on the DL,
but Gao's already cast
the Skies In Your Hand spell.
I've never heard
of that one, yo.
Ha!
♪
I returned all of
my monsters to my hand
when I cast the Skies
In Your Hand spell.
You said your name
was Gao Mikado?
You are much better
than I expected.
But I'm not done yet.
Prepare for another attack!
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Hey, what was that?
I think you
chipped a tooth.
That really hurt!
Quit your whining, Gramps.
Don't dish it out
if you can't take it.
That's our Gao!
He rips out
a Dragon Shield
just when he
needs it the most!
Now keep it up,
you're on a roll!
Your move.
Okay, kid, let's show this
relic our counter attack.
Yeah, it's time
to get serious.
I draw!
Huh, heh,
charge and draw.
I Buddy Call my partner,
Crimson Battler, Drum
Bunker Dragon to the right!
Man, I was starting
to nod off!
(grunting)
Let's do this!
I call Spin Nail
Dragon to the left.
All three of us are
gonna do a link attack
on Grandpa Tenbu.
Sounds good.
Hey, hang on a second.
Huh?
You know that I
want to knock out
that old geezer as
much as you do, right?
But we both know that
Spin Nail over there
has enough power to
defeat Gramps on his own.
You missed it, huh?
I noticed Tenbu didn't
call Boomerang Dragon.
It's 'cause that card
is no longer in his hand.
So what does that tell you,
O wise and worldly dragon?
Well, that he's holding
different cards right now.
Yeah, strengthening spells
that boost his defense.
I get it now,
the link attack's
to raise our attack power
as much as possible.
We should be able
to finish him off
for good now.
Hey, thanks for clearing that
up for me there, old buddy.
You ready?
‐Oh, yeah.
Three on one hardly
seems a fair fight.
You're one to talk, Gramps.
Drill Ram Break!
Ugh!
Don't forget what happens
when I have
Dragoblaze equipped.
I gain the
penetrate ability.
You say penetrate?
Doesn't that mean
I'm gonna receive
three damage points?
Guess you're not
just a pretty face.
Agh!
You fight quite well,
but you have
a long way to go
to be at my level, child.
I still have
four life points.
I'm afraid this
is the end for you.
Don't fret, my dear.
I won't be but
a minute longer.
No, please take your time.
Huh, wait, Gao always
has an impact card
in his hand at
a time like this.
I bet he's gonna
use his Roaring Slash,
Gargantua Punisher!
Actually, I gave that
back to my pal Tasuku.
Why do you hate me?
No biggie, I've got a
brand new impact card.
Wha‐‐wha?
So, which one is it?
When his opponent
has four life or less,
and he's equipped an item
with the word
fist in its name‐‐
And neither player
has a monster
in the center
position, then...
Final phase.
Go, Gao!
I cast!
♪
This impact card
costs three gauge
and causes four damage
that cannot be reduced.
♪
Impact!
Gigantic Crusher!
This is gonna hurt.
Ooh, yeah, that hurt.
♪
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
Thanks, just
protecting the planet.
Boy, Gigantic Crusher,
huh, that's a new one.
I've never heard
of such a card.
What can you
tell us about it?
Not much, news to me too.
No one knows.
It's a new card that
Baku just created.
Actually, it's a card
we all made together, bro.
Thanks, Baku,
you're the best.
I would have
never been able
to think up
a card like this.
That's some fine work, trainee.
Now, leave the rest to us.
I owe you a
major thanks, Gao.
You and that card saved me
from being that strange
old dragon's prisoner.
Well, hello there, my dear.
Uh, pardon.
Come here often?
Seriously?
Now you must tell us,
why are you searching
for our world's
greatest Buddyfighter?
They will be
the only person
who can prevent
what is to come.
The overwhelming threat
that is approaching
this world as we speak.
Hang on, what are
you talking about?
Don't speak in riddles.
Hmm.
Why won't he tell us?
Huh?
It's raining.
♪
Hey, this wasn't
in the forecast.
This humidity is
murder on my hair!
Hmm, huh?
(thunder booming)
♪
Oh, man, is that
another monster?
No, it's definitely human.
How are they doing that?
They aren't using
a Buddy Skill.
I don't know.
(sinister laughing)
Look out!
(screaming)
Drum!
I'm gonna eat you up!
Hey, are you okay, pal?
Y‐‐yeah.
What's your problem?
♪
(snickering)
Stop right there.
Huh?
♪
Uh?
Tenbu, are you all right?
I'm fine.
So, what is this
overwhelming threat
you were just
talking about?
An overwhelming threat?
I don't know,
I don't recall
anything about that.
Huh?
What's happening?
Look!
Unauthorized portals
from parallel worlds
are opening all over.
You mean they aren't
connected to Buddy Cards?
That's right.
And we're not talking
about one or two.
I estimate 100.
Uh, 100?
But how?
And from which world?
All of them,
Magic, Danger, Katana,
Ancient, Legend!
And monsters are starting
to come through the portals!
♪
Are you seeing this, folks?
Portals from parallel worlds
have opened above the Sky Tower
and a terrifying number
of illegal monsters
are coming to Earth!
What does this mean
for our planet?
♪
Who's behind this?
Well, one thing
is definitely clear,
this has to be the
overwhelming threat
that Tenbu was talking about.
Wait a minute, sir,
the monsters' signals
are disappearing.
What's that?
♪
(water rushing)
What, you can't really
be hungry already?
Okay, then give me more,
more of your glorious power.
With the 100 demons
under my control,
I'll devour this entire world
and its pathetic
future along with it.
(sinister laughter)
Oh, great Yamigedo,
leave it to me.
The almighty Ikazuchi!
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna teach
you about the new card,
Gigantic Crusher.
Sounds fun!
It's a powerful impact card
that causes a lot of
damage to your opponent
in one blow.
If both of your
centers are open
and you have a
fist item equipped,
then you can deal four
damage to your opponent
that cannot be reduced.
Huh, what was that?
As you can best your
opponent in one move,
you'll likely
win every match
that you use this card in.
Let me out of class early
so I can go get one!
(chuckling)
♪
Next time, Buddyfight
decks start disappearing
and all clues lead to
the Ice Prison Emperor,
Cocytus Greed.
Gao challenges him using Tenbu.
Next episode: The
Hundreds Demon Attack!
Protect Tenbu!!
Join us for a Buddyfight!