(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the Eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them and
there's only one way we can!
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
Zanya, Zanya,
we found him!
Well, not us exactly,
but isn't it great?
Nin.
A girl!
She thinks she saw Ziun
while walking on that
mountain over there.
You can just see it
through the trees.
Anyway, she said
we need to go straight
for about ten minutes
then turn right at the fork,
then we keep walking about
another eight minutes,
then head left and continue
past some large rocks.
He really does
talk a lot, doesn't he?
And fast.
"X" marks the spot at
the cave where he's hiding.
‐I say we make a‐‐
‐Nice work, Tsukikage.
‐Nin.
‐Oh.
(snoring)
Well, Z, do you
think it's him?
Yeah.
That's him, no doubt.
We've found the First
Omni Beast, Lord Ziun.
(snoring)
♪
When can I return
to active duty?
Yeah, I'm itching
to get back at it.
I want to test my
Justice Drum power
against those
filthy 100 Demons ASAP,
and become a
true Omni Lord.
Come on, you
know we're ready!
I've even mastered the Hero
World deck like you asked me to.
♪
Gao did fight with
a Hero World deck,
but something wasn't
right about it.
‐It's like...
‐What is it?
Tell me what's
troubling you.
Well, I wouldn't say
that he's mastered the deck.
The way he fought
looked more like
he wanted a hero
to rescue him.
Hmm.
(gasps)
And if that's the case,
then Gao may be...
Hmm.
The topic of your return
must wait for another day.
I asked you here
for a different purpose.
I wanted to inform
you personally
of the next move the
Buddy Police is taking.
♪
We've decided to ask the Eight
Omni Lords to assist us.
As you're no doubt aware,
simply finding them will not
be enough to seal up Yamigedo.
So, what exactly
do you want us to do?
Forge strong
bonds of friendship
and ask them to
join our decks.
It's the only hope the
planet has for survival.
If we were to have any chance
of sealing up Yamigedo again,
we're going to
need your help.
Please become
part of my deck.
I'm all for
lending you a hand,
but I'm afraid my joining your
deck is out of the question.
Huh?
I don't understand.
Aligning forces is perfect.
You're a
Katana World monster
and I use a
Katana World deck!
So why are you
turning me down?
Simple, because
you're weak.
♪
Nothing personal, but I
measured your level of strength
that time we
fought before.
Joining a fighter with your
skills wouldn't benefit me
as I wouldn't
become any stronger.
♪
Hmm.
You okay, Z?
I don't get it!
I know I'm stronger now than
when I fought him before,
but it didn't
show at all.
What am I doing wrong?
Game over.
Winner: First Omni Beast,
Lord Ziun.
Impossible.
I lost again!
Please just one more time,
I'm sure I can beat you.
Just let me prove it.
It'd be a complete
waste of time.
You fail to grasp the true
nature of Katana World.
A thousand fights would
yield the same result.
Now, go, and
don't ever return.
(crying)
I can't stop
thinking about it.
What did he mean "the true
nature of Katana World?"
We'll figure it out, Z.
Cho‐Osaka, Cho‐Osaka.
Come on, we got to transfer
trains at this stop, big bro!
(grunting)
Sorry.
You okay, kid?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, hey, aren't you
Zanya's little brother?
And there's Zanya too.
Who is that?
Jin Magatsu.
A Buddyfighter from Aibo's
middle school division.
No, I meant her,
oblivious one.
(glass breaks)
Oh, she's Jin's tutor,
Miss Megumi Mamakari.
It's quite a coincidence
running into you guys.
We're here visiting
our families and you?
Looking for Omni Lords?
♪
Did something happen?
No, nothing special.
Well, keep at it.
Catch ya later.
Nice running
into you guys.
♪
You fail to grasp the true
nature of Katana World.
(gasps)
Hey Jin, wait up!
As a fellow Katana World user,
I have a question for you.
Can you tell me what is the
true nature of Katana World?
I have to know.
Well, then, I
guess you'd better
stick close to
me for a bit, huh?
Despite what
you might think,
I used to be a rich
kid from a nice family.
Oh, great,
here we go again.
But it is true.
I used to Buddyfight
with the local kids
around here all the time,
and it's where I met my buddy,
Evil in Heart, Yamigitsune.
So I guess this place
means a lot to you, huh?
The day I met Yamigitsune,
I came here to say goodbye
to this place for good.
My father was swindled
by a man that he trusted.
We became penniless and were
going to have to move away.
♪
If it's even, I'll make
a living by tricking people,
and if it's
odd, I won't.
I'll promise never
to deceive anyone!
I don't know if it's the true
nature of Katana World or not,
but whether we're talking
about ninjas or skull warriors,
they fight to
protect their masters.
Isn't that the function
of a Katana World monster?
♪
Tell me, Zanya, what
do you want to protect?
(grunts)
So, it's decided.
Wait.
Huh?
Would you like
to be my buddy?
♪
Yeah, sure!
What do I call you?
Aside from "my buddy".
Yamigitsune.
Maybe the one true
nature of Katana World
is different
for each of us.
What do I want to protect?
I know the answer
to that already.
I'm a Buddy Police officer.
I'm grateful for the
advice you've given me.
♪
Hey, hang on a sec.
How about a little
test of luck?
Do you want even or odd?
Even.
You got it.
♪
What's this?
Just a card
I don't need.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were
becoming a nice guy.
Aw, get out of here.
Thanks a lot, Jin.
Guess we'll see
you around Aibo.
♪
Lord Ziun!
You in here,
Lord Ziun?
He's not home.
I guess we'll just have
to wait 'til he comes back.
(laughing)
‐Huh?
‐Lucky for you!
The forecaster of
disaster is on the case!
I secretly attached one
of my clones to Lord Ziun
to track his every move,
and I can see
him right now.
Hold your tongues in silence
and give me a second to zone
in on his exact location,
and it is...
Zing!
Like hounds on a scent, we
go down this mountain path
and take a sharp right
onto the paved road.
Then, we merge onto the
busy four lane highway
and head due left and
once we spot the ocean,
we march straight
along the seaside road
‐where we'll find him.
‐Nin.
Oh, I see.
Is that where Lord Ziun
is right now?
Don't tell me that you put a
clone on him too, Tsukikage.
‐Nin.
‐Oh, shucks!
Why didn't you just
say so in the first place?
♪
This is it,
we're here!
Let's land.
I hope this works.
He'll be surprised to see us.
Ah, this feels good
on my old bones.
I should have done
this ages ago.
There he is,
go ask him!
No, I can't bother him
while he's bathing.
Huh?
I had a feeling
he would come back.
I'm confused!
What was the point then?
I thought you came here
to challenge him
to another Buddyfight.
The polite thing
is to wait
until he's finished
in the hot springs.
A few more minutes won't
make much difference.
Okay, but you need him to agree
to join your deck, right?
So, why not hurry it up
and Buddyfight him already?
You've got it all
wrong, little brother.
To be honest, I didn't come
here to Buddyfight him at all.
Huh?
(chuckles)
It's okay.
I didn't understand
it either
until Jin helped
explain it to me.
Of course, now I don't know how
I could have ever missed it.
Care to share?
♪
I'm starving!
How much longer do you expect
us to wait for this guy?
It'll take as long as it
takes and not a second less.
(Ziun yawns)
That was like
Heaven on Earth.
Quick, get ready,
he's coming out.
♪
(sighs)
I thought I told
you to go away.
I apologize for returning,
but I have a good reason.
I'm a Buddy Police officer
and I've been assigned
an important mission
that I must complete.
The future of the planet depends
on the Omni Lord Operations
and I will risk
everything if I have to
to ensure its success.
Of what mission
do you speak?
To protect the
citizens of this world
from illegal monsters of
any size, shape or form.
Ah.
And the reason
I'm here is
that I need your
help to do it.
I'm begging you, please,
give me one more chance.
Hmm.
Noon tomorrow.
We meet at Cho‐Sakurajima.
Thanks, you
won't regret it!
Wherever there's
a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana
will be there!
Today, I'm coming
to you live
from hot and
humid Cho‐Kagoshima
in southern Japan.
We'll be bringing you
up to the minute coverage
from this unique stage
built atop a luxury yacht!
Now to introduce the
players in today's match.
First is Zanya Kisaragi
of the Buddy Police Youth.
Do your best, Z!
This time he's yours!
Opposing him is First
Omni Beast, Lord Ziun.
Who you may remember
defeated Zanya
in their only
other meeting.
First Omni Beast Lord?
Omni Lord?
(gasps)
Could you possibly be
one of the Omni Lords
that everyone's
been talking about?
I know not what people
speak of, but I know this.
I am one of the Omni Lords who
sealed up Yamigedo long ago.
This is incredible!
Did you hear that?
One of the Omni Lords
has been found
and on my broadcast!
I need to inform
the Amanosuzu Group
as soon as possible to
collect that cash reward.
Hey, that's right!
Maybe I could
get me a reward too!
I think you missed
the boat, pumpkins.
Yeah, I mean,
this is live TV.
Stay true to yourself
and victory will find you.
The moon is full,
and the heavens glow!
To heed my sword, luminize!
Kisaragi Legend:
Asure Dance!
If you think you can stop me,
you're welcome to try.
Luminize!
Disaster Charge!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
Katana World!
I'm with
Katana World as well.
Count Dawn!
Zanya's Buddyfighting
an Omni Lord.
Yes, I'm well aware.
What's happening so far?
On the first move, Zanya called
Yumi Ninja, Suiha to the center.
He then added
Byakyua from his deck
to the cards in his hand
and attacked the fighter
causing two damage,
and he just set
his Super Lethal Formation
before you came in.
(both gasp)
Ziun's up, and he
calls two monsters.
I wonder what he'll do.
Let's watch!
Dokakusai, Irukamaru,
attack the fighter.
Let me get right
to the point!
Penetrate!
Sword of the
thrashing seas!
At the end of the turn,
Dokakusai goes directly
to the drop zone.
Who knows when
I'll be back?
End of move.
Your move.
That fight with Ziun
taught me something.
You see, I tried so hard to
impress him with my strength
that I stopped
being a Buddy Cop.
There's no way that I
could have won like that.
Now I understand
what I need to do.
Okay, Z, now I see
what you meant.
The same is true for us.
Really, how so?
We were also guilty of only
trying to show our strength
and we forgot what
was truly important.
Like you, this prevented us from
fighting to our full potential.
Nin.
Hmm.
After hearing what
your friend, Jin said,
our eyes have
been opened.
Nin.
As ninjas, our job is
to protect our master
and that's you, Zanya.
Nin!
We're now prepared to
put our lives on the line
to accomplish this.
Nin!
Tomorrow, let's unite our
powers and win the fight.
Together, we'll
protect the world.
‐Yeah!
‐Nin!
‐Huh?
♪
No way!
You just created a card!
Can it be?
It's time for us
to unite our powers.
I call Nanomachine Ninja,
Byakyua to the right!
Put your hands together
for the coolest ninja around.
I buddy call Nanomachine
Ninja Tsukikage to the left!
Nin!
On a white knight, the moon's
shadow magically appears.
I pay one gauge and
call to the right...
‐Ready, brother?
‐Nin!
♪
Ghoul Deity Combined!
Gojinmaru!
(gasps)
Somebody stop the train!
There's a new monster
in the house with
Byakyua and Tsukikage
in its soul.
I need the Tako scope to check
out the deets on this one.
Ghoul Deity
Gojinmaru.
Attribute ninja,
Size Two.
It has 7,000 power
and defense.
A critical of two and
he's got Soul Guard,
Double Attack,
Move and Shadow Dive.
He's too amazing
to believe!
I equip Water
Slash Sword, Murasame!
Let's go guys!
‐Nin!
Even a monster in
the opponent's center
doesn't stop this guy.
Gojinto, first strike!
(grunts)
Gojinto, second strike!
The Double Attack
causes double the damage.
Secret skill:
Drop lift reversal.
(yells)
Zanya destroys Murasame and
now it's Lord Ziun's turn.
Like wow!
Way to go, Zanya!
When did you get
to be so strong?
Hmm.
Lord Ziun tries
for a counter attack,
but he can't break through
Gojinmaru's defense.
♪
I'm gonna cast.
Sword Skill:
Sendou Spin.
Zanya's counter spell
neutralizes the link attack
and on top of that,
it destroys Shiden
and sends Bokunryu
to the drop zone.
(growls)
End of move.
If this keeps up, he'll
finally be able to beat him.
Zanya pays one life to retrieve
Murasame from the drop zone
and equips it again.
He then moves Gojinmaru
to the right,
positioning himself
for another assault.
Gojinmaru,
attack the fighter!
‐Nin!
(grunting)
(yells)
The first strike hits hard.
If his Double Attack
lands, it's game over.
That's the last
time you damage me.
I cast Demon Way, Oborogenbu!
‐Nin?
Lord Ziun nullified
Gojinmaru's second strike,
but the tenacious Zanya
is thirsty for more!
I call Tsukiusagi
to the center.
Guard with
Lightning Speed.
I wouldn't dream of
letting you get by me, pal!
(grunts)
He's blocked
another one!
End of move.
Oh, total shocker.
I mean, he is an
Omni Lord after all.
Zanya better pick it up or
he'll be crying for a week.
Oh, I don't know.
Remember, Zanya has that
special trump card I gave him.
But he can only use it
if he understands
the true nature
of Katana World.
If not, he'll be
just another wannabe.
♪
Lord Ziun means business.
Calling out two monsters
with the Penetrate ability.
Kimensai, Dokakusai, go forth
and attack the fighter!
I don't think Zanya has a hope
of blocking these attacks.
A little damage
if you please.
(cackling)
End of move.
Both players are down
to two life points.
Z, just hang on.
Let's see,
inventory check.
I still have Gojinmaru
and my Marusame.
Besides, I've got Clear Serenity
in my held cards.
If I use it to
increase my gauge,
I can activate
the Star Crusher
that I put in
Super Lethal Formation,
which will prevent him from
using any defensive spells.
Meaning, I've won.
I cast!
Clear Serenity!
I do protest.
I cast Ninja Arts Snake Gaze!
Lord Ziun has
used a counter spell.
Zanya's bold attempt
to increase his gauge
by three with Clear Serenity
is put on ice,
leaving him stuck at one gauge
with Lord Ziun in full command.
(grunts)
I can't believe I
didn't see this coming.
His counter spell prevents me
from activating Star Crusher.
And now I'll use my
Ninja Arts Snake Gaze
to block Gojinmaru
from making a move.
(grunts)
(growls)
I admit you got me there,
but you can't stop Murasame!
Spells aren't the only way
of avoiding an attack.
I forgot Tsukiusagi.
Zanya is forced to attack
Tsukiusagi instead!
Two‐zero for me.
End of move.
Just when I thought
he had him in his sights.
This is bad, man.
All Lord Ziun's got to
do is buddy call himself
and Zanya's a
goner for sure.
It's not over
'til it's over, Gao.
How can you say that?
There's no possible way
he can win this fight now.
Oh, is that right?
I'll take the pleasure
of finishing you myself.
Therefore, I buddy
call myself to the center.
I give you an
"A" for effort.
You've come a long
way in a short time
and I respect
your resolve,
so I will help you,
but know this:
I cannot and will
not join your deck.
You fought valiantly,
but now, I will end you!
I pay three gauge and
activate Absolute Sword,
Azure Cascade Formation.
♪
(yells)
What I want to protect most
isn't my life points.
It's the lives of all the
people who live in this world.
Ah, I think you
finally get it.
♪
Game over.
Winner: Zanya Kisaragi.
Someone tell me
what just happened here!
Let me guess.
That was the card
you gave him.
Yep, it's one of the
trickiest there is,
and there are
two ways to use it.
As an impact card that inflicts
damage to your opponent,
or in the event that your
life points become zero,
as a counter impact card
that boosts your life to one
and causes two damage
to your opponent.
It can only be used
if the player's prepared
to lay down their life.
I'd never be
able to do that.
That was amazing, man!
I'd never be able to
pull out a win like that!
Tell me, Gao,
would you be willing
to engage in a
Buddyfight against me?
Huh?
I'd like to assess your
current level of power.
Sounds like a blast!
Why don't we go
with Hero World?
Yeah!
Actually, if
you don't mind,
I'd prefer you used
a Dragon World deck.
Okay, if you
really want me to.
I think I even
have it right here.
Huh?
What's wrong,
I don't get it.
Is everything okay, kid?
It's weird.
The deck won't fit
inside the case.
I'm afraid Tasuku's
fears were correct.
If that's the case,
then I fear that Gao
may be unable to use
Dragon World decks anymore.
Darn it!
Why won't it fit?
Huh?
What's up, are
you feeling okay?
♪
It's like I've lost
control of myself.
What's happening?
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today's subject is the Ghoul
Deity, Gojinmaru card.
Lay it on me!
It was created by Tsukikage
and Byakyua combining
and then further evolving.
It's called when both
monsters are in the field,
then put in its soul.
The Shadow Dive and
Double Attack abilities
make it an extremely
powerful card.
I'll say!
Gojinmaru also has
a Move and Soul Guard
to defend you on
your opponent's turn.
Sounds like the
perfect monster!
Kind of like Drum
without the attitude.
(laughs)
♪
Next time, to be able
to use Dragon World,
Count Dawn says Gao needs to
deal with his painful past,
but we learn Count Dawn
has some demons of his own.
Next episode,
"Tragic Earth Lord!
A Requiem for Daichi!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!