Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth,
to become Buddies with humans.
But now, a swarm
of evil monsters
known as The Hundred Demons
have come here illegally
and plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy Skill, on!
Thanks for meeting me
away from the others.
Don't you think it's
about time you told me?
We are on the same side.
Tell you what, exactly?
Enough games; we've
known each other too long.
I know you have intel about
the overwhelming threat
Tenbu spoke of before
he lost his memory.
You have no need to worry.
You sure about that?
If this terrible threat appears,
I promise to tell
you everything.
Above all else,
I am true to my word.
Well, let's just hope
that day never comes, huh?
I take it that until
the girl is old enough,
you'd like things to just
continue as they are?
Even if he did fully
awaken in the near future,
it would still leave ample
time for her to grow up.
And while we're pointing
fingers, Asmodai,
why are you carrying on
as if you know nothing?
I guess I'd like to keep
playing with Tetsuya.
The little guy's
kind of grown on me.
(screaming)
♪
Did you guys get an invitation
to Suzuha's party this weekend?
Sure did, bro, at her
family's country estate.
It's gonna be totally choice.
But she's keeping secret
what she's celebrating
until the day of the party.
Rumor has it that she's
going to be officially named
the Head of the Amanosuzu Group.
Good for her,
that sounds amazing.
Yeah, well, who cares,
I'm just gonna fill my belly
with plate after plate
of delicious grub.
It looks like all the students
of Aibo Academy will be invited.
You should come with us, Gao.
I can't; this Sunday I'm
scheduled for a double shift,
so I'll be on duty all day.
Bummer, bro, you're
gonna miss a feast.
They're really
working you hard, huh?
Kuguru's right, kid, this
Buddy Police gig is grueling.
Every day, we gotta work
late responding to calls.
We never have time to
relax or go to cool parties.
Good evening.
Suzuha, is that you?
I think my blood sugar's low.
It looks just like Suzuha.
But it's a robot.
Here's an invitation.
Party at Country House, don't
miss good times and good food.
These rich folks are weird.
Well, I guess it saves her
from having to do it herself.
Sorry, but, I won't
be able to make it.
Taste what you'll be missing.
That'll sure hit the spot.
Yeah, it will!
You two are going to party.
(screaming)
Ha ha ha ha.
Wait, where's the food?
Oh, good, you're
finally here, bia.
Why'd you bring us here?
That's easy, to make sure
you'll be attending my party,
of course, bia.
Because, I can't very well
announce our wedding engagement
without the groom
present, can I?
What?
Congratulations, Lady Suzuha.
Why choose Gao as
your future husband?
Is it because of his
skills as a Buddyfighter?
No, it's because of love, bia.
What gives? I'm your best
friend, why didn't you tell me?
Because it's not true!
You're scheduled to promise
to marry tomorrow, bia.
Tomorrow?
Something's off, is that
really Suzuha up there?
And so you don't try to
leave before the party,
I've set up some special
bridegroom training for you.
After all, happy
wife, happy life.
Where are we?
I don't know, but
it looks familiar.
It's Principal
Ikarino's dungeon stage!
Not exactly, Mr. Mikado.
Although similar
to the one belonging
to Aibo Academy Elementary
School's Principal Ikarino,
this isn't his,
but rather, an exact replica.
It's all part of Lady Suzuha's
Buddyfight training.
To practice in real
world surroundings,
she had various fighting
stages built within the chateau.
Would somebody tell
me what's going on?
We're dragged here
against our will,
and now she says we're engaged
and I'm in bridegroom training!
Is this some kind of joke?
Yeah, let us out of here!
And give us some
food for the road.
I wish we could, but it's
totally out of our hands.
We've fallen out
of favor with her.
My lady sent us
down here as well.
Why'd she do that?
We don't know.
It happened yesterday.
♪
It is time to rise
and shine, my lady.
Lady Suzuha?
♪
It's Mary Sue.
Why do such a thing?
Because she was being
a nuisance, bia.
You should have called us.
What is that shadow?
I see you are also
a nuisance, bia.
(screaming)
She called her Buddy a nuisance?
A demon must have possessed her!
We need to find a way
out of this dungeon,
and go rescue Suzuha.
Let's do it!
Wait, stop!
(panting)
Let's try there!
(screaming)
We'll have to find
another way out!
Maybe down here!
(screaming)
What's the deal with
this house anyway?
As previously mentioned,
this is an exact replica
of Principal Ikarino's
dungeon stage,
and as you are no doubt aware,
there is but one way out.
You mean we have to
win in a Buddyfight.
(sinister chuckle)
How fun to see Mikado
squirm like that.
All this does seem a
little over the top though.
I mean, big parties
and dungeons?
I don't know, I think it will
all be quite amusing, bia.
‐After all...
‐The deal was that I,
the Mysterious Dekarabia
could do as I please, bia.
This is Mysterious Dekarabia,
pair her up with her as a Buddy.
Suzuha Amanosuzu?
But why her?
Why do you think it is that the
Hundred Demons keep losing, huh?
Well, I don't know.
It's because you're
pathetically weak!
(screams)
No matter how great
the Hundred Demons are,
if the fighter's weak, they
can't release their full power.
Nobody's ever beaten Gao Mikado
in an official Buddyfight,
however, several have almost
been able to pull it off.
Suzuha Amanosuzu is one of them.
If I'm going to be
working with this girl,
then I insist on
doing things my way.
I don't care how you do
it, just bring me Tenbu.
Understood.
Oh, this is going
to be such fun, bia.
(high‐pitched noises)
That's the bucket of
bolts that Shanghaied us!
That's my lady's state of the
art Buddyfight training robot.
It is capable of transforming
into 1,024 different fighters.
And next you'll be telling me
that I've got to
defeat all of them.
It is the only way
to get out of here.
1,024 fights?
Fine by me.
I've got a few new moves
that I've been wanting
to try out, anyway.
Time for a fighter change.
♪
Think you can
handle the Seifukai?
Now it looks like Genma,
this is gonna be fun.
♪
Okay, is everyone ready?
Buddy...fight!
You're looking at a live shot
of the majestic
Chateau De Amanosuzu,
where Lady Suzuha Amanosuzu
of the eponymous
international supercompany
is scheduled to make an
important announcement tonight.
And with the influence
of her family's
world‐renowned equipment
manufacturing enterprise,
much attention is being
drawn to this event.
Shake your tail,
we gotta get going!
I'm actually a little
tired right now.
Gao's been fighting
for three straight days.
He must be totally
exhausted by now, meaning
Mysterious Dekarabia should
be able to defeat him easily.
Don't you want to defeat Gao,
and take Tenbu away from him
while the entire
world is watching?
Baku, hurry up!
We're going to be late.
Why aren't you all dressed up?
The invitation was very clear in
asking us to wear formal attire.
‐These are my formal clothes.
‐Yeah, right.
You're lucky, Zanya,
you dress formally every day.
Father says,
"Clothes make the man."
Are you okay, Zanya?
No, Gao's gone missing.
We haven't been able to
contact him for three days.
It's not like him; He's
vanished without a trace.
I had no idea, bro.
I figured he wasn't
in class all week
because he was
on Buddy Police biz.
You don't think
he's been defeated
by a Hundred Demons monster?
We considered it, but if he was,
I'm sure they would've
contacted us to brag about it.
I just really hope he
hasn't gotten himself
in over his head with something.
There's just one hour
until the party begins,
and we still have no idea
what the big news is.
The whole world is
anxiously awaiting
Lady Suzuha Amanosuzu's
big announcement.
That's all they've talked
about on the news lately.
Any word from Mikado yet?
Strangely, no.
Where can he be?
We've reached out
to his friends,
even Miss Amanosuzu, but
with all that's going on,
she's too busy to speak to us.
Really? Would you say
they were close friends?
Yes.
Something's off.
If a close friend
of yours went missing,
wouldn't you be at
least a bit concerned?
As we enjoy
the beautiful sunset,
we're only moments away
from the big surprise!
(screaming)
Huh?
Okay, pal, take him out!
This'll finish you!
Game over, winner is Gao Mikado.
All right, that's
almost a cool thou'.
Gao Mikado continues to amaze,
that's 999 consecutive wins!
Is he a machine, too?
He never tires or gets hungry.
I expected nothing
less from him, bia.
Now then, let's see
how he reacts to this.
Anyone hungry?
Are we ever!
You have to beat me first!
So not fair.
I was so focused, I didn't
realize how majorly hungry I am.
I can't feel my tail.
I need to eat.
♪
I commend you on
a most brilliant plan.
By showing them food,
you made them realize
their exhaustion and hunger.
You truly are a demon.
And proud of it.
Now, if you'll excuse me, bia.
How are you holding up?
In case you forgot,
it's almost time, bia.
Almost time for what?
Whatever it is, I hope it
comes with a side of fries.
Why, time for us to announce our
engagement, of course, and also,
time for me to defeat
you, and take that
fifth Omni Dragon Lord Tenbu
card off your hands, bia.
The live broadcast is
about to begin, bia.
Warp successful!
What's going on?
I don't believe it!
It's a copy of
the dungeon stage!
And unless my eyes
are deceiving me,
it looks like Gao Mikado
and Lady Suzuha Amanosuzu
are about to Buddyfight!
I'm sure no one in
the world expected
this evening's party to be
starting off quite like this.
That's Paruko.
♪
I don't know if I
can fight anymore.
I mean, I can barely
even lift my arms.
Yeah, but we have to.
Without us, Suzuha's doomed.
Hah, a warm breeze could knock
you two down in your condition.
How'd you find us?
Let's just say there's
honor among friends.
And now that I found you,
I order you to rest.
♪
I will face your
opponent in your place.
♪
Hey, is that‐‐it is!
The famous Buddy Police
Youth leader, Count Dawn!
What was it that
gave me away, bia?
Something you demons
could never understand.
When someone close
to you goes missing,
concern jumps to the forefront.
Unless, of course,
you know where they are,
I had my servants
conduct a thorough search
and they easily
confirmed my suspicions.
Fine, very well, I'll
fight you instead, bia.
It looks like Count Dawn
will be subbing in
for the exhausted Gao Mikado.
That batty clown
will spoil our plan!
Good thing I came
prepared: use this.
My chance to show my
true skills to the world!
Bask in the brilliance of
Dawn, messengers of justice!
Luminize, Dawn Army!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path,
witness their
awesome power, bia.
Luminize, Hundred Magic!
Buddy...fight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Legend World!
I'm with Magic World, bia.
The first move goes
to Miss Amanosuzu.
Youth officers Zanya
and Tetsuya are heading
to Chateau De Amanosuzu
as we speak.
I call Sky Poet,
Amon to the center.
Okay, attack him, bia!
Anything my princess commands.
♪
End of move.
Hm, I forgot how fun this is.
Your move.
Now Count Dawn gets
to strut his stuff.
I'm curious to see what other
surprises he has up his sleeve.
This is the first time
seeing him fight.
(screaming)
That's one fight
you'll have to miss.
Why's that?
Even with your
obvious exhaustion,
we don't want to
risk you butting in.
I wouldn't do that.
Take a good look, we have
another Hundred Demons monster.
Awaken, power of darkness,
power of evil, power
of the Hundred Demons!
Iron Cyclops has his eye on you!
(screaming)
♪
What's this?
You there, reporter, I'll
give you the privilege
of broadcasting my
mind‐blowing fight!
♪
Okay.
Darkness Barrier, activate!
♪
Are you all right?
Will you be able to fight?
We have no choice, or
else we're stuck in here.
I'm getting tired of this guy.
♪
Burning like an inferno,
with limitless spirit!
Luminize!
Crimson Dragon Fist!
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power!
Luminize, Hundred Dungeon!
Welcome to this special report.
A Darkness Barrier has just been
raised at Chateau de Amanosuzu.
I will be broadcasting
live from the scene,
where the exhausted Gao Mikado
has accepted
a Buddyfight challenge
from the notorious Death Shido.
Stay with us for
this doubleheader.
Are you with me, Paruko?
You know I am.
Alrighty then,
Buddy... fight!
Time to raise the flag!
I'm with Dragon World!
I'm fighting for Dungeon World.
Gao has the first move,
and he calls Crimson Battler,
Break Shoulder Dragon.
Come on, Break Shoulder,
attack the fighter!
You got it.
Give me a break, that was weak.
I cast Divine
Protection of Shalsana!
With his counter
spell's ability,
Death Shido regains
one life point,
and with that,
Gao's move is over.
Things are heating up
at the dungeon stage.
Count Dawn is preparing to
dazzle us with his first turn.
I call Night Witch
Clear to the left,
and Wolfman Gutz
to the center area.
♪
Hi, all.
Tell me what to do already.
And now, I Buddy Call myself
to the right position!
The Buddy Gift helps him
regain one life point.
I'm anxious to know what
kind of ability he has.
Time for my trusty Takoscope.
Let's check out his
deets together, shall we?
Seventh Omni
Earthlord, Count Dawn.
Hang on a second.
Why do I feel like I've heard
that name somewhere before?
Anyway, he's just a size 0,
but he has the Wydar
Sarkal attribute.
He has 4,000 power, 1,000
defense, a critical of 1,
and one ability.
I wonder if he'll show us
the hidden strength
of the Buddy Police.
Feel the power!
All right, boys.
Watch me clear the way!
Oh no you don't.
How do you like me now?
♪
You think you'll get
the better of me?
Think again, you brute!
End of move.
So this is Count Dawn's
fighting style.
What's up with Suzuha's deck?
You noticed that too?
It's different
from her usual one.
And check out her Buddy,
that is not Mary Sue.
I call Zafar to the center,
and Zagan to the left, bia.
Lady Suzuha uses Nice One to
increase the cards in her hand,
but the ability of
Count Dawn's monsters
prevents them from
being destroyed
if there's a
Wydar Sarkal monster
in the right position,
leaving her no choice but
to attack Count Dawn first.
What action!
Let's see how this plays out.
Zagan, attack the
Count on the right.
♪
I will rise once again!
Zafar, attack
the beast in the center.
Topside Blaster!
I'm sorry, boss, he got
the better of me this time.
End of move.
♪
I attack Break Shoulder
with my Fate Skeleton!
I'm broken!
End of move.
In the game so far,
Gao is down to 6 life,
while Death Shido has
received no damage at all.
Your move.
All right.
Charge, and draw.
I equip Crimson Fist Dragoblaze!
It looks like Gao's
pulling out all the stops,
but in his exhausted condition,
can he eke out a win here?
I call Guns Knuckle
Dragon to the left area,
and I call Power Stamp
Drake to the right!
When called,
Power Stamp Drake
has the ability to destroy
either the opponent's right
or left monster in the field.
In a match like this, it's
always good to have options.
Stamping out the enemy!
♪
Check it out, that was cool, yo.
What's bugging you, A‐dawg?
Nothing, just looks
like a bad storm coming.
Oh, I get it now,
it's the Gao formation.
Guns Knuckle Dragon,
go attack Roper!
♪
Power Stamp Drake,
attack the fighter!
Let's have a stabbing good time!
I'd never let you get
your grubby mitts on me!
I cast Great Pillar of Fire!
What?
♪
Crimson Fist Dragoblaze!
Now I cast,
Quiescence of Cassiade!
Now, any damage I receive is
reduced by three whole points!
Say what?
Unbelievable, even the Gao
formation couldn't strip
any life points away
from Death Shido!
Uh oh.
You okay?
Get a hold of yourself, kid!
Come on, stand up!
We need you, I need you!
Gao!
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm happy
to tell you all about
the Seventh Omni
Earth Lord, Count Dawn.
He's able to revive no matter
how many times he's defeated.
If you pay one life at
the beginning of your turn,
you can call him
from your drop zone.
And being size 0,
you can call him
without worrying
about other card's sizes.
That's our Count for you.
He can be used in any deck,
no matter what the flag, adding
a punch to all kinds of decks.
I know a few guys
who could use a punch.
♪
Next time, the Great Ikazuchi
finally makes an appearance,
raising a flag that
nobody's ever seen before.
Wait until you see
the terrifying ability
hidden in his deck.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!