(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster,
Yamigedo has
been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the Eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them and
there's only one way we can!
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
Yamigedo's
Thunder Mind activate!
(screams)
I said, "Feed me,"
and I mean now.
(roars)
Here comes Yamigedo's
double attack!
(screams)
Dinner is served!
Thunder Claw, Narukami!
You're not that tough.
Time I showed
you the skills
I picked up in
the great old US of A.
‐Not yet!
‐Huh?
The dark and evil power
they call demonic,
and all of it is
controlled by me!
Time for Final Phase!
I cast.
Did he say "Final Phase"?
I guess he must
have an impact card.
Now is the time
to show your power.
Unorthodox Arts!
Shoraiabare Kandachi!
‐I shall ride again!
‐Good night!
(screams)
♪
All of his monsters and
his item have been destroyed!
What an incredible card!
But that's not all.
For each card
that was destroyed,
he inflicts damage
points to his opponent.
(growling)
(grunts)
(screams)
Noboru!
♪
I promise you,
Mr. and Mrs. Kodo,
the Buddy Police will do
everything in its power
to find your son, Noboru.
Thank you.
You're our only hope.
Goodbye.
It's all my fault.
Hmm?
It's because of me
that Noboru's...
Nonsense!
Blaming yourself or
anyone else for that matter
won't bring him back.
Now go home and
get some rest.
♪
We're really
sorry, Gao.
It's okay.
It's up to you
to save Noboru.
Huh?
We can only count
on you now.
I will, and I won't
rest until I do!
♪
Go home?
No, I want to
look for Noboru!
I know, and we
have to find out
who that mysterious
monster is as well,
but the rest of the team
will have to manage that
without you and
Drum, I'm afraid.
You're cutting us out?
Don't forget the two
of you are still on leave.
I don't recall approving
your return to active duty.
Don't worry, we'll
find him for you.
I promise we
won't let you down.
But you don't
even have Jack!
♪
Sorry, I‐‐I shouldn't
have said that.
(sighs)
(crying)
Gao, wait up!
Hmm.
♪
It's clear this one
lacks the fortitude needed
to be Master
Yamigedo's buddy.
♪
He'll be like
this for some time.
♪
That's all well and good,
but why don't you
tell us who you are.
♪
That's what Gallows
here wants to know.
I am a 100 Demons Monster
from Darkness Dragon World.
They call me The First Knight
of the Apocalypse, Gratos.
Why did you decide
to show up now?
Awaken, young boy.
(grunting)
Who are you?
Where have
you brought me?
♪
Judging by the stench, I'd have
to go with Bad Guy Secret Lair.
You won't be able to hold
me down here for long!
♪
You are destined to become one
of Master Yamigedo's pawns.
Aren't you even going
to say "please", Boneface?
Dream on!
♪
By the powers of darkness.
You will do Master
Yamigedo's bidding.
(shuddering)
Gao.
♪
Huh?
You feel that?
I just got a bad vibe.
Hundred Demon's
detected, ki.
‐Let's burn some rubber.
‐Okey‐dokey.
(imitating motorcycle engine)
We've lost the
100 Demons signal, chief.
(grunts)
(brakes squeal)
Trying to put yourself
in the hospital, flake?
Yeah, rat fink!
♪
Apologies there, Mack.
I'm a humble wanderer
named Mukuro Shigamine.
I come all the way
from Hero World.
I'm still adjusting to the
ways of your planet, see.
I'm the guy who tracks
down evil 100 Demons
and demolishes
them with my fists.
I am the great Ban Enma,
otherwise known
as 100 Demons Hunter.
Hang on, I have no
time to talk to you!
I'm hot on the trail
of one right now.
Got to split, Daddy‐o.
You seem swell, so sorry
for what I got to do.
But I'll be needing
you to hand over
your Omni Lord Emblem,
hunter boy.
Do it nice and easy, now.
You've been in
the sun too long.
You do have one, don't you?
Hardly, pal.
You want to be
a wise guy, huh?
Huh?
Trying to ruffle
my feathers?
You still deny you
have the Omni Lord Emblem?
Sure do!
What are you
jiving about anyway?
Describe this
emblem thing.
It's shaped like an orb
and the Omni Lord symbol
is smack dab
in the middle.
Just like that, Mack.
What's the dealio?
You wise to this, Ricky?
No, not at all.
I know nothing
about the thing, ki.
Well, you heard him.
You're barking up
the wrong tree,
and now we've
cleared that up.
This is for spitting
that grody toothpick at me!
Nice try, but I've
Seen Through Your Moves!
Why you!
It looks to me like you're
gonna need a little persuading.
I've got ways of
making you talk, Bazoo.
‐We're coming, chief!
Who's the chump in the hat?
I could handle him on my own,
but you need some exercise.
Go take care of him, boys.
‐Alright!
Are you sure?
A fight between rival groups
of alleged illegal monsters?
That's right.
Send us everything you have.
Working on it.
It should be on
your screen now.
‐The 100 Demons Hunter.
‐And Shigamine!
Something must be up,
and I'm gonna find out what.
Sure that's wise?
I mean, you don't
have a buddy.
I can handle it.
Hmm, suppose I
have no choice.
Buddy Police Youth,
emergency launch!
‐Roger that, Count.
‐Nin!
‐Come on, A‐Dog!
Let's fly.
Sorry, Tets,
but I got to pass.
What are you
talking about, yo?
Can't risk another mano a mano
with that Shigamine guy again.
Best I sit this one out.
Oh, come on!
You can't do that!
(groans)
Hmm.
(yells)
(groaning)
♪
Huh?
Get ready
for our turn.
Let's go super bashing.
He deserves
a good beating.
(yelling)
(siren wailing)
Huh?
We're the Buddy Police and
we're taking you into custody.
Huh?
Hey, chief,
what's happening, ki?
Zanya.
What can I do
for you, Lord Ziun?
My Omni Lord Emblem is currently
resonating with another.
Whoa, would you
look at that?
That can only mean that there's
another Omni Lord nearby.
Huh?
No way!
That tiny dragon
is an Omni Lord?
♪
Huh?
There must be
some mistake, ki!
I'm just little old Dragon Kid,
Ricky from Ancient World.
Someone's trying
to pull a fast one.
This true, Ricky?
Tell me.
(stammering)
What, chief?
Tell me what
an Omni Lord is.
Help, chief!
Ricky!
I'll be taking this
Omni Lord Emblem
and don't try
to follow me.
No, get back here!
Auf Wiedersehen!
(all groaning)
♪
There's no
time to lose.
Go and follow them.
Are you sure?
‐That's an order.
‐Right, sorry, Tasuku.
Let's go, Tsukikage.
‐Nin!
‐Buddy skill on.
♪
We're going
after them too.
‐Got it, chief!
Not so fast, punk.
I already told you, I'm
taking you into custody.
Well, you can try,
but I got to warn ya, pal.
I'm not going anywhere.
Not until my Ricky's
back safe and sound.
Then you leave me no choice
but to take you by force.
This ought to be good.
You got guts to
fight me all alone.
Maybe I'll stick
around a bit.
Get your dirty
mitts off of me!
Put me down.
Let go of me, ki!
Nin!
Good work.
Let's go cut 'em off.
Let me go, ki!
Huh?
Who's that?
It's Mukuro Shigamine.
Am I seeing things or
was he carrying Ricky?
♪
What are you
thinking, kid?
Let's go!
You'll see.
I guess our leave
is over, huh?
♪
If you're with the Buddy Police
like you claim to be,
then why aren't you calling out
your buddy to back you up?
I don't have
a deck right now,
but it won't stop me
from taking you guys in.
(laughing)
You should be a comedian.
But you're wrong.
Show him, boys.
‐Yeah!
Just kidding, Daddy‐o.
I'm only interested
in a fair fight,
and stop acting all tough.
Not everyone will be
as forgiving as me.
(motorcycle engine revs)
♪
Buddy Police Barrier!
Now you're cornered.
You have two options.
You can give yourself up or
you can Buddyfight against me.
Tough guy, huh?
I think I'll go for
door number two, copper.
♪
Zanya!
You're back?
Nin?
Don't just
stand there!
Give me some
help here!
I was right,
he was kidnapped!
Why'd you take Ricky?
Because the little guy's
actually an Omni Lord.
‐Huh?
It's not true.
I don't know what
they're talking about, ki.
Hang tight, Ricky.
I'll have you
free in no time.
Don't be a fool.
You're still on
assigned leave, aren't you?
Yeah, but‐‐
I can handle
this, now go.
Come on, Zanya.
Just give the
kid a chance!
I promise it won't
be like yesterday.
He brought
his Hero Deck.
Don't tell him.
He's right, Zanya.
I know I can do this.
Do what you want.
You won't
be sorry, man!
Warp successful!
Wherever there's a Buddyfight,
Paruko Nanana will be there!
Emergency launch
from the eye of the storm!
Luminize!
Beaming Sunshine Guardians!
Blending with the
shadows to cut down evil!
The lone wolves
of justice!
Luminize!
Shadow Heroes!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Hero World.
I'm a real fighter
for Hero World.
Talk about a
total thriller!
Today's battle is
a Hero World showdown.
With Justice Drum
as his buddy monster,
Gao must be using his
Superhero Attribute deck
and with Schwarz as his,
Shigamine must be using
Dark Hero attribute cards.
So, let's get
to the action.
Gao went first and called
Cyber Police Assault Leader.
True to form, this
long arm of the law
is blasting some major damage
off the newcomer to our planet.
Please forgive me, Count.
Now that it's done
there's nothing we can do.
Except sit back and hope
that Gao can get it together
long enough to win this.
(siren wailing)
Now it's Shigamine's
turn at bat.
For my first move,
I call Darkness Fist,
Gwen to the left.
Whenever a Dark Hero
is called to the field,
Shigamine's First Dark Hero
Hideout card's ability
is activated.
Now I can draw one card.
I'm gonna pay one gauge
and then discard one
Dark Hero from my hand, see?
Which lets me buddy
call my big gorilla
Shadow Hero,
Schwarz to the right.
Guten tag.
♪
Dumb strike.
(screams)
I'll get you for that!
Schwarz destroys Assault
Leader with his ability.
♪
I equip.
And cut all down as a defender
of the Transient life.
Sword of Fallen Heroes,
Shadow Requiem!
(grunts)
Gwen, unleash your
rage on the fighter.
Nothing lives forever.
Darkness Fist,
the fallen palm!
(screams)
When Darkness Fist, Gwen
brings damage to an opponent,
he returns to
the player's hand.
Get him, Schwarz.
Hell Despot!
(grunting)
Auf Wiedersehen.
Think you can
keep up, kid?
At the end of the move,
Schwarz returns to
his player's hand as well.
The emblem's mine!
I cast.
I've Seen Through Your Moves!
A counter spell
helps him avoid damage.
Super awesome!
Gao still has his
groove on, yo.
I'm almost there, Gao.
The blade of justice,
Heroic Blader!
Lightning Chaser,
let's ride!
Gao has called Heroic Blader
and Lightning Chaser.
Two fearless members
of the Cyber Police.
Here I go.
Time to turn up the heat.
I pay one gauge
and transform.
Fiery Inspector
Prominence Burst!
♪
Heroic Blader,
attack the fighter!
I cast.
There I See It!
There I See It! is a spell.
It can destroy one monster
that's a Size One or smaller.
I wish for your
victory, boss.
Let's see you
do that again.
Permission to
use force, chief?
Permission granted.
Go attack the fighter.
Guess there's no need to worry
about the kid after all.
He's doing well.
Prominence Burst's
fighting technique
tries to make other
Hero cards in the deck
destroy the
opponent's monsters
while at the same time,
increasing its
own critical by one
with each successful
take down.
Yeah, but unfortunately,
the Dark Heroes
that Shigamine's got
stacked in his deck
are disappearing
from the field
once they've made
their attack.
As a result, they
can't be destroyed.
You could argue that
they're the mortal enemies
of Prominence Burst.
That's my take anyway.
Nin!
I agree, Gao's really
in tough with this guy.
Let's hope he has a plan.
♪
And now, I'm gonna call
The Scar to the left position.
♪
Looks like someone
wants to get sliced up.
You want some nice scars?
Once again, First Dark Hero
Hideout's ability is activated.
I discard one card.
And I shall call
Shadow Hero, Schwarz
to the right position.
Dumb strike!
(groans)
I got to stop him
from doing that!
I cast.
My handy spell
Hyper Energy!
That's not
good for Gao.
That spell increases
Shigamine's gauge by four.
Go, The Scar,
get the fighter.
I'm gonna carve you up
like a stuffed turkey.
Soul Slayer!
I cast.
I've Seen Through Your Moves!
That doesn't
work on both of us.
(screams)
♪
Schwarz, hit him
with Hell Despot.
Ja wohl!
(grunting)
♪
It's like child's play.
And faster than you
can say "Hero World"
Gao's down to
one life point.
Lucky for him,
Shigamine's move is over.
It's time for Final Phase.
(gasping)
♪
(roar)
I'm scared.
I cast!
(groans)
This'll be the end of you.
Well, look who we have here.
‐Get him!
‐Huh?
‐Yeah!
(shouting)
Harder!
(grunting)
Your lucky day, Ace.
I got to scram.
Chief!
Come on, Ricky.
Well, I guess with the 100
Demons Hunter interrupting,
I'll have to rule
this one a tie.
I really owe
you one, Gao.
Thank you for
saving Little Ricky.
We owe you one, ki.
I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
If you hadn't come
when you did, I‐‐
I'd have lost.
(gasps)
That's just crazy talk.
I know that if you had
I'm Still Alive! in your hand,
there's no way you
would have lost the fight.
If Ban here hadn't barged
in, you'd have been fine.
What are you
thanking him for?
You call yourself
a true Buddyfighter?
Who are you?
What have you done
with the real Gao?
♪
(siren wailing)
See ya, Gao,
got to split.
♪
Are you okay?
Don't tell me you
were watching me.
(chuckles)
I've definitely had
better days, huh?
You have to
listen to me.
There are no heroes
that are going
to come to your aid
when you're in trouble.
It's time you realize
that you have to deal
with your problems
by yourself.
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101!
Today, I'm gonna teach
you all you need to know
about Infinity
Death Crest!
Bring it!
It's a Dark Hero
impact card
that can cut down evil
with endless blades.
If you have no monsters
in the field,
and you have a
Dark Hero item equipped,
you can pay two
gauge to cause
four damage on
your opponent.
Whoa, that's a lot!
Use when Dark Hero
monsters leave the field
after their
attack is over.
Sounds perfect, but
speaking of leaving,
can I go for
lunch already?
(laughing)
♪
Next time, Ban Enma and
First Knight of Apocalypse,
Gratos come to blows.
Ricky must say
farewell to Ban
and you won't believe
what happens next.
Next episode, "Descent
of the Fire Lord!
Burn Nova Revived!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!