Buddyfight uses special
cards that act as portals
to bring monsters from
other worlds to Earth
to become buddies
with humans.
But now a swarm
of evil monsters,
known as the 100 Demons,
have come here illegally and
plan to destroy the planet.
It's time for an
emergency launch.
Buddy skill on!
♪
Huh?
What's Tasuku doing?
Don't look at me, kid.
I call Purgatory
Knight's Leader,
Demios Sword Dragon
to the right.
Attack the fighter!
(grunting)
Oh no, not this
scary guy again.
I don't understand.
Demios Retribution!
(grunts)
Why‐‐ why is he fighting
the Purgatory Knight?
♪
I buddy call Jackknife Dragon
to the right!
Attack the
Purgatory Knight!
Blade Terminate!
My Final Phase!
I cast.
(thunder rumbles)
♪
Impact!
Counter final.
I cast.
♪
(ticking)
Let the world distort.
Turn back the sands of time and
erase all sadness from the past.
Sword of
Nothingness,
Distortion Punisher!
Game over.
Winner: Purgatory Knight.
You see that?
The shadowy
creature behind him?
I sure did.
It looked like
an armordragon.
I don't get it.
With each fight,
it's the same result.
How come I can't defeat
the Purgatory Knight?
Gao could do it,
so why can't I?
Is he better than me?
Hey, Tasuku!
Gao, what are you‐‐
did you see the fight?
I sure did.
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine, I've had
a lot worse than that.
(gasps)
That badge.
♪
So tell me, how did you get
recruited by the Buddy Police?
Well, an opening
came up when you left
to train in Dragon World,
and it's something I've been
thinking about for a while.
So, Drum and I talked it over
a bit, and said, why not.
This is Takihara.
I've just arrived
at the location
where the criminal
fighter was last seen.
Over.
Finish him, Drum!
Huh?
Drill Rad Bunker!
What do you mean, Gao Mikado
and his buddy monster, Drum,
were taking down the criminal
fighter when you arrived?
It's true, and he
says he has something
to discuss with
you, Commander.
I do!
(screams)
Oh, sorry,
Commander I.
It's just, well,
I have a favor to ask you.
I knew they'd have
to replace me,
but I just didn't think
it would be so soon.
Oh, well, I mean,
Commander I
definitely took a
bit of persuasion.
And Takihara and Stella
put in a good word for me,
so he agreed to
bring me in as a trainee,
but it's not really
going too well.
I messed up big time!
I lost the Grandpa Tenbu card
that was entrusted to me.
So, you came to Dragon World
to find his card.
Yeah, but I can't help thinking
that I'm in over my head.
I'm not like you.
You two are more
alike than you'd think.
Huh?
♪
Well, don't
leave us hanging.
Spit it out.
Gao tried to be like
Tasuku and failed.
Now, Tasuku's
doing the same.
How so?
Gao could beat this guy,
so why can't I?
Hmm.
Nobody has the power
to become someone else,
but if you train
hard enough,
you can become a stronger
version of yourself.
And you, Tasuku, you know
you possess the ability
to become stronger.
You're talking about
Jackknife "Gold Ritter"?
Out of the question!
That card destroys
my bond with you.
I'll never use
that card again.
(metal clanking)
(gasps)
What's he doing here?
♪
There's no need
to be worried, guys.
He's my training partner.
You're kidding, right?
So, who's inside
the armor, then, huh?
There's nobody inside.
What?
♪
Hmm, Jack's right.
He's a special warrior created
by Armordeity, Dynamis.
Did you say Dynamis?
Never heard of
him, who's that?
You got to get
out more, kid.
Dynamis is only the master
of all armordragons.
Not to mention
my father's mentor!
And not just his!
Every famous warrior
from Dragon World
has trained under Dynamis'
wing at one time or another.
Indeed.
A most grueling process
that forces one
to face your former self.
"Facing one's
former self," huh?
♪
‐Time to raise the flag.
Charge and draw.
I buddy call Jackknife Dragon
to the right.
And I pay two gauge to activate
Jackknife Dragon's ability!
Jackknife
Thunderstorm!
Then attack the
Purgatory Knight!
End of move.
Your move.
Draw, charge and draw.
I call Silver Staff
Dragon to the left.
Crossbow Dragon
to the center,
and I buddy call Demios Sword
Dragon to the right.
I pay one gauge
and equip Fatal.
Demios, attack
the fighter!
We meet again.
It's me, your buddy.
Don't call me that!
Demios Retribution!
Your turn, Silver Staff.
Silver Staff.
Time to witness
the rule of Purgatory.
Lay down,
Kanonas Katharterio!
As you wish!
(screaming)
Great, now that nasty monster
eater gets to attack again.
Demios Retribution!
(grunts)
Arrows of demise!
Crossbow,
lay down your life.
Kanonas Katharterio!
I live to serve my brothers.
(screams)
Man, at this rate, he'll
devour his whole team.
We once fought side by side
and lost, former buddy.
Now, be honest.
Don't you still
crave this power?
No, not at all and teaming
up with you was a mistake!
And fighting me
is another one!
(grunting)
This is brutal.
He's gonna finish Tasuku
off on his first turn.
The fear you hold for me is your
own doing, for you created me.
I am your past and
I will never go away.
That's enough!
I cast!
Blue Dragon Shield!
End of move.
He was lucky to
escape that one, huh?
It's like he's
holding back.
Tasuku.
What Purgatory Knight
says is true.
The past can
never be erased,
but that doesn't mean
you have to let it dictate
how you live the
rest of your life.
I know that already.
I don't think you do.
Earlier you
made it clear
that you're still
consumed by the past
when you broke
your bond with me,
but you know
deep down, as I do,
that the decision you made
then was the right one.
We both know that ever
since that fateful day
when you found
yourself all alone,
you chose to fight
instead of being afraid,
but what were
you fighting for?
I wanted to see
justice done.
You were in such a
hurry to become an adult
that you refused
to accept the fact
that you were still
a child, and as a result,
people took advantage of you
and convinced you to
choose the wrong path,
but you must believe me.
The Jackknife "Gold Ritter"
is your true power.
You may not have chosen to
put that card in your deck,
but it's in there now
and it represents a power
that you cannot ignore.
You know in your
heart that it's true.
Even though your past
was unusually difficult,
don't let it
hold you back,
because if you
hope to truly grow
and become a stronger
version of yourself,
you must use that power.
"To become stronger
than my former self."
♪
I pay one gauge and evolve
Jack into Jackknife Dispersal
and one more gauge to evolve
him into Jackknife Aggressor.
Successive cast.
Two Dragonic charge cards
and a Dragonic Grimoire.
♪
‐I got it.
‐You know you must use it.
You got it, Jack.
I will face solitude
without fear or regret
and wield the
blade of justice.
I equip!
Yes, that's it.
You are truly worthy
of being my buddy!
Combining the
power of Dragons
and the power of humans
will create a golden era
that will
protect the world
and secure a path for
a promising future.
A human and
dragon unite.
Jackknife "Gold Ritter".
♪
I won't be leaving
you alone this time.
Jack, but how?
You turned into
Gold Ritter.
Yes, I did, but I too
have become stronger.
‐You knew.
‐Let's go.
Yeah!
Go annihilate that guy!
(screaming)
I inflict five damage!
He's gonna use
Gargantua Punisher!
But what about his gauge?
I cast Dragonic Charge.
But if he uses it now, the
counter final will get him.
Nah, he'll be just fine.
Look, he doesn't have
enough gauge for that.
Final Phase!
I cast.
(thunder rumbles)
♪
Impact!
Gargantua Punisher!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Tasuku Ryuenji.
Use your past as
a source of strength
and create the future that you
believe in, boy of destiny.
♪
That was totally awesome!
It was better than that!
You actually completed
Dynamis' training!
Is that unusual
or something?
Are you for real?
Overcoming
one's former self
is the most
difficult task of all.
I've never seen
it done before.
Like Jack said, I could never
take your place, Tasuku.
But I'm starting to
believe that if I try hard,
I could become a stronger
version of myself.
Glad to hear it.
Huh?
♪
It's Armordeity Dynamis.
No way!
♪
From the very moment that you
arrived here seeking my help,
I foresaw that this
momentous day would arrive.
♪
Hey, what's going on?
Huh, what is going on?
You are now a fighter
for Star Dragon World
and Jack remains
your loyal buddy.
"Star Dragon World?"
It's a planet with a highly
advanced civilization
and it lies far, far away.
"Far far away?"
The outer rim?
A place even more
distant than that.
(gasps)
Jackknife Dragon,
Findar the 100th,
or as you shall now be called,
Star Guardian Jackknife Dragon.
Help the boy of destiny
achieve his true desires.
That was intense.
But hey, we
have to split!
We need to
go find Heim.
It's a big planet, you
have any idea where he is?
Oh!
Good thing you
have me, huh, kid?
So what?
Do you know
where he is?
Do you even know
where you are?
It's my home!
All I gotta do is ask.
(howling)
(howls)
(distant howling)
Just as I thought.
He's at the
Gargantua Ruins.
That's amazing.
All that from some howling?
You can thank me later.
Good luck, Tasuku.
Catch ya later!
Let's go with them.
Maybe we could help.
But you must be tired.
I'll have plenty
of time to rest later.
As you wish.
♪
You think you could
escape from us, Demon?
(growls)
♪
I'm impressed you
knew where to find me.
Give Grandpa Tenbu
back to us!
Aw, you chased me all the way
here just for that old timer?
Very well.
If you defeat me,
I'll give him back.
Wait!
♪
So, he's brought
friends along.
Listen, illegal monster,
give that card back to Gao.
Ha! Or else what?
Are you going to try
to beat me in his place?
Couldn't have said
it better myself.
Heim might be using
another body double.
Time for a Buddy Police
emergency launch.
Alright.
Decker Road open!
♪
Decker Drum's on patrol!
Leave this chump to me.
Wait, Drum!
One of Decker Drum's
seven secrets.
Super Decker Scope.
Ha, see, I told you!
The real Heim's there.
Here's another
of my seven secrets.
Decker Boomerang!
♪
Think you could pull another
fast one on us, Demon?
Oh, no!
We fight with
honor here!
Huh?
♪
Hey, guys, thanks
for coming out.
(snickering)
Very well then,
I was trying to save you
the embarrassment
in front of your friends,
but if you want
me, here I am!
♪
Come on, Tasuku.
You got this.
Ravenous fiends
walking a wicked path!
Witness their
awesome power.
Luminize!
Hundred Legend.
Unite elite warriors
of the future!
Radiant Evolution,
luminize!
♪
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Legend World.
I'm with Star Dragon World!
Huh, "Star Dragon World,"
did you say?
It makes no matter.
Charge and draw.
I call Bronze Giant,
Talos to the center.
‐Attack the fighter.
‐Your wish is my command.
‐Sledgehammer!
‐End of move.
Your move.
Draw!
Now charge and draw!
I call Shadowscare
to the left
and I buddy call
Star Guardian
Jackknife Dragon
to the right.
I pay one gauge and one life
to equip Star Saver Asteroid.
♪
I've never seen or
heard of these monsters
and items before,
have you?
No, but Star
Dragon World is cool.
Shadowscare,
go attack Talos.
Yes, Master, let's
show him the light.
Visionater!
Now I'll use Star Guardian
Jackknife to attack the fighter.
Alright!
(growling)
(roars)
Star Blade Terminate!
And now it's my turn.
I think not.
I cast!
‐Holy Grail!
‐End of move.
‐He blocked it.
‐So close!
I draw.
Charge and draw!
I call Loki, the Ehrgeiz
to the left
and I pay two gauge to buddy
call myself to the right.
(growls)
But why is Talos here?
He wasn't called!
When I appear, I have
the ability to summon
a Size Two monster
from the drop zone.
So, basically, you
wanted me to destroy Talos.
That's correct.
Loki, the Ehrgeiz,
go attack Shadowscare.
Leave it to me!
I'm sorry, Master!
Now I'll attack the fighter
with Heim on the right!
Ha ha,
a demon fillet!
Talos, your turn!
(growls)
First, I cast
Proto Barrier!
End of move.
His gauge increased?
Tasuku has five life,
but Heim has eight
and Talos in the center
with 6,000 defense.
It's not looking good.
Nah, this is where Tasuku will
start to show his true power.
I draw!
Charge and draw!
I call Dragonarms
Artiliger to the left,
and Dragonarms Cavalier
to the center!
Did he say "Dragonarms"?
Setting up such a field
can only mean one thing.
You're hoping a strong
defense will save you.
Wouldn't bet on it.
Crossnize!
Your time has come!
Dragonarms loaded.
Check it out,
what's going on?
♪
Roll shift.
Variant form.
All devices engaged.
SCS active.
Load, finish.
Cavalier Soar!
A monster equipping
another monster?
That's right.
Dragonarms can be
put into the soul
of Star Dragon World monsters
to gain a new power.
That's what
Crossnize is.
‐Crossnize is the bomb!
Okay, Jack, ready?
You bet!
Star Saver Asteroid!
Cavalier Sword!
Ha, so it's just
a simple link attack.
That's what you think.
Okay, Jack!
(roars)
How'd he do that?
By crossnizing
with Cavalier,
Jack obtains the
Penetrate ability.
Blast away, Artiliger!
Is that all you've got?
Your luck will run out
as soon as it's my turn.
Final Phase!
‐I cast.
‐What?
Wicked!
Is this Tasuku's
new impact?
The light that blazes
a path to the future.
Edge of the
Soaring Star!
Impact!
♪
Radiant Punisher!
Huh?
♪
Game over.
Winner: Tasuku Ryuenji.
‐Alright, he did it!
‐Oh, yeah!
You see that?
Star Dragon World
is amazing!
♪
I think these
belong to you.
Thanks, Tasuku.
I owe you one.
Sounds like you and your
friends have your hands full
fighting against all
these 100 Demons monsters.
Hmm, you don't know
the half of it.
We Buddy Police Youth hardly
have any time to eat or rest.
Buddy Police Youth, huh?
Yeah, Tetsuya and Zanya
are on the job now, too.
Cool, that's great for them.
Well, Jack, we'd
better be going too.
(grunts)
Tasuku, what's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'll be okay.
You won't unless you finally
agree to get some rest.
You two should go.
He's exhausted from
so many days of training.
We'll follow you
in good time.
Until then,
good luck to you.
♪
I promise I'll return
to Earth soon, Gao,
and when I do,
those illegal monsters
won't stand a chance
against both of us.
(wind whistling)
(roars)
(growls)
How long have
I been asleep?
It doesn't matter now.
Oh, I'm sure my friends
will be expecting me.
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today, I'm gonna tell you all
about the Star Guardian,
‐Jackknife Dragon card.
‐Sounds good.
It's a Jack card that
has attained the power
of Star Dragon World.
When he appears,
he can put
any monster in the
drop zone into his soul,
so that's when
you should put
a Dragonarms card in
the soul to Crossnize.
Oh.
With the Dragonarms
in his soul,
he can acquire all
sorts of useful powers.
I wish I had some Dragonarms
to go grab me a monster lunch.
(laughs)
♪
Next time, Death Shido
tries to get Tenbu
with First Omni
Beast, Lord Ziun,
but due to a
misunderstanding,
Ziun challenges
Zanya by mistake!
Next episode "Hoo‐hah!
A Hundred Thousand Ziun
Years in Search of Friends!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!