(roaring)
Now that the
devastating monster
Yamigedo has been revived,
the only way to
seal him away again
is with the power
of the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us
to find them.
And there's only
one way we can.
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
With a blazing fury,
I'm gonna track
down every last one
of these evil
Hundred Demons
and demolish them
with my fists.
For I am the great Ban Enma,
Hundred Demons hunter.
You're in a pretty
feisty mood tonight, ki.
I sense that we're
closing in on another one.
So where in the world
are we, anyway?
Beats me.
(sneezes)
It's terrible, chief.
Huh?
Take a look at this.
That Gao guy's
not doing so good.
Why, what happened?
We welcome you back now
to our introspective report
on the search
for the Omni Lords.
Following his stunt at
the Chateau de Amanosuzu,
the mysterious Buddyfighter
known as Ikazuchi attacked
the Buddy Card office
and destroyed it.
Gao Mikado of the
Buddy Police Youth
challenged the criminal
fighter to a Buddyfight
but surprisingly suffered
his first ever loss
and the culprit escaped.
Gao actually lost a fight, ki.
(sighs)
♪
Tasuku, please come in.
Thank you, Mr. Mikado.
I can't believe it,
you came to
our house again.
How goes the search
for the Omni Lords?
Do you have some secret
news to share with Gao?
Actually, I do.
He's upstairs
in his room.
His friends
Baku and Kuguru
are visiting, too.
Is it okay
if I go up?
Of course, I'll
take you myself.
Great, thanks.
Gao's super busy
catching up
on all his schoolwork.
Hey, Tasuku's here!
‐Huh?
‐Uh.
Can't play with me 'cause
of your homework, huh?
Yeah, we're just
taking a little break.
It's really not at all
what it looks like.
The truth is, I got
bored with homework
and wanted to build
a new deck instead.
So don't be mad
at these two.
Oh, that's okay.
I might just forget
to bring you a snack
when I bring theirs.
Come on, that's not fair.
Hey, you guys.
Tasuku!
Everything cool?
What brings you here, man?
I just wanted to see
how you were doing, Gao.
(birds chirping)
Poor Gramps.
You are the reason
Tenbu's gone.
Huh?
That is what you're
thinking, isn't it?
Hey, Jack.
You're right,
I blame myself.
But it's not just Tenbu.
(gasping)
If what happened to
Tenbu happened to Gao,
I don't know
what I'd do.
And this Omni Lord
orb thingy or whatever
is no help at all.
I wish it would give me
a clue or something.
If you wish to spare Gao
from the same fate as Tenbu,
then you must
become stronger.
And you have
to be prepared
to protect your
Buddy at all costs.
It all comes down to
how badly you want it.
I know the fear of
losing one's Buddy.
Up to now,
you have embraced
the grueling training
required to better yourself
and your skill.
Continue in this way.
Be confident and the path
will make itself clear.
Thanks, Jack, you always
know what to say.
I'm prepared to train
as hard as I have to.
I also dropped by
to give you this.
Whoa, thanks!
It looks a little different
from your other one.
This one is
a Neo Deck Case.
I'm actually using
one just like it.
Now you're able to
Luminize again, bro.
I know, right?
Lets head over
to the dojo
and put together a
Hero World deck stat!
Good idea.
Hmm?
Hero World, huh?
(roaring)
Uh, can't we use any
stronger Hero cards?
If it's power you want,
I'd use that one.
Eh, not what
I had in mind.
Its defense is too low.
What's wrong,
it looks like
you're worried
about something.
If it's the
missing Omni Lords,
don't burden yourself,
we'll find them.
I hope so, the fate of
the world's depending on us.
That might be the case,
but having a purpose
keeps us sharply focused.
Huh, Rescue Dragon,
Mach Braver, huh?
It's a size one monster
that has this
super hero attribute:
1,000 power,
4,000 defense,
a critical of one,
and he has an ability
that activates
as a counterattack.
It's a very reliable card.
What does the "Rescue" part
of Rescue Dragon mean?
You mean you
really don't know?
Of course I do,
I'm just drawing
a temporary blank here.
He saves people
who are in danger.
That's what rescue means.
He rescues them, huh.
(thunder cracking)
Gao!
Watch out,
you purple blob,
I'm gonna save my Buddy!
(yells)
(screaming)
Hey, where you going?
I've got to rescue
my friend Gao!
♪
What's happening to him?
(electricity sparking)
I'm not losing the kid
to any monster!
(yells)
Hey, pal, how
did you do that?
Yikes, how come
I look like this?
Obviously it's because you
learned the word "rescue."
Yeah, like I said,
I just forgot
the word, is all.
The word and your
feelings became one,
and you achieved a power‐up.
Oh, yeah!
Is that true?
I don't know.
Behind every true rescue
beats a heart of justice
that seeks to save
others above all else.
From this day forth,
you'll be known
as Justice Drum.
With Drum's power‐up,
we've got some work to do.
I'll have to completely
recalibrate the deck.
Now I don't need to
fear anything at all.
Huh?
Justice Drum and I
will take down
Ikazuchi for good!
♪
(grunt)
(whimpering)
‐Huh?
The last time we saw you,
you hit my friend Baku here.
Don't try that again.
Oh, yeah,
I remember you.
Even if we were possessed
by Hundred Demons monsters,
hitting people is
totally unacceptable.
I helped you guys.
You delinquent, hoodlum,
good‐for‐nothing.
Why, you...
Mmm, chillax, bro.
I have no beef with you.
Let me at him,
stand back, chief.
I'll take care
of these small fries.
Go get 'em, Ricky.
Show 'em what
you're made of.
With pleasure, ki.
Uh.
(shouts)
Take this and
this and this,
I'm gonna knock you
into next week.
Consider that a warning
of what I could
do to you, okay, ki?
(laughing)
We'd better
head straight home.
Gotcha.
Huh?
There he is!
Hey, Ricky, after him.
Okie dokie.
Buddy Skill on.
(vocalizes motorcycle engine)
‐Huh?
‐It's him, Ban Enma.
I'm here, too, ki.
I need you to
come with me, kid.
Oh, yeah, and just what
are you up to, huh?
You'll see soon enough.
Grab this and hold on.
Huh?
(vocalizes motorcycle revving)
(shouting)
♪
I don't know
if I trust this guy.
I want to make sure
he's not gonna trick Gao.
Oh yeah, those handlebars,
I really want
to touch them.
No one gets
away with that!
On second thought,
maybe later.
Time to lay some rubber.
Not so fast!
(grunting)
‐How's it going?
‐Huh?
There's no easy
way to say this,
but what you're
feeling will pass, kid.
Just 'cause you
lost your first fight's
no reason to be
moping around, you dope.
You brought me here
'cause you're
worried about me?
Hey, chief.
(grunting)
Lookin' good.
(laughing)
It's funny that you're
here giving me advice.
My big brother Yota
used to do that.
You two are a lot alike.
Where is he now,
this brother of yours?
He's not with us anymore.
Oh.
Don't worry, I'm okay.
It was kind of
tough for a while,
but I learned
just to focus
on the happy
memories of him.
Memories, huh?
(stretches, groans)
I don't have any
of those, daddy‐o.
Huh?
The first memory I have
is of the sun
glaring in my eyes.
No matter what I do
or how hard I try,
I can't remember
where I'm from
or anything I've
done in my life
up till now.
It's such a rip, you know.
But the worst
thing is that
I don't even
remember my own name.
That's rough.
Sounds like amnesia.
Whatever you call it,
it doesn't change anything.
Wait, so the
name Ban Enma...
Just some name
I picked up.
You asked me once before why
I'm a Hundred Demons hunter.
Well, I'll tell you,
if you still want to know.
Yeah, sure.
It all started when I‐‐
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you trying to
touch my handlebars,
you scuzzball?
No, not at all
I was just...
Why, you...
Huh, what's that?
I warned you once
before, dragon.
No one ever touches
my handlebars, you dig?
(yells)
Not this again.
Hey, boys, chief's
flipped his lid.
You know what to do.
‐Right.
(drum booming)
Hey.
Cut it out!
I'm too far gone for
that to work this time.
Come on, you
always say that.
Nuh‐uh, no dice.
I am not gonna do it.
(drum booming)
Hey.
I'd comment on this,
but I'm just glad
he didn't hit me again.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Ha!
Uh, remind me why
I'm doing this again.
You wanted to cheer up your
friend Gao, remember, ki?
Oh yeah, that's right.
'Kay, Gao,
if I know you,
only one thing
will cheer you up,
that's fighting me.
Actually,
I'm really not
in the mood for
that right now.
I thought you said
you never back down
from a challenge.
So are you gonna fight me
or are you gonna fight me?
Yeah, you gonna fight, ki?
Fine, okay.
I accept your challenge.
♪
Crossnize!
Dragonarms loaded.
Roll Shift.
Variant Form.
All Devices Engage.
SES Active.
Load Finished.
♪
Cavalier Sword!
Ready, Jack?
Yep.
Star Saber, Asteroid!
Cavalier Sword!
(explosion)
Game over.
Winner, Tasuku Riuenji.
How was the Neo Star Pulsar?
Holding up nicely.
So we'll be able
to fight him next time?
Yeah, don't worry,
I'll be ready.
I'm terribly sorry to
interrupt your training,
but you have a call
from Baku Omori
and he says that it's urgent.
Thanks, please
put him through.
Sorry to bother you, bro,
but we need you
at Castle right away.
It's Gao and that
Hundred Demons hunter.
♪
It's all the rage
with Boppers who
are totally hip!
Luminize!
Enma Alliance,
Nice to Meet You.
Emergency launch
from the eye of the storm.
Luminize!
Beaming Sunshine Guardians!
Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
We are fighting
for Ancient World, ki.
We're with Hero World.
An exciting Buddyfight
between Gao and the
Hundred Demons hunter
is underway.
But hang on a second,
I've just noticed that Drum
is sporting yet
another new form.
I've got to know what
his new powers are.
I'll use my
trusty Takoscope
to check his deets.
Rescue Dragon,
Justice Drum,
a size two monster with
the super hero attributes.
He has 5,000 power,
5,000 defense,
with a critical of two.
And as I suspected,
he has one ability.
Now back to the game.
The first move goes to Gao.
I charge and draw.
Check this.
Transform Super
Burning Speed,
round up all criminals!
Explosive...
Takedown!
Rampage Sonic!
(shouts)
Rampage roundhouse kick!
End of move.
Causing three damage
is one way to
kick things off.
But it's clear that
the Hundred Demons hunter
won't be going down
without a fight.
He pays two gauge and calls
Wicked Dragon Emperor,
Billion Knuckle to the left.
Which of you wants
a good beating?
By popular demand,
I Buddy Call Dragon Kid,
Ricky to the right position.
(grunts)
You won't be sorry,
just wait till they
get a load of me!
And I equip Sky
Splitting Armor, Masurao!
Billion Knuckle,
go hit him hard.
‐(yells)
‐I cast Justice Will Prevail!
(shouting)
Counter Attack!
(yells)
What an amazing move.
Gao received two damage,
but he was able to
take out his attacker.
However, Billion Knuckle
just revives with Soulguard.
Not bad, small human.
I think he looks
ready for more.
Come on, Ricky, let's go.
All right.
(yelling)
Take this and that
and some more.
♪
Sky Splitting
Armor, Masurao!
(yells)
End of move.
Hey, Baku.
The fight's already
started, bro.
But why are they
fighting each other?
Gao calls Cyber Police,
Assault Leader to the left
and Cyber Police,
Heroic Blader to the right.
He's set up the Gao Formation!
'Kay, Assault Leader,
go and destroy
Billion Knuckle.
Yes, sir.
You fool, I cast
Gathering of
the Armed Dragons!
Do your worst.
(machine gun blasting)
I don't feel a thing.
Now get a taste of
my counter attack!
Mission failed!
Boss, I await my orders.
Hold on.
Aww, isn't it cute
that he calls
our little Gao boss?
Weird that he's
with the police
but carries a
Katana Sword though.
Ah, he's cool,
I'll let it slide.
Come on, Heroic Blader,
let's go do a link attack
on Billion Knuckle!
Rampage roundhouse kick!
Evil Defeating Slash!
It's up to you, Ricky!
Leave it to me, ki.
And my link cut.
Oh, Ricky's handy ability
neutralizes Billion
Knuckle's life link.
And with that,
he ends his move.
(growls)
Draw.
Charge and draw!
I pay two gauge and call
Bash Dragon Emperor,
Champion Lord
to the left position.
♪
I feel very, very fine.
I send Forbolka from
my hand to the drop zone,
increasing my gauge by two.
And I send Thunder
Tornado from my hand,
and activate
Demonic Wind Strike.
(grimacing)
Hold on.
No way!
He destroyed
Gao's Rampage Sonic!
He's using all the monster
abilities possible
with a size three
monster in the field!
Come on.
Heroic Blader,
move to the center!
Sure, boss.
Move completed.
Ricky, hit that
bucket of bolts
as hard as you can.
Take that and that and that.
I wish for your
victory, boss.
Champion Lord,
unleash your fury on Gao!
I'm gonna let
off some steam!
(yelling)
♪
Wait, there's more.
My double attack!
(screaming)
Now for my finishing blow!
After that
punishing combination,
Gao's down to
just one life!
Will the young fighter's
losing streak continue?
I cast I've Seen
Through Your Moves!
What suspense!
Gao saved a counter spell
for the 11th hour!
He survives for now,
but what's next?
Boy, that was
pretty close.
The Demons Hunter
has eight life left.
So he has to win
it on this turn.
I think he will.
Gao still has a choice
card up his sleeve, bro.
(yelling)
♪
Hah!
And I think he just got it.
I pay one gauge
and Buddy Call
Rescue Dragon, Justice Drum
to the right position.
Justice is served
to crush all evil,
because, I,
the invincible hero,
Rescue Dragon,
Justice Drum,
am here to save the day!
♪
I call Cyber Police,
Commander Gale
to the left area.
I never thought
I'd be heading
to the front lines again.
Here I go.
Time to turn
up the heat!
I pay one gauge
and transform,
Fiery...
Inspector...
Prominence Burst!
Yeah!
Well, that's
Hero World for you.
Robots and super heroes,
Gao transforms into
something cool again!
One more time,
it's the Gao Formation!
This kid never
gives up, ki.
Yeah, I know.
I've got him
cornered like a rat
and yet he looks
super confident.
If you want
to get the chief,
you're gonna have to
go through me first.
Champion Lord
has the Dragon Lord
Stand Of Courage ability,
which redirects an attack
meant for the
chief to himself
and he has 6,000 defense.
So what will Gao do?
He doesn't have any
monsters in the field
with over 6,000 power.
Go and give Drum a hand,
Commander Gale.
Heroes, the time has come
to let our hearts
burn brightly together
with the flame of justice.
What's happening?
Justice Drum's power
is getting a major boost!
Commander Gale's ability
can increase the power
of any super hero monster
on the field by 1,000.
Now he has 6,000 power,
so he's strong
enough to defeat him.
Okay, Drum, it's time to
show everyone your new power.
Yeah!
♪
Justice Break!
(screams)
‐Link up.
‐What's that?
You want my extra attack?
Break!
Sorry, chief.
With life link,
he receives one damage.
What's that ability?
When he destroys a monster,
he gets an extra attack.
That's Justice Drum for you.
So does it keep going
for every monster
that he destroys in a row?
At this rate,
I'll be defeated
in no time at all.
Justice Ram Bunker!
(yells)
Commander Gale, go
attack the fighter.
(shouting)
I'll clinch it
in one blow.
Well, Gao,
you're good.
Every time one of my
super hero attribute monsters
destroys an opponent's
monster with an attack,
my critical
increases by one.
And it increased when he
destroyed Champion Lord.
And it also went up one
when he took out Ricky.
Add it up and it makes
a critical of four.
Prominence Burst!
(yelling)
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
Thanks.
But I owe it
all to justice.
You're lucky
we felt sorry for you
and let you win, ki.
Thanks for challenging me.
Huh?
You've made me feel
a lot better.
I just did what Yota
wasn't able to.
Huh?
I know I could
never take his place,
but I'd like to try
if you'll let me.
Huh?
Think of me as
your big brother Ban.
Gee, thanks Ban.
All right.
Gao!
Ah, no it's those
weirdoes again.
Let's high‐tail it
out of here, quick.
Okie dokie.
Buddy Skill on.
Later, Gao.
We've gotta book.
And next time,
I'll be out for
my own justice.
What's gotten into you?
Can you tell
us why you're
hanging out
with that hoodlum?
‐Huh?
‐For once, I agree with her.
I guess that makes
three of us.
You do realize
he's interfered
with Buddy Police missions
in the past, right?
And as a member of
the Buddy Police Youth,
you've got to
be more careful.
Yeah, but the fight
was really fun.
Yeah, you two did
burn it up out there.
The addition
of Justice Drum
made the deck even more
powerful than before.
Heroes sure are great.
Whenever you're in
trouble or in a jam,
heroes appear
out of nowhere
just when you need
them to save you.
Huh?
♪
What's wrong?
You know, before
losing to Ikazuchi,
Gao would have
been thinking about
how to best use the
cards from Hero World.
But now it seems like
all he's talking about
is wanting to be
saved by a hero.
Are you overthinking it?
I don't think so.
Gao's not dealing
with the sadness
he feels from
losing Tenbu.
Hang on, you're
saying that by being
defeated by Ikazuchi
and losing Tenbu,
Gao has changed?
I am.
And the weird thing is
that he isn't even
remotely aware of it.
You know that he saved me
from the edge of despair.
Well, now it's my turn.
Until Gao returns
to his old self,
it's up to me
to take care of him.
♪
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'll teach
you about Hero World's
Rescue Dragon,
Justice Drum.
Intense!
This exciting
new Drum card
kicks aside all enemies
who stand in his way.
Every time he destroys
an opponent's monster,
he gains an extra attack.
So as long as he
keeps defeating them,
he can destroy them all
until there's none left.
That's my Buddy!
When used with Fiery
Inspector, Prominence Burst,
it grows stronger each
time a monster is defeated.
Kind of like Drum's ego.
♪
Next time, Tasuku
travels to Chou Nagoya
to find an Omni Lord,
and infiltrates
a dangerous
underground Buddyfight ring,
which brings
him face to face
with a familiar foe.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!