(roaring)
Now that the devastating monster
Yamigedo has been revived,
the only way to seal
him away again is with
the power of the
eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them,
and there's only one way we can.
‐We gotta Buddyfight!
Prominence burst!
Ahhh!
Okay, boss, I'm leaving
the rest to you.
Understood.
Might be my adrenaline talking,
but try and cut Gao
some slack, huh?
I will, and I'll start
by giving him the victory.
♪
Deela Column!
Is this some kind of attack?
Oh, it feels so warm.
♪
Tomorrow's a big day.
At the next Buddyfight Club,
Tasuku will fight me,
and if I win, I will
take his Buddy monster,
the Star Guardian, Jackknife.
It's crazy, me helping
that criminal Death Shido
after all she's done to Gao.
Imagine all this time
it was Sofia Sakharov,
and in order to save her I have
to risk losing you, Jack.
♪
Don't worry, I know
you can take this guy.
I'm your Buddy and
I stand behind you.
Thanks for saying that, but
I can't help thinking...
What'll happen if
you don't beat Suzaku?
That can't happen,
I won't lose you again!
There are no guarantees in life.
That's right, the amazing
Variable Cord lets you put
as many of your held cards
as you like into his soul!
You think I should
back out of the fight?
This is no time
to doubt yourself.
There must be another way, why
should I have to sacrifice you,
Jack, all for that
self‐serving Sofia Sakharov?
But think of the bigger picture.
Questioning her will give us
valuable intel on Yamigedo.
Yeah, you're right.
It's just so unfair.
(yelling)
♪
What's wrong?
Speak to me, Jack, Jack!
That Neodragon, Star Guardian,
Jackknife should be experiencing
the consequences of his
transformation about now.
And if truth be told, he
doesn't have much time left.
What're you saying, Suzaku?
Unlike you guys, he didn't
go through the necessary
safeguarding in Star Dragon
World that allows him
to function in other worlds.
Then his systems are
under significant stress.
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
What are you going to do?
Leave him be.
I'm only joking.
♪
Well, his only hope is to
return to Star Dragon World
and to receive
proper maintenance.
We understand.
Hold that thought.
They're onto us.
Let him go.
He is of no threat to us.
Hm.
What do you mean you
don't know what's wrong?
Jack is wasting away
before our very eyes!
How can you not know
the cause of his pain?
Well, Star Guardian, Jackknife
is sort of a
mechanical life form.
Workings of his body are
a complete mystery to us.
There are just too many things
that we don't yet understand.
(phone ringing)
That's strange, I'm
receiving a call for you.
It's Rouga Aragami.
You've got nerve!
Is it me, or do you seem
more uptight than usual?
Nothing's happened
to your Buddy, has it?
What do you know about it?
I thought I'd repay
my debt to you
by rescuing Sofia
from Suzaku Kenran.
So I sent my Buddy to scout a
way out of Cho Nagoya Castle.
That's when he heard the
news that your Buddy Jack
isn't long for this world.
That's not true,
that's impossible!
Kenran said something else.
You must return Jack
to Star Dragon World
so he can go through
some kind of maintenance.
If you don't, he's a goner.
I'll do whatever I have
to do to save him.
♪
Suzaku Kenran, come on out,
I wanna talk to you!
‐You know why I'm here!
‐Relax.
Why are you yelling?
So, what brings you here so
terribly early in the morning?
Don't tell me you're here to
beg me to cancel our fight
with Star Guardian,
Jackknife as the prize?
I made it quite clear
what would happen to that
deceitful girlfriend of yours
if we don't do battle.
I came here to ask,
please save Jack.
What do you mean, what's
the matter with him?
He's gotta go to
Star Dragon World
or else the unthinkable
will happen.
‐Don't play dumb.
‐So, you know about that.
I do.
Do you even know what
Star Dragon World is?
Star Dragon World?
It's a planet with a highly
advanced civilization,
and it lies far, far away.
Not exactly, but I know
it lies far away from here.
True, but Star Dragon World
is not just a vast distance
from Earth in proximity of
place, but also in time.
You see, it's the future
reality of Dragon World.
The future, what do you mean?
Are you saying that you
come from the future?
That's right, long ago
when the heartless beast
Yamigedo spearheaded
the Hundred Demons Army
in a merciless assault
on the universe, destroying
countless worlds,
the Armordeity, Dynamis,
was forced to act.
Her desperate search for
individuals worthy of becoming
Omni Lords required her
to travel through time
to the distant future's
version of Dragon World,
known as Star Dragon World.
There she found me and brought
me here to your time.
‐So you're‐‐
‐I am.
You're the Sixth Omni
Storm Lord, Variable Cord!
Suzaku Kenran is an identity
I created to live incognito
amongst you humans, and
I started Buddyfight Club
to attract and meet this world's
most powerful Buddyfighters.
♪
But for what purpose?
To help in our crusade
against Yamigedo.
The only way we can ensure
sealing him away again
is by befriending and recruiting
the number one
Buddyfighters in this world.
I'm curious, would you allow
me to join such a cause?
Hm, you rank yourself one of
the most powerful Buddyfighters
‐on Earth?
‐Yes, and I'll prove it
by defeating you at
your next club meeting,
but not without Jack.
So we have to get Jack
to Star Dragon World
to get him the help he needs.
I will agree on one condition.
Here we go.
You must let me win the fight.
I have my reputation
and cover to uphold.
As you know, I've never
lost a match, and though
I can't imagine that I'd ever
lose to someone like you,
I've learned that you humans
are full of surprises.
Hang on a sec, you're telling
me to throw the fight?
Yes, well I guess that's
one way of putting it.
Good, it's agreed.
♪
It's so weird, why is
this happening to Jack?
(whooshing noise)
Tasuku!
Why did you leave me and
come here by yourself?
I didn't want to.
I just don't know what to do!
I need your advice, help me!
He really asked you
to lose on purpose?
I just don't see the point.
Why would Variable Cord want me
to let him win if he's looking
for the most powerful
Buddyfighter in the world?
I wish I had an answer for you.
Either way, you can't
give in to his demands.
But if I don't do what he
wants, you know what'll happen.
Don't let that
influence your decision.
I'd prefer to have my
remaining hours lived honorably.
‐Are you sure?
‐Listen,
let's defeat Kenran together.
Think of it as my last wish.
What I want most in the
waning moments of my time
is to fight alongside
you as your Buddy.
♪
The first rule
of Buddyfight Club,
you do not talk
about Buddyfight Club!
The second rule, you do not
talk about Buddyfight Club!
The third rule, when betting
on a fight, the stakes must be
whatever you value
most in your life.
The fourth rule, the winner
can do whatever they want
with the loser's most
prized possessions.
The fifth rule, if
you win five fights,
you earn the right to
challenge Suzaku Kenran!
I feel like I'm going to cry.
The big day has finally arrived!
In the circle of destiny
sits the beautiful young girl
who infiltrated our last meeting
under the guise of Death Shido.
And our very own Suzaku Kenran
will fight Tasuku Ryuenji
of the Buddy Police
to decide her fate.
The first‐ever Star Dragon World
battle is about to begin!
We have an expanded audience.
I better put on a good show.
Twinkling stars that
light the cosmos,
dance like an electric
storm and unite as one.
Luminize Gorgeous Galaxy.
Unite Elite Warriors
of the future,
bringing evolution!
Luminize!
‐Time to raise the flag.
‐I'm with Star Dragon World.
‐I'm with Star Dragon World too.
♪
‐You okay?
‐Yeah, I'm fine.
The first move goes to
Tasuku of the Buddy Police.
He calls Photon Crown,
Geocorona to the center
who attacks, causing two damage!
Draw, charge and draw.
I call Brun Deus,
Akision to the left.
Azul Deus, Tesslamagna
to the right position.
And lastly, I call Vert Deus,
Matrix to the center.
Suzaku starts out with his
tried and true formation.
He destroys Geocorona,
but the move ends
with Tasuku still
at ten life points.
Tasuku responds with some
draw spells to put more cards
in his hand, then
calls Shadowscare
and Buddy Calls Jackknife!
(background chatter)
Okay, let's crossnize.
You heard right!
Crossnize is a unique ability
to Star Dragon World monsters.
Fighters can use this super
skill to put Dragonarms
in the card's soul
to get new powers.
Dragonarms loading.
Roll shift, variant form.
All devices engage.
SES active.
Load finished.
♪
Cavalier Sword!
‐You sure?
‐We have to,
and stop worrying!
I pay one gauge and one life,
and I equip Star
Saber, Asteroid!
♪
Shadowscare and Jack,
do a link attack!
Yes, my master.
Vision Nailer!
Cavalier Sword!
Penetrate!
♪
I cast Earth Barrier.
Ha, are you just about to
stand by and let Jackknife go?
♪
‐Matrix.
‐Yes, master?
I know your mind very well.
(shouting)
Disarm!
Jackknife revives
using Soulguard!
(grunting)
Poor Jack.
‐Tesslamagna.
‐We are sworn to protect Suzaku.
All those who oppose
him will be destroyed.
(explosive noises)
‐Akision.
‐Understood.
Commencing attack maneuvers.
♪
End of move.
I will activate an ability
and then draw three cards.
And Suzaku continues to
replenish the cards in his hand.
I draw, charge and draw.
I cast Sudden Wormhole!
That timely spell
card lets Tasuku
call a monster
from the drop zone.
I call Shadowscare from
the drop zone to the left.
‐Time to shine!
‐Attack with me.
You're the boss.
‐Star Saber, Asteroid!
‐Vision Nailer!
Okay, Jack, I want you
to go after the fighter.
Right, Star Blade Terminate!
♪
‐End of move.
‐So how you holding up, Jack?
‐Your move.
‐I draw.
Charge and draw.
If I didn't know
about our agreement
I'd say you're
trying to beat me.
I knew you'd be far too honest
to engage in deception,
but I did tell you I couldn't
imagine losing to someone
like you, and now
I'm sure that I won't.
Play time is over.
I pay two gauge and Buddy
Call to the center...
Sixth Omni Storm
Lord, Variable Cord.
♪
Suzaku's called his
Buddy, Variable Cord!
This has the potential
to get nasty, gentlemen!
I place my nine held cards
into Variable Cord's soul.
♪
Amazing, look at that!
Four Elgar Cannons, Four
Divisigators, and One Vogel!
All nine cards in his
hand are Dragonarms!
Variable Cord has 15,000
power and 10,000 defense!
Not to mention a knock‐up
critical of seven.
Then I guess my fate is sealed.
Variable Cord,
attack the fighter
with Variable Typhoon!
♪
(screaming)
In the blink of an eye
he's reduced to two life.
And Akision's closing
in to clean up.
I cast (unintelligible) Bullet!
He pays one gauge,
and desperately fires
off a counter spell.
He can destroy one monster
with 3,000 defense or less.
I cast an Akision.
(explosive noises)
He's rather persistent
for a human.
He leaves me no choice.
‐Tesslamagna.
‐I will destroy him!
End of move, your move.
Draw, charge and draw!
How can you keep going when
your Buddy's suffering so?
(groaning)
He's right, what am I gonna do?
Oh, it's like a deer in
the headlights out there.
Is he injured?
Maybe he's not happy with
the cards in his hand.
My guess is Suzaku
somehow forced him
into throwing the
fight to save Jack.
‐You think so?
‐But he's too noble
for such dishonorable schemes
and is having second thoughts.
Will he do it?
Tasuku, we agreed,
you won't let my condition
sway your principles.
Letting emotions
affect your decisions
is never the right choice.
‐But Jack‐‐
‐I tell you this,
if you choose to throw
this fight for my sake,
then I can't continue to
be your Buddy any longer.
You mean you'd
really perish for me?
It's my wish to be your
Buddy until the end.
Then you will be.
I will honor you, and fight in
a way that will make you proud.
I call Dragonarms,
Artiliger to the center!
♪
That's my Buddy,
Tasuku out there!
Time to crossnize!
Dragonarms loading.
Roll shift, variant form.
All devices engage.
SES active.
Load finished.
Artillerail‐gun!
Looks like he means business.
By crossnizing with Artiliger,
Jack gains the power
to neutralize the abilities
of all monsters he faces
that are size two or smaller.
‐Let him have it, Jack!
‐Right!
You risk much if you continue
down this path, young man.
I know, Jack, let's
do a link attack!
Artillerail‐gun!
(screaming)
Unbelievable, this
kid just wiped out
Variable Cord with
a beautiful link attack!
Is it history in the making,
Suzaku's first loss?
That's as close as
you're going to get.
I'm not done, final phase!
‐But how?
‐Excellent.
Show it to me, let me
see your new impact.
The light that blazes
a path to the future.
Edge of the soaring star!
Impact!
♪
Radiant Punisher!
(explosions)
♪
Game over, winner,
Tasuku Ryuenji.
If I didn't see it,
I wouldn't believe it.
An impact for the ages, remember
the name Tasuku Ryuenji!
The first and only fighter
to beat Suzaku Kenran!
There are two sides
to every coin, Tasuku.
This time you lost the toss.
(background chatter)
Jack!
Speak to me, hold on, pal!
Jack, come on, please wake up!
You fought well, Tasuku.
You have convinced me.
You are no doubt one of the
world's best Buddyfighters.
♪
This day keeps getting weirder!
Suzaku's just changed
into Variable Cord!
I may be going out on a limb,
but does this mean he's been
the Sixth Omni Storm Lord,
Variable Cord all along?
In my exhaustive search for
the most powerful Buddyfighter
on your planet, I was
watching for someone
who not only possessed
physical potency,
but demonstrated strength
of character as well.
If you were one composed of
weak resolve who went along
with my tainted back room
offer to throw the fight
I would never lend you my power.
For this, I commend you.
Do you mean that you're gonna‐‐
Let us create a
bond of friendship
to seal Yamigedo together.
Sure, but let's help Jack first!
As you wish.
♪
‐Rouga.
‐What is it?
Tell me, what would you do if
you were in Tasuku's shoes?
Would you have done
the same as him
and risked your Buddy's life?
‐What do you think?
‐Hm.
‐You humans are so gullible.
‐Huh?
We were about to lose patience.
We've been waiting thousands
of years for Star Guardian,
Jackknife to appear before us.
Once we're sent
to the distant past,
what will happen to us
after we seal Yamigedo?
You shall have to remain
living in that world.
After we complete this
monumental task for you,
you won't even let us
return to Star Dragon World?
Fear not, one day I will
send you a Neodragon
that holds the ability
to travel through time.
♪
And Jack is that dragon.
He can't!
♪
Jack, what're you doing to him?
Isn't is obvious?
I'm going to use his ability
to travel through time.
I regret that it will
be impossible for me
to return him to you though.
Your Buddy's time
has come to an end.
The stress of traveling
to the future won't be kind
to him in his frail condition.
I'm sorry things
worked out this way.
No, you can't!
I bid Earth farewell as
I head back to the future.
We'll leave Yamigedo
to you this time.
♪
Variable Cord, no!
At least arrest that girl!
♪
This isn't over, I know
that Jack's still alive,
and I'll do whatever
it takes to get him back,
even if it means
traveling to the future.
Jack is my Buddy, and I'll
never give up on him.
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101.
Today I'm gonna tell you
all about the monsters
Akision, Tesslamagna,
and Matrix!
‐I'm down!
‐Together, these three
Neodragons are capable
of extraordinary power.
When Akision, Tesslamagna,
or Matrix are together
on the field, the fighter
using them is allowed
to draw one card at
the end of their turn.
‐Are you serious?
‐So if all three of these guys
are around at the end of your
turn, you can draw three cards.
Which could become six,
then nine, then‐‐
a little help, teach?
♪
Next time, guess who's back?
Noboru Kodo challenges Gao
to a dragon battle,
but then that freak show
Ikazuchi turns up.
Next episode, Unorthodox Arts,
Shoraiabare Kandachi!
Join us for a Buddyfight!