(roars)
(zapping)
Now that the devastating
monster, Yamigedo,
has been revived, the only way
to seal him away again is with
the power of
the eight Omni Lords.
It's up to us to find them,
and there's only
one way we can!
We gotta Buddyfight!
I'll clinch it in one blow!
Well, Gao, you're good!
Every time one of my
superhero attribute monsters
destroys an opponent's monster
with an attack, my critical
increases by one.
And it increased when
he destroyed Champion Lord.
And it also went up one
when he took out Ricky.
Add it up, it makes
a critical of four.
Prominence Burst!
(agonized scream)
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Thanks, but I owe it
all to justice.
Buddyfight Club?
I'm sure that
you've heard of it.
Of course I have,
I mean, who hasn't?
The illegal
underground fight club
that's always changing locations
and inviting onlookers who make
crazy wagers,
like double rare cards
or even their own
buddy monsters.
I loathe the very idea of it.
I see that I've
upset you, I'm sorry.
It's not you I'm mad at.
I can't stomach anyone
who would degrade
Buddyfighting in such a way.
I couldn't agree more.
I'm shocked
these brush events
actually exist.
I thought it was all
an urban legend.
For a lady with such
an upstanding position,
I'd be surprised if you knew.
We've been investigating
these scandals for many years,
but until now, they've...
they've always managed
to elude us, I'm afraid.
And is this tip
you received credible?
Mmm, in our line of work,
we are forced to treat
every lead the same
until proven otherwise.
Someone sent us coordinates
of the fight club's next event
and we believe
the sponsor's buddy
could be an Omni Lord.
What's the location?
Cho‐Nagoya.
(grunts)
Look at this; there's
an Omni Lord in Cho‐Nagoya.
How do you know,
what are you looking at?
Why is it that I'm always
the last to know what
you're up to anyway?
'Cause you're denser
than a wrecking ball.
She's hacked into
Amanosuzu's network.
Now we're able to track
the Buddy Police's progress
in finding the Omni Lords.
Huh?
But surely that must be illegal!
You really are clueless.
I hate it when she does that!
Looks like Master Ikazuchi's
already given her
a Hundred Demons card.
Doesn't need
you slowing her do‐‐
Hey, get back!
Oh, great.
Why does everyone
always leave me?!
Okay, I'm heading out
for duty, Count Dawn.
Before you go, I'm curious
how the Neo Deck Case
is working out for you.
So far, only you and Gao
have been issued with them.
It's great,
no problems at all.
I can fight at any time.
Then you are approved
for Emergency Launch.
Just please promise
to be careful.
It's possible Ikazuchi
and his cronies are using
the same intel.
‐10‐4.
Lucky for you,
it's a beautiful day.
♪
Here we go.
(screams)
♪
So this is Cho‐Nagoya?
Let's start by talking
to people at card stores.
♪
Look, it's Sofia Sakharov.
Hmm?
♪
You coming?
I'm afraid her presence here
can only mean one thing.
(footsteps)
You better not be trying
to pull a fast one.
Come on, little darling.
Does this look like
the face of a liar?
Just show it to me.
Ain't you a right
old spark plug?
Don't go getting all
riled up now, y'hear?
I'm a man of my word!
I don't have all day.
Show me the invitation
from Suzaku Kenron.
Suzaku Kenron?
If you believe the rumors,
which I do, he's the one
running Buddyfight Club.
There's only one way
to get through the door.
You need a special invitation
from him to enter
these secret events.
Hmm.
Hold you horses,
I got it right here.
Huh?
Rouga?
It's been a long time.
How are you, Sofia?
What brings you out
to Cho‐Nagoya?
Nothing really, just
travelling around a bit.
I thought I saw
a familiar face,
so I came closer,
then I overheard
what you two
were talking about.
Why don't we just pretend
that you were never here?
Suzaku Kenron, huh?
They say that he's the
head of Buddyfight Club.
Don't tell me you
wanna come, too?
No true Buddyfighter
would turn down the chance.
I've heard that he
is exceptionally skilled
and that he uses
a world no one's
ever heard of.
I'd like to see that.
I was just fixing to sell this
to your pretty friend here.
Is that the invitation?
It could be yours if you
pony up more than her.
Why you‐‐
Wish I could,
but I have no money.
Okay, partner, then this
conversation's over.
Nothing is over
until I say it is!
My Hysteric Spear!
(grunts)
You can make the power
of the cards real?
Drop that invitation and leave
unless you want to get hurt.
You too.
That's enough!
On behalf of the Buddy Police,
I'll be taking that invitation,
Rouga, not you!
Well, this oughta be good.
Still taking things
by brute force, huh?
I guess some things
never change, do they?
I don't know, a lot's changed
for you lately, hasn't it?
I saw your fight.
I pay one gauge and one life
to equip Star Saber Asteroid.
Rainbow Vision,
Shadowscare to the left,
and I buddy call Star Guardian,
Jackknife to the right.
With a buddy gift,
he regains one life point.
For Peluda, it's a size one
and Zazamera a size two.
When those monsters are called,
their Thunder Mines
are activated!
I knew what to expect!
Crossnize!
Dragonarms loading.
Rule shift!
Variant form.
All devices engaged.
SES active.
Load finished.
(roars)
Cavalier Sword!
Okay, Jack, do a Penetrate
attack on the center!
10‐4!
Cavalier Sword!
And Penetrate!
Your pathetic encounter
with that brat and his
strange parade
of Hundred Demons flag;
you realize if you hadn't
failed to finish him,
Gao Mikado would never
have lost his first fight.
(gasps)
Huh?
Thanks, it's been fun.
Come back!
Teleportation.
Ace, think that's our cue.
I can't let you do that.
I'll even use force
if I have to.
I welcome it: a battle
with you to finally settle
the score between us!
♪
(grunts)
Your Future Force, right?
♪
(grunts)
You okay?
It's nothing.
Don't be shy, show me the
power of Star Dragon World.
I don't mean to interrupt you,
but what if I told you I got
more of them there invitations?
That be of interest to ya?
It just might be.
Suzaku Kenron gave
me just one job,
to mosey 'round town
looking for skilled fighters,
then invite the best to his
upcoming Buddyfight Club.
So, why did you sell
an invitation to that girl?
Come on, you can't blame a guy
for trying to make a living,
now can you?
(grunts)
Huh?
Why not settle out differences
at the Buddyfight Club?
I told you,
I'll arrest you here,
even if it's by force!
(grunts)
Don't have a conniption fit.
This feller here's now
an invited guest of
the Buddyfight Club,
so if you wanna play rough.
♪
Hundred Demons?
Hardly, friend.
Don't be ridiculous.
See, they're the doormen
that'll be keeping the riffraff
out of our event.
They're illegal monsters!
Bullseye!
Let's retreat
and fight another day.
How can you say such a thing?
If I was you,
I'd listen to him
and get gone right quick.
No, wait!
And lemme give you
a little advice:
If the folks at
Buddyfight Club
even suspect you're
with the Buddy Police,
they'll be on you like
a hound on a squirrel,
so you'd best wear a disguise.
♪
Rouga used that
distraction to slip away.
♪
Buddyfight Club
is being held
at this castle?
Seems a little much.
Hmm?
(door opens, footsteps)
The first rule
of Buddyfight Club:
you do not talk
about Buddyfight Club!
(cheering)
The second rule:
you do not talk
about Buddyfight Club!
The third rule:
when betting on a fight,
the stakes must be whatever
you value most in your life.
The fourth rule:
the winner can do
whatever they want
with the loser's
most prized possession.
The fifth rule:
if you win five fights,
you earn the right
to challenge Suzaku Kenron.
What's this?
Tetsuya, what on Earth are you
doing in a place like this?
Uh, yo, yo, yo,
back it up there, homes.
Don't be dissin' me,
I'm just trying
to spectate, yo!
You call that a disguise?
Told ya, your cover's blown.
Game over.
Winner: Death Shido.
Death Shido?
Guess he got the same tip
on the Omni Lords that we did.
For a first‐timer
at Buddyfight Club,
Death Shido's on fire,
with a five in
a row winning streak.
Meaning a fight challenge
to the great Suzaku Kenron
is up next.
That was a magnificent fight.
So, that's‐‐
Suzaku Kenron.
Well, are you really
planning to fight me?
Before I do, I have
a question I'd like
to ask you:
Is it true that
your buddy monster is,
in fact, one of
the Omni Lords?
What?
First, let's have our fight.
If you should win,
I'll answer any question
you might have.
You do wanna fight, don't you?
Of course, let's go.
(cheering)
Before we get started,
be warned that I'm on
a 100 million fight
winning streak.
You still wish to fight?
Uh, 100 million?
(laughs)
Only kidding, of course.
100 million is an exaggeration,
but the truth is
I've never lost.
Why are you still here?
Losers are not permitted
to hang around.
(screams)
Let's be sure you
understand the rules.
The winner takes the
other's buddy monster,
and then they can do with
the beast whatever they like.
Are we agreed?
How an anyone be involved
in such a scheme?
(grunting)
Are you stalling?
I agree, now hurry up
and luminize.
Just to be sure,
is that really your buddy?
Why would you
ask such a thing?
Hmm, very well, let's begin.
It's Death Shido
against Suzaku Kenron.
And get this, it's
the ultimate stakes,
their buddy's on
the line if they lose!
Ravenous being
walking a wicked path,
witness their awesome power!
Luminize, Hundred Danger!
Twinkling stars
that light the cosmos,
dance like an electric storm
and unite as one!
Luminize, Gorgeous Galaxy!
Say it with us: Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
I'm fighting for Danger World.
I'm with Star Dragon World!
Did he say, "Star Dragon World"?
Tasuku's not the only one?
Who is this guy anyway?
This was definitely worth coming
all the way to Cho‐Nagoya.
Charge and Draw.
I call Brun Deus,
Akision to the left,
Azul Deus, Tesslamagna
to the right,
and I call Vert Deus, Matrix
to the center position.
Suzaku Kenron
leads out of the gate
by calling three monsters.
I'm confused; the player
with the first move
can only attack once,
so why do that?
Matrix.
Yes, Master, I know
your mind very well.
Crush!
(gasps)
End of move.
I will activate an ability
and then draw three cards.
When Akision, Tesslamagna,
and Matrix are in the field,
they each allow the player
to draw a card at the end
of the turn.
So that's why he called
all three monsters!
I Link Attack with
Armor Knight Salamander!
Come on!
(roaring)
Penetrate!
♪
Your turn,
Minotaur, go attack!
(grunts)
♪
End of move.
Death Shido cut down
Suzaku Kenron's life
by five points
in just one turn!
Your move.
I draw, charge and draw.
First, I choose to cast
a Sudden Wormhole
and I call the Matrix
in my Drop Zone to the center.
Our crafty leader's used a spell
that lets him call a monster
from his Drop Zone.
Tesslamagna.
We are sworn
to protect Suzaku.
All those who oppose him
will be destroyed.
(zap)
Akision!
Understood, commencing
attack maneuvers.
(scraping)
'mander!
Matrix.
(grunting)
(gasping)
End of move.
Once again, I get
to draw three cards
from my deck.
Why does he keep increasing
the number of cards in his hand?
I call Armor Knight
Ogre to the right
and buddy call Crush Execute
Dragon, Zarrtelganger
to the left!
(growls)
If you make me angry,
you'll regret it, grr!
I cast Invigorating Breath!
Death Shido's life
has increased once again!
Zarrtelganger,
use your strength;
attack Matrix in the center!
I'll crush you
where you stand, grr!
♪
Ganger Crush!
(grunting)
Ogre, attack
the fighter with me!
Ogre!
♪
End of move.
Suzaku's down
to just one life!
Will this newcomer,
Death Shido, be the one
to hand him his
first‐ever loss?
Now for my secret weapon.
I pay two gauge and
buddy call to the center
Sixth Omni Storm Lord.
Sixth Omni Storm Lord?
Variable Cord!
As we thought, his buddy
really is one of the Omni Lords!
I place nine cards from my hand
into Variable Cord's Soul.
No way, that's so many!
♪
That's right, the amazing
Variable Cord lets you put
as many of your held cards
as you like into a soul!
That's why he was boosting
the cards in his hand.
Oh no, Variable Cord's
Soul contains much more.
Winchisker, Divisigator,
and three Elgar Cannons
for a total of five
Dragon Arms cards.
Meaning that Variable Cord
now is Crossnized with
an incredible five Dragon Arms.
Check out his
unbelievable stats.
He has 13,000 power
and 4,000 defense,
not to mention a remarkable
knockout critical of six!
Akision, attack the right!
Tesslamagna, attack the left!
‐Yes, Master.
(screaming)
Now attack the fighter.
Variable Cord.
♪
Variable Typhoon!
(screams)
From 11 life down
to 5 in one blow!
And with that,
Winchisker's ability,
Hysteric Spear, has been
completely destroyed.
What's Death Shido gonna do?
Unreal.
♪
I will cast Thunder Devastation!
(blasts)
I didn't see that coming.
Death Shido's wiped out
all of Suzaku's monsters.
Master Protection.
But, like so many times before,
our resourceful leader revives
Variable Cord with Soulguard!
I call Armor Knight
Salamander to the right!
And I call Zarrtelganger
to the center position.
'mander!
I'll squash you flat.
Quick, Salamander,
unleash an attack
on Variable Cord!
'mander!
Master Protection.
♪
Your turn, Zarrtelganger!
Go take down Variable Cord!
Ganger Crush!
♪
Master Protection.
End of move.
This is over;
there's no defending this.
Attack the center.
Variable Typhoon.
♪
I'm sorry,
I couldn't squash him!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Suzaku Kenron.
Wouldn't you know,
our wonderful leader
is victorious as usual.
Extending his winning streak
in impressive fashion.
As agreed, I'll be
taking your buddy now.
I thought so; this is
a Hundred Demons card,
meaning you lied.
It's not your
buddy after all!
The deal was our buddy monster
would be the spoils of victory!
Now bring out your
true buddy at once.
♪
(screaming)
What?
It's Sofia!
Who'dve thunk it?
Hiding behind Death Shido's mask
and fooling everyone here
is some girl!
You understand that
my hands are tied, my dear.
You see, it's an unwritten rule
that has never been broken:
Girls are not allowed
in Buddyfight Club.
What will Suzaku do to her
for crashing the party
and lying about who she is?
Oh, I hate to think,
I can't even watch.
Hmm?
The Buddy Police will
take her into custody.
What a fool.
I don't believe my beady eyes!
A Buddyfight mole
has actually managed
to infiltrate
our Buddyfight club!
Get him, boys, we can't let
him leave here in one piece!
(grunting)
If you wish to place her
in protective custody,
you'll have to
defeat me first.
Okay, Tasuku Ryuenji?
Ryuenji?
Can it be?
How do you know who I am?
'Cause I work for
Suzaku Kenron, partner!
(gasping)
It was him all along.
That's right, Buddy Cop,
I played you for a total fool.
Why bring me here?
Because I wanted to fight you
and try to win your
buddy monster as well.
No chance.
Even if it would
save the girl?
(moaning)
I would never risk
losing Jack for her
or anyone.
Tasuku!
(screaming)
(chuckles)
So, it's decided.
At the next Buddyfight Club,
Tasuku will fight me
and if I win, I will
take his buddy monster,
the Star Guardian, Jackknife!
(cheering)
Welcome to Tasuku's
Buddy Police 101!
Today, I'm gonna teach you
about Sixth Omni Storm
Lord, Variable Cord.
Crossnizing with other cards
makes this neo‐dragon
the most powerful card ever.
When called, you can put
as many cards as you want
from your hand into his Soul,
so by putting several
dragon arms cards in there,
his power is limitless.
Limitless?
He also has Penetrate
and Soulguard,
so you can really clean up
with him in your deck.
Speaking of cleaning up,
can we forget the blackboards
for today?
(chuckles)
♪
Next time, we learn Asmodai
was the Second Omni Demon Lord
all along, and Tetsuya
fights Mukuro Shigamine
from Hero World with
the Omni Lord emblem
on the line.
Next episode...
Join us for a Buddyfight!