[UKAI]
I'll be seeing you at
Nationals this year.
[NEKOMATA]
Hmph! Yeah, that's what
you say every year, Ukai.
[UKAI]
Oh be quiet! This is
going to be the one.
[GUY A]
This oughta be good! The
trashcan showdown, cats versus
crows! Can't wait to see it!
[TAKEDA]
But that June at the
Inter‐High preliminaries,
both schools narrowly missed
earning a ticket to Nationals.
[TAKEDA]
In March of the following year,
Karasuno High, representing
Miyagi prefecture,
and Nekoma High, acting
as Tokyo's second
representative school,
both appeared at the spring
high school national tournament.
[TAKEDA]
Karasuno was defeated in the
third game, and Nekoma made it
to the quarterfinals,
before they were also
eliminated.
After that, the two schools held
many, many practice games...
but both coaches eventually
retired without ever having
faced each other in an
official match.
[TAKEDA]
These events led to the steady
decline of both teams over the
years to come.
[TAKEDA]
But now...
Gah!
[TAKEDA]
...their fated rematch
is about to start!
[SHOYO]
Kenma!
[KENMA]
Huh? Hey.
You're really on
the Nekoma team?!
[KENMA]
Uh‐huh.
How come you didn't tell
me that when we met?
Well, you...
didn't ask.
[SHOYO]
(stunned) But when you left,
you said "later",
so you must've known I was
gonna be here, right?!
[KENMA]
Uh, you had "Karasuno
High School" written
on your t‐shirt, so...
[YAMAMOTO]
Well, well, well!
You know, that's our setter...
What's your business with him?
[SHOYO] (gasp) I...
I'm sorry! Ah!
[KENMA] Calm down.
[RYUNOSUKE]
And what about you? Shorty's
with us... So what's YOUR
business with HIM, brush head?!
(SHOYO panicking)
[YAMAMOTO] What's
it to you, buddy?
You lookin' to rumble?
Eh city boy? (growling)
[KOSHI]
Um yeah you guys ARE
about to rumble...
The game's just
about to start.
And stop saying "city
boy"; nobody says that.
(RYUNOSUKE stunned)
[YAKU]
Yamamoto please...
Could you stop picking
fights all the time?
You're making a damn
fool of yourself.
(YAMAMOTO stunned)
[YAKU]
Yeah..
that's our team idiot...
You'll just have
to excuse him.
Sorry about ours too...
He's embarrassing.
(YAMAMOTO big shock)
(RYUNOSUKE startled)
(YAMAMOTO lovestruck)
[YAMAMOTO]
Girl...
hot... wow...
[INUOKA SHIBAYAMA] Sweet!
[SHIBAYAMA] Easy
on the eyes too!
[INUOKA]
Love me a girl manager!
[INUOKA SHIBAYAMA]
Yeah, yakisoba!
[YAMAMOTO]
Damn you, Karasuno!
(dramatic sobs)
[INUOKA]
Jeez, get it together,
would you?!
Uh Hinata...
How do you already
know one of those guys?
Oh, I met him earlier
while I was out...
I guess he's Nekoma's
setter, that's all.
A setter...
(scared)
[KUROO]
I look forward to
playing with you today.
And we're also looking forward
to playing with you guys.
[SHOYO] Whoa! Check this out!
[INUOKA] Hold that side.
[TOBIO]
What? It's just a gym.
[KUROO DAICHI, internal]
Ah, so he's the shrewd type.
[NAOI]
Man, 8 years, huh? Barely
recognized you with that
haircut.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah, well maybe you oughta
try something new once in a
while, Naoi.
(NAOI & KEISHIN chuckle)
[NEKOMATA]
Ah, Keishin!
[NAOI TAKEDA] Hm?
[KEISHIN] (surprised)
Coach Nekomata!
It's been a while.
I see you're still the spitting
image of your old grandfather,
aren't you, boy?
[TAKEDA] I‐I'm
Ittetsu Takeda, sir!
[DAICHI] Let's stretch out!
[ALL] Yes sir!
[TAKEDA]
I spoke to you on the phone;
thank you so much for your time.
[NEKOMATA] Well, after all
those dozens of phone calls,
(KURASUNO doing stretches)
I started feeling like I had
to respond one way or another.
Ah, I'm sorry
about that!
Aw, I'm just pullin'
your leg, son!
We've already had ourselves
several good practice games
over the past three days...
And I expect this one'll
be interesting too.
[TAKEDA]
Yes! Thank you, sir!
Oh, and it matters not to
me that Ukai's not here...
We'll still destroy you.
(KEISHIN & TAKEDA
straighten up)
[DAICHI]
We haven't been a team
for very long...
We're still kind of
finding our groove...
So we're not
very coordinated.
[DAICHI]
On top of all that, this is
our first game using our new
starting line‐up...
We don't know anything
about Nekoma as a team,
but whatever kind of
wall we find ourselves
up against today...
...we can rise above it!
[KUROO]
We are plasma.
Let's make our motions fluid.
[KUROO]
Keep the oxygen flowing so
the brain can work to its
full potential!
[KUROO]
Here we go!
[NEKOMA]
Okay!
[KENMA]
Kuroo... don't say that stuff...
It's really embarrassing.
[YAMAMOTO]
Aw, don't be like that!
It adds to the mood.
[KAI]
It helps us get into
the right mindset.
[KUROO]
Guess you're outnumbered.
(KENMA sigh)
(long whistle)
[TAKINOUE] Sweet! Just in time!
[DAICHI & KUROO] Line up!
[SHIMADA]
Ah yes here we go again.
Cats versus Crows!
[NAOI]
Let the practice game
between Nekoma High
and Karasuno High
officially begin!
[ALL]
Thank you for the game!
[DAICHI]
You don't seem as nervous today.
[SHOYO]
Really?
[INUOKA]
Huh? You're tiny!
Gah! Don't you mock me!
I'm not mocking you
at all, dude!
Huh? Really?
[INUOKA]
Yup!
Tch!
(internal) He's as
paranoid as always.
(nervous)
[KENMA] Hey Shoyo.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[KENMA]
Remember when I told you
that I think Nekoma's
got a pretty good team?
Well, it's not because
I'm good... We all are.
[SHOYO]
Huh?
(whistle)
[KUROO]
You can do it, Kenma!
[YU]
Asahi!
[ASAHI]
I got it!
Agh, sorry, guys!
[YU]
That's what happens when
you skip for a month!
[ASAHI]
Uh, my bad!
[DAICHI]
Kageyama cover!
[TOBIO]
Got it!
(INUOKA, NEKOMATA
& YAMAMOTO shocked)
(SHIMADA & TAKINOUE pleased)
(whistle)
Whoa, that was crazy
fast! But how...?!
A quick‐attack from
that distance?!
How'd he do that? I mean the kid
didn't even open his eyes!
[TAKEDA & KEISHIN]
Heh heh!
[KENMA] That's amazing...
You've got skill.
[SHOYO] Huh? (laugh)
[YU]
Good job, Hinata!
[SHOYO] Thanks!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Let's do this thing!
Kuah!
[YAKU]
Comin' atcha!
[YAMAMOTO]
Eat this!
[TOBIO]
Yes, nice receive!
(internal) Another one!
[INUOKA YAMAMOTO]
Agh!
(YU surprised)
(whistle)
(SHIBAYAMA breathless)
[NEKOMATA] (stunned, laughing)
Well, nobody could've
retrieved that, right?
[YU]
You got this!
(KEI smacked, annoyed)
[INUOKA]
All yours!
[YAKU]
Thanks!
[KOSHI]
Hey, nice work.
[YU] Oh, thanks Suga...
(whistle)
[YU] That libero of theirs
isn't playing around.
[KOSHI] Huh?
[YU] Even though he's never seen
Asahi spike... he got to it.
[DAICHI] Get ready, Hinata!
[SHOYO]
Ah! Sorry!
[YU] (surprised) Sorry, but
could you hold this for me?
[TOBIO] You're such a moron!
[KOSHI] Uh‐huh...
[YU] It's cool, guys!
[RYUNOSUKE] Go for it, Noya!
[TAKEDA]
Nishinoya sure moves
around a lot, doesn't he?
[DAICHI] Left!
[KOSHI] Yes sir... The libero
specializes in defense
so he'll come in and out
several times during a game.
[KOSHI]
Our middle blockers,
Hinata and Tsukishima,
have to go to the rear to serve,
and then after the rally's done,
they switch out positions
with Nishinoya.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Aw yeah, it's my turn!
[RYUNOSUKE] Yeah!
(whistle)
(KURASUNO cheers)
'Kay guys, now bring it in.
(long whistle)
[TAKINOUE] Wow.
That's a pretty early
time‐out don'tcha think.
[NEKOMATA]
Their spiker and libero are
extremely talented.
But their setter is the most
outrageous player in the whole
bunch.
[NEKOMATA]
That boy's a monster.
He's speed‐tossing
straight to the spiker's
optimum strike point.
He could thread a needle
with that control.
Well, not much you can do about
a prodigy like that.
But... just because they have
one genius on the team...
that doesn't necessarily
mean they'll win.
If their team's offense is
hinging on Hinata...
then we should stop him first.
[YAMAMOTO]
Who's Hinata?
[KUROO]
It's Karasuno's number 10.
[NEKOMATA]
Right, he and number 9
make for a deadly combination.
A demon... and his iron club...
So our first step is
taking the club away.
(whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrating)
[TAKEDA]
Alright! They're in top form!
[KEISHIN] I'm getting bad
vibes from these guys.
(TAKEDA question)
[KEISHIN]
For some reason I get the
feeling they're scrutinizing
our every move.
(whistle)
[INUOKA] (annoyed) No way!
[YAMAMOTO]
It's okay, bro!
You were pretty close!
[TOBIO, internal] Their number
7's got his eye on Hinata.
[INUOKA] I'm sorry!
[TAKINOUE]
Nekoma decided to move
their blockers to the side.
[SHIMADA]
Mm‐hm... an area block.
[TOBIO, internal]
What tha...
That kind of block isn't
designed to track the ace.
Don't tell me...
[KEISHIN]
They're trying to lead Hinata.
[KENMA]
We have to confine Hinata
to a smaller area.
[KENMA]
From what I've seen so far...
I think he just charges straight
to wherever we don't have any
blockers.
[KENMA]
So if we block him on one side,
he'll go the opposite way.
And then you just
have to follow him.
You got it!
That combo move is scary...
I think anybody would be
thrown off guard the first
time they see it.
But... just like when you can't
beat a level in a game...
the more you try...
[KENMA]
...the better you get.
[INUOKA, internal]
Okay, I just gotta
follow number 10!
[TOBIO, internal]
He got to it again?!
[SHOYO]
It's a quick attack!
(SHOYO surprised)
[YU]
(slide) Dammit...
[DAICHI]
Don't let it get to you!
[TAKEDA]
A setter dump.
(KEISHIN frown)
[TOBIO]
Hey... Don't tense up.
(SHOYO look)
[TOBIO]
They see your weaknesses.
[DAICHI]
Front!
[RYUNOSUKE]
(slide) Sorry Noya,
can you cover it?
[YU]
Sure thing!
[TOBIO]
Right side!
[SHOYO]
Huh? Why's HE calling for a set?
[YU]
Kageyama.. heads up!
(RYUNOSUKE & ASAHI stunned)
[TOBIO]
Hey! That one's called
a straight hit!
It goes down the side!
Be selective with your spikes!
(SHOYO annoyed)
[RYUNOSUKE]
His perfectionism really
starting to piss me off. Heh...
[KOSHI]
You and me both.
[DAICHI]
Nice drop, Tsuki!
[KENMA, internal]
This guy thinks things through,
and he's in tune with
his surroundings...
He's the complete
opposite of Shoyo.
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Let's go!
[KUROO]
You got it?
[YAMAMOTO]
You bet!
[YAKU]
Nice receive!
[KENMA, internal]
Who do I send it to?
[KEI, internal]
To the right?
[KENMA, internal] Left.
(KEI gasp)
[KENMA, internal]
So he was watching closely.
He's quick too.
(whistle)
[NEKOMA] (celebration)
[TOBIO, internal]
That glance was just a decoy!
[NEKOMATA]
Kenma is not a fan of
interacting with people...
but he eventually became so
conscious of their eyes that he
turned it into an advantage.
[NEKOMATA]
His skills of prediction
are razor‐sharp.
He can tell a lot about
his opponents just by
observing them.
But of course, that's not what
makes our team such a force to
be reckoned with.
[KENMA]
All my life... I've never
had any luck making friends
for myself.
[KENMA]
I don't have any interest in
other people. I'm always
extremely aware of their eyes.
[KENMA]
I did all I could not
to stand out.
[KENMA]
Since he was my age and
lived close by, Kuroo was
my one friend.
(KENMA gasp)
[KENMA]
I don't like sports very much,
but I've always played around
with volleyball.
[KENMA]
When we were in middle school,
Kuroo talked me into joining
volleyball club...
It was okay, I guess.
[KENMA]
I kept playing it when I
got to high school...
Our school had a good team
my first year...
[KENMA]
... but there were
so many people,
I couldn't deal with
being a part of it.
[GUY B]
Hey first‐year, clean up faster
so we can go home!
[KENMA]
There's nothing special
about upperclassmen;
they were just born a
year or two sooner...
So why do they act like they're
better than everyone else?
[KUROO]
You can't quit... Not only do
you have greater observational
skills than us...
you're also a good strategist.
All the first‐ and second‐years
already know how amazing you
are...
This team's gonna go
really far with your help.
(pensive)
[TAKEDA]
He doesn't stand out.
[KEISHIN]
Huh?
[TAKEDA]
Even an amateur can
tell that Kageyama's
got a certain intense greatness
about him, you know?
[TAKEDA]
I'm not saying Nekoma's setter
ISN'T doing amazing stuff out
there,
but you wouldn't know
just by watching him.
Well yeah.. that's because
their receives are stable.
[KEISHIN]
The most important component for
a diverse arsenal of attacks is
solid receiving.
You want receives that land
the ball neatly above the
setter's head.
The better they are, the
more room the setter has to
put his abilities to work.
[KEISHIN]
We've got Kageyama, holding this
ragtag group together with his
overwhelming talent...
whereas Nekoma's setter is
supported by the receiving
skills of his entire team.
[KUROO]
We are plasma... Let's make
our motions fluid...
Keep the oxygen flowing..
so the brain can work to its
full potential!
(SHOYO grunt)
[INUOKA] One touch!
[YAMAMOTO]
Nice cover, Yaku!
[NEKOMATA]
We don't need a superstar
for the team ace.
[NEKOMATA]
All we have to do is keep
racking up points one by one,
slowly but surely.
(whistle)
(NEKOMA celebrating)
[SHOYO]
I'm really going for it on
the next spike, so give me
a set, okay?
But that's really risky
for us right now...
One mistake and
we lose the set.
[SHOYO]
(panic) I know that! Trust me!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice!
[KENMA]
But it's just like when you
can't beat a level in a game...
[KENMA]
The more you try...
(SHOYO gasps)
(TOBIO grunts)
[KENMA]
...the better you get.
[INUOKA]
Finally got you that time!
(long whistle)
NEKOMA] (happy) Alright!
[TOBIO]
Look.. we can't get
discouraged right now...
We can take the next set!
There's not a spike in the world
that can't be stopped, Red...
You gotta stay focused.
We'll nail this
one for sure!
Kick its ass!
Right!
(long whistle)
(whistle)
[SHIMADA] Aw, not again.
(INUOKA triumph)
[YAMAMOTO]
Nice block, Inuoka!
[KEISHIN]
Their Number 7's no joke.
He's got Hinata's
patterns figured out.
(SHOYO panting)
[YU]
Nice cover, Daichi!
[RYUNOSUKE] Left!
[TOBIO] Tanaka!
[KEISHIN] I can smell you
wondering
why I'm not taking
Hinata out of the game?
(KURASUNO celebrate)
[KEI] (surprised) Nope.
If this was an official game,
I probably would have...
but for now I'd rather give him
a chance to find a solution.
(SHOYO panting)
[KEISHIN] Of course, if
this makes him lose his
will to fight,
I'll take him out
in a heartbeat.
[TOBIO]
He juked him!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Damnit!
[TAKEDA]
So close!
(SHOYO panting)
(NEKOMA cheers)
[KOSHI, internal]
He was completely shut down
during his first and only game
in middle school...
and now he's no match
for Tsukishima's height
in high school.
[KOSHI]
So he found a way to overcome
those setbacks and face even the
tallest opponents...
but now, even when he
uses his best attack...
[KOSHI]
All it takes is a single
blocker to stop him!
He's staring straight into the
"human wall". The more it stops
you, the more your heart breaks.
Huh?
(SHOYO panting)
(TOBIO shocked)
(KENMA surprised)
(KUROO surprised)
He's smiling.
Hinata...
[SHOYO] Somehow...
that was different.
[TOBIO] What?
[SHOYO]
It wasn't the same as the
confusion I felt back then.
When I couldn't see past the
blockers to the other side
and didn't know what to do.
It wasn't like that.
[SHOYO]
I can tell my opponent's having
trouble keeping up with me.
Before, all I felt was fear and
hate whenever I got blocked.
[SHOYO]
Now when a blocker stands in my
way, it's just exciting!
[SHOYO]
With your amazing sets
and a good strategy...
I think I can find a
way to get past him.
[SHOYO]
All I want is...
One more set...
How's that sound?
[TOBIO]
Yeah we'll see.
(whistle)
[YAMAMOTO]
Let's go!
(gasp)
What?
(shocked)
(whistle)
His... eyes were open...
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, what was that?
Hinata's been leaving it
up to Kageyama...
[KOSHI]
Something must be wrong!
[KEISHIN]
Hey, time out, time out!
(long whistle)
[SHOYO]
(panic) I‐it's not that I don't
trust you or anything, but...
uhh let's see...
Dude. What are you
freaking out about?
[KEISHIN]
Kageyama... From now on,
I want you to try sending
slightly weaker sets to Hinata.
[KEISHIN]
No more direct delivery.
So you want an
indirect delivery?
A what?
[KEISHIN]
Your sets are usually powerful
with a straight trajectory...
It needs to float a little bit.
[KEISHIN]
I know it's kinda
tricky to change it
on the spot though...
Can you handle it?
[TOBIO]
I can do it.
(long whistle)
So what's the purpose
of floating the set?
I want to give Hinata some
extra freedom in the air...
I noticed that he was
trying to dodge that
blocker mid‐jump just now.
[TAKEDA]
Huh?
[KEISHIN]
There's a technique for
shaking off blockers;
it looked like that's
what he was after.
Too bad it was a complete
and utter failure.
(awkward laugh)
[SHOYO, internal]
Up 'til now, I could hit it
without thinking at all...
It's so weird to be the
one lining up the shot!
[KEISHIN]
One more time‐out!
(long whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Whoa whoa whoa...
You gotta calm down, kid.
[SHOYO]
Yes, sir! I'm sorry, I just keep
screwing up over and over.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey, don't even
worry about that!
Thanks to you, I always
get to hit the ball unmarked!
There's nothin' wrong with
lettin' me carry the game
every once in a while,
right buddy?
(ASAHI awkward laugh)
[YU]
Okay, but Asahi's getting
more points than you.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Ah! That's beside the point!
Who asked you?! Ain't that
right, Asahi?
[ASAHI]
Oh, yeah, it doesn't matter...
We're gonna win all of those
points back.
(SHOYO surprised)
[KEI] But if you keep messing
up, you're probably still gonna
get switched out.
(SHOYO nervous)
[RYUNOSUKE] Tsukishima!
(KEI startled)
[DAICHI]
If you're trying to learn
something new,
then you should keep at it...
You might jump all by yourself,
but we're all right
here to back you up.
(RYUNOSUKE grin)
(SHOYO amazed)
[DAICHI]
And besides, Mr. Ace here says
he's gonna win all of
those points back for us.
[ASAHI]
(slapped) Uh. That's
not what I said.
[KOSHI]
Daichi! Don't put too much
pressure on him;
what if he breaks into
a million pieces?
[YU]
That's right! This guy's
fragile, you know!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uhh... can we just get
back to the game? Please.
(long whistle)
[YU]
Asahi!
[ASAHI]
Left!
[TADASHI]
Go!
[CHIKARA]
That was great!
(whistle)
[TAKEDA]
Aw, it's all he can do just to
return the ball!
[TAKEDA] Is there any way we
could make this go smoother?
[KUROO] Go for it!
[YAMAMOTO] Yes sir!
[KEISHIN]
Not even a pro can be
expected to get a play
right the first time.
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice receive!
[SHOYO] Right here! (leap)
[KEISHIN]
But every great accomplishment
begins with baby steps, you
know?
[YAMAMOTO] Hey, I'm open!
Send it this way!
[KEISHIN] You remember
Karasuno's Tiny Giant,
Sure, that's the ace
Hinata wants to be like.
He lived up to the nickname...
Only stood at about
five‐foot‐five or so...
And he kept getting blocked
whenever he first started.
[KEISHIN]
But by the second half
of his second year,
there was nobody who
could compete with him
in midair combat.
[KEISHIN]
He couldn't rise above the high
blockers, so he would aim for
the gap instead.
Sometimes he would intentionally
make the ball ricochet off their
fingertips.
And that's how he developed
his own personal style as a
smaller player.
[KEISHIN]
Well, that's what I understand
from what my grandpa anyway.
Former Coach
Ukai said that?
Yup, the one and only.
And I still remember his advice
like it was yesterday too.
[UKAI]
Man has no wings... so he
finds his own way to fly.
(INUOKA straining)
(shocked)
(whistle)
Aagh! That's an out!
Wow, Shoyo...
That was amazing!
(pant) Once more!
[KUROO]
The small fry... Hinata, was it?
He was pretty good, even if that
last one was out.
[DAICHI]
Oh no, he's nothing compared to
that Inuoka guy, even though he
seemed kinda impressed by us.
[KOSHI]
Uh, you guys are
creeping me out.
[KOSHI]
Next Haikyu!!
"Worthy Adversaries."