[Toru]:
A one‐handed set?!
[Crowd/Team Karasuno]:
(loud cheering)
[Takinoue]:
They got got it!
They tied it back up!
So what is
this called again?
It's a deuce!
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
The first team to score
two points... wins!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Ohhhh‐oh‐OOOOOOH! Sei‐joh!
[Crowd]:
Seijoh!
[Seijoh Cheer Leader]:
Ohhhh‐oh‐OOOOOOH! Sei‐joh!
Seijoh!
[Seijoh Cheer Leader]:
Ohhhh‐oh‐OOOOOOH! Sei‐joh!
Time to get out there
and finish this!
Right!
Kunimi... you ready?
Yep.
Duuude, I am so proud of you
badass first‐years!
Since when does Kunimi know how
to go after a ball like THAT?
[Tobio]:
Don't just let it go!
[Shoyo]:
Kageyama!
Trust me... I'll do the broad
jump as many times as it takes!
Right.
You ready?
Yeah!
Tanaka!
We've got
the flow now!
Serve up a
point, Tanaka!
Yeah you know it, bro!
They're not
in position!
Come on, block that!
Chance ball!
It's a chance ball!
Just one more ball!
[Hajime]:
Good job, Watari!
Number 10
recovers quick!
Nice one‐touch!
[Shoyo]:
Almost there!
I know you're
getting the set.
[Hajime]:
I'm not gonna
leave you unmarked!
He's not jumping as high now!
The timing's off!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Hinata!
See that?!
Hinata just saved
our asses big time!
There we go!
It's time
to rush em!
Right!
We've got 'em
in check now!
We can still come
back... Stay calm!
Sir!
[Daichi]:
Give us another
one, Tanaka!
Hanamaki!
Yup!
[Team Seijoh]
(cheering)
[Shimada]:
The score's
still the same...
If Seijoh doesn't
cause a break...
Karasuno still has the
advantage for right now.
That said...
[Shimada]:
Oikawa's up to serve at the
worst possible moment!
I will not let you have
control of this game.
It's OUR victory. We have
to get to the next round.
[Toru]:
I'll beat him... I swear I will!
I'll humiliate that whole team!
This one play will put Seijoh
back on top! I know it!
[Asahi]:
Nishinoya!
Good eye Nishi!
Well done!
Thanks, man!
[Seijoh Scorekeeper]:
Wow, I can't believe Oikawa
flubbed a serve.
Match point
Karasuno again.
So now their hotshot is
messing up his serves...
Maybe he's starting
to lose it!
Yeah... even
he's not perfect!
The score is even now...
At the end of the day,
a point is a point.
Iwaizumi is so cool!
That makes me
feel inferior...
Oh really? So did you think
you were better than me before?
Depending on the situation,
there can be a huge difference
between a break point
and a side‐out point.
[Irihata]:
But the team places a lot of
value in what Iwaizumi thinks,
so his words and actions
have been holding
the team together
since the start.
Wait a second... Did you say
Aoba‐Johsai's never been
to the Nationals before?
They're such a strong team!
Yeah, but they're lagging behind
in the grand scheme of things.
[Takinoue]:
Both teams are
exhausted physically,
but I bet Seijoh's the
most mentally frazzled!
Stay on top
of 'em, guys!
[Haruka]:
Wow!
They're past 30 points now!
Both sides
have it rough.
Maybe...
[Takinoue]:
But it seems like Karasuno's
barely keeping the ball in play.
Their attacks feel
kind of uninspired.
That said, the
psychological pressure
must be far worse on
Seijoh's side.
Serve up a good one, Oikawa!
Crap, the rotation's
gone full circle!
[Hanamaki]:
Serve's up!
[Shimada]:
I'm sure he's still
kicking himself
for the serve
he flubbed.
Can he handle it?
Oikawa... If you get distracted
worrying about Ushiwaka,
you're gonna get
punched in the face.
If you're blind to the opponent
that's right in front of you...
then that'll be
the last opponent
that you get to
challenge.
I couldn't agree more.
One play takes it!
Yeah!
[Toru]:
Heads up, it's
a chance ball!
[Hanamaki]:
Right here!
Considering how bad he
screwed up the last one,
I think that's the best serve
I've seen all day!
Sorry, guys!
All that matters is
keeping the ball in the air!
Try to stay calm! Don't let a
decoy fool you into jumping!
A quick‐attack? Or maybe
a situation like this
calls for their ace!
Over here!
The other side?!
[Tobio]:
Him again?!
Kunimi!
They may know you're a decoy...
but you still have to go in!
What for?
They could obviously tell
the ball was headed left.
Waste of energy.
You're a good player; why
can't you take this seriously?!
What, I'm not serious unless
I'm running myself ragged?
Chance ball!
[Toru]:
Got it!
He's still got energy?!
[Toru]:
I saw you slacking on
your decoy work, Kunimi.
Sorry, I‐
At least be sneaky
when you cut corners...
or else Mizoguchi
might yell at you again.
HEY! Kunimiiii!
The thing about you, Kunimi,
is that you're efficient,
and you never do any
more work than necessary.
That said... when the rest
of us are too tired to play...
you're going to
make up for it.
A good setter ensures all
of his teammates are working
at full power... no matter
who they are! Right?
13 again?!
A feint!
Crap!
[Spectator 3]:
Seijoh caught up!
And now they've got
match point again!
Yeah... and it's
Oikawa's serve.
We were teammates
for 3 whole years.
But until now...
[Tobio]:
I'd never once seen
Kunimi smile during a game.
Listen, I want to
tell you something.
Who are you?
Now that I've seen
this side of you...
I don't know if I
can compete with you.
[Shoyo]:
Kageyama? Hello?
Kageyama! HEY!
Jeez... You're not about
to freak out on me, are you?
Listen to me! Obviously
a king is gonna be scared
of a GREAT king! It's right
there in the name!
I mean the guy even LOOKS
way smarter than YOU do!
[Daichi]:
Sorry, Kageyama.
But hey... I promise that I'll
get it back to you next time.
[Daichi]:
Then we'll do
what we usually do...
and follow your lead
for the attack.
Kageyama! Quit
doubting yourself!
What did I tell you before?!
Our guys... are all good.
Sure hope His Highness didn't
get spooked by that other king.
He's gonna be alright...
Kageyama's not the same lonely
king‐of‐the‐court he used to be.
[Seijoh Cheer Leader]:
Let's go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
GO!
COME OOOOOON!
We're gonna
get this one!
Yeah!
[Toru]:
Ugh... Great.
This is quite a bother...
[Hajime]:
Serve's up!
[Toru]:
Tobio... You're
evolving so quickly.
And I think that
might be my downfall.
But...
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
Front!
It's back up!
[Takinoue]:
They not gonna make it!
They're out of formation!
[Keishin]:
Just when the pressure of
the game gets you on edge,
a diversion slips
in to trip you up.
They are so focused on ripping
the win from our grasp...
Over here!
Center!
Left side!
Asahi, go!
[Hanamaki]:
Keep it in play!
[Toru]:
Iwa!
It's up‐
[Hajime]:
It's all you,
Kindaichi!
[Yutaro]:
This kid's got me beat in
speed and reflexes... but!
If we're talking about sheer
height... I've got 'em!
[Spectator 1]:
It's up!
Get it!
It's mine!
You know just
what to do!
Yeah!
[Asahi]:
Left!
[Tobio]:
Right now!
Right here!
This timing... at this angle!
It'll be perfect!
Tobio Kageyama...
You ARE evolving quickly...
and it might very well
be my downfall.
But...
...not today.
(final whistle)
[Team Seijoh]:
(cheering)
Let's go...
[Daichi]:
Hinata, Kageyama.
Let's line up.
I'm sorry, Captain...
You didn't mess up.
And there's no need
to be sorry.
Thank you for the game.
Listen up guys...
I want to tell you something.
The next time Karasuno gets a
chance to do a quick attack...
Kageyama's going to opt
for the super version...
I'll bet
you anything.
So tell me, how did you know
they'd go for that
freak quick attack
at the end?
Because Kageyama has
been learning and growing
alongside his
teammates.
[Toru]:
He's learned how
to build up a rapport.
[Toru]:
During that long rally, his
physical and mental exhaustion
maxed out.
At that moment, his back
was against the wall,
and he was faced with an
oh‐so‐vital opportunity.
And for the new and
improved Tobio Kageyama...
...there was only one choice.
Line up!
Thank you
for coming!
Thank you for coming!
Good game, guys!
You did your best, guys!
Let's go.
Really takes
me back.
Always hated it when people
told us how great we did
when we lost.
There was nothin'
I wanted to hear.
But... now that I'm here
on the other side of it...
[Takinoue]:
I gotta be honest...
I dunno what else
to tell 'em
Listen... That
last block was‐
We should head out... The next
team needs the court to warm up.
We'll have to find
somewhere else to cool down.
[Senseki Captain]:
Senseki, fight!
Seijoh will be going
to the quarterfinal...
after they take
a little break.
[Senseki Captain]:
Senseki, fight!
Fight, fight, fight!
[Team Senseki]:
I'm surprised you
didn't tell them
it takes more than
one guy to win. I mean...
that's what you said
a while back, isn't it?
Well, Karasuno isn't a
one‐man show... I was wrong.
'Cause you're
a dumbass.
Oh, come on!
[Toru]:
During that last play
in the 2nd set,
Kageyama guessed that
I'd send it to you...
That proved to me
that he was finally changing
from a dictator
into a real leader.
At the time, I knew it was
a possibility that he'd give
the ball to the shorty,
even if he was still acting
like a dictator,
but it wasn't a sure thing.
I didn't realize the
difference for certain
until later on
in the game.
As soon as he showed me
that he could read my attack,
that gave me the
opportunity to turn around
and read HIS attack, too.
You know what
that means...
Our little Kageyama's finally
learned how to trust people.
And... that... makes
me even more annoyed.
It's time for
the meeting.
Sorry.
[Tobio]:
Oikawa read me like a book.
Don't you apologize!
Shut up!
Stop making it
sound like setting
the ball to ME
was a mistake!
The meeting's about
to start, you two.
You two played an amazing game
today... You know that right?
Yeah... but we lost.
Yes, I know you did...
But still... Would you
call it a waste of time?
Do you think losing
means you're weak?
If you think about it...
losing is a trial by fire.
To see if you can
get back up...
after you've been
knocked to the ground.
But if you guys just stay
lying down forever...
then I'd say...
that makes you weak.
Hey... let's get some food...
Don't worry I'm buyin'.
What? You're treating us?
But sir, we‐
Just do what
I tell ya.
[Keishin]:
Sorry to drop in so late.
Not at all! You used to come
in right at close all the time.
You kids worked really hard
out there today...
And all that strenuous activity
has worn down your muscles.
By now, you're probably
all in pretty bad shape.
[Keishin]:
You build it back up with food.
That's how you gain muscle mass.
This will make you stronger.
Now dig in... You've all
earned a good meal.
Thanks for the food.
Thank you.
Ah... Enjoy!
Thank you for the food.
Go on guys.
[Keishin]:
Eat.
Fill yourselves up...
And enjoy it.
And slowly...
Slowly, but surely...
You will get stronger.
[Takeda]:
I'll pick up
the check, Coach.
[Keishin]:
Hey, don't sweat it,
Specs... Check please!
[Lady Chef]:
Here we are.
I gave you a discount.
[Keishin]:
Thanks... WHOA! Damn,
those boys can put it away!
Next Haikyu!!
"The Third Day."