(sneakers squeaking on court)
(hitting ball)
[SHOYO] (faceplant)
Dammit, stop dragging your feet!
What happened to those
reflexes you had? Get it
together!
[SHOYO]
(grunt) All I'e been
doing is receives...
Kageyama, we're running out
of time! I wanna jump around!
I wanna do some spikes!
[TOBIO]
Well that's too bad!
[RYUNOSUKE]
That's enough!
A word to the wise.
Daichi's a nice guy
most of the time,
but you will NOT like him
when he's mad. Trust me.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Yeah, we know.
If he were to find out
we're practicing early...
I'm so dead. (realize)
Not that I'm afraid
of him or anything!
Of course not; that would be
ridiculously ridiculous!
[SHOYO TOBIO] Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE] Anyway, it's
probably for the best if we keep
this little practice session a
secret between the three of us‐
(startled)
[KOSHI] Aha! Just
as I suspected!
[RYUNOSUKE] Suga!
[KOSHI] Hey.
[RYUNOSUKE] How'd you know?!
[SHOYO, internal] The
third‐year.
[KOSHI] Come on.
Something was obviously up...
I mean, why else would you
offer to take the key to the gym
when you always show up to
practice at the last minute?
[RYUNOSUKE]
(startled) (nervous)
Don't worry, I won't tell;
your secret's safe with me.
[KOSHI]
A clandestine crash course;
that's pretty exciting.
(breath of relief)
[RYUNOSUKE]
(battle roar, into spike)
[RYUNOSUKE] Whoo, I'm on fire!
[KOSHI] (hit effort)
[SHOYO] (bonked)
(annoyed) Hey, you're
not paying attention.
[SHOYO]
Hey, I wanna hit too! Throw
me a bone here, Kageyama!
you're all about
your sets, aren'tcha?
Go ahead, send one
over this way!
[SHOYO] Come on, just one!
For practice! Please?
[KOSHI] I don't think
he wants to.
[TOBIO] No.
[ALL] (stunned)
[SHOYO]
Aw man, don't be like that!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah, dude, send him one!
[SHOYO]
Mmph! Fwup! ...Ah.
I sent that one head‐on...
You received to make
a set and attack...
Don't run your mouth if
you can't follow through.
[TOBIO] I'll be sending all the
sets to Tanaka during the match
on Saturday.
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[TOBIO] Leave all the attacking
to him... You just do your best
to not get in my way.
[SHOYO] (angry)
[SHOYO]
Okay fine, then as soon as I
get good enough at receives.
Will you at least throw
a few sets to me too?
[TOBIO]
I'll set to whoever
I have to to win.
It's just... I highly doubt that
person is going to be you.
[SHOYO] (surprised)
(extended angry breaths)
[RYUNOSUKE] Watch your mouth!
[KOSHI]
How's he ever gonna learn
if you don't set to him?
[TOBIO]
It's almost 7.
We should clean up.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Oh, crap! Hurry up!‐
We can't leave any traces!
[KOSHI] (worried)
We need to find a mop!
[SHOYO] Rrghh...
(courtyard chatter)
[SHOYO] Dammit!
[HIKARA] (snooze)
[RYUNOSUKE] (snoring)
(GIRLS giggling)
[SHOYO]
(startled) (disappointed)
[KOSHI]
Try this... Drop your hips down
a little bit lower
and hit the ball like you're
trying to return it to exactly
where it came from.
[SHOYO]
Okay!
[KOSHI]
Here we go!
[SHOYO]
Ooh, nice one!
[KOSHI]
Hey, Hinata. How about I start
setting
for you tomorrow morning?
Would you like that?
[SHOYO]
(look) (gasp) You
mean it?! Really?!
Well, I am Karasuno High's
official setter, after all...
And you want to
practice spikes, right?
Exactly! Spikes are my
favorite thing to do!
When you hit the ball just
right... It feels so cool!
[KOSHI]
(laugh) I guess you really got
a thing for spikes, don't you?
Yeah... When I was in middle
school, I could barely get
teammates at all,
much less a setter to toss
practice balls with me.
[SHOYO]
I used to get my friend in
basketball club to help me out.
Hup! Ah, oops, sorry, I hit
it the wrong way again!
[SHOYO]
After I dropped out of the club,
I would ask the first‐years, the
setters from the girls' team,
and pretty much anybody
who didn't say no to
practice with me.
I made a lot of
friends along the way...
But none of those people could
ever become my real teammates.
[SHOYO]
That's why... I was so
excited to see who the
setters were here.
You're an idiot.
And now, uh...
You're clumsy.
(piano slam)
...you know the rest.
Well like I said,
I'm a setter too...
I'll toss you a few, okay?
[SHOYO]
(excited) (piano slam) That'd be
nice, but...
if I were to say yes after
telling you all that...
it kinda feels like... I would
be admitting that he beat me.
(awkward sigh) So why do you get
so competitive when it comes to
Kageyama?
[KOSHI]
If you ask me, it's better to
avoid making enemies with guys
like that.
[SHOYO]
That day at the tournament...
Kageyama was so good at
everything he did.
And he was way taller
than me... and stronger.
[SHOYO]
It just really bothered
me to see him standing
in my way like that.
[KOSHI]
Yeah, I think I get it.
[TOBIO] (yawn)
[SHOYO]
That's why I came to Karasuno...
because I want to beat him!
[KOSHI]
Really? If he's the reason you
came here...
Then is he whole the reason
you play volleyball in the
first place?
[TOBIO] hm?
[SHOYO]
Ah! Um, well...
[TOBIO, internal]
Is he practicing during lunch?
[SHOYO]
I just think that if I can get
strong enough to finally win
against Kageyama...
then I will be able to
stand up to all kinds
of tough opponents...
cause I've never seen
anyone play like him.
I don't ever want to lose again!
[KOSHI]
I see. So what you're saying is,
if you had to rank all the
players in your own age group,
you'd give Kageyama the
top spot? That's quite
an endorsement.
[SHOYO]
(startled) (groaning) Well...
[KOSHI, internal]
He doesn't want to admit it.
[KOSHI] He's no longer your
most powerful enemy...
[SHOYO] (listen)
[KOSHI] Now, he's your
most powerful ally.
[SHOYO] (think)
I can do everything
without your help.
[SHOYO] (seething)
[KOSHI] (laugh)
[KOSHI]
Anyway, let's do some receives.
[SHOYO] Sure!
[SHOYO]
Thanks for taking out the trash!
[DAICHI]
1, 2, 3, 4!
[ISASHI CHIKARA KAZUHITO
RYUNOSUKE KOSHI]
5, 6, 7, 8.
[DAICHI]
2, 2, 3, 4.
[ISASHI CHIKARA KAZUHITO
RYUNOSUKE KOSHI]
5, 6, 7, 8.
[DAICHI]
Legs! 1, 2, 3, 4.
[ISASHI CHIKARA KAZUHITO
RYUNOSUKE KOSHI] 5, 6, 7, 8.
[SHOYO] (stretching)
[DAICHI]
2, 2, 3, 4.
[ISASHI CHIKARA KAZUHITO
RYUNOSUKE KOSHI]
5, 6, 7, 8.
[DAICHI] Arms! 1, 2, 3, 4.
[SHOYO] (OM stretch) (huh?)
[TOBIO] Let's go.
[SHOYO]
What?! Sorry, where are we
going now?
Well it's not like we can play
volleyball here, can we? I found
a practice spot.
Ah? Really?! Where is it?!
Wow, great job, Kageyama!
[TOBIO]
Oh my God, you're so annoying!
[SHOYO]
What? What do ya mean?
[KOSHI RYUNOSUKE]
(yawns)
[DAICHI] You two look
sleepier than usual.
[KOSHI RYUNOSUKE] (startled)
[KOSHI]
O‐oh, really? Maybe I've
been studying too hard or
something...
[RYUNOSUKE] I've been
studying hard too!
[KOSHI] It doesn't sound very
convincing when YOU say it!
[RYUNOSUKE] Eat it!
[KEI] Excuse us.
[DAICHI]
Oh.. hey guys. These are the
other new first‐years.
[DAICHI]
Normally we'd wait 'til next
week to start new members,
[DAICHI] but since we have that
match on Saturday,
[KAZUHITO] Wow, they'e huge.
[CHIKARA] (nod)
[DAICHI]
we're making an exception
and bringing them in now.
[KEI TADASHI]
Nice to meet you!
(BOYS running and chanting)
[TOBIO]
Be aware of your feet
AND your hands!
[SHOYO]
(surprised)
Hey, I need
you to focus!
[SHOYO] (annoyed)
I know, I know!
[SHOYO]
We're gonna win this match
and get let into the gym!
Then we'll play for real!
[SHOYO]
Oh... right, I forgot.
If we lose on Saturday, you
don't ever get to be the setter.
[TOBIO]
That's why I need you to focus!
[SHOYO]
Gaah!
I told you, you gotta ease
up a little when we're
practicing outside!
[TOBIO]
If you could receive worth a
damn, I wouldn't have to!
[SHOYO] Pardon me... your
Majesty.
What?
[SHOYO]
(scared) Uh‐oh.
[TOBIO]
Tch.
[SHOYO, internal]
What's with him? He doesn't like
being King of the Court?
I think that's a
pretty cool nickname.
Hey, I wonder if I'll get
a nickname too? Just like
the Tiny Giant!
The Wind of the... Whirlwind!
No wait, that' too much wind.
The Forest... no that's lame...
the Shadowy, um... The North
Eastern... Tornado?
[TOBIO] Hey! Pull your head out!
[SHOYO] (startled)
So anyway, what do you think
the first‐years we're gonna
be up against are like?
They can't be tougher
than the upperclassmen.
It makes no difference to me how
skilled they are... We'll defeat
them no matter what they'e like.
you're right; that's exactly
what I was gonna say!
(taken aback) Tch.
don't you "tch" me!...
One more time!
(smacked, fall over)
[TOBIO]
You've got to learn to stop
receiving with your face!
I can't put my finger on it,
but there's something I don't
like about those rookies.
But you never like anybody when
you first meet them, Tanaka...
It's you... you're
just a paranoid guy.
I don't like
your tone...
They're a bit further along
than I expected they'd be...
you think Saturday's
game will be okay?
[RYUNOSUKE]
(surprised) Are you kiddin'‐
Of course it will! They've got
Yours Truly on their side!
Well, at least
Kageyama's good.
(hurt)
[KOSHI]
You know, I think he's actually
calmed down a bit since middle
school. That's positive.
[RYUNOSUKE]
What?! No way, he's
a snotty little shit!
[KOSHI]
Well, he seemed to have absolute
confidence in himself back
then...
Maybe over confident.
He's a lot less brazen
now, don't you think?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Okay, but he's still
a little shit.
[KOSHI]
Oh, right, my bad... Maybe
you're not the best person
to ask about that.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh... hey...
That's not cool...
[SHOYO]
(slide) (panting)
(catch)
[SHOYO]
Okay... One more try!
[TOBIO] You ready?
[SHOYO]
Yeah!
[TOBIO]
(startled) Behind you!
[SHOYO]
Gotcha! (confused)
[KEI]
Are you guys seriously
practicing out here?
You must be the first‐years
who made all that trouble on
the first day.
[TADASHI]
T‐shirts, out here?
Aren't you cold?
[SHOYO, internal]
Whoa, they'e tall!
[SHOYO]
Give it back! Hey!
[KEI]
Shouldn't you elementary
schoolers be home at this hour?
[SHOYO]
(irritated) Who are you
s'posed to be?! (look)
[TOBIO]
I guess you're the other
new first‐year players.
[KEI] Hm?
[SHOYO] Huh? Quiet!
[TOBIO, internal]
Interesting.
[SHOYO] I'll do
the talking! Hey!
[TOBIO] Question..
How tall are you?
Glad you asked! Tsukki here
happens to be six‐two!
He's almost six foot three!
[SHOYO]
(surprised) Six foot two?!
What's the point of you bragging
about how tall I am, Tadashi?
you're right,
sorry, Tsukki.
You're Kageyama from
Kitagawa First, aren't you?
[TOBIO] Tch.
[KEI] A star player like you at
a school like this...
[TOBIO] So?
[SHOYO] Look, pal!
[KEI TOBIO] Hm?
We're not gonna lose to you,
do you understand me?!
(seething)
[KEI] Isn't that cute?
(SHOYO confused)
[KEI]
I didn't realize that little
skirmish actually meant
something to you...
We couldn't care less about it.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[KEI] we're not concerned with
winning or losing,
but if it's that important
to you two...
Maybe... we'll just
throw the game.
You mean WHAAAAT?!
Fine... I don't care if you
throw it or work yourselves
to death...
cause I'm still going
to win on Saturday.
You mean "we" right?!
(laughter) So confident!
Well that's the
King for you!
[SHOYO] (OM startled)
(OM nervous)
Hey... don't call me that.
[TOBIO] (grunt) Huh?!
[KEI] Ha, I knew it.
Rumor has it you lose your
cool every time someone
brings up your old nickname.
[KEI]
But who wouldn't want to be King
of the Court? I mean it really
suits you, Your Highness!
[TOBIO] (seething)
[SHOYO, internal]
Your funeral, dude.
[TOBIO]
What is your problem?
[KEI] I saw you, you know?
At the finals.
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[SHOYO] Hm?
I still can't believe your
teammates put up with all
those selfish sets you used
to toss up...
I know I wouldn't. Oh!
[KEI] So that's why you're
here! I bet they finally
got sick of you.
[TOBIO] (breath)
[TOBIO]
(angry) (grab)
[KEI] (grabbed)
[SHOYO] (gasp)
[TADASHI]
(gasp) Tsukki!
(quiet anger)
Hmph.
[SHOYO, internal]
What the? I don't really
understand what's going on,
but it's not like him to not
just say anything back to these
jerks!
[SHOYO, internal]
Come on, Kageyama, get the last
word as you walk away like you
always do!
[TOBIO]
We're leaving.
(stunned) What?! Wait!
[KEI] Running off?... Guess the
King's not a threat after all.
[SHOYO] (glare)
[KEI]
I hope His Majesty puts up more
of a fight on Saturday.
[KEI]
(shocked)
Would you just shut up
about the stupid King?!
I'm here too!
[SHOYO]
You have no idea what
I'm capable of!
[KEI] Oh yeah?
[SHOYO] (startled)
What's that look for anyways,
buddy?! Are you trying to
start something with me?!
(sigh) There's no need
to argue, alright?
Let's all just enjoy playing
some volleyball together.
[KEI]
It's just a game, right?
[SHOYO] (gasp)
What's that supposed to mean?!
[KEI]
Exactly what it
sounds like. Bye.
[SHOYO]
Hey, not so fast!
You never told me who you are!
[KEI]
I'm Kei Tsukishima,
Year 1 Class 4.
[TADASHI]
I'm Tadashi Yamaguchi.
[KEI]
As of today, we're officially
your new teammates...
Even if doesn't feel like it...
anyway, I looking forward to His
Majesty's royal sets.
[TADASHI]
See ya!
What is their deal? Those two
are some major league butt wads.
We should show those
pukes who's boss!
[TOBIO]
That goes without saying.
[SHOYO]
(annoyed) Hey, where ya going?
[TOBIO] Huh?
We still got some work
to do, don't we?
(unsure) (determined)
[TADASHI]
Hey Tsukki, wait up!
Is something wrong?
I hate guys like that...
Always trying a little
bit too hard.
[KEI]
They'e both a touch
over‐zealous for my taste.
[TOBIO] Focus! You have
to brace faster than that!
[KOSHI] How late are they
planning to practice?
[SHOYO] I know that!
[RYUNOSUKE] Eh, who even knows
with these two knuckleheads...
All I know is I'm sleepy.
[KOSHI]
(troubled)
Your Majesty.
(angry)
(startled) Ggh!
Quit it, Kageyama! It's
too dark to see out here;
don't hit it so hard!
[TOBIO] (heavy breathing)
[TOBIO]
Sorry.
(scared, into stumble)
[SHOYO, internal] He doesn't
look sorry at all. What's gotten
into him all of a sudden?
[TOBIO] (heavy breathing)
[SHOYO, internal] He's been
extra tense since we ran into
that tall guy.
[SHOYO, internal]
But I can't really spike if he
won't send me anymore sets.
I guess I'l just do my best
at receiving until he decides
to do one.
[SHOYO]
Hey! Try another one of those!
♪♪♪
[TOBIO, internal] (gasp)
That's new. He couldn't handle
a ball at that speed before!
Okay! Now no holding back!
[TOBIO]
(focus) Fine by me!
(hit, stumble) (grunt)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Whoops, overslept!
I'm so late, I'm so late, the
boss is gonna murder me!
[RYUNOSUKE, distant rap]
Kiyoko made me breakfast,
so I couldn't leave the house!
[RYUNOSUKE] (chuckles)
Yeah I wish... hm, huh?
(impact, hop up)
(grunt)
Damn, how long have they been
back and forth like that?
Well, I got here
15 minutes ago, so...
It's been non‐stop?!
(shocked)
[KOSHI] (nod)
[RYUNOSUKE] Wow.
(hit, stumble)
[TOBIO, internal]
He makes up for his bad
technique
with raw athleticism, but...
[TOBIO]
Everybody has their limit!
[SHOYO] (small exert)
[TOBIO] Let's take a
break for‐ Uh?
[SHOYO] Not yet!
[SHOYO]
No! It hasn't hit the floor!
[TOBIO] Okay, Fine!
[SHOYO] (look)
[RYUNOSUKE]
That's brutal! Can he hit that?
[TOBIO, internal]
Damn, force of habit.
[KOSHI]
Hinata's had amazing athletic
ability since middle school.
[SHOYO] (run)
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?
[KOSHI]
But... besides all of that...
He's got this... insane
thirst for victory that
keeps him going.
[TOBIO, internal]
His weapon isn't physical
prowess and it's definitely not
size... It's something else...
[TOBIO, internal]
It's that every time the going
gets tough...
He has just enough left in him
to take it one step further!
[SHOYO]
(grunt) (exert)
[KOSHI] (gasp)
[RYUNOSUKE] He did it!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice one, Little man!
[TOBIO, flashback]
I'll set to whoever
I have to to win...
It's just... I highly doubt that
person is going to be you.
[SHOYO]
I don't ever want to lose again!
But it's... not over yet.
Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Here we go!
There it is! He
finally set him one!
[SHOYO] (grunt) (panting)
[RYUNOSUKE] Too bad.
There's no way he's got enough
strength left to spike it down.
(happy)
(spike)
I gotta hand it to him,
the kid can jump.
Can't believe he
managed to hit that.
[SHOYO] (happy)
[RYUNOSUKE] Check out the
stupid look on his face.
So I guess getting a set
must be really important
to the guy, huh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?
I made a lot of friends
along the way...
But none of those people could
ever become my real teammates.
[SHOYO] (coughing) (pant)
[KOSHI] I suppose getting tosses
from the setter was just
something we taken for granted.
[TOBIO] Hey.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOBIO]
Tomorrow... we'll win.
(determined)
He's no longer your most
powerful enemy...
[SHOYO, internal]
Now he's my most powerful ally.
(awkward) Hmph.
(annoyed) Yeah? Tell me
something I DON'T know!
(sudden nausea)
[SHOYO] (puke)
[RYUNOSUKE] Ugh, that's sick!
(freaking out)
[KOSHI] Tanaka, get some
water! Oh god... and a bucket!
A‐and some towels...
(heavy running)
[TOBIO]
(shocked)
[SHOYO]
(battle cry)
[TOBIO] (angry)
Quit running, you little moron!
[TOBIO SHOYO]
(panting)
Why are you dorks wasting
precious energy right before
a game?
You should take
a breather, idiots.
[SHOYO]
Man... we tied... (panting)
[TOBIO, panting]
I can'... let you.. beat me...
[SHOYO] Back atcha...
[SHOYO]
(heavy breathing)
[SHOYO, internal]
This guy really gets
on my nerves...
(pant)
[SHOYO, internal]
He's gonna start sending
the ball my way now...
Sets from a real setter!
[SHOYO]
You ready to win this or what?
(surprised)
[TOBIO]
We need to go and get set up.
Yeah.
[KEI]
Morning, my liege!
(surprised)
(pissed)
[SHOYO, internal]
This time...
I'll break through
any wall they put up!
[TADASHI]
Kageyama's such a whimp.
He didn't even stand up for
himself.
[KEI] Shut it, Tadashi.
[TADASHI] Sorry.
[KEI]
It's time to see what the King's
made of. And the shorty too.
[SHOYO]
Grr! Next Haikyu!
"The View from the Summit!"