(whistle blows)
That's rough!
Yeah, that makes the
4th service ace in a row.
He's obviously got
quite a lot of power...
but that control
is simply unreal.
Okay... but if we can
deal with that serve...
It's true that his
serve is nasty...
[Koshi]:
but the worst thing is,
we don't know anything about him
as a setter.
One more, like that!
(whistle blows)
[Crowd]:
Ooooooolé!
[Omisaki #2]:
Sorry!
[Yutaro]:
Chance ball!
I got this one!
Okay!
Yeah, the thing
about setters...
[Keishin]:
They're a lot like
conductors for an orchestra.
You can have the same song
and the same musicians...
but changing the conductor gives
you a whole different sound.
Aoba‐Johsai... Their teamwork
seems to be really polished.
See that number 4
on the left side?
That is Hajime Iwaizumi.
[Tobio]:
I heard he's played with Oikawa
since elementary school.
They have almost a
psychic connection.
I don't think the
vibe's different
because the junior setter they
used during the practice game
a while back was no good
or anything like that...
I mean,
he's at Seijoh.
True.
But... this Oikawa
character here...
[Keishin]:
He seems to know his team so
well that he's able to conduct
them all at 100% of their
potential. Impressive.
[Shoyo]:
The Great King
is awesome!
I wanna play him!
Me too!
I hope he aims one of
those serves at me!
[Yu]:
Oh, man...
[Shoyo]:
You're cool
too, Noya!
Someone's excited.
Hey Hinata! Look over
there! The Paparazzi!
[Shoyo]:
A TV camera! Sweet,
we're gonna be famous!
[Committee Member]:
Hey, you two!
Middle sc‐
Sorry, elementary schoolers...
Please, keep it down, alright?
Sure...
Sorry, mister...
(final whistle)
Wow, it's quiet
for once.
Because everyone's
exhausted.
We played two games...
But we won both in
straight sets though,
so it could be
a lot worse.
[Keishin]:
If we win tomorrow, we'll be
up to two full games a day,
PLUS the opponents
will be tougher.
We'll have to work hard
to keep the energy up.
Right.
Okay, meeting time,
everybody.
(yawning)
You kids have
got to see this!
Get your butts in here,
the volleyball club
is on television!
What?! TV?!
[Shoyo/Yu/Ryunosuke]:
Show us!
[Koshi]:
Please?
Duuude!
We're on TV!
Awesome!
You do know that's
just the local news...
Quiet!
It's still
cool, alright?!
[Female Anchor]:
Champion ace Wakatoshi Ushijima
from Shiratorizawa Academy
in Block I set his team off
to a great start today...
These reigning champs kept the
momentum going from last year
by scoring 25 to 10
against the opposing team
from Ougi South High School
during the first set,
and a devastating 25 to 6
in the second set.
Did she say "25 to 6"?
[Female Anchor]:
They won by a landslide,
never once losing the lead.
With that kind of skill, it's
easy to see why Shiratorizawa's
worthy of the Inter‐High title.
That said... Block A seems
to be the group to watch.
That's the gym
we played at today!
[Female Anchor]:
And the PLAYER
to watch is Toru Oikawa,
the team captain
from Aoba‐Johsai High.
(growling)
Not only is he talented,
but his striking good looks
and personality make him popular
with female fans as well.
The next opponent,
of Aoba‐Johsai
made a strong
impression today...
[Female Anchor]:
beating Date Tech
in straight sets
despite every little
indication that Date
would go on to the Best 8.
Karasuno High.
Yeah!
[Ryunosuke]:
What?! It's THAT douche?!
[Female Anchor]:
We asked the captain for his
thoughts about facing Karasuno
in round three tomorrow.
Karasuno's a decent team...
I hope they do their best...
so that we can annihilate them.
[Female Anchor]:
I'm sure everyone watching
hopes the best team wins!
Coming up next, it's time
for the local weather.
Let's go to Komata over
at the Sendai Station.
Ah! They showed your game
for a second or two
at the start
of the broadcast!
You all looked
very impressive to me!
Listen, sir...
We get what you're trying
to do, alright...?
Um... sorry!
[Daichi]:
We should probably
get going guys.
Let's go.
I messed everything up!
I‐I‐It's just a
meeting! Come on!
[Keishin]:
Alright, today's game
with Date Tech...
it's sorta like...
your first sip of beer!
The first sip of a
beer tastes the best...
It's great! There's
nothing like it!
Um hey Coach...
could you put that into
terms minors can understand?
Ah...
Well... by using the Date Tech
game to debut that freak quick
we've been workin' on,
we were able to take the enemy
by surprise, you know?
[Keishin]:
But we've played
against Seijoh before,
so they already know most of
what's in our bag of tricks.
That said...
you need to remember that you
guys still have a great deal
of offensive power.
[Keishin]:
The first step is surviving
that serve Oikawa does...
We can't let it control
the flow of the game.
Because if that happens, we're
toast. So try to be careful.
[Keishin]:
As you know, our current
formation is based on all of you
except the setter
going after the serves.
But this time, I want
our two middle blockers
to focus entirely
on attacks
and not participate
in serve‐receives.
You got that, boys?
Yeah...
I guess...
Hey, it's called division of
labor. Cheer up little Ginger.
Oh, also...
Seijoh made you think... "Whoa..
They're tough. We're screwed."
That sound about right?
Huh?
[Keishin]:
But think.
What if we had been watching
ourselves in that game?
If we were able to see it from
the spectators' perspective?
[Keishin]:
We'd be sayin' "Check out
that block, it's terrifying!
No way are we gonna win!"
We'd be losing it!
But we took those guys on...
and won. And we can do it again.
YEAH!
Alright! Let's run
through the formation
while we've still
got some time!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes, sir!
[Mori]:
Hey Coach.
Oh, Mori!
Here you go.
It's today's game.
[Keishin]:
Ah, thank you!
Next time we go
drinking... it's on me.
Aw yeah, that's what I'm talkin'
about! I'm holdin' you to it!
Oh, is that
the Aoba‐Johsai game?
Yeah... Sure is.
It'll be a big help, but I don't
expect us to magically overcome
Oikawa's serves just
by watching it today.
But then again, though...
it's better than nothing, right?
Wow, Coach, next time
your drinks are all on me!
Sweet talker! See you
tomorrow. Don't be late!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes, sir!
[Toru]:
Listen carefully. The Inter‐High
tournaments are coming up.
My special protégé, I'm wanna
crush you fair and square
at an official game where
we both play the setter.
Is it just me...
or is Kageyama more tense
than he usually is?
Here he goes.
Stop frowning,
Kageyama!
If you don't, you're gonna
get wrinkles and you'll end up
looking like a
gross old grandpa!
Huh?!
Tomorrow...
That guy's going down.
Can we...
really stop Oikawa?
Not only that,
but we're gonna be on TV
so you need to practice
smiling for the camera too!
Oh give me a
frickin' break!
If we're gonna win this... We're
gonna have to stay focused!
Sweet!
[Yutaro]:
Goodnight, captain!
[Toru]:
Uh‐huh! See ya.
(humming)
Huh?
Hey... Tomorrow's a big day;
so don't stay up too late.
Oh really, now...
What are you, my mother?
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I take it back!
I'll be there, bright‐eyed
and bushy‐tailed, I promise!
Don't you worry!
[Yutaro]:
I don't have time
for this, Loserkawa.
I have to lock up the club room,
so move your ass, Lazykawa!
[Toru]:
I don't like
these names...
[Yutaro[:
Shittykawa then!
[Toru]:
Now you're just
being vulgar!
Wait a sec...
Could this kid be...?
[Crowd]:
You try to get all in our space,
we'll slam that ball
back in your face!
[Cheer Leader]:
Let's go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
[Crowd]:
Go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
[Cheer Leader]:
Go go, Sei‐Sei‐Sei‐S‐SeiJOH!
[Crowd]:
May the best
team win today.
We plan to.
Karasuno cleared the
first day... Not bad!
I had to take another
day off for this.
Guess I can forget
vacation for a while.
Got that right.
You know, Date Tech had
a supportive crowd...
but this...
[Oikawa Fangirls]:
Ready, go!
Go Oikawa!
You're amazing!
This is
something else.
I'm not losing
to these assholes!
YEAAAAAAH!
Coach. Looks like we've
got the opening serve.
Alright.
Okay! Now!
Good luck, Oikawa!
We love you
Karasuno High...
[Daichi]:
Fight!
Now let's do
some serves!
They're sure
Oh! Hey, uh, that
apprentice of yours,
how are his serves
coming along?
Well, I wouldn't
say "apprentice."
The jump float serve...
do you think you could
teach me how to do it?
That was only
a week ago.
[Shoyo]:
Come on!
He might just
pull off a fluke...
but he's got a long way to go
before he can really do it.
Excellent work, Makki!
You are sharp as ever.
Hey, I'm sorry, Kindaichi...
That was a bit high
for my taste.
Um... okay...
Right!
Our little Iwa seems
kind of tense today!
Hey, you shouldn't
worry yourself too much
about looking good...
After all, the girls are too
busy watching me to notice you.
I really gotta
hand it to him;
Oikawa pays pretty close
attention to his teammates.
I can't make an informed
assessment of their technique...
but I can tell that
Seijoh's got strong chemistry.
They're so in sync.
Really?
Hey, let's line up guys!
For the first time, I'm playing
against him in an official game.
Thank you for the game!
Alright, the game's about to
start! Time for round three!
Who's gonna make
the Best 8?
It's an
interesting matchup.
Yeah, but Aoba‐Johsai's
got this one in the bag.
[Toru]:
Oh, Tobio?
I came here looking forward
to defeating a setter
who's worthy
of facing me.
So at least...
try to keep up.
Let me tell you somethi‐
We're not gonna lose!
Hinata, you idiot! Can't you
be quiet for five minutes?!
We'll beat you.
Just like last time!
Let's go, S‐S‐S‐S‐SeiJOH,
[Crowd]:
Go, go, S‐S‐S‐S‐SeiJOH,
[Cheer Leader]:
You can do it, S‐S‐S‐S‐SeiJOH,
[Takeda]:
Remember, guys! You've
beaten Aoba‐Johsai before.
They may not have been
at their best last time,
but I still think the fact that
we've overpowered them once
already is good enough
reason to be confident.
Not to be cocky!
But confident.
[Team Karasuno]:
Sir!
[Daichi]:
Karasunooo, fight!
[Team Karasuno]:
Fiiight!
Well then, let's do
this thing, shall we?
Just like we
did yesterday.
Don't let me down,
fellas... alrighty?
That was... intense.
[Takinoue]:
Aoba‐Johsai's mood
just did a 180.
He says that
before every game.
Coming from him, that kind of
thing can sound like a joke,
but to his teammates, it's as
serious as a heart attack.
They know that he's saying
exactly what he means,
and they respect
him for it.
[Irihata]:
That's why they put all
their trust in him in return.
Here we go!
Yeah!
[Daichi]:
Let's see it, Tsukki!
Kunimi!
Right!
Good one!
Look, two of them are
getting ready to jump!
Interesting...
I'm open!
[Tobio]:
It's been a while since
I saw him set a ball up
from this close.
(crowd cheering)
[Takinoue]:
A setter dump,
right off the bat?!
Work it Owikawa, Work it
Owikawa! Get thaaat Point!
Really?!
A setter dump...?
That's when the setter
makes an attack, right?
I'll give you a little hint;
I'm about to do that again...
Pay attention this time and
maybe you'll be able to stop me.
Hey... is he really serious
about doing another setter dump?
People never do those
moves twice in a row.
Making you think that
is exactly how they trick
you into screwing up.
Aah, so THAT'S it!
You're really smart, Tanaka!
Alright
cut it out,
there's no sense in
psychoanalyzing it...
That's just like
trying to predict
what somebody's next
move is going to be
in a game of
rock‐paper‐scissors.
[Daichi]:
Don't think
too hard.
[Shoyo/Ryunosuke]:
Okay!
[Hajime]:
Matsukawa's serve!
Stay focused!
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice one, Cap!
B!
Bring it this way!
Hey, it's Number 10!
He's gonna do it!
[Brown‐haired Guy]:
It's that quick attack!
Crap... this
one's head‐on!
Hey! Check out
the Seijoh setter!
[Takinoue]:
It's gonna be another dump...
but way more obvious, this time!
Nice try!
He just changed from
a spike... to a set!
Hey... that
was too low.
Oh yeah?
My bad...
But well,
y'know, Iwa...
you do always seem to
hit them either way.
Did you
see that?!
They're so good,
it kinda pisses me off!
Oh, Oikawaaaa!
He's so incredible!
They're a lot tougher
than I thought...
What the hell are
they feeding these kids?
Well... it may be true...
that we won a practice
game against Aoba‐Johsai...
[Takeda]:
...but like you said,
now that they've got
their official conductor...
the tune is
different.
Crap.
[Daichi]:
Relax, you two.
Listen, we already knew
Oikawa was good, remember?
Our setter and our attacks
are impressive too...
We can win this.
Right!
[Hajime]:
Give us another one, Matsukawa!
[Daichi]:
Nishinoya!
Gotcha!
Okay! Bring it to me!
[Hajime]:
Number 5!
Ooh! They
faked him out!
A pipe?!
(crowd cheering)
[Brown‐haired Guy]:
He did a setter dump too!
That guy must
really hate losing.
That was pretty amazing!
Oikawa.
That's our
next play too...
So I suggest that
you pay attention.
That so?
You little prick...
[Toru]:
Tobio's Kageyama's
an insufferable brat.
[Hajime]:
Look who's talking; you were the
first one to do a setter dump‐
[Toru]:
Luckily I have
you guys! Group hug!
[Hajime]:
Yeah, you're way more
annoying than he is.
Next Haikyu!!
"Toru Oikawa is No Genius."