[IRIHATA] Hey...
Welcome back, Oikawa.
[TOBIO] (uncertainty)
[IRIHATA]
How's that leg doing?
Never been better! Glad I can
come back to practice now...
It was just a tiny sprain.
Listen, son... Don't
ever do that again!
They brought Kageyama
like we asked them to,
so we can't just show up
without our official setter...
That would make
us look bad.
I'm sorry.
[GIRL A]
Careful, Oikawa!
Please don't hurt yourself!
(GIRLS squealing)
Hey, it might be because he's
got all the ladies' attention...
but I already hate this guy.
Yeah that's Seijoh's
team captain.
[RYUNOSUKE SHOYO]
(surprised)
Oikawa. A super
offensive setter.
[TOBIO] Top of his class
in attacking and team play.
[TORU] Sorry I had to leave you
guys hanging while my leg was
[SHOYO, internal]
(surprised) If HE thinks this
guy is good, then... Hmm...
Yeah... and he's got
a bad attitude too.
What? Is it worse
than yours?!
[TOBIO]
Even worse than Four‐Eyes.
[SHOYO] That IS bad!
(KEI glaring)
Since you know him, I guess
he must've also gone to
Kitagawa First, huh?
Yeah. He was my
upperclassman.
[SHOYO, internal]
If he's above the
King, then he's...
...the Great King?!
Hey there! Long time
no see, Kageyama!
How long has it been since I saw
you? You've really grown!
[TORU]
How's it feel to be the King?
He's good... I learned
everything I know
about serving and
blocking from him.
(SHOYO gasps)
[TOBIO] Do not
underestimate him.
[SHOYO, internal]
He must've invented
that killer serve.
Still... for now we should
stay focused on the game...
We are gonna take
that last set!
Y‐yeah!
[TOBIO]
Tanaka, stop with the faces!
Now get over there and warm up!
And be extra thorough so
you don't get yourself
injured again!
Alright.
(GIRLS squealing)
[RYUNOSUKE] I'm
gonna kill this guy!
(TOBIO frown)
[GIRL A] Come on, when are
they gonna let Oikawa play?
[GIRL B]
No he can't go in yet.
[GIRL B] If he doesn't
warm up first,
[DAICHI] Stay focused!
[GIRL B] he might hurt
his beautiful body.
[GIRL A]
Oh nooo, that would be awful!
[GIRL B] I know, right?
(RYUNOSUKE growling)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Comin' atcha!
[DAICHI, internal]
One more point.
[KOSHI, internal]
That's all we need.
[SHOYO, internal]
We might just win
against a top 4 team!
[YUTARO]
Don't start getting cocky yet!
[MATSUKAWA] Yes!
(whistle)
[HAJIME]
Nice, Kindaichi!
[DAICHI]
It's alright. Shake it off!
(thinking)
[TORU]
Uh‐oh. Looks like
we're in trouble.
You warmed up?
I'm ready anytime.
(whistle)
(GIRLS squealing)
[TORU] Just leave
everything to me, okay?
[AKIRA]
Right.
[SHOYO, internal]
Ahhh... It's the Great King!
[DAICHI] Cut that out!
[RYUNOSUKE] Bleeehhhh!
(annoyed)
Wait, are they swapping
our setter out?
He's not the setter.
He was filling in.
[HAJIME]
You're up, Oikawa!
It doesn't matter how
powerful their attacks are.
If they never make a solid
connection with the ball...
then what's the point?
Hm?
What?
[KEI] Huh?
[KOSHI, internal]
He's targeting Tsukishima!
(STUDENTS dodging)
(whistle)
(KOSHI TAKEDA startled)
[TADASHI] Tsukki!
(CROWD cheering)
[SHOYO] (panic)
[DAICHI] (annoyed)
[TORU]
I just started watching,
but looks like I was right.
[TORU] Number 6... and Number 5.
[KEI] (surprised)
[SHOYO] Uwah!
You two must be first‐years;
your receives are terrible.
[KEI] (annoyed)
[SHOYO] (stunned)
[KOSHI, internal]
His momentum's even better
than Kageyama's.
And he's got the control to land
the ball anywhere he chooses.
This guy's really good.
[KOSHI, internal]
So that's Seijoh's captain.
Now... one more time.
(KEI grunting)
(whistle)
Poor Tsukki!
(AOBA JOHSAI cheering)
[KEI] Damn.
[DAICHI]
Don't worry about it, guys!
[SHOYO, internal]
Tsukishima's a jerk and he gets
on my nerves... but for some
reason... grrr.....
[TORU]
Ah, just one more point to tie.
[SHOYO]
Hey, Great King!
Why don't you aim for
me?! I can take it!
Just aim the ball right at my
head! Unless you're too scared!
[TORU] Great King?
Stop it, you're acting
like a toddler!
(angry) Excuse
me?! Hmph.
[SHOYO, internal]
This freakin' guy always
knows what to say
to make me mad... but still...!
[RYUNOSUKE] Listen up! The cool
thing about volleyball is...
[SHOYO] The cool thing about
volleyball is...
...everybody you see on this
side of the net is your ally,
okay Tsukishima?!
[KEI] (pissed)
[RYUNOSUKE] Wise words from a
wise guy!
[DAICHI]
Okay... Let's fall back as a
group... Tsukishima, you stay
close to the sideline.
[KEI] Right.
[DAICHI] Now... Let's go!
Oooh... The Captain is the
strongest receiver,
and now he's expanding
his defense zone.
[GUY A]
One more!
[TORU]
Still... It takes more than one
player
to defend the whole court!
Argh!
Tsukkiiiii!
How can he pinpoint
someone who's so far away?!
But he's emphasizing
control, so the momentum
should be slower!
It's up!
You're awesome, Tsukki!
Oh, you got it! Niiiiice!
I guess I made it
too easy... Oh well.
[TORU]
You guys just gave us
a little gift though.
Agh Dammit!
Oh my... Look at that
delicious chance ball...
Don't mind if we
do, thank you!
[YAHABA] I got it!
[KOSHI, internal] Uh‐oh,
this rotation doesn't give us
enough blocking height...
[YAHABA] Kindaichi!
[YUTARO, internal] Alright, I
shook off all the blockers‐
(surprised)
[YUTARO]
Where'd the shorty come from?!
[TOBIO] There it goes! Get it!
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice one‐touch, pal!
[DAICHI] Chance ball!
Just wait, carrot‐top, next time
I'm gonna smack you down!
[TOBIO, internal]
If you miss Hinata by even the
smallest instant, he'll be
impossible to catch.
The only thing that can
keep up with him...
[TOBIO]
...is the ball!
(TORU stunned)
(long whistle)
(STUDENTS surprised,
taken aback)
What was that?
That guy moved across the
court in a split second.
The ball flew straight into
his hand like a magnet.
(amazed)
Aww yeah!
[DAICHI] Line up!
(TAKEDA floored)
[KOSHI] (notice) Is there
something wrong?
[PLAYERS] We did it!
[TAKEDA]
Incredible...
[KOSHI]
Oh yeah, that's right!
I guess this is the first time
you've seen
Hinata and Kageyama's special
attack in action...
It's pretty cool, huh?
In fact, it's so cool it kinda
freaks me out! Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE TOBIO DAICHI]
We're ready!
[SHOYO] Uh, ready!
(TAKEDA startled)
[KOSHI] You're supposed to
give them some feedback.
[TAKEDA]
Oh, sorry, I didn't know.
Lemme see... Well,
like I said...
I don't know that much about
volleyball... but still!
[TAKEDA]
I can tell something really
great is starting to take shape.
[RYUNOSUKE DAICHI]
Huh?
[TAKEDA]
We've just had some really
gifted first‐years join the
team...
and things didn't run so
smoothly at first... but now...
I think I understand why!
Even if everyone doesn't
always agree...
[TAKEDA]
Whenever people are brought
together.. it creates a chemical
reaction.
[TAKEDA]
Somewhere in the world,
there's a fateful encounter
happening at this very moment.
[TAKEDA]
It could be happening somewhere
far away in a completely
different country...
...or on the other
side of the globe.
Or maybe... it's on a
small Eastern island...
in a tiny Northern town...
in an ordinary high school...
in a regular volleyball club.
[TAKEDA]
I believe that encounter was
made at Karasuno.
I don't have any proof yet...
But I can't ignore what I
believe!
And before too long...
this team is going
become even stronger.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Uh...
I'm sorry!
That was too weird,
wasn't it?! I'll stop!
No no no, that was
great, Takeda! Thanks!
[ALL]
Thank you!
[TAKEDA]
Uh... sure.
[TOBIO]
Kindaichi.
[YUTARO]
(serious) We cannot deal with
Kageyama anymore, Coach!
I know he's got amazing
attack power and everything...
but he's obviously been
holding the whole team back!
(sigh)
[YUTARO]
Seriously...
we're better off without him.
Hey uh...
Don't even apologize to me!
(speechless)
And I'm not going
to either!
Okay.
To me, you're always gonna
be that self‐centered,
pain‐in‐the‐ass
King of the Court,
the number‐one person on Earth
I want to defeat one day!
Fine.
So don't ruin that!
There's no need for the two of
us to make up...
I mean we were never
friends to start with!
Fine.
But next time we
meet... I WILL win!
[TOBIO] Yeah well... (surprised)
[SHOYO SHOYO] Weehoo! Time to go
wash up, oh yeah!
You can call me Shoyo, Future
Ace of Karasunooo‐ (startled)
[SHOYO, internal]
(gasp) Whoa, it's about to go
down! Are they gonna fight?
I should probably stay away
from something like that...
[TOBIO]
Kindaichi.
The next time you and I meet...
We're gonna beat you again.
(surprised)
[AKIRA]
Hm? Hey, what was
that all about?
He just... used
the word "we".
[AKIRA] Huh?
[SHOYO] Are you crying?
[TOBIO] Of course not, you
little freak! Just go wash
up already!
[YUTARO] Until now, it was
[SHOYO] Aw, you don't have to
hide your feelings, Kageyama.
[YUTARO] like he was
on a team by himself.
[TOBIO]
Agh... you IDIOTTTT!
[YUTARO] Have...
have I already lost?
[SHOYO] Ow ow ow!
Ow! What was that for?!
[EVERYONE]
Thank you for playing with us!
[DAICHI]
Takeda's right, but...
...if we ever want to play and
win a real game against Seijoh
with Oikawa in the
setter position.
We're still missing
a vital ingredient.
[TORU]
Wow.. Very well said captain.
(surprised)
That's surprisingly astute.
(smirk)
[SHOYO]
Look out it's the
Great King again!
[RYUNOSUKE] What's your damage?
[SHOYO] Gotta problem?
[RYUNOSUKE] Wanna
knuckle sandwich?!
[SHOYO] Yeah, let's rumble!
Ah, come now, no need
to get yourselves up.
But hey, short stuff.
That one‐touch and broad
jump were great... You
should be proud.
Huh? Oh...
Next time, we should try doing
things full‐out from the start.
(surprised)
[TORU]
You haven't seen our real setup.
But don't worry... we'll
be working on perfecting
our serves 'til then.
[SHOYO, internal]
That's true, it'll be
different.
Next time we'll be dealing with
his serves the whole game.
[TORU]
That combination attack
is pretty effective,
but you're going to run out of
steam at some point.
You need to improve
your receives.
[TORU]
After all, I'm not the only
person who does power serves.
[TORU]
The Inter‐High tournaments are
coming up, and I want you to
make the cut.
[TORU]
Listen carefully...
...my special protege... I want
to crush you fair and square...
at an official game,
where we both play the setter!
[KEI] (startled)
[SHOYO] Yeah well... We can
train to receive, fancy‐pants!
[KEI]
Hey, let me go!
Just so you know,
receives aren't
something you can
master overnight.
[TORU]
I'm sure your Captain
can attest to that.
If we happen to meet again at
the tournament... I look forward
to seeing all your improvement.
Look.. Do not let
him get to you...
Antagonizing people is just
one of those things he likes
to do, so...
(DAICHI chuckling)
(TOBIO confused)
He's right... We don't have a
whole lot of time until then...
but.. luckily we have
someone coming back soon.
[RYUNOSUKE] (shock) (grin)
[SHOYO] Hm? Who's coming back?
[DAICHI]
Karasuno's... guardian.
[SHOYO, internal]
Karasuno's... guardian?
[HAJIME]
Kageyama's getting
really good, huh?
Yeah. He's a prodigy who's
finally found an outlet for
his very specific set of
abilities...
The average player's
no match for him now.
Wait, are you saying you're
not a match for him either?
Not for his sets...
When it comes to that,
no one in the prefecture
can out do Kageyama.
I'm every bit as good as him
at spikes, blocks and serves
though... Ow, what the‐?!
You know damn well your
sets are as good as his too!
That is why you're
our setter!
Sorry... but it's
the truth, okay?
Which is why we're going
to sabotage their receiving...
Because no matter how perfectly
they can catch a serve,
it's all for naught if
it doesn't make it back
to the setter.
If we get matched with
Karasuno in a real game...
... we'll have to ruin
all of their receives
so Kageyama never gets
to make one of those
flawless sets!
They can't just rely on
just one person to win!
Ah, I'm already looking
forward to cheering them
up after they lose!
(annoyed)
What? Didn't you
say you hated him
for being a genius?
Not as much as I hate
pretty‐boys like you
who get all the girls!
[TORU]
Ow! Prejudice like that isn't
very becoming on you, my friend!
Ow! OWW! Stop it!
[HANAMAKI]
(sigh) Hey, cut that out or the
Coach's gonna us one of his
lectures again!
[DAICHI]
Good job, guys!
Now let's do a little light
cleaning and call it a day!
[ALL] Yes sir!
[SHOYO] (snoring)
[TOBIO]
Watch it!
Thanks a bunch for setting
everything up, Takeda.
Don't mention it; you guys
did a great job! I still
can't believe we won
against a prestigious team like
Aoba Johsai!
[KOSHI] Come on, let's
mop up and go home.
[DAICHI] Yeah, but the
fight is just beginning.
[ALL] Right!
[TAKEDA]
Huh?
I mean... thanks to that
combo technique of ours...
we can put up a
pretty good offense.
[DAICHI] But if Hinata gets
caught by blockers and
[CHIKARA] Uh‐it's okay
if you're too tired to mop!
[DAICHI] our receivers aren't up
to par like today,
[CHIKARA] You can go home!
[DAICHI] we won't have
a strong enough defense.
[TADASHI] Aw, look, Tsukki!
[KEI] Tragic.
And besides... we uh don't
really have a coach... So uh...
when it comes to that kind
of advice... you're not all
that much help.
You have a point.
Oh! That came out wrong!
I promise I wasn't saying
you're not doing a good job!
[TAKEDA] (laugh)
I didn't take it that way...
Leave the coach problem to me.
I have someone in mind.
Huh? Do you really?
Who is it?
[TAKEDA]
Well, it's someone I've tried
and failed to win over several
times now...
...but I'm sure I'll
think of something.
Do you mind locking up when
you guys are done today?
Yeah, sure.
Whoa, I think Take's
starting to take charge.
Mm‐hm...
Hm? It's broken...
Hey, can I throw away this mop?
Someone might get a splinter.
[KOSHI]
Huh? (surprised) No,
it's fine! Just leave it!
I'm sure that it can
be fixed somehow.
Huh?
[CHIKARA]
Good night!
[KAZUHITO HISASHI]
Night!
[KEISHIN]
Meat buns?
Sorry boys, the soccer geeks
just bought up all I had...
I know life is so unfair.
I'm hungry!
Yeah, where's
your manager?!
I AM the manager!
Now get your butts home
and eat some real food!
Build up a little muscle!
[ALL]
(startled)(dejected)
[KEISHIN]
Here.
(catch)
(smacked)
(chomp)
[SHOYO]
Wow!
[ALL]
Thanks!
Now go eat your dinners.
[SHOYO RYUNOSUKE]
Woohoo!
(phone ringing)
Ugh...
[KEISHIN]
Sakanoshita.
(exhale) Not givin' up, eh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
That was nuts.
I can't believe how good
that guy's serves were...
It's a good thing he didn't
show up until the final set.
Makes sense that he came from
Kageyama's middle school.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? Hang on.
[RYUNOSUKE] Why'd you pick our
school anyway, Kageyama?
[TOBIO] (eating)
[SHOYO] Hm?
Shiratorizawa's got the best
team in the whole prefecture;
why didn't you just go there?
[SHOYO]
Shira‐Huh?
How have you never heard of
Shiratorizawa?
Those guys have got
unbelievable skills;
they rank in the top 8 in
the whole country every year!
Whoaa!
Oh yeah, I didn't make
it in there.
No way!
Well I didn't get a
recommendation from them,
so I had to take the entrance
exam and ended up failing it...
Their test is some
pure nonsense.
Passing their exam
is extremely hard...
I'd say almost impossible.
[KEI]
Aww... or maybe the King doesn't
have a head for academics.
[TADASHI] (snicker) Goodnight!
[TOBIO] Tch!
Why DID you pick Karasuno?
Let me guess, you want
to be like the Tiny Giant
too don't'cha!
No, I picked this school because
I heard that Coach Ukai might
come out of retirement.
[SHOYO]
Ukai?
He's the best coach
we've ever had!
He made a name for Karasuno by
getting us to Spring Nationals!
[SHOYO]
Really?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah dude,
some people even call him
the "Crazy Crow Coach"...
you know, since our school
name kinda means "crow".
Yeah, the second‐ and third‐
years got a little bit of
instruction from him last
year...
but it was pretty
basic and Spartan.
(thrilled)
[KOSHI]
Why are you jealous of that?
At one point they were
planning on formally
reinstating him, but...
He collapsed?!
Sorry, but the school's
not planning on
bringing him back anytime soon.
I don't care... No matter
what school I go to...
I'm still going up against
high school students...
And I'm still gonna win.
Look at this guy acting all
cool, not foolin' anyone, buddy.
[SHOYO] Pffff!
(extended flailing)
[TOBIO] Don't be stupid!
I'm not trying to act cool at
all! We did beat one of the top
4 schools today, didn't we?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
That's true... Two to one
against Aoba Johsai High..
And thanks to my boy Hinata
here... I got to score one
unmarked!
Sure thing my man!
[RYUNOSUKE]
So, you've made your debut now.
How did it feel?
(thinking)
On the other hand, you were
losin' your shit for the
whole first set, remember?
Yeah, and you lost just as many
points as you scored, so don't
go getting too cocky okay.
[KOSHI]
Come on why do you guys
have to bait him like that?!
[DAICHI] He's got
a point though.
[KOSHI] Huh?
Our team's still lacking.
And in a lot of ways...
We might've won,
but only just barely.
Okay, I'll practice
myself crazy!
Whoa, whoa! Self‐improvement
IS really important.
[DAICHI]
But... The main issue here is
that Karasuno still needs a few
more players.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOBIO] Yeah, I would agree.
We need a natural libero...
And also...
it would be really handy
to have an ace spiker who can
handle a triple block too.
Hey! I can be the ace spiker!
You can't! You're supposed
to be the decoy, remember?!
(deflated)
But you said our guardian
would come back soon, right?
[DAICHI] Yeah.
[KOSHI] Karasuno may not be the
strongest team, but we're not
the weakest either.
[KOSHI]
Look, we used to have really
skilled players..
but we failed to make sure they
trained their replacements.
[DAICHI RYUNOSUKE]
(troubled)
Well now we've
got players again...
plus we've recruited
a few first‐year guys.
[KOSHI]
We just need to coordinate
all our strengths.
Summer Inter‐High tourney.
[DAICHI]
The nationals aren't some
unreachable goal...
If we work hard and play our
cards right, I'm positive we
can get there!
Right, the Summer Inter‐High
tourney, I know about that! Uh?
So... the libero you said
should be coming back soon,
where has he been all this time?
Uhh... Yeah.. he's been serving
a week of suspension,
plus he got banned from all
club activities for a month.
[TOBIO] Hm?
[SHOYO] Huh? So is he some
kind of troublemaker?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Dude, no... He just gets carried
away sometimes. He's a stand‐up
guy though. Trust me on that.
[TOBIO, internal] If Tanaka
thinks he gets carried away,
that's saying something.
[RYUNOSUKE] And check this out.
[RYUNOSUKE] He's known as
the resident genius of the
volleyball club.
[SHOYO TOBIO] (surprised)
But I guess now that we have
smart‐ass Kageyama on the team,
he won't get to keep that
nickname anymore, will he?
[TOBIO] (annoyed)
[SHOYO] (chuckle)
Do us a favor once he's back...
Call him your "upperclassman".
He gets a stupid kick out
of it like Tanaka does.
(surprised) Hey,
it's not stupid!
[SHOYO] (smile)
[SHOYO, internal] I can't wait
to see what our team's guardian
is like.
[RYUNOSUKE] Get a move on!
[SHOYO] Ah! Alright I'm coming!
(internal) I'm gonna hit it!
(grunt)
Agh! Gwah!
Can't you stay out of
my way for five minutes?!
I could've had that
if not for you!
[SHOYO]
Yeah well I got it!
[TOBIO]
You didn't get anything!
It's out of bounds!
[SHOYO]
Whatever.
[TOBIO]
Jeez.
(internal) This time for sure!
Huh?
(surprised)
(gasp)
(internal) He redirected
its momentum and rotation,
sending it straight to the
setter position.
A perfect receive.
[SHOYO]
(shock) Are you
shorter than me?!
[SHOYO]
Who the heck is that?! He just
swooped in out of nowhere!
[TOBIO]
That receive was so
smooth and flawless!
[SHOYO]
I think I'm gonna cry!
[DAICHI]
Well, I guess I should
introduce you guys.
[DAICHI]
Next Haikyu!!
"The One They Call The Ace."