[Shoyo]:
The final set.
Listen to me...
Please keep winning!
If we screw up now...
...we're done.
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive!
Number ten!
[Hajime]:
I'm sure they've already
changed the signal
for the crazy quick attack.
Well, it's a simple signal...
So they can switch it out
pretty easily y'know.
But still... there must be
SOME sorta clue.
I guess if we see
him tracking the ball...
then it's a normal one.
But if he just dives right in...
then it's the quick.
True, we need to watch
Number 10 specifically.
[Yutaro]:
Good plan.
Number Ten is‐
At the end of the day he's
still just a decoy though...
Don't forget that...
alright guys?
[Yutaro]:
Right!
[Team Seijoh]:
Yeah!
[Yutaro]:
Not this time!
We keep messing
things up!
Still rallying.
On average, they've got us beat
at defense and blocking.
[Daichi]:
A feint!
Argh... too close!
[Takinoue]:
Our libero does have some
outstanding skill though.
[Yu]:
Asahi!
[Spectator 1]:
The setter received it!
[Spectator 2]:
Now he can't make the set!
[Spectator 1]:
Their attack's gonna flop.
[Spectator 2]:
Watch 'em go left!
It's all yours!
Mine!
[Keishin]:
Looks like my hunch
was right after all.
I suspected Aoba‐Johsai's
libero started out as a setter.
[Takeda]:
Why do you say that?
[Keishin]:
Well, think about it.
If a libero crosses the
attack line to do an overhand
set and somebody spikes it,
then that's an illegal move.
So this guy jumped just behind
the attack line to redirect
the ball in midair...
Which makes it a valid spike.
He's got expertise
in both positions.
Aoba‐Johsai really knows
what they're doing!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
Agh! Heads up!
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive, Cap'n!
Asahi!
[Daichi]:
It's coming back!
Gotcha!
[Hajime]:
Take that!
[Tobio]:
That was so close to the edge.
Awesome...
You boys are doing
great work out there...
Let's keep it up now!
[Team Karasuno]:
Sir!
[Keishin]:
They're starting to catch on
to our center attacks,
so I want you to make sure
you're using the full width
of the court
every chance you get!
Right!
[Koshi]:
How can their offense be
so perfectly airtight?!
They turn every scenario
into an advantage,
as if it was
planned that way!
Let's do it guys!
Sir!
Putting in Sugawara for a
little bit really helped us
get back on our game.
It helped us lose a lot
of unnecessary tension.
[Keishin]:
I think all of our guys
are playing at their
full potential, now.
But them...
They've been in the zone for a
long time. This won't be easy.
Yeah, Tsukishima!
Get dirty and bite 'em in the
ass when they're not looking!
Um whoa.
I'm sure even with
everyone playing at 100%...
Seijoh is still the more
capable team... But...
Having your strength
drop to 70%...
and then quickly powering up
above a hundred and twenty...
[Takeda]:
That's what this
game's all about, right?
[Takeda]:
Besides, Karasuno has
exactly what we need
to give us that turbo boost...
We have our greatest decoy!
[Shoyo]:
This is so much fun!
And our opponent is so strong!
I want to play...
Now, now, now!
[Koshi]:
Hinata?
Yeah?
You do remember what
Coach Ukai told us, right?
To use the full width
of the court... I know.
Yes... And we have an attack
that's perfect for that.
[Koshi]:
But we've barely
used it in this game.
Yeah!
[Toru]:
I don't like this.
The rest of the team is
keeping it together, but...
I can't help it;
whenever that little guy
walks onto
the court...
It makes me nervous.
He's been sitting in the warm‐up
zone for a long time,
letting all his frustration
build up inside.
[Koshi]:
Wow, Karasuno's really pulled
it together in the final set...
but Seijoh always seems
to be one step ahead of us.
[Koshi]:
Those two... If there's any
chance of us catching up,
it's gonna depend on them.
Come on you guys, we need you
to get us that extra step ahead!
[Hanamaki]:
Left side!
[Hajime]:
Nice receive!
[Ryunosuke]:
Smooth moves, Kageyama!
[Daichi]:
Chance ball!
[Shoyo]:
Remember to use the
full width of the court!
The little punk's
actually going to do it!
[Toru]:
A wide broad‐jump!
Nice kill, Hinata!
Dammit.
[Toru]:
The duo's back together.
I can't let those two
stay on the court!
Nice, Makki!
Yeah!
I wish the rotation
would move faster!
I need the shorty to move to
the back as soon as possible!
[Hanamaki]:
Got it!
Wow, the ball never hits
the floor... How cool.
Got it...!
Again?!
Use the whole court!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
That little guy's awesome.
[Shimada]:
It's volleyball...
And this game's all
about nonstop jumping...
It's like you're
fighting against gravity.
[Shimada]:
Jump to decoy.
Jump to block.
Jump to spike.
[Daichi]:
Hey, nice cover!
[Shimada]:
The longer the rally goes...
Go to the back! One more time!
[Shimada]:
the more frantic and uneasy
Left side!
the players become.
Let's stop the
next one!
When you get tired,
it makes you slack off.
I remember in one match,
I even wished someone else
would spike for me.
Oh yeah, there was this one
rally that went on forever
and I was totally
worn out.
[Takinoue]:
It got to the point
I didn't even care where
the ball went anymore.
I just wanted it to fall.
Bring it to ME!
[Shoyo]:
If I slow down for even a
second, I'll never catch up!
And with my height, if I
let up on my jumping power,
that big tall wall's gonna
shut me right out!
That's why I have
to keep running!
And keep jumping!
I want to stay in the court!
You won't hit
unmarked... No way!
[Tobio]:
Now! Take advantage of the
entire width of the court!
And then...
Break through the center!
Yeah!
Now that's a pipe!
That was a great kill!
Hinataaaaaaa!
Damn!
Sorry... I let
'em trick me.
[Tobio]:
I knew the timing was perfect
to pull off a pipe...
And yet... I almost handed
it to Hinata just now!
He nearly took the
toss away from me!
He IS the greatest decoy.
[Spectator 1]:
Karasuno caught up.
[Spectator 2]:
They're tied.
I'll get
the towels.
Thank you.
Thanks.
The rallies are longer than
they were in the first two sets.
I'm sure it's tough.
Still...
...seems nice.
What's the plan?
That broad jump's no joke.
It's a simple move.
Just shut him down.
[Daichi]:
Yeah, nice kill!
[Ryunosuke]:
Boom!
Hinata's about to be
in the back row.
Hey! You're doing
okay, right?!
Uh... Yeah,
I'm good!
Score as much as you can
before you move back.
You got it!
[Matsukawa]:
Nice receive!
[Toru]:
Kindaichi!
[Asahi]:
Number 12!
[Daichi]:
Nice job, Nishinoya!
Now!
Whoa! Another
broad‐jump?
Is he...?
[Takinoue]:
He's unmarked! Th‐they're
not blocking anymore!
There ya go!
Hit it unmarked!
Bring it.
Nice try.
[Hajime]:
Nice, Watari!
[Daichi]:
They planned that!
[Asahi]:
That was quick! They just
switched up their game
in no time at all!
A setter dump, really?!
[Keishin]:
They confused us
for a second...
just so they could
sneak that in!
Let's nip that
broad‐jump in the bud.
Yeah but how do
we do that, Coach?
Well, the shorty's broad‐jump
may be insanely fast...
But I suspect he has a tendency
to get caught up
in the momentum...
which limits the accuracy
of its placement, right?
Instead of blocking,
I say we counter their
broad‐jump using digs.
Right!
Good point, but if we
can't make the block work,
then it's only gonna get
in the way of our receive.
No matter how difficult
it gets out there,
don't ever stop thinking or get
out of tune with your teammates!
[Toru]:
Nice receive!
[Keishin]:
Shouldn't his broad‐jump be
enough to throw them off?
Just when we REALLY can't afford
for them to hit their groove...
[Keishin]:
HE'S up to serve again.
Just one point.
Yep!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
[Seijoh Fan]:
Inside the net!
That boy is lucky!
There was no stoppin' that!
Just keep goin'!
[Daichi]:
Damn, another
2‐point buffer.
Stay calm...
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
Cover!
Okay, right here!
[Daichi]:
Kageyama!
Last hit, Asahi!
That was close!
I can tell they're
really nervous!
Whoa... I bet that's
really stressful!
One way to gain the flow is to
control a long rally like this,
and this one's
high‐stakes.. Let's watch.
[Daichi]:
Cover it!
You won't get this point and you
will not control the flow!
[Shimada]:
It's still in play!
[Takinoue]:
Yeah, But who's gettin'
the last hit?!
Center!
Hinata! It's all you!
Hinataaaaaaaa!
Block him!
Yeah!
Uh‐oh...
Now Karasuno's already used up
both of their time‐outs.
What choice
did they have?
[Shimada]:
If they hadn't called a time‐out
to physically cut off the flow,
Seijoh would've
run away with it!
[Keishin]:
There must be something we can
do to change the momentum here.
We don't need anything fancy,
I just want one good play.
Something that'll clear the air
and get us on the right track!
Whew, Seijoh touched the net!
That was a lucky break.
Yeah...
[Toru]:
Perfect.
The shorty's in
the back row now.
If we screw up..
They'll be over 20 points!
And if they take the momentum,
we'll never catch up!
Please make
Seijoh screw up!
Hey, man...
y'seein' this?
What the‐?!
[Shimada]:
Tadashi is their
pinch server?!
Has Keishin completely lost his
mind?! That's never gonna work!
The best that kid can
manage is a fluke!
Well, maybe a fluke
is what he's hoping for.
Huh?
[Takinoue]:
You never know,
something as simple as that
might be all you need
to shift the momentum.
That's their guy?
You guys think he's actually a
good server? Or did they just
throw him in the game
to shake things up a little?
Either way, it's
not gonna fly.
I hope you do good... But not
as good as I can do!
He can't even stand
being out for a second.
[Keishin]:
Tadashi! Turn the
tide for us!
O‐Okay!
[Tadashi]:
This is it.
Beyond this line
is a different world!
Wow, it's even a
different temperature!
Hey, this is your time
to shine, Tadashi!
Yeah!
Just do your
best, Tadashi!
Yeah, good luck.
Uh, don't worry, just relax
and take it easy out there!
[Daichi]:
You should take
your own advice, Asahi.
Jeez, being thrown in now
would make anybody panic!
His first high school game AND
his first serve, all at once?!
Is Coach some sorta sick‐o?!
Man, this is stressing ME out!
But I can't let
Tadashi see that...
At least he won't hit me
in the head like Hinata.
This seems kinda risky... I mean
things are already so tense...
I bet he's feeling
bad being put in
before the
upperclassmen.
Yeah, you're right.
[Koshi]:
Hey, Tadashi!
You're great! Good luck! Woo!
Oh, boy... This
isn't lookin' good.
I don't blame him.
[Shimada]:
In a team‐oriented game
like volleyball,
serving is the only time
you're ever truly alone.
All eyes are on you.
The pressure's unbelievable.
[Tadashi]:
I'm scared, but...
[Shimada]:
No matter who you are...
the moment you step
into that serve position,
you become the
star of the game!
[Tadashi]:
This is your chance to
prove yourself, Tadashi!
A jump float?!
Come on...!
[Crowd]:
Go, go Seijoh! Go, go Seijoh!
Geeeet thaaaaat POINT!
Well then...
that's that.
I‐I'm sorry.
Hey It's alright.
Yeah.. don't
sweat it, bro.
You're good.
I'm sorry.
Nah.
There is no need
to apologize.
Let it go...
Move on.
[Daichi]:
Tadashi!
S‐Sorry, Daichi!
Next time...
You'll get it.
Next time...?
Right!
[Irihata]:
Karasuno's mood just shifted.
That's Daichi for ya...
Always knows just what to say.
Wow... For some reason I don't
feel stressed out at all now.
Yeah, me neither.
Weird... They brought that
guy in and then kicked him
right back out as soon
as he messed up.
I kinda feel
sorry for him.
That's the point of using
a pinch server like that.
That point was huge because
it wasn't just the flow
but the whole team's pride
was riding on it.
And Tadashi
couldn't cut it.
One point!
[Shimada]:
But this was a chance for him
to develop a frustration
with his own
powerlessness.
And that's enough to
make anyone stronger.
[Ryunosuke]:
Boom!
Get some!
The buzz cut guy's
pretty fired up now.
Oh yeah, I was
noticing that myself.
That's my point. The smallest
thing can turn the game around.
[Daichi]:
The prize for winning this
game is the chance to play...
...again!
Yeah! Let's keep
it goin', you guys!
It's like we're
chasing after Seijoh,
but they're just barely
out of reach.
[Shimada]:
Unless we can use the break to
score, we're dead men walking.
[Keishin]:
Their accuracy's dropping
with their energy.
[Toru]:
Kunimi!
That's advanced.
This is
dragging out...
That was out...
[Ryunosuke]:
My bad!
[Crowd]:
Seijoh! Seijoh!
Geeeeet thaaaat POINT!
Woo!
Come on...
Get that break!
[Tobio]:
Leave it!
[Daichi]:
Good eye!
Good, good!
Give us another one!
Back‐to‐back!
I cannot let it
hit the floor!
Did he seriously
use his foot?!
There we go!
Ow... Ooh.
Nice one, Red!
Wow! Ha‐HA!
[Shoyo]:
You're up, Kageyama!
One more...
Here you go!
Whoa, Daichi!
I'm not losing
this game!
I'm not losin'
[Daichi]:
I'm not losing.
But...
Gotcha!
[Daichi]:
I'm sure they
feel the same way.
I cannot believe this...
[Takinoue]:
They got match point!
[Crowd]:
One more point! One more point!
[Yu]:
Hey! Don't
wimp out now!
Let's give it
all we got!
Yeah!
Whoo! Now that's
a kill, Asahi!
One more!
[Daichi]:
Let 'er rip, Tanaka!
[Tobio]:
One point!
[Asahi]:
Give it to 'em!
If I flub this serve,
it's game over...
And if they receive and make a
strong attack, we're done for!
They're gonna quick attack!
Don't let it fall!
[Ryunosuke]:
At least...
...touch it!
Oh, crap!
[Takinoue]:
It's going over! They're
gonna go for a direct!
[Toru]:
A one‐handed set?!
[Crowd/Team Karasuno]:
(loud cheering)
[Yu]:
Wow, you two really are
going the extra mile!
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
Thanks!
[Shoyo]:
24‐24. That's deuce.
[Tobio]:
First team to score
two points wins.
[Daichi]:
And that's gonna
be us, right?
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
[Shoyo]:
Next Haikyu!!
"Lonely King No More".