[Daichi]:
Chance ball!
Aw, yeah!
That's it, buddy!
Nice job!
Alright,
nice kill!
[Ryunosuke]:
You're up, Tsukki! Go for it!
You know, if they keep
this back‐and‐forth momentum
going like it is for
a little while longer,
then I'm thinking Karasuno'll
probably take the first set.
But for them to
get a solid lead...
There you go!
Oh man, nice one‐touch!
Counter! Now!
[Yu]:
Chance ball!
C quick? Not today!
Whoa... That's two blockers on
Hinata's and Kageyama's attack.
Guess this is a first
for us, isn't it?
I can't say I like it.
No way... It's come down to set
point for us against Date Tech?
Hey! Not too bad!
Karasuno is totally
crushing it!
[Shoyo]:
Give it here!
Yeah!
Whoa! Karasuno
just won the set.
So Karasuno's a real threat once
they get in the groove...
You don't think they'll be able
to snap up the second set, too,
do you?
Hmm... I can't say for certain,
but I know we won't see the same
[Mizoguchi]:
Look alive, Kunimi! We don't
developments that
we saw in set one.
[Irihata]:
Date Tech, specifically that
massive number 7 fellow,
Man, that was close...
is still reeling
from the shock
of Karasuno's
special quick attack.
That really tall
number 7 guy...
and their number 6 down
there at the end...
both of them were able
to actually get a hand
on the combo attack.
Yeah, they're
pretty tough, huh?
The best thing we have
going for us right now
is our dynamic duo
and that move of theirs.
We can't have it put in a box
like when we played Nekoma.
For the second set,
we're gonna begin the rotation
two places ahead.
In set one...
[Keishin]:
Hinata was matched up with
No‐Brows Number 7,
so I think it's better
to avoid that this time.
That's why we'll start
two positions up.
[Takeda]:
That makes sense.
That way, Number 7 won't
be able to mark Hinata
as closely as he
did the first time.
Smart thinking, Coach!
Obviously, he's not going
to be completely unmarked...
All this will do keep the two
of them separated... Besides...
If Hinata's LESS
marked during this game,
then it stands to reason
that the rest of you are gonna
be covered even more.
[Asahi]:
We can't always
just lean on Hinata.
Keeping him in constant play,
keeps US open...
As ace... I promise
I'll do what it takes.
That sounded
so badass!
He's growing up
before our eyes.
Thanks, DAD...
Me too!
Well...
I uh... I can't really do back
attacks like you can, Asahi,
so... I'll make as many points
as I can from the front!
[Hinata]:
And I'll be the greatest
decoy you've ever seen!
Good. Thank you...
You can definitely
count on me!
Sure!
Go, go, Date Tech,
Date Tech, here we go!
It's time to start set two.
I'm sorry about that,
Tsukishima...
With the new matchups,
you'll be opposite
their number 7 a whole lot.
It's alright...
I mean, c'mon let's be
honest about this...
Nobody's expecting me to
score the game‐winning point
on that guy, you know?
It's Hinata's job to deal out
the real damage...
[Kei]:
Think about it.
From my position, all I'm
supposed to be responsible for
is holding down the fort
the best I can...
It's no different than
any other game, really.
And face it, putting
all that aside...
it's pretty clear that
their blockers have already
locked onto YOU, anyway.
[Daichi]:
Alright, let's go!
[Moniwa]:
Nice receive!
Looks like Karasuno
switched up the rotation...
And I think
I know why.
It's to try and keep Aone
away from their Number 10.
Listen, no matter
what the matchup is...
we need to focus on
shutting that spiker down.
Listen Aone, I know we have
a tendency to be snotty
when we're out of uniform...
but while we're on the court,
we should be
good underclassmen.
[Daichi]:
Kageyama!
Hinata had him on the hook,
but then he went left.
[Daichi]:
Yeah, Tanaka!
Nice one!
I'm open!
Watch number 3!
That only happened because Date
Tech was specifically focusing
on the guy with the man‐bun.
He won't be able to do that with
the receives all over the place.
Leave that to short stuff.
Nice, Aone!
Yeah!.. Let's do
that again next time!
Great job, Daichi!
[Team Date Tech]:
(cheering)
[Spiky‐haired Guy]:
Karasuno Number 10's
in the front row now.
Okay, bring it on!
[Ryonosuke]:
There it goes!
Cover it, Kageyama!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it here!
I don't believe it,
he's even faster
when he's right in front
of you. He's a monster!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
[Mizoguchi]:
After they changed
the rotation...
it kind of seemed like
it brought in new life
into that special technique
of theirs somehow, didn't it?
Whatever effect it had
will wear off as time goes by...
If Date wins this set..
and manages to keep the same
momentum into a third set...
[Irihata]:
Karasuno loses the advantage...
It's all gonna depend on how
well they can hold their own
against Date Tech's number 7
without their number 10
on the front row.
Whether or not they can
beat the iron wall,
comes down to how much they rely
on that little decoy of theirs.
[Daichi]:
All yours, Hinata!
Everyone's talking about that
number 10's quick attack!
Which guy?
He's in the
back row right now.
[Moniwa]:
Great work, guys!
Tsukishima. I've been thinking
about what you were saying
before the game started...
about how it's your job
to hold down the fort
while Hinata's
in the front row...
Pulling that off against
a team as tough as this...
that's really
impressive.
The way things are,
those two aren't just
important to our offense...
they're fundamental players.
But we have to
survive the moments
when we can't use their
attack... That's crucial.
[Asahi]:
It's like when you receive,
to set up a spike,
even if you can't
make the hit yourself.
Right now...
whether or not we hold down the
fort... that decides our fate.
Cover me, would ya?
[Tobio]:
Got it!
When the going gets tough,
the ace gets the set.
Open!
Asahi!
[Moniwa]:
Watch the left!
[Asahi]:
All the walls in the world...
...won't stop me!
AAAAAAAAH!
I can see why they're
so famous for blocking.
[Spectator 3]:
Number 10 is just
the middle blocker,
Try again, Asahi!
but he seems
like the ace.
Don't let it
get to you!
[Irihata]:
Number 7's block is the driving
force behind the iron wall.
They need him in the front row
quick or they're in trouble.
[Moniwa]:
Let's keep it up!
[Team Date Tech]:
Yeah!
[Irihata]:
How much more can you take...
ace of Karasuno?
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive, boss!
[Tobio]:
Open!
[Moniwa]:
Number Three!
You won't break me again!
[Moniwa]:
One touch!
Counter!
Hey... don't be getting cocky!
[Takeda]:
We've got our own wall!
Those guys just shut down
a quick attack!
That was a great block!
[Black‐haired Guy]:
So it looks like
Number 3 and Number 11
are the tallest guys
on Karasuno's team.
Yeah! That's
a block point!
Sweet!
And now, if Date Tech
gets the next point...
[Takinoue]:
Number 7 moves
back to the rear!
[Moniwa]:
Shake it off!
You ready?
Okay!
Now let's widen the gap!
[Ryunosuke]:
Booyah!
Uh‐oh, Karasuno number
10's in the front now!
Let's go!
Just six
more points...
Wreck 'em as much as you
can while you're up front,
little man!
[Yu]:
Number 12!
[Ryunosuke]:
Kageyama! Cover it!
Here!
Bring it to me!
He's really
something, huh?
He just goes running straight
in for a quick attack
where you'd normally
use the left side guy.
Bam!
YEAH! That'll cut
you down to size!
[Sasaya]:
Nice, Kamacchi!
[Takeda]:
Agh! We can't get
a solid lead!
Just be patient...
We'll get there.
Nice one, Asahi!
That's a chance ball!
Give it here!
Dammit‐!
Awesome kill!
Keep going!
Just one more point
to match point!
You're so
close, guys!
Nice receive!
Perfect... That giant Date Tech
blocker's in the back, now...
and Shorty's still
positioned in the front...
Now they can
widen the lead!
Kamasaki...
You hiding behind Aone
to let him get all the glory
or do you want him
to carry you?
Huh?!
Screw you, dude!... Takes more
than him to make the iron wall!
Got that?!
Yeah!
Try again.
Yeah.
[Takeda]:
Number 7's coming back
to the front row.
[Keishin]:
We're good.
We've still got
our freak quick‐attack.
But...
[Daichi]:
Nishinoya!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it on!
Waterfall ball...
Close one.
Yeah, but it's
still match point!
Go for the point!
Alright!
Hey, Don't you sweat it, Aone,
we're just getting started...
You can stop
the next one!
It's match point
for Karasuno now.
[Spectator 2]:
Their number 10's
on the back row now.
[Keishin]:
This is gonna be their strongest
turn for blocking us.
[Ryunosuke]:
Serve's up!
[Moniwa]:
Good call!
It's fine...
I'm sorry, you guys,
You are such a
clumsy little moron!
It happens to everybody; all you
can do is regret it for a second
You're not helpin'!
and then let it go!
Sir!
[Spiky‐haired Guy]:
If Date Tech gets two more
points, it'll be deuce.
And with this rotation,
that could very easily happen.
Yeah, well, Karasuno better hope
that doesn't happen right now,
what with Number 10
being out and everything.
Shake it off!
You're good!
Man, their number
7's intimidating.
Yeah...
I could've sworn he had
that one... But hey...
[Shoyo]:
he's gonna have
a real hard time
Alright, here goes!
with Asahi in the
front row, right?
Asahi!
Asahi...
Our ace is
out there... It's okay!
[Tobio]:
Right here!
[Daichi]:
Watch for that quick!
This is a good
arrangement,
but Date's watching
extra close now.
Asahi, here!
Cover!
Got it!
I'm no ace if I can't make
the last ball count!
We shut this guy down once;
so if we can't do it again,
then we have no right to say
we're the Iron Wall!
[Sakunami]:
Nice block, Moniwa!
Crap! The back's
wide open!
[Spectator 3]:
He got it!
Hey, cover!
Every ball is an opportunity!
Left side! One more!
Asahi!
[Takinoue]:
That's a little
close to the net?!
[Shimada]:
A joust!
[Takinoue]:
Let's see who's
got the strength!
I can't make it...
(crowd roaring cheers)
[Spectator 3]:
His foot?!
No way...
Did he just...?!
One more time!
Yeah, nice follow‐through!
[Asahi]:
Get back... get back, NOW!
Get a running start and
jump as high as you can!
Keep doing it as many times
as you have to,
just make
this count!
Stay focused and don't stop
moving!
If you stop wanting it
for even a second,
the ball's gonna
hit the floor!
[Yu]:
Kageyama, cover!
On it!
[Koshi]:
One more time!
Until I can score!
Asahi's favorite toss is
slightly in front of the net.
A medium‐high set.
Uh‐oh...
Why would
he do that?!
It's fine.
This is the best chance
we have... Trust me.
Yeah, do it, Asahi!
Clear that wall!
Do it!
Gooooo!
GOOOO!
(final whistle)
YEAAAAAAAAH!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Oh, yeah!
Got 'em!
I knew you guys could win!
Let's line up, guys.
[Date Tech/Karasuno]:
Thank you for the game!
(applause)
[Yu]:
You did it, Asahi!
That was nuts!
First Date's block
was like BAM!
And then, they
were all wuwuwuwu!
If it was me,
I'd go FWOOSH!
Use your
words, Hinata.
If I'm this team's ace...
[Asahi]:
you guys are
the heroes.
Heroes!
Oh yeah, I like
the sound of that!
Look, despite that insane
quick attack of theirs,
you did really good out there
today, Aone... They just‐
Nationals!
He is right, Moniwa!
We are just gonna have
to get our revenge
in the spring
preliminaries!
[Futakuchi]:
Prelims are in September, so
let's head home, make a plan,
and get ready to crush Karasuno
if we get matched with them
at Nationals‐
But the third‐years will
be long gone by then.
Oh I get it,
so you don't think we're worth
waiting around for, huh?!
Huh?! What are
you talking about?!
We've discussed
this before, you two!
Third‐years are done
after Inter‐High!
Yeah, but...
[Moniwa]:
You guys will
be fine.
[Moniwa]:
Our school's known for being
a serious contender...
but that excludes
us third‐years.
Let's face it, we're
the chaff of the team.
It's only thanks to you guys
that we've been able to keep up
our reputation as
the Iron Wall.
When Nationals come next year...
you have to stay!
Start preparing for it right
now with a brand new team...
and if you can't win
this year, win next year!
Whether it's Seijoh or Karasuno
or Shiratorizawa...
take down everyone in your path
and make it to Nationals!
But...
Understand?!
Sir...
Hey, you need to
speak up, Futakuchi!
Sir!
[Yui]:
Great work out
there, you three!
Congratulations!
Oh, hey there...
I didn't know you ladies came
out to support us, thanks.
You honestly had no
idea they were here?
There's our girl!
Glad you got
your revenge.
Right! And we'll
win again!
[Takeda]:
Um, hey Coach?
Hm?
That last set...
What exactly did you mean
when you said that
it was our best one?
Well when the
receives are crazy
and you can't do the kind
of attack you want to do...
the last ball
ends up left...
It'll always go to the position
where the ace is waiting.
[Keishin]:
In a critical moment like that,
I wanted Asahi to see
how it feels to rip a
point out of that Iron Wall
Thank you for coming!
with his own
two hands.
[Takeda]:
Oh, I see.
I'm sure it boosts his
confidence for the next play.
Well, I heard something about
Asahi getting his man‐bun
in a bunch after Date Tech
handed his ass to him.
But I think this
helped him get over it.
He really held his own
against that Iron Wall,
with or without
a decoy.
[Keishin]:
Besides... for a spiker, there's
a certain amount of pride
to be taken in having
the ball sent to him.
It's proof of how much
your setter trusts you
when all the chips
are down.
In his case, he's got TWO
setters who believe in him...
so how could he
NOT be confident?
I've never seen a block as
intimidating as Date Tech's.
Me neither...
So have you figured out how
the two Karasuno first‐years
have been able to differentiate
between their normal
and their
super‐quick attacks?
[Shimada]:
I couldn't make out
any signals during the rally...
[Takinoue]:
Yeah.
That's good... They couldn't
read our signals!
Uh‐huh... I guess we
should keep 'em then.
Couple of lunkheads like you
managed to put it all together;
I must say,
I'm impressed.
For your information,
it wasn't us!
Of course not... So
who did it for you then?
[Shoyo]:
Sugawara.
Congratulations, Captain.
You got your revenge.
Yeah.
Even so...
I would have preferred to
beat them with MY sets though.
Ah! I‐I'm sorry! Uh...
Let's just keep that between us.
I'm glad
to hear it.
I'm glad you're still keeping
yourself involved with the game.
That's good.
Let's be ready to
win again tomorrow.
Yeah!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Seijoh! Goooo, Seijoh, go!
Aoba‐Johsai won.
That's not good.
The King...
[Toru]:
and his little,
dark horse.
Once we chew you up and spit
you out, we can go on home.
We'll be at nationals.
[Ryunosuke]:
He thinks he's all that
just 'cause he has fangirls.
[Yu]:
Yeah, we've
still got Kiyoko‐
[Kiyoko]:
Hey Oikawa!
[Ryunosuke/Yu]:
What?! How could you?!
[Kiyoko]:
Kidding.
[Ryunosuke]:
Kiyoko...
[Yu]:
Don't scare us like that!
[Kiyoko]:
Next Haikyu!! "The Conductor."