(final whistle)
[Asahi]:
It's been three months
since they defeated us.
The wall just fades away,
and then the view of the other
side is totally clear!
In the past,
I'd been able to see the view
he was talking about...
[Asahi]:
but when faced
with that iron wall,
I couldn't picture
anything beyond it.
I still wonder... what
it must look like over there.
Rollinggggg...
Thundeeeeeeer!
[Yu]:
Again!
Alright, listen here!
You guys have nothing
to be afraid of at all!
Focus on what's in front of you!
I promise I'll
always have your back.
Whoa... HE'S AMAZING!
[Captains]:
Line up!
Thank you for the game!
[Crowd]:
Go, go, Date Tech,
Date Tech, here we go!
[Oiwake]:
Listen to me, boys.
So Karasuno surprised us
with that quick attack...
but it was just
the spiker's height
that threw us off,
that's all.
[Oiwake]:
Despite that incredible jumping
power, at the end of the day,
all he did was
a normal quick attack.
Don't lose sight of that.
Just don't let him or that ace
of theirs score a single point!
They know we're
the iron wall...
so get out there...
and remind them!
[Team Date Tech]:
Yes sir!
[Keishin]:
From what they showed us
in round one...
I'm thinking they'll come out
strong with their first serve...
They as notorious
for their serves
as they are for their blocks.
[Keishin]:
Date Tech's strategy is
to tank their opponents' morale
from the get‐go.
So let's be sure to
receive high on the first one,
you guys got
that?
Right!
Oh, and... you know
what to do, don'cha?
Yeah.
Perfect... Make me proud, team!
Let's clear that wall!
[Team Karasuno]:
Sir!
Karasunoooo... fight!
Fiiiight!
Hey, looks like Karasuno's
starting their ace
in the back row.
[Irihata]:
Right, probably because that's
the strongest formation
for receiving.
Date's in the same position
as the first round.
You can do it!
Let's go!
Bring it on!
[Moniwa]:
Do it, Kamasaki!
[Sasaya]:
Serve's up!
Daichi!
Nice receive!
His form is flawless.
He's able to mask where he plans
to send the set... but...
[Ryunosuke]:
Sweet! Nice moves, Hinata!
Uh‐oh! So they
DID block it!
And here I was thinking
we had them a step behind.
[Takeda]:
Jumping after seeing the set.
That's called
read‐blocking, right?
[Keishin]:
Yeah.
The other schools we've dealt
with used "commit blocks",
meaning they make the jump as
soon as they have a vague idea
of where the set is headed.
[Keishin]:
But Date Tech prefers
hardcore read‐blocking,
meaning they don't jump until
they can see the set in motion.
In other words...
...it'll be almost impossible
to fake them out.
That WOULD put them a step
behind to block it, but...
That number 7... he's so
damn big and so fast...
he could close
the gap, quick.
Wow, that's scary.
That read‐blocking is
gonna be a problem...
How do you think they're
going to fight it?
Who knows?
After all, Karasuno hasn't
even brought out the big guns
in this tournament yet.
[Daichi]:
Go for it, Kageyama!
[Shoyo]:
Yeah, get the point!
Damn! It went straight
to the libero!
That was a pretty
impressive serve, there...
Now if he can just learn
how to control it,
he'll be in
business.
Whoa, he saved it!
Amazing!
Tanaka, cover it!
Gotcha!
Back here!
A back attack?!
There were barely any of
those in the last game.
Hey, Asahi!
Man...
Oh, darn.
Don't let it get you
down! Keep moving!
[Crowd]:
Go, go, Aone! Way to go, Aone!
Hey, Aone! Hey, hey!
I'll get it next time!
Thanks, but I don't mind...
I'll do better too.
C'mon, this is
a sports tournament...
You should be at
each other's throats!
What good do you think that
would do, Futakuchi?
Ow!
A net touch, huh?
[Daichi]:
That was lucky!
I‐It's fine!
Don't sweat it!
They must be really happy
that Date Tech hit the net.
Karasuno would have been
in a lot trouble.
They're not
half bad, though..
Their blocks and
their quick attacks
seem to work
fairly well together.
[Irihata]:
They've got potential.
[Moniwa]:
Nice receive!
I'm open!
Asahi!
Wait, I'm confused; did we
get a point for it being out?
Asahi, it's your serve!
Karasuno's doing a good job
of keeping the lead.
But Date Tech's not giving them
enough room to make any spikes.
Well, not the kind of
spikes they need, anyway.
Mm‐hm.
So far, they've been able to
narrowly avoid Date's blocks,
but if they slip up once,
they'll have the rug pulled
out from under them.
[Moniwa]:
Futakuchi!
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice one, Hinata!
Seriously?
Chance ball!
[Oiwake]:
In a fraction of a second, we
take what was almost their point
and make it our own.
[Oiwake]:
We break their spirits while
boosting our own morale.
The perfect marriage
of offense and defense.
That... is the block.
[Obara]:
Nice block!
That was awesome,
Aone!... Agghhh!
They ARE called the iron wall...
And he's part of the reason.
[Keishin]:
I was right.
This is bad.
Dangit!
Just shake it off
and stay focused.
Huh?
Trust me... The next one's ours.
You think so?
Oh! You mean... time for
whoosh?!... And kaboom?!
It's been quite
a while, hasn't it?
I'm gonna need your fastest
speed and your highest jump too.
And I'll bring the
ball straight to you.
You can count on it.
Karasuno's probably going
to use that Number 10
for their
fastest attack.
Still, they won't be able to get
around our iron wall.
So why aren't they acting
the least bit nervous?
[Keishin]:
When we played against Nekoma...
who can tell me why our
special technique didn't work?
Ooh! 'Cause Inuoka's
too awesome!
That's uh... not quite the
answer I was looking for,
but you're
not wrong.
It's because of
their middle blocker...
He learned Hinata's
movements.
Uh‐huh... That's it.
That wasn't all though.
Nekoma had another star player
that made things
complicated for us.
What was his name?
[Keishin]:
The one with the
two‐toned hair.
Kenma!
Seriously dude, what do you
have a cold or something?!
I'm fine Inuoka;
just leave me alone.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't expect them to come up
with a countermeasure
that quickly...
but once the word gets around,
every team is gonna learn
how to adapt to that
Hinata‐Kageyama combo we've got.
[Keishin]:
Don't get me wrong...
it's a deadly weapon,
but it's not invincible...
The most important thing is...
[Tobio]:
Is how we use it.
Tanaka!
Got it!
[Tobio]:
Even flawless
read‐blocking is no match
for Hinata's
breakneck speed!
(crowd cheering)
That was intense!
Yeah!
[Hajime]:
There's that monster
quick‐attack.
[Mizoguchi]:
That move is killer.
It's a game‐changer...
That's for sure.
Nothing pisses me off
worse than a prodigy.
That was a
crazy set...
It's like he sent the
ball extra hard just to get
Aone out of the way
or something.
It had to have been calculated;
the spiker hit it perfectly.
There's no way they
planned to do that;
it must have
been a fluke!
That kid...
You ever seen him?
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice going, carrot top!
No sir...
You nailed it!
Well at least not
from the most recent
middle‐school
tournament anyway.
Was it a fluke... or not?
It's all you, Tsukishima!
Yep.
Hey, Your Highness..
How about a little something
a further from the net...
I'd like to stay
clear of their blockers.
Sure, asshole.
Huh?
I said sure, okay?!
Look, I know it's not easy
for you to take orders from us
peasant commoners, but I'm here
to win if you don't mind.
What?!
Guys, knock it off,
now's not really the time!
Looks like Kageyama
finally busted out
that quick
attack, huh?
Date Tech must be
shaking in their shoes...
And for good reason; you won't
find another technique like that
combo attack in
the whole world.
[Irihata]:
It's something
else, alright.
[Team Date Tech]:
Yeah!
[Tobio]:
Great job, dumbass!
[Shoyo]:
I'm so sorry, guys!
There's still plenty
of things they could stand
[Shoyo]:
My bad, Noya.
to improve upon though.
I got you!
[Moniwa]:
Show 'em what
you got, man!
You see, that was
just a normal Set.
He must have
been really lucky...
or only number 10 can
pull that move off.
Good job!
That was great,
Tsukishima, keep it up!
[Tadashi]:
Go, Tsukki!
Yeah! Time to take
back what's ours!
[Moniwa]:
Nice, Kamasaki!
[Sasaya]:
Yeah, that was great!
I don't think so!
Yeah!
The point gap
isn't changing.
That's true, but look
at the rotation.
[Irihata]:
Karasuno number 10's
back on the front row.
Oh great... him again.
Kageyama hasn't thrown
any of those crazy sets
since his Number 10
left the front...
And come to think of it,
when I saw him play
back in middle school,
[Date Coach]:
I seem to remember
him repeatedly
leaving Keetagawa's
spiker in the lurch
with impossible balls
just like that.
I know, and as soon
as I saw him set before...
I was really afraid he had gone
back to his old bad habits.
But then...
[Oiwake]:
...their number 10 hit it.
Almost like it was planned out.
[Moniwa]:
Futakuchi!
[Kamasaki]:
That's how it's done!
Date Tech's pretty
tenacious, aren't they?
Yeah, now that Karasuno's number
10's moved up to the front...
[Spiky‐haired Guy]:
Date's best blocker
Number 7's up there too.
[Spiky‐haired Guy]:
Unstoppable force
meets immovable object.
They're probably thinking
that superhuman quick attack
was just happenstance.
Let's go all in!
Right!
[Daichi]:
It's in! Forward!
He saved it!
That's nuts!
[Tobio]:
Nice receive!
[Spiky‐haired Guy]:
But there's no way they
Where's he
gonna send it?
That's right!
[Daichi]:
Excellent work, you two!
[Tobio/Shoyo]:
Thanks!
The kid did it again! The exact
same lightning‐fast set
but even farther
back from the net!
You mean that
wasn't... just a fluke?
[Team Karasuno]:
Let's go!
Oh, wow. Date Tech just
called for a time‐out.
Dude, is that
number 10 even human?
How is he able to hit
all those sets?
Technically it's not
the spiker who's so amazing;
it's the setter who
lines up the ball for him
to hit it
so perfectly.
Tch!
It's like watching a pair
of fine‐tuned robots...
We were mind‐blown
the first time, too.
[Oiwake]:
If that quick attack
is for real,
we won't be able
to read‐block it.
But if we don't
counter somehow...
then that'll be just as bad
as throwing in the towel.
[Oiwake]:
If it looks like number 10 might
attack, don't mark the set.
Mark HIM. Stay one
step ahead of his jump.
There's still the possibility
that it was just luck,
so keep that in mind.
Don't concentrate
too hard on it,
just stay cool
and play it by ear.
Right!
I don't think I've ever seen
anything like that before.
Do you think he's the only
one that can do that move?
[Moniwa]:
If that WASN'T a fluke,
then they've gotta be
some kind of monsters.
True, that quick attack
was terrifying...
but if we focus too
hard on that,
they're just gonna sneak
past us with a normal attack.
It's not that
big a deal...
All we really have to do
is stop their number 10.
[Kamasaki]:
You're WAY too chill,
you know that?
[Futakuchi]:
Better than
having NO chill.
That's why you can't
get a girlfriend.
[Kamasaki]:
What'd you
say to me?!
Aone, You know
what to do!
But still... if Date
can stop that number 10,
they'll
be golden.
Hm?
I mean, he's the only Karasuno
guy who seems to be untouchable
when it comes to
Date Tech's iron wall.
Yeah, I guess so.
Either way, we know we have
our strategy planned out!
Yeah!
[Oiwake]:
We've gotta do something
about that Number 10.
[Team Date Tech]:
Number 10.
[Crowd]:
[Crowd/Team Date Tech]:
Number 10.
[Keishin]:
That's right Kageyama...
We're building a reputation
with everybody talking about our
little red 10...
So we need Hinata to
shine bright out there.
Bring it on!
Jeez, you're slow!
We almost missed the game!
Yeah well we actually had
some customers for once!
[Yui]:
Hurry, hurry!
Oh, good, we made it! The boys
are still playing round two!
Can't believe they're
beating Date Tech!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it here!
Damn, that guy
is really fast...
Whatever, we at
least tried, right?
Huh?... What was that?
So quick!
Those two are first‐years,
aren't they?
Hey did you see how high
that little guy can jump?
What are YOU
looking smug for?
[Koshi]:
Great work, Hinata!
Who's that?
Right! Now do another
quick attack just like that!
[Koshi]:
Make it count!
So Suga's not in the lineup?
[Asahi]:
Nishinoya!
Go!
Give it here!
Which one of them
will it be?
He's jumping!
O‐Or not?!
That was a
normal one.
So I guess they're setting
at different speeds
for different
situations.
You haven't seen these crazy
first‐years we just got.
They still have a lot of work to
do, but if they keep trying,
[Daichi]:
I really believe Karasuno
High's gonna have the
perfect volleyball
team one day.
I get it.
Damn it. Who IS
that little guy?
[Moniwa]:
Alright, alright!
Don't lose focus!
Remember, you're putting in
some good work out there too...
Their number 10 might
have caught you off guard,
but you guys have outdone all
kinds of spikers in the past...
Including Karasuno's ace!
And this time is no different!
Right!
Why do you keep
saying "you guys"?
You're part of this
team too, you know?!
Futakuchi...
And I always thought
you were just a dumb,
bratty underclassman!
Wow, thanks a lot, pal.
YEAAAAHHH!
[Date Tech Fan]:
Nice kill, Aone!
Whoa, did that guy really
just jump twice?!
Well, I guess when
you're that enormous,
even a little jump can
put your hand over the net.
[Keishin]:
Not only is he tall, he's got
long arms and broad shoulders
to his
advantage.
But there's even
more to him than that.
He's calm enough not to get
tunnel vision,
plus he's got the tenacity
to stop the ball no matter what.
Those two traits combined,
are what make his blocks
so incredible.
Check it out...
Now THAT'S a block.
Yeah, that kind of technique can
completely turn things around.
So if Karasuno doesn't
score the next point,
then Date Tech will
just ride the wave.
We'll stop this too!
Yeah!
Let's go! Keep your head
in the game!
Come on!
[Moniwa]:
Futakuchi! You got this!
[Daichi]:
Cover me!
[Yu]:
All you!
[Ryunosuke]:
Open!
Center!
Hinata!
Right!
Yeah!
Nishinoya!
Kageyama!
Here!
Three attackers up
front... Which one?!
Bring it here!
NUMBER 10!
[Tobio]:
I have to create a path...
...for the ace!
...And then the view of the
other side is totally clear!
Yeah...
I remember!
OOOOH YEAAAAAH!
Hey, wasn't that...
[Shimada]:
the same pipe
Nekoma did?!
Asahi!
You guys are great...
I really mean it.
Thank you so much.
[Yu]:
Are you kidding me?
That was all you, dude!
[Tadashi]:
Good job, Asahi!
Please blaze a trail
for Asahi too!
Yes!
Hey, what's the matter?
Well, I... I wasn't the one
who scored that last point.
I can't take
the glory...
NUMBER 10!
But still, it...
it felt really good.
Like I said, decoy...
Your job is just as cool.
The greatest decoy...
I get it.
Alright... At this point,
we've showed 'em every weapon
we've got
in our arsenal.
[Keishin]:
Now... the real work begins.
[Aone]:
It's changed.
[Futakuchi]:
What's changed, Aone?
[Aone]:
Karasuno.
[Futakuchi]:
No kidding! Now that they have
that setter and the short guy,
it's hard to figure
out where to block‐
[Aone]:
The manager's
girly hairstyle.
[Futakuchi]:
Oh, that? Our next Haikyu!!
"Back Protection."