[SHOYO]
I am SO sorry, Tanaka!
I mean it.
[RYUNOSUKE]
I told you, it's okay... I'm
worried about YOU; do you feel
any better yet?
[SHOYO] Yeah... I do now that
I'm off the bus and I've rested
a little bit.
Sweet, I'm glad to hear that!
After all, whether we
win or lose today totally
depends on you!
[SHOYO] HUH?! (panicking)
[RYUNOSUKE] And let me hit
everything unmarked like you got
to do in the 3‐on‐3, okay?
[KOSHI]
Tanaka! Don't pressure him!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? What? Can't hear you.
[SHOYO]
(stomach gurgling) I‐I'll do
the best I can, I swear!
[SHOYO]
Hurghhh, I'm going to the
bathroom! (groan)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Comin' out both ends?!
You're workin' overtime!
[TOBIO]
Huh? He's getting sick again?
That is so pathetic! I'm gonna
teach him a lesson...
[KOSHI] (worried) Hey what
are you talking about?! You
know beating the little guy up
isn't gonna do any good!
[TOBIO]
Well, it's worth a try!
[KOSHI]
Hold him back, Tanaka! Help me!
[RYUNOSUKE] You got it!
[DAICHI] (worried)
[TOBIO] Let go of me!
(crows cawing)
[YAHABA]
Hey, we're playing Karasuno
today, right?
Doesn't that one guy go there?
[YUTARO] Who?
[YAHABA]
The King of the Court...
Didn't you guys go to middle
school together?
Or something like that?
[YUTARO]
Right... Kageyama...
There's nothing special
about that guy.
[YUTARO]
He had the best technique out
of anybody on the team,
but the jerk couldn't act like
a team player to save his life.
[YUTARO]
Too full of himself.
Yeah... Well I'm wondering why
he went to Karasuno High...
I mean they haven't had a
great team in a long time.
All I know about them now is
that they've got some super
hot babe for a team manager.
They have a girl?!
[YAHABA] Yeah, she's got
this sexy vibe about her.
[DAICHI] Have you seen Tanaka?
[KIYOKO]
No.
[YAHABA]
And one of their team members
looks like a juvenile
delinquent...
The guy's even got
a shaved bald head.
And it seems like he's
pretty stupid too.
HMMM?
[YAHABA YUTARO]
(startled)
[YAHABA]
Um... hello...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Don't mock my team, bro.
(crow cawing)
We'll have your heads.
[YUTARO YAHABA]
(scared)
Heh. Come on, Tanaka, there's
no need to talk like that.
[KEI]
I mean look what you've done;
the hotshots from Aoba Johsai
High School
are practically
shaking in their shoes.
You idiots really think
we're afraid of you?!
[YAHABA, internal]
Who is this beanpole?
I didn't know they had
a player that tall.
Oh yeah, good thinkin'...
It'll hurt worse if we kick
your asses on the court instead.
[DAICHI] Hey! Knock it off!
I cannot take you anywhere!
[RYUNOSUKE KEI] (startled)
[DAICHI]
Please excuse him!
[YAHABA] Uh, it's fine.
[RYUNOSUKE] (straining)
[DAICHI]
Don't make that face at me!
[YUTARO]
So how ya been? Your Majesty...
I bet you've already whipped
your new loyal subjects into
shape. Haven'tcha?
[RYUNOSUKE] (enraged laugh)
[DAICHI] (grab)
Uh‐huh.
(shocked)
[TOBIO]
(smacked) Ow!
What was that for?!
[YUTARO] Yep, that's the
King... Stuck up as ever.
[RYUNOSUKE] You're growing
up so fast!
[TOBIO] What?!
[GUYS] (revving up for the game)
[SHOYO]
Whoa... No way... This gym is
huge.. THEY'RE huge...
[DAICHI] All together!
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[ALL] Thank you for having us!
[AOBA JOHSAI]
Thank you!
Every single player on the
Seijoh team has
exceptional offensive
and defensive abilities
individually.
[DAICHI] Their guys are all
good enough to be the ace
no matter where they go.
[HAJIME] Serve up!
[MIZOGUCHI]
That's good, keep working on it!
And they're also famous for
their power blocking guys.
I dunno what you two
are so scared of;
Hinata's gonna take those losers
by surprise and blow 'em away!
[SHOYO] (startled)
[RYUNOSUKE] Plus.. I know how
much you suck so I'll be there
to cover for you the whole time!
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[DAICHI KOSHI] (amazed)
Oh, but you're on your own
whenever you serve the ball,
remember?
Try not to screw up okie dokie!
[KOSHI DAICHI SHOYO] (panicked)
[RYUNOSUKE] (laugh)
Aw I'm just kiddin'! Fumblin' a
serve isn't all that bad my man!
Just let it roll off your
back and keep slammin'‐
Hm? Hey hang on..
Where'd he go?
[TADASHI]
The bathroom, I think.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Not again!
(flushing)
[SHOYO] Ugh, I'm
in trouble... ggh!
[YAHABA]
Man, those Karasuno guys sure
are arrogant. Who do they think
they are?
[YUTARO] Ugh, yeah. Huh?
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[SHOYO, internal]
Hey... He was next to Kageyama
in that game last year.
I could never forget a guy whose
head looks like an onion.
Hey... take it you're one
of their first‐years.
What's it to you?
So... How is King Kageyama?
Has he learned any manners?
Or is he still the same
conceited jackass?
What are you, crazy?!
"Conceited" doesn't
even come close to it!
[SHOYO]
It's like I'm a small, sad
little peasant p
putting up with the daily
torture of living in the Land
Without Fun or Happiness!
[SHOYO]
Just 'cause he's KINDA good,
he thinks he's the boss of
everybody!
See what I mean?
(laugh) He hates that guy!
I mean, I'll be
the first to admit
he's good at receiving,
blocking, and serving...
Oh yeah.. Real good!
[BOTH]
And his sets are...
[SHOYO] great too...
[YUTARO] a pain in the
ass...
[BOTH] Huh?
Are you sure?
Uh‐huh.
Let me guess, you've never had
to hit one of Kageyama's crazy
sets in a real game, have you?
They're terrible! It's literally
impossible to hit one!
[SHOYO]
That bad, huh?
[YUTARO]
He's a selfish dictator.
What's the point of him being a
setter if he can't put the ball
where anyone can hit it?
He doesn't belong in
that position.
[YUTARO]
To him, a "teammate" is
just a mindless slave
who does whatever he tells them.
[YUTARO]
Anyone he can't use... goes
straight into the trash...
[SHOYO] (think)
[YUTARO] Buh‐bye!
[RYUNOSUKE]
(laughter)
[YAHABA YUTARO]
(startled)
You wanna know if he's changed
since middle school?
You just wait and
see, Onion‐top!
[YUTARO]
What'd you say?!
Isn't that right, shorty?
[BOTH]
Uh?
[SHOYO, internal]
Anyone he can't use
goes in the trash?
What happens if I screw
up in front of him?
I have had enough of you!
(screaming)
I'll get swapped out!
[SHOYO] (nauseous)
I'm gonna be sick!
(shocked)
Yeah, this is gonna
be a good game.
(warming up)
(sick)
[DAICHI] Hinata!
Don't let your jitters get the
best of you my man... Relax.
Yes sir, I'll relax
as hard as I can!
[DAICHI] Hey Kiyoko, do you
think you could give him
[KOSHI] Hey, it's time to
go get changed.
[DAICHI] a few words of
inspiration?
[SHOYO] O‐okay!
[KIYOKO] Hm?
[KIYOKO] Excuse me.
[SHOYO] Huh?
Do your best.
[SHOYO] (overheat)
[KIYOKO DAICHI] (startled)
[DAICHI, internal]
Well, I killed Hinata...
Sorry, guys.
(whistle)
[UMPIRE]
Let the practice game between
Karasuno High and Aoba Johsai
officially begin!
[PLAYERS]
Thank you!
Is that short guy supposed
to be their middle blocker?
That has to be a mistake right?
Is that really
Kageyama over there?
Why's he with these guys?
("I dunno" mumble)
(panicking)
C'mon, pull yourself
together, Hinata.
[SHOYO]
Yes sir! I'll get it
together right now!
[DAICHI]
Seriously...calm down!
Hey, Hinata! You know
the plan right?
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOBIO] Do it exactly
like the 3‐on‐3, okay?
Yeah, I understand!
(startled) You
sure about that?
[HAJIME]
Do it, Matsukawa!
[DAICHI] I got it! Right here!
[SHOYO] (stumble)
You moron! What's with you?!
That obviously wasn't your ball!
I'm sorry!
Ennoshita, cover!
Tanaka!
On it!
(grunt)
Ah...
That's one point.
(growling)
[SHOYO] (trembling)
[DAICHI] It's okay Hinata,
just take a nice deep breath and
pay attention to
your surroundings.
I'm sorry!
[TOBIO, internal]
He's completely cracked
under the pressure.
(whistle)
(falling)
[SHOYO] Oof!
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[DAICHI]
Hinataaa!
Please stop stressing
out, buddy.
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah! Thanks a lot pal!
It touched the net.
Karasuno's finally
on the scoreboard.
[SHOYO] (yanked, trembling)
[TOBIO] Come oooon!
Quit being nervous
or I will kill you!
[YUTARO] Well... There's the
great leader I remember.
[SHOYO] That's not helping me
calm down!
[AKIRA] He hasn't
changed a bit.
[TOBIO] Why not?!
Alright! We're gonna take
all those points back!
Next one to serve‐ (shock)
(internal) Oh no...
Hinata's up to serve.
[TOBIO] Talk about bad timing!
(SHOYO nervous)
[DAICHI] Just breathe, Hinata!
[SHOYO, internal] If I flub this
serve,
(gulp) we automatically lose
a point and the set's over!
Dude, call me crazy, but I
think Hinata just stopped
breathing; is he okay?
How do you expect me
to know that, huh?
Anyone he can't use...
goes straight into the
trash... Buh‐bye!
[SHOYO, internal]
You can't mess this up. If you
do, you'll get benched!
Just calm down... Everything's
fine... Everything's juuust...
(whistle) (panic)
Gah... Crap, that was
a terrible hit!
Gah! Guah! Ach!
[SHOYO] (nervous trembling)
[TOBIO] (seething)
(seething intensifies)
(long whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Pffff...
Damn, Kageyama...
(KEI laughing)
[RYUNOSUKE] I sure hope you've
got a couple brain cells left
over after all that!
[KEI] That was perfect!
[KOSHI] Stop, you're only
making it worse!
[DAICHI]
Knock it off, you two!
[SHOYO, internal]
I'm so dead...
[KEI RYUNOSUKE]
(stifling laughs)
[DAICHI]
Ah... Hold on, Kageyama...
[SHOYO] (shrinking back)
D‐don't hurt me!
L‐let's talk about this!
W‐wait a second! N‐no!
(panicked breaths)
(nervous)
(uncertain)
[TOBIO] Look.
(SHOYO yelps)
[TOBIO]
What could you possibly
be freaking out about?
How tall those guys are?
Your first practice game?
(nervous)
[TOBIO]
There can't be anything scarier
than hitting me in the head with
the ball...
...right?
No, that's my worst nightmare.
Well, in that case you've got
nothing left to be scared of
anymore...
I mean, you've already
done the most terrifying
thing you can do.
[TOBIO]
Which means... Might as well get
over it and get your head in the
game, dumbass!
(startled)
So I'm not in
trouble then?!
No.. Who cares?
Gah! (internal) Well if
I can get away with that,
I guess I can get away
with anything!
Thanks for freaking
me out, Onionhead!
Hm?
[SHOYO, internal]
Still, we did just lose the
first set thanks to me.
Kageyama's not the only teammate
I should be worried about.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Sidebar, Hinata.
[SHOYO]
(startled) (nervous)
[RYUNOSUKE] Listen up.
[SHOYO] Yes?
Don't go thinkin' you have
to be as good as these more
experienced guys already...
That doesn't make any sense.
But I have to do things
right... Or else..
I'll get taken out. And I
want to play the whole game.
Look, kid... You're stupid if
you think that crap is gonna
change my mind!
I know good and well
what a klutz you are!
[SHOYO] (shocked)
[RYUNOSUKE] Daichi knows too
and he still let you play!
[DAICHI] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] Forget about being
swapped out!
You can worry about
that when... uh...
(confused)
When you do get swapped
out, how about that?!
HUH?!
[RYUNOSUKE] You're not that
bright as it is, don't waste
[TAKEDA] Do you think we should
step in?
[RYUNOSUKE] brainpower on
stuff that hasn't happened yet!
[KOSHI] No, I think Tanaka can
handle it.
[RYUNOSUKE]
See, here's the cool
thing about volleyball.
Everybody you see on this
side of the net... is your
ally, okay?!
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[RYUNOSUKE] So it's fine
if you kinda suck.
Just do your thing, even if it
messes us up! We're here to back
you up, bro!
[TOBIO] (sigh)
We're a team! Us and you!
(excited)
Now, who's your favorite
upperclassman?!
It's you for sure!
[RYUNOSUKE] Haha, call
me Mr. Tanaka Sir!
[KOSHI] Tanaka really wants
[KOSHI] to be treated like
an upperclassman.
[SHOYO] Mr. Tanaka Sir!
[RYUNOSUKE] If you say that,
[DAICHI] Yeah... well it's still
[RYUNOSUKE] I'll
help with anything!
[DAICHI] good to have
him on the team.
[SHOYO] Wow. Thanks
Mr. Tanaka Sir!
[DAICHI] Crap like
that always sound best
[RYUNOSUKE] (big laugh)
[DAICHI] coming from someone
who's honest to a fault...
like he is.
(whistle)
[GIRL A] What's up?
[GUY A]
Eh, just a practice game.
[GIRL B]
Looks like they're
starting the 2nd set.
Dude, you gotta teach me how
to do that back‐of‐the‐head
serve later!
[SHOYO] (embarrassed)
[KEI] Yeah, it's great; could
you teach it to me too?
(whistle)
[DAICHI]
You're up, Ennoshita!
(focused)
[TOBIO]
It's just like the 3‐on‐3.
First, go to a spot where they
don't have any blockers.
Then at your maximum speed, I
want you to jump and swing as
hard as you can...
Be careful not to bump into
our other spikers though, okay?
[SHOYO]
Yeah I Gotcha!
[YAHABA]
Kunimi!
[RYUNOSUKE]
You got cover?
[TOBIO]
Yeah!
Let's take it
to the left!
[DAICHI]
No, right!
They can't do quick attacks.
I'm sure they'll shoot for
an opening on the side.
Huh?
What in the hell?
[SHOYO]
Huh? I didn't touch it...
(whistle)
(internal) So they CAN
do quick attacks?
Maybe it's a bluff.
Either way...
If you keep missing those, it's
only a matter of time before the
King tears you a new one!
(startled)
[TOBIO]
Hinata!
(scared)
Here it comes.
Sorry 'bout that...
That last set...
it was a bit too high.
(stunned)
He's sorry?
I guess so.
[SHOYO]
That's cool, I forgive you.
[TOBIO] (pissed)
[SHOYO] Owowowow! Stop giving
me the iron claw, Kageyama!
(confused)
(whistle)
[HAJIME]
Service!
[SHINJI] Nice serve!
[CHIKARA] Hey, comin' atcha!
[TOBIO]
Got it!
[YUTARO] They go the right
and center.
[RYUNOSUKE] Over here!
[YUTARO] Left side's waiting.
(internal) Who's the
King gonna pick?
Okay, here goes!
Huh?
[BOTH]
Woooo!!
Yes!
Nice one!
Wow!
I see...
It's that weird set‐and‐spike
routine again.
[GUY B] Did you see that?!
[GUY C] He's fast!
Come over here, you two!
Uh?
Huh?
[DAICHI RYUNOSUKE]
Nice play!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Awesooome! That was
so team‐like!
Huh? What do you mean
"like"? We ARE a team.
(smile) Yeah,
you're totally right!
Nice one, first‐year.
Thank you!
[YAHABA] Quick‐attacks? Really?
[DAICHI] Give me one more of
those.
[TOBIO] Sure!
[YUTARO] He seems a lot
different since the first
set ended.
(internal) That's right, start
panicking. I want you to be
totally focused on Hinata.
[TOBIO]
Okay guys, Hinata's on track
now. Time for the counterattack.
[KEI SHOYO CHIKARA] (focus)
[RYUNOSUKE] Heh!
[RYUNOSUKE] A chance ball!
[SHOYO] I got it!
I know what to look out for now.
You're not foolin' me kid!
What did you say?!
You're mine now!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Eat this! You like that?!
[YUTARO, internal] Dammit,
the shorty was a decoy.
[RYUNOSUKE] Wooo! Got'em!
Aw man I thought he
was sending it to me!
[RYUNOSUKE] How do
you like me now?!
[YUTARO SHOYO] Huh?
Told you we'd show
your asses up!
(pissed)
Uwah... I acted all tough
and talked smack 'cause
I thought the ball was for me.
I feel dumb!
And there's nothing
wrong with that...
You were convinced you
were going to hit it..
so you convinced
all of them too.
Does that work?
Apparently.
Dammit.
[HAJIME]
Relax, Kindaichi...
We're making all our
attacks count today;
there's no need to
let it get to you.
Right.
[GUY A] Whoa... Even to
the untrained eye, it's
pretty obvious
(whistle) (KURASUNO cheers)
[GUY A] that their blocks
are being scattered all over
the place.
[RYUNOSUKE] Slick move, Daichi!
[GIRL B]
Was Karasuno High ever
this good before now?
(face‐smacked) Bleh!
(concerned)
Pff! (giggling)
[TOBIO] Not again!
[GIRL B] They make a lot
of mistakes, though.
(grunt)
(short whistle, long whistle)
[HAJIME]
Over here!
[AOBA JOHSAI] Yessir!
Something wrong, Hinata?
No.. It's just that the first
time I played in a game,
I felt like it was up to me to
carry the whole thing by myself.
[KOSHI] Great!‐ Let's keep
this energy going
[TAKEDA] Great play guys!
[SHOYO] But now, I'm surrounded
[KOSHI] and win the second set!
[SHOYO] by a team full of
players who
[SHOYO] are a lot better
at the game than me.
[SHOYO] I can depend on them.
[RYUNOSUKE] Leave the next one
to me!
All I gotta do is
believe and jump!
I guess I never really had
to worry about much else, huh?
[DAICHI] Huh...
[TOBIO] Hurry up.
[SHOYO] Don't throw towels
at me!
[DAICHI] He may not
realize it yet,
[SHOYO] Don't throw
towels at me!
[DAICHI] but that leap of faith
of his is one hell of a weapon.
[YAHABA]
Okay what's the deal?
That Kageyama guy isn't
anything like you said he was.
Yeah, well I've never seen him
like that either!
How was I supposed to know that
there would actually be a spiker
on this planet who could hit
those ridiculous royal sets?!
[IRIHATA] That's not quite it.
[YUTARO] (surprised)
From where I'm standing, their
number 5 player hasn't been
looking at the ball at all.
[YUTARO]
Wait what are you
talking about, Coach?
[IRIHATA]
The best I can figure out is
that Kageyama is purposefully
aiming the ball to match the
downward swing of the palm of
the spiker's hand.
[HAJIME]
Is that even possible?
So Kageyama... changed
his playing style?
[IRIHATA]
I'll tell you one thing ‐ that
number 5 of theirs must be
pretty darn talented
[IRIHATA] if he can get a
self‐centered and arrogant
player like Kageyama
[KEI] Hey, you want a drink?
[IRIHATA] to adjust his habits
like that.
[KEI] Your face is a little
lower down than I thought.
The really incredible part of it
is that Number 5
apparently trusts in Kageyama's
sets one hundred percent.
[IRIHATA]
He simply believes
the ball will come.
[IRIHATA] If they shake off your
blocking, just receive and keep
the ball in the air!
You boys are our starting
lineup. Show 'em what
you're made of!
[ALL] Right!
(whistle)
[IRIHATA] (sigh)
[HAJIME] Let's turn
this game around!
[AOBA JOHSAI] Yeah!
[MIZOGUCHI] Kageyama's really
good...
I kind of wish we
could've recruited him
back at Aoba‐Johsai...
Didn't you try to
get him here, sir?
Yeah... but even if he had come
to our school, despite all of
his technical ability,
would he have made plays like
that? I don't think so.
[MIZOGUCHI] Huh?
[TOBIO] Get ready!
[IRIHATA] I think it's Karasuno
‐ specifically Number 5
[TOBIO] I want us to take the
second set!
[IRIHATA] that made him into
the player we see now.
[SHOYO] Ow! Don't hit me so
hard!
[TOBIO] I'm encouraging you.
[DAICHI] Hey, time to start.
[MIZOGUCHI] Hm? Oh.
[DAICHI]
Chance ball!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Four‐eyes!
Aw yeah!
[TADASHI]
Good one, Tsukki!
Nice, Tsukishima!
Your sets are so precise, it
actually makes me nauseous.
[DAICHI] Tsukishima is being
kinda rude about it,
[TOBIO] What! Next time I'll aim
for your glasses, how's that?
[DAICHI] but I understand where
he's coming from...
[KEI] Go ahead... You'll just
get kicked out of the gym again.
[DAICHI] Anytime he wants the
ball to come his way,
[TOBIO] Then I won't let them
see me.
[DAICHI] it's already right
there in front of him.
[KEI] Do you think you can get
away with that? Come on.
[DAICHI] It's a little scary...
but...it works.
We're in the middle
of a game guys.
Can we maybe save
this for later?
Your serve, Tanaka!
[TADASHI HISASHI KAZUHITO]
You got this!
Ah, I get it now.
[TAKEDA]
The team rotates every time they
earn a point and get serving
rights...
[TAKEDA] Which means Kageyama,
Tsukishima, and Ennoshita should
all be playing forward now.
[CROWD] (cheers)
[KOSHI] Right. So at this point,
their positions are the opposite
of what they were when the game
started.
Thanks to Hinata's decoy
tactics, the overall success
rate of our attacks
increases whenever we have
him in the front row...
Also, whenever the ball
goes to Tsukishima...
(smile)
(impressed)
[TAKEDA]
His blocks are every bit as
intimidating as Seijoh's are!
I'm sorry, is blocking your
specialty too? Just try and
stay out of my way, would ya?
Watch your mouth... Get too
close and your skinny ass'll
get blown away.
[KEI TOBIO] (angry)
[CHIKARA] Uh.. Let's not
fight, okay guys? (worried)
You're s'posed to fight
the guys in blue! Blue!
[TOBIO KEI] (growling) (focus)
[RYUNOSUKE] Here comes the ball!
What are you so proud of?
I was the one who blocked
it, you know.
Oh whatever, it
hit my hand too!
[DAICHI] Knock it off!
Cut that crap out!
[KEI TOBIO] (startled)
(internal) Heh, for once it's
not me getting yelled at‐
(shaken)
[TOBIO]
Wipe that grin off your
stupid face or I will
wipe it off for you!
What did I just tell you?!
(whistle)
[HAJIME] Crap...
This is too close.
[MIZOGUCHI]
Get it together, Kunimi, that
won't happen if you cover!
[MIZOGUCHI] I was right,
that Number 5 of theirs
[AOBA A] Shake it off, guys!
Go for the next one!
[MIZOGUCHI] is unstoppable, huh?
[AOBA B] Let's get ready.
We can do this!
I agree... Combining him
with Kageyama is even more
intimidating...
but it's not just them.
[IRIHATA]
What Tanaka lacks in
composure he makes up
for in power and guts.
[IRIHATA]
Tsukishima's a smart blocker,
even if he's not too ambitious.
[IRIHATA]
Their captain Sawamura neatly
covers the team's weak areas.
[SHOYO] Over here!
[IRIHATA] Some of the team
members are amateurs, and their
defense is full of holes...
[IRIHATA]
...but the offense is flexible
enough to make use of their
greener players.
[IRIHATA]
They really took us by surprise.
So this is Karasuno.
A wild... disjointed...
(whistle)
[ALL] Yeah!
[TOBIO] Oo!
[IRIHATA] ... interesting team.
(long whistle)
[GUY A] Whoa!
[GIRL B]
I can't believe
they won the set!
Damn.
[RYUNOSUKE] Hell yeah!
[CHIKARA] Lookin' good out
there, Kageyama.
[TOBIO] Oh, thanks.
Time to take the final set..
[RYUNOSUKE] right?
[SHOYO] (splutter, coughing)
None of the guys on their team
can serve like Kageyama...
[CHIKARA] It's an advantage.
[RYUNOSUKE] This is our
comeback!
[SHOYO] Yeah!
[DAICHI] Totally... It's
been huge for us...
[DAICHI] Because our receiving
could use some work...
[SHOYO RYUNOSUKE, chanting]
Comeback!
[DAICHI]
Thank you.
[TOBIO] Don't get comfortable.
[DAICHI CHIKARA] Huh?
That setter of theirs...
I don't think he's..
their starter...
(GIRLS cheering and squealing)
[ALL]
Huh?
(gasp)
[IRIHATA]
Hey... Oikawa's back.
'Bout time.
[SHOYO]
So that's not Seijoh's
official setter?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Who cares? I wanna know why this
joker walked in lookin' so smug.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Kageyama, what do you know?!
[TOBIO]
Well, you'll just have to find
out next time.
[SHOYO RYUNOSUKE]
What?
[TOBIO] Next Haikyu!! "Versus
The Great King."