[SHOYO, voiceover]
There's an enormous wall in
front of me, blocking my way.
[SHOYO, voiceover]
I can only wonder
what's on the other side?
What does it look like?
Is it the view
from the summit?
I'll never be able
to see it on my own.
But if I have
others on my side...
[ALL]
Thank you!
[SHOPKEEPER]
Good morning!... Come on in!
[CUSTOMER]
Alright!
(cheers on TV)
[SHOYO] Eh?
(exhale)
(amazed)
(shocked)
[KARASUNO] (cheering)
[TV ANNOUNCER] He did it!
That's five points in a row
for Karasuno High
[MAN A] Whoa!
[TV ANNOUNCER] in the Spring
High School National Volleyball
Championship.
He might be surrounded by
players as tall as 6 foot 2,
but that does not stop
Karasuno's Tiny Giant from
making a huge impact.
[MAN B]
Oh, Karasuno, the next town
over... They're not half bad.
[IZUMI]
Hmph! Hurry up, Hinata, we're
gonna lose our soccer field!
Karasuno...
[IZUMI]
Hinata, slow down!
(pre‐game warmups, shouts
of encouragement)
(exhale)
(OM inhale)
It's huge.
(sniff)
It smells like Air Salonpas.
[IZUMI]
Don't say stuff like that,
Hinata... It's dorky.
[KOJI]
Yeah, don't be that guy.
But guys, this is my very
first real volleyball game!
I've waited 3 long
years for this!
[KOJI]
That's true, I guess it
is kind of amazing that
we made it this far.
[GUYS]
Two and three and...
(jogging, volleyball efforts)
(encouragement)
[SHOYO]
Izumin, Koji... Thanks for
coming to help our team out.
[BOTH] (surprised)
[KOJI] Don't make it weird!
(pout)
Our game was the first
one to finish; no need
to make it a big deal.
[SHOYO]
You too, first‐years!
I'm so thankful you three
joined the volleyball club
with me this season!
[MORI]
Uh, sure... We're pretty
terrible at this whole
thing, but okay.
Spare us the tears, Shoyo.
I'm not crying!
You've got tears
in your eyes.
[SUZUKI]
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt...
but we really
should warm up now.
Huh?
Come on, Captain,
you're in charge here.
He's right, Shoyo! You're
the one who dragged us into
this tournament thing,
and you still haven't explained
what all the rules are!
Uh! I know that!
Even though we barely made
the cut... we're here to
win this! Okay, guys?
[IZUMI]
We can't win with a thrown
together team of rookies!
[SHOYO]
Sure we can!
[KOJI]
Kitagawa First might
be tough though.
[SHOYO]
Maybe... but I'll
beat 'em anyway!
(IZUMI sighs)
(KOJI stunned)
(startled)
[SHOYO]
Uh? Ah... Gyahhh!
[IZUMI]
Excuse us! Move, dude!
(SHOYO yanked)
[ALL] Uh...
[KOJI]
They're tall!
(mighty cheer from stands)
[SHOYO] (startled) Huh?!
[CROWD]
Kita Go! Kita Go!
Hey, Kitagawa
First is here.
They're huge.
Those guys scare
the hell outta me.
They're the best
team around here.
They've got the King.
The King?
(cowering)
[ORANGE] What you don't know?
That's what they
call Tobio Kageyama.
He's a setter. And he's
supposed to be awesome.
Tch! Dammit, we're going
to going up against these
freakin' guys.
It'll be fine! I don't care
how big they are; I'll bust
right through 'em!
Maybe you're right,
Hinata; you are a
really good jumper!
You've got this!
(SHOYO's stomach gurgling)
[KOJI] Uh...
[SHOYO] Wonder where
the... bathrooms are...
(SHOYO nauseous)
(ALL worried)
[KITAGAWA A]
Have you guys even heard of
Yukigaoka Middle School?
[KITAGAWA B]
No, but the whole team looks
pretty shrimpy, and they don't
even have a libero.
[KITAGAWA C]
This'll be a piece of cake...
I almost feel a little guilty.
[SHOYO] You three!
(KITAGAWA startled)
You better not get all cocky...
(nauseous, grunting)
Because as soon as my tummy
stops being upset, I am gonna
wipe the floor with you jerks
out there...
Do you hear me?
(nauseous, pained)
[KITAGAWA] Uhhh...
(bust out laughing)
[KITAGAWA A]
I can't wait to see that!
[KITAGAWA B]
He needs his mommy! (laughing)
[KITAGAWA C]
Look, he's wearing the
captain's mark too!
[SHOYO, internal]
Ugh, they're making fun of me!
[TOBIO]
Hey... second‐years.
(gasp)
The official warm‐up's about
to start... Get moving.
[KITAGAWA A]
Yes sir! On our way!
[KITAGAWA B]
Whatever you say, Kageyama!
(scared)
[KITAGAWA B]
Hurry up, man. We
need to fill two more!
[KITAGAWA C]
The game won't last long
enough to drink all those...
Not against them.
[SHOYO]
Gah!
[KITAGAWA A]
Hah! Yeah, good point!
[SHOYO] What did you say?!
[TOBIO]
Look, you three.
You're not even warming
the bench yet.
You think you have the right
to look down on the competition?
(scared)
[TOBIO]
You can't hide behind our
school's reputation.
[KITAGAWA A]
W‐we're sorry!
Whoa... Uh!
Thanks, bro; I was about to
tell those losers off myself,
but whatever...
(TOBIO annoyed)
(SHOYO startled)
They were making fun of you
because you can't even handle a
little stomachache...
You have no right
to run your mouth.
[SHOYO]
Huh... Hey!
Why did you come to
this tournament anyway?
Just for fun or what?
(offended) No way,
I came to win!
You make winning sound so easy.
[SHOYO]
(uneasy) I know I'm
not very tall... but...
Huh?
I can still jump!
Hm...
As long as you don't
give up trying,
there's always a
chance at victory!
[TOBIO]
Yeah, well not giving up is
easier said than done!
[SHOYO]
Look, today's the day I finally
get to play volleyball on a real
court with 6 players.
So I'm gonna win the first
round, then the second, and
every match after that!
And not just in this
tournament, but all of them!
[TOBIO]
From the first round, to the
second, the final, all the way
to nationals...
I'm going to be the one standing
in the winner's court, got it!
(determined)
[TOBIO] Hmph!
What's your deal?!
[SHOYO] Oh, Izumin.
[IZUMI]
I thought you went
to the bathroom;
why were you picking
a fight with him?
We should get back!
Aren't you sick? Hey!
[SHOYO]
Nope!
Dude...
(warming up)
[SHOYO, internal]
Man, they're pretty good.
[KOJI]
Oh? (wincing)
So that scary guy must
be their setter.
I think that's Kageyama, the one
they were calling King of the
Court or whatever, right?
Anyway, remind me
what a setter is?
[IZUMI]
That's the position that
hits the ball up first...
We just learned that yesterday!
Oh, did we?
(playing volleyball)
[TOBIO]
Your timing is too slow...
A quick attack should
be faster than that!
[YUTARO]
Sorry.
[COACH] Kageyama...
[TOBIO] Hm?
You shouldn't be
obsessing over speed...
It isn't about your personal
technique;
it's about how well you're
able to set up the ball for
the spiker to hit.
You understand?
[TOBIO]
Yes sir.
(troubled)
(whistle blowing)
[SHOYO]
This is finally happening!
[CROWD] (cheering)
(whistle blowing)
[ALL] Time to start!
[AKIRA]
The other team's
kinda scrawny, huh?
[SHOYO]
Koji! I want you to show me
your back number, okay?
[KOJI] What?
(whistle blowing)
[SHOYO] Koji!
[KOJI] Gah!
(whistle)
I'm sorry.
Nah, don't worry about it!
[KITAGAWA #8]
You got this!
(startled)
(whistle)
(CROWD cheering)
[SCORER A] Man, those poor kids
aren't ever gonna score a point.
[SHOYO] Hang in there, guys!
[SCORER B] Well, at least we'll
be done a little sooner.
[SCORER A] Yeah, I've got
some shows to watch. Uh?
[SHOYO] There's No reason to
beat yourself up!...
[CROWD] Let's go Kitagawa, go!
(continuous cheer)
Just try harder next time.
[KOJI] Uh.. yeah!
This time I'll nail it!
[SHOYO, internal]
I've worked too hard
to get here...
I'm not gonna let it
end that easily!
[SHOYO]
Huh? I'm...
the only club member?
Oh yeah, the numbers
go down every year.
And so you know, our boys'
volleyball is just a fan club;
it's not a real team.
Okay...
So what do you want to do then?
You can pick a different club,
or I can put you in
girls' volleyball.
Hm? Uh.. that's
not gonna work...
I can do it by myself!
If you want.
I'll be the next Tiny Giant!
Huh?.. Tiny what?
(whistle)
(cheering)
(exert)
[GIRLS]
Nice serve!
[GIRL]
Nice receive!
(encouragement)
[SHOYO]
Gyah!
Got it!
(breathless)
[GIRL B] Circle up!
Okay, let's go for a run.
[GIRLS] 'Kay!
Perfect!
[IZUMI] So, that happened.
[BOY B] Wow.
You're on a break,
right, Izumin?
Set me up for some spikes!
Why would I do that?
I just wanna see if
I can hit a good spike!
No way dude,
I don't even know how.
All you have to do is
throw it so I can hit it!
I can't, okay? The
upperclassmen are watching.
[BOY C] Over here!
[BOTH] Oh? Okay, one sec!
(disappointed)
(leap)
(cheering)
[BOY A]
'Sup, Hinata? I heard you joined
the girls' volleyball team;
what's up with that?
(SHOYO spitting)
[BOY B] Man, you're
such a player!
It's not like that!
[BOY A]
So which girl you after?
[BOY B]
There's a lot of smokin'
hot third‐years on the team.
(startled) Well, yeah some
of them are cute, but‐
[BOY A]
Awww yeah!
Shut up, you guys!
I'm on the boys' team, okay?!
(whistle)
(cheering)
[KOJI]
You know... You sure practice a
lot for someone who never
actually gets to play.
Hey!.. I'll get to play
one day; just wait and see!
(run efforts)
[SHOYO] Everybody turns me
down now, but I'm gonna get a
whole bunch of guys to play!
[KOJI] If you say so.
[SHOYO] Hey, Koji‐
[KOJI]
For the last time,
not happening.
(whistle)
(cheering)
[SHOYO]
(exert) Hey, Izumin!
(IZUMI startled)
[SHOYO] You got a second?
[IZUMI]
Sorry, I've got an exam to cram!
(whistle)
(cheer)
Aw, man...
[SHOYO] It's okay!
[YUTARO] Hey, nice one!
[KOJI] Heads up!
Hm? (knocked out)
Shoyo! Are you okay?
[SHOYO] Ow...
My bad, dude.
(SHOYO perk up)
(KOJI surprised)
Could you set for me real quick?
(grin)
This time, I'll‐ (hit)
[SHOYO]
Koji! Izumin!
[IZUMI]
Hey, can we stop now?
My arms hurt and I can't seem to
aim the ball that well...
This is getting old.
Just one more try, I promise!
I'll get some first‐years
to join me soon!
[IZUMI]
But you just said one more
a few minutes ago...
This is the last one
for real, okay?
Thank you!
Ready?
Oh... oops‐
[IZUMI]
It's all you, Hina!
[SHOYO, internal]
I may be on the short side,
but I can jump high
to make up for it.
Higher than any wall!
( surprised)
(whistle)
(cheering)
[YUTARO] Yes!
[IZUMI] Shake it off, Hinata!
[SHOYO] Uh?
[KOJI] I'll throw you
another one, okay?
[SHOYO] S‐sorry!
[SHOYO]
Man, that should've been
my shot.
[SHOYO]
I'll get the next one.
(whistle and cheering)
[YUTARO] Sweet!
Wow... Their number
5 doesn't mess around.
Well, at least Yukigaoka's
scoring a few points in the
second set...
That's a little better
Those are all the other
team's errors though.
[KOJI] Here goes!
Huh?
[IZUMI] Gotcha!
(grunt)
[SHOYO, internal]
The wall! I can't see
the other side!
(whistle)
(cheer)
Man... It's like they're
anticipating their every move.
And the short guy
can really jump too.
[KOJI] Hang in there, dude.
You'll get the next one.
[SCORER A] It's too bad.
[IZUMI]
That's right! We got this!
(whistle and cheer)
[YUTARO]
Phew! That was close!
Pick up the pace!
Tch!
[AKIRA]
Nice.
Yeah... The captain's doing
those crazy sets again though.
What's the deal? The other team
doesn't even have any defense.
[AKIRA]
Why's he going all out?
[TOBIO, annoyed]
The real question is why
aren't you guys taking this
game seriously?!
Dude, chill!
It's not the time!
Check that out...
The setter for Kita First
is really good at what he
does and all, but...
it's almost like he's
playing by himself.
(whistle)
[KAWASHIMA]
Got it! Huh?
[AKIRA]
Looks like that's gonna
be a service ace!
[TOBIO] Not yet!
[YUTARO] He'll never hit that.
[SHOYO, internal]
It's not over until the
ball hits the ground...
(slide and tumble)
(CROWD cheering)
Ah! You okay?!
Man, that's gotta hurt.
He's a tough one.
If Kita gets one more point,
then this thing is all over.
Uh‐huh.
[SHOYO]
Man...
[KAWASHIMA]
Sorry... that was my fault.
Nah, I'll get the next one!
[KAWASHIMA] Look!
[SHOYO IZUMI] Huh?
Um... You almost
got hurt just now.
[KAWASHIMA] But we're never
gonna beat these guys.
[BOY] Almost over!
[KAWASHIMA] Why are
you trying so hard?
[TOBIO] Do it just
like the last one.
[CROWD, repeating]
Kita Go! Kita Go!
[SHOYO] Huh? Uh... I'm sorry...
[SHOYO]
I don't really understand
what you're asking me. But
it's... not over.
[TOBIO, internal]
(breath) He's right,
it's simple...
[TOBIO, internal]
No matter how tricky the
ball is, there's still a
reason to go after it.
[SHOYO]
Koji!
[SHOYO, internal]
The ball hasn't
hit the floor yet.
[IZUMI] Nice one!
[TOBIO, internal] No matter
how bad the odds are,
[TOBIO, internal] there's always
a reason to keep playing.
[KOJI] Come on, Shoyo!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Because we haven't lost yet!
[YUTARO] One‐touch!
Cover it, get back!
[AKIRA, internal]
I'll never make it in time.
Aw yeah!
(happy)
(look, startled)
[TOBIO]
Why didn't you run for it?
Uh, sorry.
Don't ever let your guard down;
don't stop playing
until the game is over
Yeah, I understand
that but...
it would take a miracle
for them to catch up to
us at this point.
The point they scored was
no miracle... It was stolen.
By that kid! Right there!
He stole our point!
[KOJI] Right, let's
get another one!
[AKIRA] Uh, okay...
I mean, you're not wrong,
but come on, dude...
(scowl)
[KITAGAWA #1] Inside
the net! Front, front!
[MORI] Izumi, I'm free!
[SHOYO] As long as you don't
give up trying, there's always
a chance at victory!
[IZUMI] It's all yours, Hinata!
[TOBIO, internal]
A miss hit? It didn't count as a
dribble...
[TOBIO, internal]
But nobody's covering
over there.
(gasp)
[TOBIO, internal]
No, he went left!
I swear I had my eye on him!
[TOBIO, internal]
So how...
How is he over here?!
[IZUMI]
Hinata!
Are you okay, kid?
(whistle)
[SHOYO] It was out?
(sad)
(CROWD cheering)
(long whistle)
[IZUMI]
That looked like it hurt...
[TOBIO, internal] I could
barely keep track of him.
[KOJI] You did your best, buddy.
[TOBIO, internal]
That was the setter's mistake.
There's no way he could have
anticipated it.
[TOBIO, internal]
How did he hit that?
Is it even possible for a person
to react that quickly?
Hinata, let's line up.
[TOBIO, internal] Athletic
ability... reflexes...
[YUTARO] Hey Kageyama, what are
you doing?
[TOBIO, internal] a sense
of control over his body...
[YUTARO] Quit daydreaming and
get in line so we can crush
[TOBIO, internal]
and most importantly,
determination to win. He
may have all that, but...
(frustrated) What have you
been wasting all your time
on for three years?!
(breath)
[KOJI] What did you say?!
[IZUMI] Koji, calm down!
[KOJI]
You don't know a damn thing
about what Shoyo's been doing!
[IZUMI] You can't pick a fight
in the middle of the court!
[KOJI] Watch me!
[SHOYO, internal] My first and
last real game in middle school.
[REFEREE] Game's over, boys,
line up.
[IZUMI]
Come on, Hinata, let's go.
[SHOYO, internal]
We lost every set.
Start to finish, the game
lasted only 31 minutes.
(STUDENTS muttering)
[KOSHI]
So that's the King
of the Court, huh?
[DAICHI]
Uh‐huh, He'll be a force
to be reckoned with when
he gets to high school.
[RYUNOSUKE]
The short kid seems
promising too.
(troubled)
Hey, we never stood
a chance anyway;
I heard those guys are
candidates for the nationals.
[YUTARO]
I could go for some
food right about now.
[AKIRA]
Whatever. You're always hungry.
(KOJI sighing)
No matter how good or
bad each team is...
...in the end, it all comes
down to winning or losing...
If you lose... then you have
to step off the court.
(deep breath)
[IZUMI]
(surprised) Hey, wait up!
[KOJI]
Hey! What's the rush?!
[SHOYO]
Hold it!
Hmm?
(sob) You might be the King
who rules the court for now...
(sobbing)
[SHOYO]
But I'm gonna win!... (sob) One
day I'm gonna stay in the court
for longer than you!
(SHOYO sobbing)
[TOBIO]
Only those who win get to
stay in the court... Only
the strongest.
So if you want to keep
playing, then you have
to become stronger.
[SHOYO, internal]
So what am I missing? (CM sigh)
[KOJI IZUMI] (surprised)
[SHOYO]
Thanks for everything!
(choked up)
Dude... Don't
make it awkward!
[KOJI]
You don't have to
thank us, alright?!
[SHOYO]
Huh? What are you crying for?
[KOJI]
(sob) I'm not crying, okay?
See ya, Shoyo!
[IZUMI]
See you later! Bye! Woo! Hah!
[SHOYO]
30 minutes over
the hills by bike!
[SHOYO]
It's my first day at
Miyagi Prefectural
Karasuno High School.
[BOY A]
Hey, does any one want
to join the soccer club?
[BOY B]
We need someone to manage the
baseball club; you interested?
(SHOYO running)
[BOY C] Huh?
[KIYOKO]
Here... These are all
the current applicants.
[DAICHI]
Thanks. Wow, that's not
very many. Didn't we used
to get more of these?
[KOSHI]
I'm sure we'll get more, Daichi.
[RYUNOSUKE]
You're looking radiant
today, Kiyoko!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Gah... I love when
she ignores me.
[SHOYO, internal]
Get ready, Karasuno,
'cause I'm here!
[SHOYO, internal]
I'm gonna practice like crazy!
I'll challenge that
King of the Court guy...
[SHOYO]
...and get revenge!
[SHOYO] (land)
(stunned)
[SHOYO]
What?! You're here too?!
[TOBIO]
(startled) (stumble)
Huh...
(panicked stare)
Omph!
Ow.
[SHOYO]
What's the King of the Court
doing at this school?! Maybe
it's somebody else?
Yeah, that's it! Someone who
looks just like him... and
happens to be in the gym...
and happens to play
volleyball... No way, get real!
[SHOYO]
Next Haikyu: "The Volleyball
Club of Karasuno High."