(gasp)
[TOBIO, internal]
A perfect receive.
[SHOYO, internal]
Is this who they meant?
[YU]
Huh?
Uh? Are you
shorter than me?
Gah! Hey! You had better
watch what you say to me!
Whoa, I am so sorry! Um
Anyway... I just wanted to
know how tall you are.
I'm 5'2, that good
enough for ya?!
(internal) He's barely
in the 5‐foot range!
Wha... what's
with you?
Somebody to look down at...
I haven't had that feeling
since middle school!
You freaking kidding me!
You're not looking THAT
far down!
Huh? Long time no
see, Nishinoya!
[YU] Heey, how's
it goin', Tanaka?
[SHOYO] Huh?
[DAICHI KOSHI]
Nishinoya!
[YU] Yo!
[DAICHI]
Oh, that's right,
you haven't met yet.
Nishinoya's a second‐year.
[SHOYO TOBIO] Hey!
[YU] Cool, nice to meet you,
first‐years!
Hey, I got a question for the
angry‐looking guy that just
threw that serve!
Where did you
come from?
Went to Kitagawa.
Seriously?! That's a
great school;
no wonder you're
so talented!
I played against those guys
in middle school and they
beat us 2 to 1!
[YU] They had someone back then
who could serve even better than
you!
[DAICHI KOSHI] Okay, looks like
Um... anyway, so um where
did you go to middle school?
Chidori‐yama!
(surprised)
Wow, they're pretty good
too! Why'd you come here?
[TOBIO]
Is it... because you heard
Coach Ukai was coming back?
Not really... I wanted to come
back here because... Well...
[SHOYO TOBIO]
(serious)
...Karasuno's school uniforms
for female students...
are the hottest!
[SHOYO] Uh?
[TOBIO] Hm?
But not just that!
The girls themselves aren't half
bad either!
Whoo! But most of all... Yeow!
OUR uniforms are awesome
too.. And black!
[YU]
My middle school had
blazers, so I've always
like military style...
And they just
have to be black!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I know what you mean brotha!
So the uniforms are perfecto...
All the ladies are beautiful...
And a short commute!
It was a no‐brainer! Hm?!
[YU] Ah! Omigod it's Kiyoko!
Come to my arms, sweet mama!
[KIYOKO] (screaming)(slapping)
[KOSHI] So I guess hasn't
changed all that much has he.
[SHOYO] He's like a horny
tornado...
[DAICHI]
I know right... He can be pretty
noisy... But whenever he gets
focused on the game...
[DAICHI]
Not so much.
So... Where's Asahi?
Is he back yet?
[DAICHI] Ah... Well, uh...
[KOSHI] Ah... (troubled)
[YU]
Ah? Tch!
[YU] Damn coward!
[SHOYO TOBIO] (startled)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey Noya! Show some respect
for your upperclassman‐
Oh Shaddap! He's a scared little
crybaby and you know it!
If Asahi's not coming back
then neither am I!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey! Noya, wait!
[YU]
My job... is just to
keep the ball in play.
The sky belongs to the spikers.
I can't compete in their space.
[YU]
But if I can just keep the ball
up in the air... I know I can
trust the ace to nail it.
No matter what happens, even
if it bounces off a wall of
blockers, I won't let it hit
the floor.
[YU]
So don't change a thing.
Ask me for the ball just
one more time... Ace!
[SHOYO]
Uh, hey!
[YU]
Hm?
You're a libero...
um right, Nishiya?
You're on the defense.
It's NishiNOya... Why do
you think I'm a libero...
Because I'm short?
Huh? Course not.
You're good at receives.
Hm?
[SHOYO]
That's the right fit for
the libero position
because solid receives are the
backbone of the defense, right?
Look at you... You really
know your stuff, huh?
The Captain says you're
the guardian of Karasuno
or something like that!
Huh?! Guardian, where'd
that come from?!
I‐It's not like I'm that big
of a deal; that's kind of
embarrassing, actually...
He really said that?
Mm‐hm, mm‐hm!
[YU]
Does he think giving me a
badass nickname is enough
to make me come back?!
I mean, he's not wrong, but...
D‐Dammit, Daichi,
that's not fair!
I... still really
suck at receiving...
[SHOYO]
And it's kinda the most
important part of the game.
Hm?
Could you teach
me... Nishi...
[SHOYO]
... I mean, Mister
Upperclassman!
(shocked)
[SHOYO] Uhhh...
[YU] Look.
[YU]
After practice I'm gonna treat
you to some ice cream!
[SHOYO] Huh?
[YU] I'm your Upperclassman.
And that's what
upperclassmen do!
(happy) Does that mean...?
[YU]
That doesn't mean I'm gonn
come back to volleyball club.‐
I'm just gonna teach you how
to do receives, that's all!
[SHOYO]
Thank you!
(sigh)
[YU]
Okay, I'll show you again.
[CHIKARA HISASHI]
Hm?
[YU]
Schwoom.. swish.. and bam!
You got it?
[SHOYO KEI] Huh?
[TADASHI] Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE]
I told you...
people who act on instinct
really suck at putting
stuff into words.
Oh I don't know...
I'm pretty sure I understood
what he meant.
Yeah, that's 'cause
you're the same way...
It's all sound effects, it's
like... Whamajam!
and "kablooey!" and
stuff... You're like a
bunch of five‐year‐olds.
Huh?
A libero, huh?
That's an interesting
position.
[DAICHI]
It is. The libero specializes in
defense... A digger.
They're not allowed to
make serves or spikes.
Instead, they maintain the
rearguard position and keep the
ball from hitting the floor.
So I guess that's why you
called him the guardian...
That's impressive!
If we can convince him to
come back, I think the
team'll be in great shape.
[YU] Man, you guys are giants!
How tall are you?
[DAICHI] He may be small,
but he's got a huge presence
[TADASHI] Tsukki is...
[KEI] What did I tell you?
[DAICHI] I'd feel a lot safer
with him on our side.
[TADASHI] Sorry, Tsukki,
I forgot.
It's at least good to see
Nishinoya still hasn't lost
his touch, isn't it?
I heard he trained through
his entire suspension...
He was gettin' it on
with the ladies' teams.
Haha! Just like Hinata!
Um hey, Nishinoya?
Huh?
Who's that Asahi guy you
were talking about before?
Dude! That's the one
thing you shouldn't say!
He's Karasuno's Ace...
Well, s'posta be.
The Ace, huh?
(internal) So, we do have one.
What are you all
speechless for?
That's what...
I wanna become!
Huh? Really?
A shorty like you?
[SHOYO]
(surprised) (sad)
[SHOYO] Huh?
[YU] I like your style!
You wanna be the ace because
it's flashy and cool, right?
Hell yeah, buddy! You
can be the ace if you
set your mind to it!
[YU] To tell the truth, you're
a lot more promising than the
guy we have! (laugh)
[SHOYO] Huh...
Of course... everybody out there
wishes they were the ace.
Yeah! That's 'cause
the ace is the best!
[YU]
I mean even the WORD "ace" is
awesome, right!
"Setter" and "libero"
sound kinda plain and
boring, you know?
[TOBIO] (annoyed)
[KOSHI] Just let it go...
But still... There's
one thing...
that the crowd loves even
more than a great spike.
(CROWD cheering)
[YU] Make a wicked
receive and they go
crazy for you every time!
[YU]
This game is "tall beats all"...
So if you're a bit on the short
side... libero's one of the only
options you got.
But I'll tell you one thing...
I don't play the position
because of how tall I am.
[YU]
Even if I was 6 feet tall...
I'd still be out there digging
the ball out.
(SHOYO amazed)
[YU]
Not being able to spike or
block doesn't mean anything...
In volleyball, you can never
lose unless the ball touches
the floor.
And the only one who keeps
it in the sky... is me!
Whoa... Amazing!
Ah‐hey, cut it out! You're
making it all weird when you
freak out like that!
[YU] Look I'll get you two ice
creams if you just chill,
alright?!
[SHOYO] Okay!
[YU] So, future ace,
what's your specialty?
[SHOYO] Huh?
Well uh, you said you
were bad at receiving...
So, what's your thing?
[SHOYO]
Well, it's not... I‐I'm uh...
Huh? Speak up.
A... decoy.
Why do you say it like
it's something bad?
Well, next to "ace" and
"guardian" and all that stuff...
decoy sounds kinda stupid,
right?
Who gives a damn
what it sounds like?
Yeah, but...
[YU]
If having you as a
decoy makes it
so a spiker can score a point...
...then your job is important...
just as important as theirs is!
Okay...
[KOSHI]
Now maybe all those powerful
spikes we hit'll finally earn
us some points...
since we've gotten
ourselves a good decoy.
This Hinata‐Kageyama combo
should come in handy.
Mm‐hm.
You do remember what
Takeda told us, right...
I think things really are
gonna be changing for us.
[DAICHI]
Let's just hope it's
a GOOD change.
[KOSHI]
(laughing) True that.
[TAKEDA]
I realize I'm asking a lot here.
Look, I'll be the first
to admit that I don't know what
I'm doing
and I need your help. Those
guys have so much potential.
Can't you find it in your heart
to help them out? Please.
(exhale) You don't know when
quit, do you, Takeda?
No sir... It's my
only real strength.
Ask me all you want, and
I'm still gonna tell you no.
[KEISHIN]
My grandpa was the super famous
coach, not me...
I told you, I'm not
the coaching type.
[KEISHIN]
Listen, Specs, I understand you
need somebody,
but it just ain't me.
Honestly... I think the
name's all you're after.
There is some
truth to that...
Coach Ukai was all
we ever had...
And I don't know
who else to ask...
But I am not the coach
those guys need...
I can't even run
a practice game.
And you think a brand‐name coach
is all it takes to fix that
little problem of yours?
[TAKEDA]
All I ask... is you try‐
[KEISHIN] Forget it.
(TAKEDA troubled)
I feel bad for you,
pal, I really do...
but the last thing I need is a
bunch of pain‐in‐the‐ass teenage
athletes to look after, okay.
I'll try again soon.
(irritated) Try again?!
What's it gonna take to
get rid of you?!
[TAKEDA]
I'm sorry to bother you, but...
If you would just come
watch them play...
then you'd see why
it's so important.
Guh... Yeah right!
I mean it! You're not
gonna change my mind!
Tch! Just go awaay...
Agh, jeez!
[KOSHI]
Here goes.
(hallway chatter)
[ASAHI]
Hey, Suga. Uh... it's
been a while, hasn't it?
[KOSHI]
Asahi... we would really like
you to come back to the team.
(awkward laugh)
[KOSHI]
Nishinoya just got back
from suspension y'know.
[ASAHI]
Really? Well that's good to
hear.
It makes me feel a lot better
knowing you guys have him
there to back you up.
That's how we feel about
YOU!
[KOSHI]
When you call for the
ball, everyone knows
they're in good hands!
Look I appreciate the thought...
But if I were to join the
team, I would just hold you
guys back like last time.
[KOSHI] Hear me out.
[ASAHI] (startled)
We've got this
amazing decoy,
and as much as I
hate to say it,
the new first‐year
setter's great too!
You wouldn't have to carry the
whole team on your own anymore!
We've got some new
tactics now...
If we just had you
and Nishinoya back..
then maybe Karasuno
could be unstoppable again!
Look we need our ace more
than ever! Things are just
starting to get better‐
[GUY A]
Asahi! It's time for
career counseling!
[BOTH] Huh?
[ASAHI]
Sorry, I gotta go.
Huh...
[SHOYO]
You go in first...
You're the one who wanted to
see the ace so bad, remember?
B.. But I'm way too scared
to walk into a third‐year
classroom!
[KOSHI]
Please wait, Asahi!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Uh Asahi?
Uh? What's up?
[SHOYO] (gasp)
[KOSHI] Hey uh...
what are you first‐years
doing over here?
Uh, well we uh....
[TAKEDA]
Yes... yes!
Thank you so much!
Oh no, pleasure's all mine!
Yes... thank you!
(thrilled) Alright!
That'll be perfect! Finally...
things are about to change!
[KOSHI]
Anyway... These are the new
guys, Hinata and Kageyama.
Ah.. it's uh nice
to meet you guys.
Hello!
[ASAHI] So how many did
you get this year?
[SHOYO, internal] Wow, is
he taller than Tsukishima?
[KOSHI] Four. Not the numbers
we wanted, but they're all
promising.
[SHOYO, internal]
Heh... is that right?
(realize) He seems nice though.
[ASAHI]
Good luck. Alright kid...
Huh? Are you gonna come
play with us or what?
[ASAHI] (taken aback)
[SHOYO] I want to be
the ace one day.
[SHOYO]
I was hoping to
see you in action!
[GUY A]
Hey Asahi! The teacher's
waiting for ya man!
Sorry... but I'm not
the ace anymore alright?
(confused)
So uh... did he get
hurt or something?
Oh no... it's nothing
like that at all.
To be honest with you...
[KOSHI]
It might just be that Asahi's
lost his love for the game.
What?! But why?!
He's so big and tall and
he gets to be the ace!
[KOSHI]
See... Asahi was Karasuno's
biggest and strongest player.
Even in the trickiest
situations, he could
always score a point.
That's why we all depended on
him and considered him the ace
of the team... but then...
[TOBIO] Was it a bad game?
[SHOYO] Huh?
In one of our games... every
single one of Asahi's spikes
was completely shut down.
It was rough... And he's the
type who feels responsibility
for everything.
(SHOYO thinking)
[TOBIO]
What's wrong with you?
[SHOYO]
I don't think it's a
good enough reason to
hate volleyball.
Well, I dunno... It could've
been a number of things.
[SHOYO]
Yeah like what else?
[TOBIO]
Beats me. But hey...
We don't actually KNOW for sure
that he hates volleyball, do we?
[SHOYO]
Ah? You're totally right
[YU]
Rolliiiing... Thunder!
[ALL]
Huh...?
(RYUNOSUKE laughing)
[KOSHI] Uh... well okay then.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Come on, dude, it's just
a rolling receive!
[TOBIO] What are
you yelling for?
(TADASHI snickering)
[KEI]
Are you hearing
yourself? (laughter)
You better watch your mouth,
you little first‐year brats,
or you're gonna regret it!‐
I'll make you do laps!
No, push‐ups!‐ You know what,
[SHOYO] That was awesome! Teach
me the Rolling Thunder too!
whatever you hate the most,
I'm gonna make you do a
[TAKEDA] Take five, guys!
Guess what? Great news!
[YU] Sure thing, kid!
[SHOYO] Sweet!
[TAKEDA]
So, the Golden Week
training camp.
We're all going
this year, aren't we?
[SHOYO, internal]
Training camp?
Yeah... All of us can surely
benefit from the practice.
That's excellent... cause on
the last day of said training
camp...
...I've arranged us
a practice gaaaame!
[ALL]
Whoaaa!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Wow, Take!
You're really pulling
your weight!
[KOSHI]
Who are we gonna be playing?
It Nekoma High School...
They're in Tokyo.
People describe them
as... catlike.
[SHOYO]
Catlike?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah, we actually know
who those guys are...
Our old coach was
rivals with their coach.
We used to play
them all the time.
[SHOYO]
Oh...
[KOSHI]
Oh, that's right!
They called it...
"Cats and Birds!"... the
famous trashcan showdown!
[KEI]
I can't believe people
actually came to see that.
But wait.. We haven't
played that school in
a while... so why now?
It's simple... but I'll
explain all the details later.
In short, I found out they were
our adversary... and then...
I just had to stage a rematch.
(surprised)
If we go up against Nekoma
High... he'll change his tune.
[KEISHIN]
(sneeze) Ugh...
[DAICHI]
Great! Looking
forward to it then!
Let's make this practice
game count guys!
[ALL]
Right!
Tokyo, huh?
Those little city boys...
They have no clue what
they're in for!
[KEI]
Did you say "city boys"?
[RYUNOSUKE]
What's it to you, F‐Four‐Eyes?!
(DAICHI awkward laugh)
Hey Daichi.
Hm?
I'm sorry... But I can't
go to the practice game.
What're you talking about?
[SHOYO] Hey! I bet Tokyo
schools are tough!
[YU] Kageyama's a great guy,
[SHOYO] They gotta be right?
[YU] and even though the other
first‐years are kinda rough,
[YU] they're a fun group.
[TOBIO] How should I know?
Just pipe down.
I think with a little
time... this team'll be
something special.
[YU]
I want to play with you guys...
but...
But if I played in the game...
and we were to actually win...
then well it would be like
saying that we don't need
Asahi and I... I just can't.
(surprised)
[YU]
We've been teammates
for so long.
I'm sorry if I'm
being selfish.
Look I get it... But I
still want you to come
to the camp okay.
Hm? You mean it?
(surprised)
[SHOYO]
Hey Noya! That Thunder thing!
Will you show me how to do it?!
Well then?
(unsure)
Huh?
[DAICHI] Have a good night!
[ALL]
See ya!
(TOBIO drinking)
[SHOYO] (drinking) Ahhhh...
Do you think if Asahi
came back, everything
would work out for us?
And what about Noya, huh?
I dunno.
I don't get it...
Sugawara said Asahi's the kind
of guy who feels responsible...
... but I think HE
might feel bad too.
They both feel like what
happened was their fault...
... but it's not like
they can win alone.
[SHOYO]
No way, you don't
get to say that!
What happened to Kageyama's
favorite catchphrase,
anyway huh?!
[SHOYO, imitating TOBIO]
"Receives.. and sets.. AND
spikes...
I'd rather do everything in
the whole game all by myself."
[TOBIO]
Would you just freakin' drop it!
[SHOYO, imitating TOBIO]
"Look at me, I'm a dumb jerk..."
(roar)
(land)
We're all on the same side...
So we should be acting like it.
Huh?
I just wish we got along
better... don't you?
(troubled)
(serious)
Yeah it's nice of you to think
of me and everything.
And I can tell it's important
to you, but I'm not really
interested okay?
Look! If you don't come
back to volleyball club,
the upperclassmen are
never gonna cheer up‐
(gut‐punched) (suffering)
[TOBIO] Do you ever shut up?
(ASAHI laughing)
[ASAHI] You two are funny.
But, listen to me.
[SHOYO] Huh?
I'm sorry but... It's just I've
forgotten what it feels like...
to send the ball through a
wall of blockers. It seems
impossible to me now.
[ASAHI]
I just know I'd fail..
again.
[ASAHI] Just thinking about it
freaks me out and it's just too
much for me right now.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[SHOYO]
Well, this might sound cocky
coming from a first‐year...
but I still think it's
important for me to say it.
Whatever it is you
can tell me okay.
I know what you mean.
[SHOYO SHOYO]
I'm short and I don't
have great technique,
so the blockers used to stop
me all the time... But...
Thanks to Kageyama's amazing
sets I can get past anybody now!
Hmm...
[SHOYO]
The wall just fades away...
...and then the view of
the other side is totally clear!
[ASAHI, internal]
The view... I think I understand
what he's talking about.
[SHOYO]
And once I reach the top
of my jump, the ball hits my
hand...
And when the weight of it,
sorta leaves a sting in my
palm...
I love that!
[ASAHI, internal]
I know that feeling too.
You know... I'm really
jealous of you...
The way things are.. I don't
have the height to clear a
wall.. or the power...
But you've got both! Look
I know you might've had a
rough time in the past...
[SHOYO] ...but you scored a
lot more times than you got
blocked, right?
(ASAHI stunned)
I mean c'mon... That is why
they call you the ace!
(gasp)
(simmering)
(bell ringing)
[TOBIO]
Oh? Let's head back, Hinata...
Hey.. Dude we gotta go.
[SHOYO]
(dazed) (pout)
[TOBIO] Hey uh...
[ASAHI] Hm?
It's impossible to win
all by yourself...
You need the help
of your teammates.
[TOBIO]
I'm still getting used
to that idea myself,
so I can't really talk, but
it's true... See you around.
(courtyard chatter)
[GUY B]
Ready to go?
[GUY C]
Yeah, wanna get some food?
(sneakers squeaking
on the court)
[ASAHI] Ah? Uh...
[SHOYO]
Come on! Gimme another one!
[TOBIO]
Alright, shut up,
I get it! Ready?
[SHOYO]
Yeah!
(gasp)
[SHOYO]
And once I reach the top
of my jump.. the ball hits my
hand...
And when the weight of
it.. sorta leave a sting
in my palm...
[SHOYO]
I love that!
[ASAHI, internal]
I know...
[ASAHI]
I know what he means.
[TOBIO]
I hope Asahi comes back soon.
[SHOYO] He's got chin stubble.
[TOBIO] What?
[SHOYO]
Maybe if I could grow
stubble like that, I'd
be more like an ace!
[SHOYO]
Do you think hair
tonic would help?
[TOBIO]
Who cares, dumbass?!
Next time on Haikyu!!
"A Toss For The Ace."