K‐Kageyama! What are
you plotting?!
Must be
something evil!
What's your problem?!
Yeah, he's not
plotting anything!
I think this is
just the first time
he's ever tried
to smile!
You didn't mean that the
way it sounded, right?
Oh, screw you, Hinata!
Our little grump is finally
showing his feelings!
Time to change it up...
Do you remember
the hand signals?
You ready?
Oh hey, did you hear about
the signals from Sugawara?
Yeah, he told me.
All right!
Let's go all in!
You got it!
[Seijoh Cheer Leader]:
Let's go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
It's been pretty
nerve‐wracking huh?
Trust me, nobody knows
that more than me.
What do you mean?
Up until last year's tournament,
I didn't get to play
in many official games.
You know, because the third‐year
players had all the seniority
and everything... And now
when I have the seniority,
Kageyama actually has more
court experience than I do.
And yet he still lets himself
get all worked up... So weird.
Well... looks like it's
already his turn to serve.
[Kei]:
You think he'll be
able to hold his own?
[Daichi]:
Alright, Kageyama!
[Ryunosuke]:
You got this, bro!
Kageyama looks
happy, doesn't he?
Sure does.
Well, hopefully
that'll be good for us.
[Tadashi]:
What do you mean?
[Koshi]:
I've just been thinking...
every player seems to have
the same sort of pride
when it comes to
being put in a game.
Great players like him
and average joes too.
Kageyama! Don't
stress, okay?
Oh... Nevermind...
He's fine.
We just need one point!
Yeah!
[Hajime]:
Watari!
[Shimada]:
A service ace!
[Takinoue]:
The libero
messed it up!
Now they're tied!
Gotcha!
I'm sorry.
It's okay,
just keep trying!
Up high!
Hm?
Up HIGH!
He wants a high 10!
We did it!
Wait, that's not
the Kageyama I know.
Nope.
[Hajime]:
Someone cover!
They're scattered!
[Akira]:
It's coming back!
It's a chance ball!
"Bring"?
Or "give"?
Which one?
He didn't say anything!
Man, I still can't
believe how crazy
Karasuno's quick‐attack is!
There we go!
Finally turned it around!
Sugawara's nice...
He always compliments me
when I do good things!
[Tobio]:
Hey, Hinata.
Proud... of you...
Thank you...?
Alright, Hinata's really
in his element now!
And Kageyama looks just like
a fish in water out there.
Well his name DOES
mean flying fish...
Oh great.
Hey... let's all relax.
Don't panic and let yourselves
get thrown off like they did.
[Toru]:
Once we gain back a
point, we're golden.
Right!
Hey... you. Stop posing like
that... It pisses me off.
You're not helping!
[Hajime]:
Got it!
[Yutaro]:
Good one, Iwa!
Looks like Kageyama's
gotten his rhythm back...
No, there's more
to it than that.
I should have lined up a bit
closer to the sideline.
[Irihata]:
Before, his focus was
glued on our blockers...
but now he's paying a little
more attention to his teammates.
Don't hold back now, boys...
If we don't take
this set, we're screwed.
Turbo‐charge
that freak quick.
Have some o' this!
Nice receive!
Kageyama told Hinata
that he's only the greatest
whenever he's around.
[Koshi]:
But...
it goes both ways.
Thanks to that combo attack...
they're BOTH the greatest!
Sweet! Our guys made it
to 20 points first!
[Shimada]:
This is the final stretch.
Alright, that's
20 points.
And now...
the real challenge
is about to begin.
Hey, since when
is this all about
Tsukishima versus Kageyama?!
[Daichi]:
C'mon, Hinata!
[Ryunosuke]:
Here goes!
[Hanamaki]:
Look out!
Chance ball!
Nice, Matsu!
Kageyama!
Any thoughts Asahi?
A little higher maybe?
Sure!
[Takinoue]:
Oh. Seijoh's finally
calling time out.
You know, whenever
number 10 goes back
and number 11
goes up front,
Karasuno doesn't do as
many center attacks.
True... Though that might
just be because Kageyama
doesn't like the tall
angry fella.
They weren't communicating
during yesterday's game,
and today isn't
any better...
I think of all Karasuno's
spikers, the beanpole
is the one Kageyama finds the
most difficult to connect with.
Please remind me to never
become friends with you, Oikawa.
Why is that?!
You point out
people's weaknesses.
Oh gimme a break I'm just
trying to strategize here!
[Chikara]:
I think he talks to all the
spikers so he can get a feel
for their emotional state
during the game...
Helps him decide how to set.
Because everyone's different.
What?
I can't read
this guy at all.
All I know is that looking
at him pisses me off!
[Koshi]:
Kageyama.
Just start with
a conversation...
Try to be
more direct.
You need to communicate
with him okay.
Okay.
[Daichi]:
Got it!
[Hajime]:
Nice receive!
They got it...
Watch that counter!
Tsukishima seems to be having
trouble hitting the ball now.
They just
caught up!
Ah crap,
man, we're tied!
It's break time.
I know I need one!
Takeda!
Right!
[Black‐haired Guy]:
So uh... do they need
more attack power or what?
Karasuno's in kind
of a tight spot
now that their number 10's
not up front.
Hey, what's with you guys?!
You need to relax!
Look! You're all doing fine!
So just chill out!
[Ryunosuke]:
Okay...!
[Tobio]:
Hey.
Was that last set decent
enough for you, punk?
Why do you sound like
Tanaka all of a sudden?
What was that, punk?!
I hate your sets because
it's like you're forcing people
to play it your way
instead of their own.
Again with this, Tsukishima?
Come on, this isn't the time to
be bickering like little kids!
What are you saying?
I like to do things my way...
So please be consistent.
Um... what's wrong?
I think... whenever Kageyama
sets an A‐Quick for Tsukishima,
he's also signaling
its hitting course.
[Keishin]:
A position near the
setter means cross‐court.
And away is
turn‐swing.
Obviously, Kageyama
places the ball
wherever he thinks the
spike should be going.
But Tsukishima probably
has a hard time
hitting anything
like that.
You're not the only one out
there thinking, you know.
[Kei]:
Whether it's about
defense formation
or deciding what
attacks to use,
everyone on the team
is always thinking.
Hinata was able to figure out
how to do those quick attacks.
So even that poor dummy is
out there using his brain...
Well maybe not
that much.
Did you say "not much"?!
I think all the time, jerk!
Now, now...
That's fair.
Wait, what did you
just say? Are you sick?
Let's try it your way...
Maybe it'll work out for us.
Tsukishima must not
be used to dealing
with that kind of directness.
He doesn't know how to take it.
[Ryunosuke]:
Good job, Noya!
I like to do things my way...
So please be consistent.
Dammit!
Y'see that?! He hit the empty
zone right behind the block!
[Hisashi]:
That was kickass!
I'm actually kinda jealous!
I thought he was going to spike
it at the last second.
He's almost got
a glow about him
when he gets past
the blockers, huh?
A glow?
Uh‐huh, that's how Tsukki looks
when he's really into the game.
Chance ball!
Another trick!
[Hajime]:
That was close!
[Daichi]:
Heads up! Chance ball!
That Number 11's
got game.
I guess so...
but it looks like he's just
trying to avoid confrontation
with Seijoh's
high‐block.
You're right, Karasuno
keeps creating diversions.
[Black‐haired Guy]:
Yeah well... He can't run
from those blockers forever.
Yeah!
[Toru]:
Nice, Matsu!
Dammit... they already
took it back.
[Hajime]:
Center, 11!
Again? I'll
get it this time!
[Hajime]:
Nice receive, Watari!
[Toru]:
I've got it!
[Yutaro]:
Center!
[Daichi]:
Good work, Tanaka!
Ah, dammit
They better be
careful right here.
This play will
make or break it.
[Shimada]:
It's up to the ace.
[Kei]:
Everyone on the team
is always thinking.
Number 11 again!
No, wait! Don't move!
Stay where you are!
Yeah!
AWW YEAH!
Tsukishima, you
magnificent bastard!
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice one!
[Kei]:
Get out of my face.
We were anticipating
a fakeout,
so our defense was too far
forward... They got us.
Uh.. gugu...
gugu... good job...
Don't hurt
yourself, Kageyama.
Wow... He actually
complimented Tsukishima.
Kageyama is changing,
no doubt about it.
What are you,
emotionally constipated?!
[Spectator 1]:
Set point for Karasuno!
[Spectator 2]:
This is crazy.
One more point!
You can do it!
Not gonna happen!
I‐wai‐zu‐mi! I‐wai‐zu‐mi!
Geeet thaaaat POINT!
[Takeda]:
It's alright! Look... the
last point is no different
than all the others you've
scored; you can win!
[Chairman]:
Well done!
[Hajime]:
Our last tournament.
The end of middle school.
Hey, you have a
genuine smile for once.
What? My smiles are always
honest and delightful!
If you have to SAY they are,
that means they're probably not.
I've never gotten
one of these before...
so why wouldn't
I be happy, huh?
[Hajime]:
Toru Oikawa laughs everything
off... but there was a time
when he couldn't do that.
He had a sturdy build.
Plus he was smart and swift.
And he just kept getting
better and better,
especially after middle school.
But still, there was always a
brick wall standing in his way.
Shiratorizawa, now known
as the best in the prefecture,
had just brought in Ushiwaka,
their new heavy.
Why can't
I beat them?!
[Hajime]:
They cleaned the floor with us.
We didn't even win a set.
We wanted to keep climbing
and reach new heights...
but we kept getting defeated
until our third year...
And then...
I'm Tobio Kageyama from
Akiyama Elementary School...
I've played this game
for years... Nice to meet you.
A genius swooped in
to take our place.
There was no mistaking
his overwhelming talent.
Kageyama always
looked so overjoyed
just to be playing volleyball.
His fire and his
technical expertise put him
miles ahead of the rest of us.
[Kita‐ichi Supervisor]:
He can play just about any
position we need him to,
but he'll eventually
be a setter.
[Kita‐ichi Coach]:
Yeah.
[Hajime]:
After that, Oikawa started to
push himself harder than ever.
You're working
way too hard!
Didn't the coach just
say that yesterday?
[Hajime]:
You'll be useless
to us if you get hurt!
Come on, it's time
to call it a day!
He was completely
losing his cool.
During a practice game, his
constant combo mistakes
made it clear he was
lacking composure.
Which led to...
[Kita‐ichi Coach]:
Kageyama, you're in!
[Tobio]:
Sir!
[Referee]:
Okay. Go in.
Forward!
Got it!
[Kita‐ichi #22]:
Nice cover!
[Hajime]:
Nice kill!
[Kita‐ichi #22]:
Serve's up!
[Tobio]:
Oikawa?
Can you maybe teach
me how to serve?
[Toru]:
Get away from me...
Go away...
Just go away!
Don't come any closer!
Get a hold of yourself,
you dumbass!
Sorry...
[Hajime]:
Kageyama. We're all
done for today.
[Tobio]:
O‐Okay.
[Hajime]:
We swapped you out today because
you needed to cool your head.
Give yourself a
little credit, alright?!
I can't do that!
Not if I'm not good enough to
bring down Shiratorizawa!
If I want to win and go to
Nationals, I need to work
as hard as I can!
All you ever say
is "me, me, me"!
What, do you think you're
the only person on this team?!
You listen to me, dumbass!
You'd better stop acting like
YOUR performance is the only
thing that matters or I'll
headbutt you IN THE FACE!
You already did!
I'm sure none of us has what
it takes to defeat Ushiwaka
one‐on‐one... But still...
That's why there's 6 people
on a volleyball court!
Who cares about that amazing
first‐year... or Ushiwaka?!
At the end of the day, the best
team of 6 wins, dumbass!
The best group
of 6 wins, huh?
(chuckles)
Whoa... Sorry, I must
have hit you too hard.
I can't even describe
how I feel right now.
It's like I'm invincible.
[Toru]:
Hey Iwa, is "dumbass"
the only insult you know?
[Hajime]:
You want another headbutt
to the face?
[Toru]:
Perfect! One more point!
[Kita‐ichi Coach]:
How about that? Oikawa seems
to be over his funk now.
[Kita‐ichi Supervisor]:
Good.
Hey, Oikawa... could you
teach me how to serve‐toss?
Yeah right, in
your dreams, dummy!
Stop picking on
the first‐year, Oikawa.
[Hajime]:
In our last middle
school tournament...
we won the first set against
Shiratorizawa Middle School.
We ended up winning
2nd place to them.
Oikawa got the
best setter award.
[Toru]:
Second place... That means our
spikers gave it their very best.
[Hajime]:
Yeah, but it also means
Ushiwaka's even better.
Damn it...
I'll beat him...
I swear I will!
I'll humiliate
that whole team!
Yeah, same here!
And you too dummy!
I don't know what high school
you'll be at in a few years...
but I swear, as soon as I get a
chance, I'm kicking your ass,
you hear me?!
Don't talk all big
with a runny nose.
You need a tissue?
Shut up!
[Seijoh Cheer Leader]:
Let's go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
[Daichi]:
Let's go!
[Hajime]:
Serve!
[Hanamaki]:
Heads up!
Uh‐oh, time for
Oikawa's serve.
You're up against the guy
who's second on your shit‐list.
So make it count, alright?
Oh, I plan to.
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
YOURS!
There it goes!
[Takinoue]:
Crap, it's heading
right back to Seijoh!
If he'd messed
up that serve,
it would've cost them the
whole set! This guy's good!
It's a chance ball!
[Kei]:
It came right back
to the setter.
The quick attacks
from the center
give them a higher
success rate.
[Tobio]:
I knew it; that's
exactly what I would do!
Oikawa's back's
against the wall,
so I'm guessing
his next move is...
...send it to Iwa!
Yeah!
No way!
Karasuno just
took back the set!
Dammit, I'll kill
that little shit!
Chill out.
Hey, what's so funny, jerk?!
You wanna fight or somethin'?!
Violence doesn't
look good on you, Iwa.
[Hajime]:
Relax. I only threaten YOU,
and you know I won't hit you.
You know...
that last quick from the center
was one of our best attacks.
Yeah?
Yet Kageyama was
able to stop it.
[Toru]:
He predicted I
would send it left.
Do you know what
that means?
He wasn't behaving
robotically like usual...
No, he noticed our
weak spot near the end...
not to mention our
unbreakable bond of trust.
We don't have that
and you know it.
[Toru]:
My point is, he just made
a solid judgment call.
That other setter...
What did he teach our Tobio?
That little self‐serving
dictator is on his way
to becoming a REAL leader.
What is this feeling? I'm
incredibly irritated, and yet...
Set 3! It's time to start!
Let's do this.
[Hajime]:
Time for the final set!
[Toru]:
I'm fired up!
This isn't like me at all.
[Hajime]:
Yeah, I'll say.
[Toru]:
What about my icy‐cool image?
[Hajime]:
Forget about your damn image!
Next Haikyu!!
"The Play to Change The Flow."