One more time!
As soon as he hits
the peak of his jump...
the ball needs
to meet his palm!
Now I just take aim...
and swing!
[Shoyo]:
(grunts)
Damn. I sent it
a little too high!
(growls)
Thanks, Captain!
Nice job
covering Daichi!
[Yaku]:
It's in!
[Yamamoto]:
Front!
Nice one Inuoka!
Over here!
Here you go!
Ready to block, Hinata?
One, two, three...
Gotcha!
[Inuoka]:
Smooth cover, Kai!
Wow... Both of these teams
have got some pretty
diligent worker bees,
don't they?
They're not flashy, but they
make themselves indispensable.
In the end, they can
make or break a game.
Kenma! One more
over here!
I don't care who says
our offense is no better
than average...
I'm the ace of Nekoma!
That's our point!
Dammit!
Look at that! Yamamoto's
especially enthusiastic today!
I wonder if he's fired up
because there's a player
on their side who
reminds him of himself.
[Nekomata]:
Or maybe he's inspired
by that vicious rivalry
between Inuoka and
that Number 10?
What's wrong with
Hinata and Kageyama?
Their attacks
aren't lining up.
Because they're doing those
crazy combo attacks where
Kageyama synchronizes with
Hinata's movements...
but now they're
trying to excecute
normal quick
attacks instead.
Look, you have to stop
tensing up like that, alright?
[Keishin]:
Hinata needs to work
It's slowing down
all your timing.
Right.
And the only
is conditioning
through repetition.
But if he gets the training
and he learns when to use
both kinds of attacks,
then eventually...
They won't be a demon
and his iron club anymore.
[Nekomata]:
They'll be a demon and a demon!
[Yamamoto]:
Serve's up!
Aw, crap! Should I hit
it over or underhanded?
Ugh!
Noya, cover!
Aw yeah! The ace might
come through in a pinch...
but he's not the only
one! Leave it to me!
Hyaaaaa! Gah!
Whoa!
They never
stood a chance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, YEAHHHH!
I'm not gonna get shut down
either! I can do this!
[Daichi]:
Hinata...
Kageyama said not
to tense up, remember?
Keep your
eyes open.
Y‐Yes, sir!
(whistle)
[Yaku]:
Fukunaga!
The buzzcut guy's moving
this way! A quick attack!
Keep your
eyes open.
[Shoyo]:
What's number 7 doing?
Nice one‐touch!
A chance ball!
Huh?
He's quick!
[Koshi]:
Nekoma's number 7's fast, too!
It's amazing to me
how two opponents
can influence each
other in moments like this.
[Nekomata]:
Each one continually
pushes the other
to new levels of power.
That makes them
"worthy adversaries".
He made
it through!
He did it!
Oh, heck yeah!
Grr... That was
still too high.
One more!
Haaaaaaa!
YEAH!
(growls)
[Koshi]:
Uh‐oh... If we're not careful,
they might beat us to 20.
It's your serve, Inuoka!
Okay!
So when Lanky McSpikehead
goes to the back row,
then Rooster Top
comes to the front...
I liked playing
with Lanky, but...
This guy's
kinda scary.
Inuoka's about 8 inches
taller than you are
and you still gave him
a run for his money...
Not too bad, Small Fry.
Ack!
[Shoyo]:
Who you callin'
Small Fry, Small Fry?!
[Tobio]:
C'mere.
Ah! Hey, lemme go!
We are going to do
the usual move, now.
What? You mean the
super hard‐hitting one?
That's right.
Aw... Can't we stick
with the soft one?
I was just starting
to get used to it...
[Tobio]:
Forget it. We can't do that
with him on the front row.
Why can't we?
Because I said, alright?!
It's a hunch.
[Yaku]:
Put it over!
[Team Karasuno]:
(Cheering)
Hah!
Awesome!... I never get
tired of that feeling!
That was a smart
choice just now.
Hey, that's
my bad, guys...
[Keishin]:
With that third‐year middle
Hey, don't worry
about it, man!
special quick attack
is more effective.
If they'd gone with a normal
quick attack, a skilled player
like that would've shut
it down without batting an eye.
Okay, I'm the next one
to serve!
[Keishin]:
If you looked up
Make sure it stays
in bounds this time.
I bet you anything you'd
see that kid's picture.
Y‐You don't have
to tell me that!
But that's alright.
We can catch up.
[Ryunosuke]:
Go for it, Hinata!
[Yamamoto]:
Nice receive!
Oh wow look at that...
Everyone's all jumbled up!
Who's it
gonna be?
They should leave it to their
most powerful attacker Number 4!
Haaaaaa!
A back
row attack!
The front three were a decoy!
They just shook off
all our blockers!
That's a
chance ball!
Who's gonna get it?
An A‐Quick!
Wow...
[Team Nekoma]:
Yeah!
That was pretty
quick, alright.
Would you look at that?
That attack has got
first‐rate stability.
[Yamamoto]:
Sweet, it's my
serve this time!
[Keishin]:
[Yaku]:
Make it a good one!
Hah!
Ah jeez.. Cover!
I'm open!
Asahi!
Who's gonna
attack next?!
Another A‐Quick?!
He's not jumping!
[Team Nekoma]:
(cheers)
Grr...
What kind of
move was that?
That's called a delayed spike...
You pretend that you're
gonna jump for a quick.
[Keinshin]:
It throws off
the blocker's timing.
That kind of attack has
been out of popularity
for a long time though...
I gotta admit I'm impressed
they thought to throw that one
in right after their A‐Quick.
Excellent!
[Keinshin]:
Not bad.
[Takinoue]:
Nekoma made it to 20 points.
They're just 5 points
away from taking it.
Son of a...
I've already used up both our
timeouts and everything.
(smug laugh)
(smug chuckle)
Is that sneaky
bastard laughing at me?!
[Takeda]:
It's crazy. Ever since their
number 1 rotated to the front
it would appear the proficiency
of all their attacks
has been
through the roof.
[Keishin]:
That's true...
But look at it this way;
with half of our lineup
being first‐years,
you might consider us
a level 1 team...
Let's give 'em hell, Yamamoto!
By that standard, Nekoma's a
good 10 or 20 levels higher.
[Yamamoto]:
Yeah!
[Takeda]:
In other words...
they're a full‐grown
adult feline,
and we're a baby birdie
fresh out of the nest.
[Keishin]:
Exactly.
Good metaphor.
They've got a perfect balance
of offense and defense...
There's no way
we can compete.
Least not today. So...
Guess that means...
[Keishin]:
All we can do is persist!
Hit 'em with our full power
and don't let up!
So you want us to beat 'em
into submission, boss?!
Wow, that really makes us
sound like the bad guys.
Wahahaha!
What's so bad about
being the bad guys?!
We'll be just like the crows
perched on the gates to Hell.
Could you please stop that,
Coach, you're freaking me out!
Our attacks and receives
may be sloppy...
but we're gonna
make this happen!
Thes're the weapons
we've got right now,
so use 'em
the best you can!
[Keishin]:
Hit 'em with all the
artillery we've got!
Hit 'em! Hit 'em...
Hit 'em hard!
Grr!
That was great!
Nice block, Tsukishima!
Keep it up, Tsukki!
[Yamamoto]:
It's okay, Inuoka.
[Inuoka]:
Sorry...
Karasuno catchin' up
to 'em, now.
Yeah, it's pretty close;
the mood of the game
has changed entirely.
(whistle)
Anybody gettin'
scared, yet?
Nope!
Good to hear it...
You just keep that ball in play.
[Team Nekoma]:
Yes, sir!
(whistle)
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Okay! Just one
more point to tie!
Okay you guys
keep it up!
Can't let 'em
score any more.
Right!
[Team Nekoma]:
(cheering)
[Takeda]:
Oh no!
This wasn't supposed to happen!
They've got match point!
[Kuroo]:
One more point!
[Yamamoto]:
Yeah!
Dammit...
[Keishin]:
look at 'em, they
haven't even flinched!
I guess we're not much
of a threat to them are we?
[Takeda]:
It's alright!
We're still sharp.
We can do this.
Aw yeah! We clawed
our way up to a tie!
Don't get too
excited, pal!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Grr...
Things might get a
little trickier now that
their Number 3's
in the front row.
Our crucial middle blockers are
working at a hundred percent.
Come on guys,
get ready!
[Keishin]:
Hinata's got the
to score points around
their blocker...
and Asahi's our top player
when it comes to offense.
With the two of them
in the front row...
this is the perfect chance
to turn this game around!
If we can get a point right now,
then it's a deuce.
You're right...
Then they'd have to score
another point, giving us time
to turn the tables!
[Takeda]:
It all depends
on this ball!
Nice receive!
Hinata's quick attacks are
still shaky. What do I do...?
Come on!
Aw, I thought
we had it for sure!
Hold on...
Here it comes!
It's a chance ball!
Agh! My bad,
you guys!
Direct spike, Asahi!
No way!
Do it, Asahi!
Yah!
They got
it again!
Oh no! It's Karasuno's
chance ball again!
That's how it goes.
Huh?
You can make mistakes...
in fact, you can fail
to make an attack at all...
[Nekomata]:
but as long as that ball doesn't
hit the floor, you can't lose.
It's a chance ball!
Hinata's so
amped right now...
it's just like when
I first met him.
[Tobio]:
He's intense,
larger‐than‐life...
There's nothing
he wants more
than the ball out
in front of him.
Well, here it comes!
That was it!
The truth is, it's
not that whoever has
the best abilities, wins.
It's that whoever lets the ball
fall down on their side, loses.
(final whistle)
[Nekomata]:
And that... is what it means
to keep the ball in play.
[Team Nekoma]:
We win!
We didn't make any mistakes
the whole time...
and we hit them with
the best weapons we have.
But still...
we couldn't beat 'em.
Nice one, big guy!
That's our setter for ya!
[Keishin]:
Those Nekoma kids have
instead of as individuals.
They deserve this win.
[Shoyo]:
One more time!
(shocked gasps)
Another game!
Huh?
[Shoyo]:
Please!
Sure! I was
planning on it.
It wouldn't be a practice game
if it wasn't followed
by a rematch
or two.
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice one!
[Kuroo]:
Let's go!
[Yu]:
One more!
(whistle)
[Keishin]:
Alright, NOW we've been
thrashed without a doubt.
Yeah we should
probably call it a day.
[Takeda]:
Look how tired they are.
One more match!
Again?! You haven't stopped
moving since you got here;
where'd you get
all that energy?!
Give 'em a rest, ginger!
If they stay, they're
gonna miss the last train!
[Daichi/Kuroo]:
Circle up!
Actually... your Coach Ukai's
grandfather and I have been
You kids really have some
talent, don't you?
acquainted for a very long
time. We used to play practice
I thought we almost had you
for a second there...
games with Karasuno
every chance we got.
I gotta say... Nekomata's
trained you guys well.
It was always a pretty
But then...
Retiring?
[Ukai]:
Yeah, I'm afraid
old age is starting
to catch up with me.
Sorry, my friend.
That's too bad...
But hey... either way, I'm sure
we won't be too hard up
for opponents
for practice games.
[Nekomata]:
The thing about rivals is...
a good one is hard to find.
Poor old Ukai... After he
retired, I heard that he
starting to have
some serious health problems...
and I was certain Karasuno would
never make a comeback from that.
[Nekomata]:
But you kids have got more
potential than I thought,
especially with your offense.
That Number 9 and Number 10
combo is something else.
That attack's gonna
be difficult to beat.
Those left players of yours
are a couple of powerhouses too.
It all comes down to how long
you keep the ball in play.
Right!
[Nekomata]:
You need a lot more practice
working together as a team,
but you've all got
outstanding promise.
With the appropriate
training, you should be able
to improve by
leaps and bounds.
Seeing that really
does my old heart good.
[Nekomata]:
I'm glad to have a worthy rival.
We'll see you again
at the Nationals.
[Nekomata]:
In that shining,
sprawling gymnasium
packed with thousands
of cheering spectators...
amidst the whirl of
excitement and intensity.
The ultimate
trashcan showdown...
The real "cats versus
crows" faceoff!
Yes, sir!
[Keishin]:
Alright! Let's get
all this stuff put away!
Right!
You little turd!
Y‐yeah, YOU are!
[Daichi]:
Come on, let's pick up the pace!
[Yamamoto]:
Hey!
Yeah? What the hell
do you want, dirtbag?!
You lookin' to get
yourself dealt with?!
Come on at me,
city boy!
Actually... it's uh...
the thing is...
Huh?
Your... Your manager...
Could you maybe, like...
Could you tell me what
your manager's name is?
A‐choo.
Grrr.... You son of aaahh!
You stay away from her...
She is our manager!
If you even
LOOK at her...
I'll yank that ugly lint
brush right out of your skull!
Don't worry... I'm too much
of a coward to talk to her.
[Kuroo]:
Fukunaga, could you
mop over there?
[Fukunaga]:
Got it.
[Kuroo]:
Yaku, you mop, too.
[Yaku]:
Okay...
[Ryunosuke]:
Kiyoko.
Her name is Kiyoko Shimizu.
That's perfect!... Her name
means "clear spring water"!
Yeah, it really does
suit her, doesn't it?
It took me a long time
to work up the guts, too,
so I know how you feel,
but...! Check this out...
You want her to flat‐out
ignore you... It's awesome.
Hwaaaaaa!
No way, man! I don't think
I can handle that!
(hearty laugh)
You know something?...
You're not so bad, brother!
Huh? Yeah, same to you.
I'm uh... Taketora Yamamoto.
And I'm
Ryunosuke Tanaka.
Heh.
How long have you been
playing volleyball?
Who taught you how to play?
How long have you been a setter?
Did you come up with
that feint yourself?
Have you been training?
Have you ever hit a brick wall?
If so, what did
you do about it?
He's growly and scary
like a saber‐tooth tiger!
That's who
he meant.
That was incredible, Shoyo!
"Swoosh!" "Vroom!" "Pow!"
Oh, I'm Inuoka, first‐year!
And you're really tall,
but you ran fast like "zoom!"
And then "kaboom!"
You were so cool when
you were like "blam!"
So were you!
It was like "sha‐ping!"
Thanks! And I'VE never seen
anybody "fwop!" like that!
It wasn't like "fwop!"
It was more like a DA‐DOOOM!
[Shoyo]:
Don't you think?
Do you... understand that?
[Kuroo]:
Nah, they sound like
a couple of toddlers.
But you know... maybe YOU should
try goofing off once in a while
instead of
acting all stoic.
That's not one
of my strong suits.
You sound like
an old man.
I‐I'm so sorry! I should
have been moving faster!
W‐wait, what are
you apologizing for?
This was all my fault;
please forgive me!
[Asahi]:
Just calm down...
Great, he's scaring
the first years...
They can't see
what a softie he is.
In a way, they uh...
Kinda look like
father and son
from here, huh?
More like a scared kid
and his kidnapper.
Um... why is your
libero staring at me?
Oh, sorry...
Maybe if you just try
to avert your eyes,
[Yu]:
Hey! I thought your
receives were really great!
he'll leave you alone‐
Our team's ace
is pretty strong...
And I've never
seen anybody actualy
retrieve spikes
from him before.
Your team has killer receiving
skills And a lot of that is
[Yu]:
because you have so much
talent as a libero!
So well done!
But I won't lose next time!
Count on it!
Ah! Hey.. wait!
Let him respond!
Um... sorry, he's
kind of intense.
He's dangerous.
Huh?
[Yaku]:
He's got lots of skill
as a libero too,
but he doesn't let
himself get any rest.
He just keeps going,
looking onward and upward.
So he's a threat.
[Takeda]:
Coach Nekomata!
Thank you for making such
a long trip to play with us.
Not at all,
it was my pleasure.
(chuckles)
[Nekomata]:
I'm sure it's hard to get
someone to play practice games
with when you don't
have connections.
You had my phone ringing off the
hook! And at one point you even
threatened to come
irritate me in person!
I‐I'm sorry!
Anyway... enthusiasm
breeds more enthusiasm.
You don't have much
experience, yet...
but if you keep your
nose to the grindstone,
and the kids'll
follow you.
[Nekomata]:
Good work.
Thank you so much, sir!
(whimpering)
I want to see you get it
together, too, Keishin...
After all, we played
three games today
and you didn't take
a single set.
Then next time we play,
I'll kick your ass
in EVERY set, old man.
Ooooh?... Is that so? Well,
I think you're full of hot air.
[Naoi]:
P‐please don't
provoke him, Coach...
[Nekomata]:
It's his own fault he looks
just like his gramps!
[Naoi]:
That makes no sense!
[Takeda]:
Uh hang on!
I thought you said you'd
only stay on as coach
for the Nekoma game‐
You expect me to take
that lying down?!
I'll get revenge in a big venue
with a crowd watching!
We'll be reunited soon, comrade!
Okay... that's weird.
Yeah I know...
Just don't look.
(laughs)
(chuckles)
You won't win
next time.
Oh really? Because
I think I will.
Cut it out;
you're being weird!
The next practice game
isn't gonna go down like that!
Good, otherwise it's not
much of a practice game, is it?!
Not them
too!
Come on,
really?!
[Shoyo]:
Kenma!
Shoyo.
When I first met you
on the street...
you said you didn't really like
volleyball that much, right?
Oh... Yeah.
[Shoyo]:
How about now? Didn't it
feel good to win?
[Kenma]:
Eh... it was the
same as always.
Next time...
I'll make you want to win really
bad... and then WE'LL win!
And then... You'll say "Man that
was a blast! I hate losing!"
And the way you talk about
the game'll change for good.
Cool... Well...
I'll be waiting.
If that had been
a real match...
We'd have been done...
as soon as we lost that
first game... That's it.
Yeah, I know.
It's good to know
you've thought about it.
Huh?
We DO have a real
game coming up...
The Inter‐High
Preliminaries, remember?
Now let's hurry
back home...
We need to do some
serious thinking
about today's
practice game.
Then we get
back to work!
Yes, sir!
[Koshi]:
By the way, Kageyama,
did you ask their setter
about that technique where
he feints with his eyes?
[Tobio]:
No.
[Koshi]:
Awww...
were you too shy to talk
to him or what?
[Tobio]:
What did you
say to me?!
[Koshi]:
[Tobio]:
Next Haikyu!!
"The Tough Opponents"!