[SHOYO]
Kay! See ya later!
[NATSU] Bye Shoyo...
[SHOYO] (panting)
[SHOYO]
We play Nekoma in four days.
And I've got new allies!
[SHOYO]
That spiker... and that
receiver are both on my side!
[SHOYO]
This'll be great!
I better hurry...
It's time for
training camp! Ah‐hahaaa!
(SHOYO nervous)
[TEACHER]
Mister Hinata... Need a
bathroom break? You can go.
(SHOYO embarrassed)
(STUDENTS laughing)
[KEISHIN] Everybody here?
[ALL] Yessir!
[KEISHIN]
We've got four days until the
practice game against Nekoma,
and after that, it'll be
time for the Inter‐High
preliminaries.
[KEISHIN]
Time is short... but we've got
a whole lot of stuff to fix.
If you sad sacks expect
to win, there's only one
thing we can do.
[KEISHIN]
Practice, practice, practice.
I want you to keep
retrieving 'til you puke!
[SHOYO] Right!
[RYUNOSUKE KOSHI TOBIO]
(internal) Well, that means
Hinata's done his job.
[KEISHIN]
Forward!
(TADASHI fumble)
Hey! How many times are
you gonna let me score
on you?! Get serious!
[TADASHI]
(determined) One more!
[KEISHIN]
Get ready!
[DAICHI] Nice receive!
[SHOYO] Good job!
[KIYOKO]
That's five for him...
Time to switch out.
[KEISHIN]
Next!
I'm ready whenever you are!
[KEISHIN]
Good. Alright now let's
work on a few spikes!
[ALL]
Right!
[RYUNOSUKE]
(battle cry)
[SIDELINES]
Nice kill!
[SIDELINES] Nice kill!
[TOBIO] Way to go, guys!
[KEISHIN]
Whoaaaa!
Yeaaah!
[KEISHIN]
Those spikes are
lookin' good, guys!
[KOSHI]
Huh?
[TADASHI]
Um... do you mind if I go next?
[KOSHI]
Oh! Sure!
[DAICHI]
Alright... let's
pack it up guys.
[ALL]
Yessir!
[SHOYO]
Uh? Wow! So this
is training camp!
[SHOYO] (extreme delight)
[TOBIO]
Is it really all
that exciting?
Of course it is! I've never
been to a training camp!
It's just a bunch of loud,
disgusting guys in your face
all day every day...
What's so fun about that?
[RYUNOSUKE] You take
that back right now!
(KEI annoyed)
[YU]
Yeah, any place within
a quarter‐mile radius
of our gorgeous Kiyoko
is automatically pure
and beautiful!
This air's as fresh as
a morning in spring!
And if your senses are so
dull you can't smell it,
I feel sorry for you!
Kiyoko lives right by here...
She goes home whenever
the day's over.
[TAKEDA]
(startled) Should I even
ask what you're doing?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Take... we can't go on...
Goodbye sweet world! Ah?!
Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE YU]
(adoration)
[SHOYO]
(glee)
[ALL]
Thanks for the fooo‐oood!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
(ravenous eating)
[KIYOKO]
Does anybody want seconds?
[RYUNOSUKE YU]
Yes please, Kiyoko!
[KIYOKO]
(startled) Wow.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Okay... The bath's open for
the first‐years now. Hm?
What's wrong, Hinata?
[SHOYO]
Hey.
There's somebody here...
It's a stranger.
Whatever... Don't be ridiculous.
[RYUNOSUKE]
We're the only ones here‐
[SHOYO]
It's... a child.
(RYUNOSUKE stunned)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nah.. you're seeing things...
I'm sure you just walked past a
mirror and saw your reflection.
[SHOYO]
Yeah, you're right. That'd
be silly... It's nothing.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh‐huh. You've gotta be uh...
just imagining things...
[RYUNOSUKE SHOYO]
(scream) Huh?
[YU]
Uh what's with all the racket?
Daichi's gonna get angry y'know.
[RYUNOSUKE]
(stunned) It's just
Noya, you idiot.
[SHOYO]
Whoa... It IS him!
But he shrank...
[SHOYO]
Maybe the ghosts made him
shorter!
[SHOYO] (panic)
[RYUNOSUKE] (laughing)
Is that why you have spiky hair,
so you look tall?! Bahaha!
[YU]
Dammit, Tanakaaa!
Don't make fun of me or I swear‐
(startled)
[ASAHI]
You should keep your voices
down. Daichi might hear you‐
[SHOYO RYUNOSUKE YU]
(scared) (scream)
[ASAHI]
Huh. Guys, it's just me, Asahi!
[DAICHI]
All of you, shut up! Shut UP!
(SHOYO receive)
[KEISHIN]
What are you, a windmill?
Move your hands AND your feet!
[SHOYO]
Yes sir! One more!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice, Hinata!
[KIYOKO]
That's his fifth one.
[KEISHIN]
Good, that should be everybody.
[KEISHIN] Time to
run some laps, guys!
[ALL] Yes sir!
[TOBIO] Pick up the pace dude.
[TAKEDA] They sure are full of
energy.
[TAKEDA] They even
practice during lunch.
[SHOYO] Jeez, I'm going!
[KEISHIN]
Yeah, I noticed that too..
Kageyama gets started early
doesn't he?
[TAKEDA]
Right... And Hinata's been doing
the same thing...
He said he needs to do that here
since he's not going over the
mountains like he used to.
[KEISHIN]
The mountains, huh? That would
explain all that stamina.
[TAKEDA]
On a different note...
Are you having some trouble
choosing the starters?
Well just the setter...
I'm stuck.
[KEISHIN]
If we're talking raw power, it's
gotta be Kageyama...
Now you've got Sugawara who's
built up experience
from playing alongside the ace
ever since his first year...
[KEISHIN]
...but still, Kageyama's
got enough talent
right out of the gate
to make up for all that.
[KEISHIN]
Then again, Sugawara's been
around for a while...
...so he's probably already got
the trust of his teammates.
[TAKEDA]
But that's not really the
heart of the issue, is it?
So could it be that...
...you're having trouble
deciding because Sugawara's
a third‐year?
(KEISHIN surprised)
[TAKEDA]
Your last year in high
school is special.
I can see why you would want
to take that into account.
[TAKEDA]
Ah! I'm sorry! I think
I'm overstepping...
[KEISHIN]
No, you're probably right.
You know... When I was in high
school,
the only time I got to be in
the starting lineup was when
the official setter
‐ who was younger
than me ‐ got hurt.
[KEISHIN]
Back then, I was just angry that
I never got the opportunity for
three whole years...
But now... as a coach, even a
temporary one... I shouldn't be
thinking like a player. It's not
right.
[SHOYO] (dramatic
running groans)
(TOBIO running) (speed up)
[DAICHI]
Hinata!‐ Stop yelling like a
madman; you're gonna need to
save that energy for the game!
[TOBIO]
Whoa, where are you going?!
(SHOYO grunting and screaming)
Huh?
[SHOYO]
Nobody's back there. Is this
path... the wrong way?
(meowing)
Huh?
[SHOYO, internal]
A red uniform?
What school is that from?
[SHOYO]
Hey, whatcha up to?
[KENMA]
Huh? Oh...
Well, it's just..
uh... I'm lost.
[SHOYO]
You're lost? Are you
from out of town?
[KENMA]
Mm‐hm.
[SHOYO]
Is that a fun game?
[KENMA]
Uh... Not really...
I'm uh just trying
to pass the time.
[SHOYO]
Oh...
Hey! Do you play too?!
[KENMA]
Huh?
Those volleyball shoes!
In your bag!
[KENMA]
Oh. Yeah.
[SHOYO]
Shoyo Hinata! So...
What's your name?
[KENMA]
Kozume.
[SHOYO]
Kozume? Is that your first name?
[KENMA]
No, it's... it's Kenma.
[SHOYO] So are you...
in high school?
[KENMA] Yeah.
[SHOYO] What's your year?
I'm a first‐year!
[KENMA] Second.
[SHOYO]
Oh crap, so you're my
upperclassman! I'm so sorry!
[KENMA]
It's okay... After all... that
age‐based hierarchy stuff that
comes with sports... it's lame.
[SHOYO]
Oh... you think? Uh, so,
do you like volleyball?
[KENMA]
Eh... It's fine... I can't say I
really care.
[KENMA]
I don't mind it or anything...
but I'm not big on getting all
worn out.
But uh... my friend likes to
play...
and he needs me...
so I play too.
[SHOYO]
Oh. Well once you get used to
it... I'm sure you'll like
volleyball too.
[KENMA]
Whatever... I'm only playing
it while I'm in high school.
[SHOYO]
Yeah, what position?
[KENMA]
Uh... I'm a setter.
[SHOYO]
Really?! You're a lot different
than the setter we've got.
[SHOYO]
He's really growly and scary
like a saber‐tooth tiger! Grr...
[KENMA] Oh.
[SHOYO]
I'm a middle blocker by the way!
[KENMA]
Cool.
Oh... but you probably think
that's a little weird...
Shorter guys don't usually
play that position.
[KENMA] Nah, I don't think
that's weird... Not at all.
(SHOYO surprised)
[KENMA]
People say a lot of stuff about
me whenever I go to a game, too.
You know, things like, "I
thought the setter was supposed
to be the team member with the
strongest abilities...
so why did they ever pick
this guy of all people?"
[KENMA]
You see... I'm not all that much
of an athletic person.
[SHOYO]
Oh... So does your school have
a good volleyball team or what?
[KENMA]
Hmm... I don't know...
Apparently it used to be good
and then it went downhill.
[KENMA]
But as of recently...
I would say, it's pretty good.
[SHOYO]
Hang on... What school is‐
[KUROO]
Hey Kenma!
(surprised)
[KENMA]
Kuroo.
[KENMA] Gotta go.
(SHOYO surprised)
[KENMA]
Later... okay?
[KUROO]
You shouldn't wander off.
[KENMA] Sorry.
[KUROO] You don't know
your way around here.
[SHOYO]
Later?
[KOSHI] Ah! Hey Hinata!
(SHOYO startled)
[KOSHI]
We were looking
all over for you.
[SHOYO]
Sorry Suga! I didn't realize
I went the wrong way.
[KOSHI]
You always give it your all,
no matter what kind of
practice we're doing.
[SHOYO]
Yeah. But I've still got
a really long way to go.
Huh?
[SHOYO]
There's a lot of things I need
to improve on.
[SHOYO]
I mean, yeah, it kinda
gets on my nerves
that no one sees me as anything
but half of a pair with
Kageyama...
but it's better than not
playing at all, right?
[SHOYO]
I want to stay on the court
the longest.
Huh?
[KOSHI]
So do I. All I want is to play
volleyball...
That's why... I do whatever
it takes to be my best.
[KOSHI]
C'mon... Don't want to be late
for lunch!
[SHOYO]
Yeah!
[MOON A] Wow... Nekoma's
setter's not very tall.
[GUYS] (warming up)
[MOON B]
Oh yeah... he sure does look
pretty scrawny, doesn't he?
[MOON C]
Maybe that's just
the backup setter?
[MOON A]
Beats me, I don't know
a thing about these guys.
[KUROO]
That short scrawny guy you seem
to be so concerned about...
[MOONS] (surprised)
[KUROO] He just happens to be
the spine... the brain... AND
heart...
[KUROO]
... of our team.
[KOSHI]
Uh, Coach?
[KEISHIN]
Hm? What's up?
[KOSHI]
Us third‐years... we don't
get a next season.
(KEISHIN surprised)
[KOSHI] That's why I want us to
win as many games as we can...
so we get more chances to play.
[KEISHIN] Uh?
[KOSHI] And if Kageyama has a
better likelihood
of making that happen for us...
...well then I think
you shouldn't hesitate
to put him in.
(KEISHIN gasp)
[KOSHI]
Daichi and Asahi have
been playing together since
their first year.
I want to stand on the court
with them. And the more plays
the better.
[KOSHI]
It's okay if I only
get to fill in,
like if Kageyama gets tired
or something happens to put
him out or whatever.
You might pity me for being set
aside for a first year...
but as long as I keep having
a chance to play... that's fine.
[KOSHI]
Even if I don't get to be the
official setter, I'll never give
up on volleyball...
I just want to be the best
part of the team I can.
[KEISHIN] Mm.
[KOSHI] Sorry...
if I'm overstepping
my bounds.
[KEISHIN] Sugawara.
[KOSHI] Huh?
[KEISHIN]
I think I might've
underestimated you.
Honestly, you're kinda
freaking me out right now.
[KOSHI]
What?
[KEISHIN]
I don't have any coaching
experience...
but I swear I'll do whatever I
can... to keep you guys on the
winning track.
[KOSHI]
(happy) Thank you, sir!
[KEISHIN]
Sure.
Let's go for the win...
I think we can do this.
Yeah.
[ALL]
Time to eat!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
(extended eager eating)
[KEI] Jeez, slow it down...
You're gonna get sick.
[TADASHI] Ugh...
Don't stop eating!
Force it down if you have to!
How can you get through the
summer if you don't eat?!
[YU] You're gonna
shrivel up and die!
[ASAHI] You've got a big
appetite today. Suga.
[KOSHI] Yeah, maybe so...
Gotta stay strong!
[SHOYO] Are you gonna eat that?
I'll take it!
[YU]
No! Tadashi needs to
eat his own dinner!
(snoozing)
[KEISHIN]
Listen up. Here's our starting
order for Nekoma.
(serious)
[KEISHIN]
I know you haven't had
much time to get acquainted...
so I don't expect any
of you to be perfect.
[KEISHIN]
Just because we've got
a hotshot libero
and our ace just came
back doesn't mean victory
is a safe bet.
The winner keeps
the ball in play.
[KEISHIN]
So let's see how far this team
can take it,
those damn pussycats are not
gonna know what hit 'em!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[YU] Asahi!
[ASAHI] (startled) (awkward)
[YU]
Just forget about Suga...
Ennoshita's the guy you
should really be feeling
sorry for here.
[CHIKARA] What?‐ Me?!
[ASAHI] (stunned)
He's a wing spiker
just like you!
It must suck to be him!
[ASAHI] (scared) Uh?
[CHIKARA] Hey um... Asahi?
It's fine... I haven't always
been devoted to the sport.
[CHIKARA]
I ran away from the
game once... I get it.
[YU]
You just wait; he's gonna become
way stronger than you are.
He just needs time. Then he will
have the regular position! C'mon
tell him, Ennoshita!
[CHIKARA] (panic) Please don't
speak for me‐ uhh...
[YU] Oh wait, nevermind, he
would actually have
to take over Tanaka's position
first, wouldn't he?
[CHIKARA] (startled)
[RYUNOSUKE] So you're comin'
after my spot, are ya?
[RYUNOSUKE]
I'd like to see you try, you
little bastard!
[CHIKARA]
Whoa! I didn't say it,
Nishinoya did!
[SHOYO]
There we go... Hey uh...
Ennoshita?
[CHIKARA] Hm?
[SHOYO] About what you said...
[CHIKARA]
Oh... About how chose to leave
the game?
[CHIKARA]
You heard about the old Coach
Ukai
coming out of retirement
last year, right?
[SHOYO TOBIO] Yeah.
[HISASHI]
It's a little bit embarrassing
for us to admit,
but a bunch of us had some
trouble adjusting to his, let's
say "hardcore" training methods.
[CHIKARA]
We'd been doing volleyball club
just to have fun,
and then suddenly it was all
about winning and nothing else.
We felt like our space had been
invaded, and it kinda scared us
away.
[KAZUHITO]
But then we really missed
playing volleyball...
And when we came back..
Well Coach Ukai had already
taken off.
[CHIKARA]
The thing is... we're not as
cool as you are.
But now that we're all here...
we promise to work just as hard
as the rest of the team...
So let's do our best, okay?
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Right!
(practice efforts)
[KIYOKO] Sir?
[TAKEDA]
Hm? Oh, are they ready?
[KIYOKO]
Yes... Alterations are
finished...
and they've been cleaned.
Here you go.
[SHOYO]
Whoaaa!
Just like I saw on TV! Oh?
[SHOYO] Hey! Why's Noya the
only one with an orange one?
[TAKEDA] Here.
[KEI] Uh thanks a lot Takeda.
Because I'm the star!
Jeez, shouldn't that
be obvious by now?
The star? Cooooool!
[TOBIO]
The libero wears a different
color jersey
because he goes on and off of
the court during a game,
so it makes it easier to keep
track of him... dumbass.
[SHOYO]
(taken aback) I‐I knew that!
Everyone knows that! Uh?
[SHOYO]
(confused) Hey... His is one
number higher than mine!
[KEI RYUNOSUKE]
I knew you'd say that.
[TOBIO]
We're only first‐years;
you should be happy we
get uniforms at all.
[SHOYO]
Uh... I know that too!
[DAICHI]
Heh, that's funny...
I guess he doesn't
remember the number.
[KOSHI] He only saw him
on TV one time.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[DAICHI]
When the Tiny Giant
played in the nationals,
his number... was 10.
(SHOYO gasp)
[SHOYO]
Wow, Coach, did you plan this
just for me?!
[KEISHIN]
No, settle down, Ginger.
[SHOYO]
It must be destiny!
[TOBIO]
Or a coincidence.
[SHOYO]
Aw, don't be jealous, okay?
[TOBIO]
Why would I be jealous of you?!
Here's the thing. When Hinata's
hero, the Tiny Giant,
was on the team, Karasuno
was the best it's ever been.
[KEISHIN]
But in spite of that, we didn't
win against Nekoma even once.
It ended in a losing streak.
So let's turn that around.
[ALL] Yeah!
[KEISHIN] Alright! You better
get your asses back to practice!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[TAKEDA] I guess Nekoma must
have a really good team.
[DAICHI] Let's do some
more drills!
[TAKEDA] So what all do
you know about them?
[ALL] Right!
[KEISHIN]
I don't really have a clue what
they're like these days...
but that team has always
had some talented receivers.
[KEISHIN]
They didn't have stand‐out
players, but their defense
was tight.
The opposite of us, I guess.
And that whole "cat" thing...
it makes sense.
[KEISHIN]
They're extremely agile.
[SHIRATO 4]
What the heck?
No matter how many
times I hit it,
I can't get it to fall
into their court!
(whistle)(long whistle)
(NEKOMA celebrating)
[SHIRATO 11]
I don't understand...
They don't have any superstar
guys on their team...
[SHIRATO 11]
... so what's their secret?
[YAMAMOTO]
Here's the most important
issue... Do they or do they
not have a female manager?
[YAMAMOTO]
My yakisoba bun is saying no!
[INUOKA] Huh? But don't you WANT
them to have one? I say yes.
[SHIBAYAMA] Yeah, I agree.
[YAMAMOTO]
You crazy?! We don't have a girl
manager, so I'm just gonna be
pissed off if they do!
[INUOKA SHIBAYAMA] Huh?
[YAMAMOTO] Or what if
it's worse?
She could be a girl AND
extremely hot!
I would never forgive those
stupid jerks for that! Never!
[YAMAMOTO] You'll pay for having
a babe for a manager, Karasuno!
[KUROO] (annoyed)
Give it a rest, Yamamoto!
[YAMAMOTO]
Hey! What's Kenma think?
[KENMA]
Does it uh...
really even matter?
[YAMAMOTO]
Humph... I knew
you would say that.
[KENMA]
But...
I do kinda look forward
to playing them...
you know, a little bit.
[YAMAMOTO] Huh?
[INUOKA SHIBAYAMA] (surprise)
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh? Whoa!
Since when are YOU looking
forward to ANYTHING, Mr.
Couldn't‐Care‐Less Kenma
Kozume?!
[KUROO]
If you're that fired up, maybe I
should make you do some extra
reps.
[YAMAMOTO]
(extended strain)
N‐no, that's okay...
(CROWD cheers)
[TOBIO]
Hey, Hinata... They said
the first‐years can hit
the bath now.
[TOBIO]
Seriously? are you
about to throw up again?
[SHOYO]
(startled) What?!
Of course I'm not!
I was just thinking...
they're all preparing
for the match...
even if they're not playing.
[SHOYO]
The only reason the Coach
put me in the game
is because of your sets.
I hate to say this, but if not
for you, I probably wouldn't be
in the lineup.
[SHOYO]
I'm going in first!
(surprised) Hey!
You got a head start,
you little cheater!
[SHOYO TOBIO] (extended powerup
yell and arguing)
[KEI]
Even going to the bathroom's
a competition... Those
guys're morons.
[TADASHI]
(yawn) I'm getting tired
just watching them.
[DAICHI]
Hey! Quit screwing around!
It's time for our
game against Nekoma.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Great, I can't wait to play
against The School for Guys
with Weird‐Shaped Heads.
Haha! Did you see those clowns?
[YU]
Yeah, well at least
they're not very tall.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Neither are you, short stuff.
Next Haikyu!!
"The Cat And Crow Reunion."