[Spectator 1]:
Hey, Karasuno's
swapping setters.
Don't feel bad...
We just need to change
up the rhythm.
I'm sorry.
I AM worried about him.
[Koshi]:
But we can't have both of them
losing their grip at once.
I already promised you that
I'd be the one to beat you!
Hey, Hinata! He's
gonna get ma‐
Don't you dare lose
to those guys first!
Well, I haven't
lost yet, have I?
The game is still on.
He is gonna
KILL you!
I guess there was
no need to panic.
Kageyama... I want you
to stay ready.
Just take a few minutes
to cool off.
[Keishin]:
Maybe you'll learn something
from your upperclassman.
You!
And you!
Aw yeah!
I hope you're ready!...
We are getting this point!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
What?
Kageyama, you're making
that ugly face again.
It's my FACE,
asshole!
You just look so tense...
And you've been so quiet.
I'm sure you're just
really deep in thought
about something, right?
[Shoyo]:
But you're hard to read when
you go all silent like that.
So you're saying I'm not
talking to the team?
Yup, you've been
quieter in this game
than in any game
we've ever played.
[Shoyo]:
It's weird!
Damn, have I gotten so bad that
THIS idiot gets to lecture ME?
Hey.. that setter Karasuno
just put in... Number 2...?
[Book‐holding Spectator]:
Looks like he's
a third‐year!
What?!
I wonder why they would
replace a guy like that
with a first‐year in
the starting lineup?!
Hey, Daichi! Why are you
being so quiet today?
Huh?
We can't have our
captain losin' his cool!
Oh, uh...
sorry.
Nobody lectures
Daichi!
'Cept for him.
[Koshi]:
Tsukishima, c'mere.
I'm not sure what Mr. Optimism
is actually good at...
...but from his warmup, it's
clear that he's meticulous
and serious about
what he does.
Look, Iwa...
Number 2's got
a low block,
so I want you to aim for
a straight‐down where he is.
Sure.
Nice receive!
Tanaka!
Gotcha!
Iwa!
Okay... Straight down
at the low blocker!
Iwa!
Rejected! guess they must've
seen that straight‐down coming.
Yeah! That was
a really nifty trick!
Right before
Seijoh spiked it,
they swapped their
blocker positions.
That was great, Tsukishima!
You pulled one over on them!
That.. wasn't
just me...
Y'see, I'm a
low blocker...
so whenever we play
a tough team
I'm always
getting targeted.
And I figured they
would be no exception.
It comes in pretty handy
to have someone as tall as you
next to me!
Um... thanks,
I guess...
Yikes.
Sorry about that.
Here we go!
Hinata, c'mere!
[Daichi]:
All you, Tsukki!
Here!
[Toru]:
Nice receive!
Man, they're giving
it right back to them!
Oh, a quick attack!
[Takinoue]:
And an A‐Quick!
Woohoo!
Hinata, that
was freakin' great!
Yeah, well you guessed
right, Sugawara!
Next time they're able to neatly
send it back to the setter,
they'll probably do a
quick attack in the center.
But I want you
to move slowly
and delay your
jump a little bit.
Y'got that!
It was frustrating to have
to watch from the sidelines,
but I think being outside the
game allowed me to assess
the situation more calmly.
I was able to see
the game with new eyes.
So the time I spent
not playing was useful too.
The energy on our side
is really amping up now!
Yeah...
You're worried,
aren't you?
Huh?
Because you benched
Kageyama, right.
And he's
so prideful...
Are you afraid that he'll get
all bent out of shape over it?
[Takeda]:
He'll be alright.
I think Kageyama's pride is
the main source of his power
and talent. That, and his
undying determination to be
a better player,
make him exceptional.
[Daichi]:
Give us one
more, Tsukki!
[Toru]:
One point
to break it!
[Team Seijoh]:
Yeah!
[Shoyo]:
Okay, what attack
are we doing next?
My technical skill's not
as good as Kageyama's is,
so I can't always
toss perfect sets...
but hand signals might help
us communicate our next move
during a game.
When an outsider looks at Suga,
they only see one thing.
[Daichi]:
A poor third‐year who got
replaced by a first‐year.
He didn't use
his code words!
Kageyama's out, so it can't
be that insane quick attack!
Right, duh!
But what they don't know, is
that Suga has spent enough time
[Daichi]:
on the sidelines to know
exactly what to do...
He's just as much of
an asset as Kageyama!
Gotcha!
When it comes
to actual ability,
I pale in comparison
to Kageyama,
but I've been watching this team
a lot longer than he has.
[Koshi]:
I know I don't have what
it takes to beat Seijoh...
...but my friends are
amazing at what they do!
This point will turn the tide!
Right!
Good effort,
Hinata.
Hey, guys.
[Hajime]:
Serve's up!
[Hanamaki]:
One point!
Oh... great.
(fangirls squealing)
[Tobio]:
Oikawa's serve.
Bring it on!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
Leave it to me!
I'll get it!
The old
hubby‐wife play.
It happens when two
receivers get mixed up.
Sorry, I should've
gone for it myself.
I was too close!
It's cool!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
[Keishin]:
Front line!
[Shimada]:
Set point
for Seijoh.
Damn... How many times
has Oikawa scored
with that
serve of his?!
[Shimada]:
If there was an ultimate
play in volleyball,
it would be scoring
all 25 points
Time to finish this.
with nothing but serves.
[Team Seijoh]:
Yeah!
[Shimada]:
The opponent never
gets a chance to attack.
That's what service
aces are all about.
I got it, it's miiine!
Okay!
Number 10 and Number 5
are after it...
[Hajime]:
No, it's a back attack!
Yeah, nice receive!
Hinata, right now,
do a direct!
[Shoyo]:
I've never done
a direct attack...
What the hell
was that?!
I‐I'm sorry, okay?!
[Koshi]:
Hey, guys.
I think I just
noticed something...
It kinda looks like Seijoh
carries out their quick attacks
a little bit slower than
we do... We should...
[Shoyo]:
Delay it by just a hair...
... and jump!
Get back!
[Mizoguchi]:
No!
It's out?!
Son of a‐
(whistle blows)
[Keishin]:
Switch sides. Let's go!
Come on, Hinata!
We'll get it next time.
Okay!
Agh, that was too close!
They figured out our timing!
[Toru]:
All their players are starting
to look before they leap now...
including the short one,
and he tends to blindly rely
on his instincts.
Here.
We'll go with the
current lineup.
[Team Karasuno]:
Sir!
[Keishin]:
Okay, our biggest obstacle
is Oikawa's serve, obviously.
So we're gonna
beef up our defense!
[Hajime]:
Karasuno's attacks
are pretty wild.
Just when we got into the right
mindset to handle that crazy
quick attack...
they decided they would try
to throw us off our game
by attacking
us like normal.
You're focusing way
too much on Number 10.
Iwa! Don't think too hard;
you'll run out of brain cells!
During the practice game,
we were scrutinizing Kageyama.
[Irihata]:
I didn't realize they
had another solid setter.
Listen.
Yeah?
Uh, Kindaichi‐ Um I
mean... Onion Head.
Number 12's quick attack is a
little bit on the slow side...
I mean, don't
you think?
You're right, it is!
It's like that guy
watches the ball forever
before he actually
goes in for the hit.
Sugawara's a control tower
they're not familiar with...
That oughta throw
these guys off.
He's different
from Kageyama.
Yeah... I put him in hoping
he'd bring the other kids
back to their senses...
but this works just as well.
We'll have to remember
this little strategy
in the future too.
Kageyama.
Uh‐huh.
Okay, so I understand
since we're both setters,
we're kinda supposed to be
competing for the same position
or whatever...
...but I just want
to play volleyball!
Uh, s‐same here.
Now that I'm actually
standing on the court,
I realize how tall the
Aoba‐Johsai guys are,
and how that makes me a walking
target for their spikes...
It's kinda scary.
But y'know what...
I know I'm okay, because...
Now I have you
right there behind me.
That's reassuring.
The points we make while
I'm on the court...
and the points we make with
you on the court...
...they're all
points for Karasuno.
So I will give it
my absolute best...
and you give it your best too...
That is how we'll beat Seijoh.
Yeah.
Are you crying or
something, Kageyama?
No I'm not, butt‐wad!
Don't yell at me! I was just
concerned about you, that's all!
Worry about yourself and that
lame direct you just screwed up!
Sh‐shut up! I've
never done it before!
Well there's a whole
lot more of those to come
when I get back
in the game!
[Daichi]:
Let's go!
Yeah!
[Daichi]:
Suga! You don't have
to get all introspective
and overthink this.
Uh, I won't.
We'll make a comeback
in the second set.
The first step
to achieving that...
[Daichi]:
is breaking
Oikawa's serve.
Seijoh's rotation is
the same as the first set,
but Karasuno moved
theirs up a little bit.
[Takinoue]:
Huh. Wonder why
they did that?
Yes! Ha!
Alright!
Nice, Tsukishima!
Uh, thanks.
[Koshi]:
Do that again, okay?
He's really nice...
He always compliments me
when I do good, too!
That's great...
[Chikara]:
It is, but Sugawara doesn't
do that just for the sake
of being friendly... I think
he talks to all the spikers
so he can get a feel for their
emotional state during the game.
Helps him decide how to set.
Because everyone's different.
[Chikara]:
Tsukishima, on the other hand,
is a special case,
because unlike with the
older players, Sugawara doesn't
know much about him.
Oh what's that face for?
It looks like you're thinking
"Why should I be concerned
with how a jerk
like Tsukishima feels?"
Uh‐You don't know what
I'm thinking about!
'Kay it's sort
of like this...
You know how you adjust your set
if Hinata isn't able to hit it?
Yeah.. He'll just
swing at nothing.
Well, my point is,
our other spikers
have enough technical prowess
to hit the sets that aren't
tailored to
their strengths.
So maybe this sounds
sort of biased...
but you know, if you ask me...
we have some pretty
advanced spikers.
Uh, yeah, I agree
with that. Sure.
In that case...
...don't you think if they
were all hitting at 100%,
they'd be able to compete
with most any blocker
they were up against?
[Hanamaki]:
One point!
[Shoyo]:
Looks like the Great
King's up to serve.
[Toru]:
Serve‐receive W‐Formation!
[Keishin]:
When Oikawa serves...
We'll delegate our defense
to just a select few.
[Keishin]:
That serve of his
is a serious threat...
so a moment's hesitation
could be the end of us.
So, I say we tackle this using
our two outstanding receivers,
Nishinoya and Daichi.
We've never done
this formation in a game.
But I think you'll do fine.
We will!
[Shoyo]:
Wow!
They have a different
rotation this set...
I wonder why they
moved it slightly forward
from the first one.
[Takinoue]:
I'm assuming they
lined it up like this
to match with
Oikawa's serve.
Those serves cleaned
the floor with us in set 1...
not to mention the 5 points
we lost to service aces.
[Keishin]:
Until we can stand up to that
serve, we'll never beat Seijoh.
Here goes!
[Crowd]:
Ooooooooolé!
Daichi!
Yes!
[Takeda]:
Nice receive!
[Koshi]:
We really need to score
a point to break the cycle
of Oikawa's serve.
If we can, it'll make
a huge difference.
But it's gonna put a lot of
pressure on one person.
I'll send it to the player who
broke the flow in the first set
after Oikawa tried
to bring him down.
That'll get him
back on his feet.
Tanaka!
It's all up to you!
Yeah!
YEEEEEAAAAAH!
Who‐ho‐hoa!
That's the
point breaker!
That was very
impressive, captain.
[Yu]:
Let's keep it up!
[Daichi]:
Tsukki!
[Chikara]:
You know, if you ask me...
we have some pretty
advanced spikers.
Don't you think if they
were all hitting at 100%...
they'd be able to compete
with most any blocker
they were
up against?
[Keishin]:
Man, our morale
is through the roof!
Seijoh's may have us beat in
experience and technical skill.
And it'll be a nightmare if
they can pick up a solid lead.
But if we hang in there, we
should be able to take control!
[Takinoue]:
Wow, it's anybody's
game right now.
I guess... but their
blockers are all over us.
Good job, Kindaichi! You're
figuring out all their patterns!
Uh, yes sir.
It's not that Mr. Sunshine
and Rainbows is a bad setter.
His attacks are just so
textbook and predictable...
He never rushes
a setup either.
Listen, Karasuno may have
a lot of offensive power,
but it's nothing we haven't
seen before from other teams
we've played, right?
Now let's leave these
losers in the dust.
Gotcha!
Y'know... At this point
in the game...
I think Seijoh's got a good
sense of what our setter's
gonna do next.
I think you're right.
[Matsukawa]:
Serve's up!
[Crowd]:
Ooooooooolé!
[Shimada]:
Seijoh scores
back‐to‐back.
Yeah, and the break is where
the flow really starts to move.
We need to
crank things up!
Karasuno's been using
their left players a lot
since they swapped out
their setter, haven't they?
Well, that's because each
of their lefts is a force
to be reckoned with...
Still... I'm sure they're easier
to deal with than that
number 10's constant
bobbing and weaving.
It's like there's a noose
tightening around my neck.
And yet I feel so calm.
Impatience isn't
clouding my judgment.
I guess because I have a
clear goal right in front of me.
Yeah, let's
get that point!
[Tobio]:
I used to think that
if I got benched...
...it meant I wasn't
useful to the team anymore...
Honestly, that probably
WAS the reason back then.
But...
Now I have you right
there behind me.
That's reassuring.
Sugawara and I have
different strengths,
but I think our goal
is the same.
[Hajime]:
Left side!
[Koshi]:
Heads up!
[Yu]:
Open!
[Tobio]:
All I want is to
play volleyball!
I want to be
in this game!
[Koshi]:
I want to stay longer...
Just a little longer!
[Tobio]:
The intensity of the court...
[Koshi]:
Please... let me keep
playing with my team!
[Tobio]:
The rush of adrenaline...
[Koshi]:
I don't want to leave!
[Tobio]:
I want to be out there
fighting... and winning!
[Koshi]:
I want to make
these sets myself!
[Tobio/Koshi]:
I HAVE to!
So...
So I will give it
my absolute best...
and you give it
your best, too...
and that...
[Tobio/Koshi]:
That is how we're
going to win this game!
[Koshi]:
Nice receive!
YES!
Awesome block!
Sorry Hinata...
That last quick attack took me
longer than it should have.
Oh! No
it's fine...
[Spectator 1]:
They're calling for
Karasuno's number 9.
[Spectator 2]:
I guess they're
switching setters.
My time's running out.
[Asahi]:
Suga.
Send me the next ball, okay?
I'll make it count.
Right!
[Yutaro]:
Serve's up!
Amazing.
I hate to admit it, but...
Well, when Hinata
hits your sets...
somehow he looks
completely different.
And... I'm sure
you know this...
[Koshi]:
...but everyone on our team
is good at what they do.
Yeah.
So go wi‐
Let's win.
Right!
Good job.
Well done.
Yeah, You kept it neck and
neck against those guys.
That's because we're
a great team.
Listen here, kid...
From here on in, I think
we'll be pushing this
setter route as
aggressively as we can.
Sure! Thank you, sir!
What was that?
Well, you are talking
in his setter language.
[Takeda]:
That's probably
music to his ears.
If everyone does
their best to succeed,
then I'm confident we
can beat Seijoh... But...
[Koshi]:
...to get the boost we need,
the best bet for Karasuno
is to have its greatest decoy
working at 100%
of his potential.
And the one to
make that happen...
[Koshi]:
...will be you... Kageyama.
[Toru]:
Welcome back, Tobio!
[Tobio]:
Watch it, pretty boy.
[Toru]:
Now, now, settle down.
We know you're not capable
of anything serious.
[Shoyo]:
Tsukishima, he's meaner than
you! You gonna take that?!
[Kei]:
It's not a
competition, Hinata...
Next Haikyu!!
"Evolution."