[Shiratorizawa Crowd]:
Shiiiiiiratorizawa!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Go, go‐go‐go‐go SeiJOH!
This is going to be the
day that I humiliate you
once and for all...
Are you ready big guy?
I would rather you drop
the nicknames, Oikawa.
(starting whistle)
[Student 1]:
I'm starving!
[Student 2]:
Lunch time!
Hey Hinata, I'm really hungry!
It's time to eat.
Mhmm.
I heard you guys played
a close game yesterday.
Yeah, man, our team lost in the
third round last week also...
The guys who beat us made
it all the way to Nationals.
What's wrong?
You okay?
Bathroom.
[Ryunosuke]:
When Hinata and Kageyama first
came to the volleyball club...
Daichi told us that
we would be going
to the Spring
Nationals.
Spring Nationals...
First qualifier's
in August, right?
Yeah, that's right...
He said we'd go back there.
There's no time to
lick our wounds, boys.
[Daichi]:
Hey... I think this might be a
good time for me to retire.
Ever since third‐years
were allowed to play
in the Spring Nationals...
I've wanted us to survive
to the finals and go to Tokyo
so we could do that.
But...
[Daichi]:
now that I've seen
those incredible
first and second‐years
in action,
I feel like it might be
better to give up the club
to them early.
It's better to restructure
the team around them,
since they have so
much potential.
I just think I ought
to step aside and‐
[Koshi]:
Daichi. Is that really
what you want to do?
I know being the
captain means
you have to make the
tough decisions...
but it doesn't do any good to
remove yourself completely.
It's one thing if that
was your plan from the start.
[Koshi]:
But come on...
you shouldn't just leave
because of the new guys!
I will stay like
I said I would!
And I'm not going anywhere
unless the younger members
ask me to leave!
Whether you
two stay or not!
I told you yesterday
I'm still in!
[Asahi]:
I'm not going to
college anyway...
I guess if the underclassmen
didn't want me to stay I'd go,
but... I... I...
[Daichi]:
Look!
I still... I still want to stay!
I love this game...
you know that, don't you?!
[Teacher]:
Mr. Takeda?
May I have a word with you
about volleyball club?
Okay.
[Shimada]:
So, you actually got to play.
How was it?
Did you enjoy
it, Tadashi?
No...
No!
I thought as much.
In the moment, you tense up and
can't move the way you want.
Then the ball doesn't
fly right...
That's no fun at all.
When I was younger, I used to
like playing volleyball
because it was just a fun thing
I could do with my friends,
you know?
That's all this game
was to me...
But I was wrong;
it's not like that at all.
I can't do what
those other guys do.
[Tadashi]:
I want to control my body!
I want to control the ball!
I want what it takes
to stand up to my opponents!
"If you really want to get the
most out of playing sports,
then you have to be strong."
[Shimada]:
Coach Ukai...
The older version...
That's the advice
he would always give me.
I wasn't his star ace...
in fact, wasn't even in
the starting lineup.
I practiced hard though,
and sometimes I felt
like throwing in the towel.
But...
[Shimada]:
The first time I nailed
a service ace
during a real game....
I realized... wow,
this is the play I spent
all those long
hours practicing for.
That day, I decided to buckle
down and work even harder,
just to see if I could
experience that game,
that point, that moment,
all over again.
Well then...
Let's work!
The next game will be
here before you know it.
Tsukki! Are you
ready for lunch?
Please not so
loud, Tadashi.
Sorry, Tsukki!
Tsukki!
[Teacher]:
I received statements from
both Sugawara and Sawamura
that they'd be staying
in volleyball club
past the Inter‐High despite
their plans to attend college.
But then, Sugawara...
Excuse me.
[Teacher]:
Young man.
I understand your feelings,
but you really should
prioritize your studies.
If you ask me, you don't
stand to gain anything
by staying in the club.
Maybe not... but...
I don't play volleyball
just to get ahead, y'know?
If I'm not mistaken,
Sugawara's not part of
your starting lineup, right?
Umm... no.
And I doubt he can
get a sports scholarship.
As it stands right now, he
and Sawamura both tend to get
excellent grades.. but can
they maintain those grades?
[Teacher]:
Therefore, I'd like you
to speak to those two.
And focus on their
futures rather
than their current
feelings on the matter.
I don't want an adult
talking them out
of what's best for them.
[Takinoue]:
Poor kids...
Yeah what about em?
You know... I bet
they're really bummed.
That's why I gave 'em the
whole day off from practice.
Can't believe it
was just yesterday.
Aoba‐Johsai... They're
pretty good, huh?
Damn right they are...
They played a great game.
I mean, we were on fire,
don't get me wrong...
But to tell you the truth, I'm
not so sure we can pull that off
the next time we have to
play against those guys.
And even if we do, it's not
like Seijoh's gonna be any less
killer than they
were yesterday.
Did you notice how they
did their time‐outs?
[Takinoue]:
Uh‐huh. It was mostly just a
meeting between the players.
I mean, the coaches
watched from a distance.
Well, I'm sure
they helped a little.
Seijoh's guys are always
thinking and adapting
to every situation they're
faced within a game.
No matter what kind of
weapon we throw at 'em...
they've always got something
to counter it with.
Yeah, they refused to be
tripped up by anything we did.
It was pretty stressful
for me to watch.
[Keishin]:
You know... I think there's only
one team who has what it takes
to pry the points away from a
well‐oiled machine like Seijoh.
And that's Shiratorizawa.
[Toru]:
After all the practicing and
planning and strategizing...
all it's taking is
sheer force to tear us apart.
Oh well. It doesn't matter HOW
the victory's won, right?
'Cause the loser... is the
one who lets the ball drop.
[Toru]:
That's what counts.
Here's the thing...
If you sustained an injury
and it wasn't given
the proper amount
of time to heal...
Because you wanted to keep
playing since your time here
[Takeda]:
was limited, I'd
have to stop you.
Some things can't be done
no matter how you feel.
You four still have some time
before graduation...
The good news is...
you have some options.
Now... neglecting and failing
your entrance exams
is not one of them!
To overcome your obstacles...
it takes patience and hard
work... sometimes sacrifice.
[Takeda]:
Every hour you spend
on your extracurriculars
is time that other students
will spend studying
and preparing
for the workforce.
That's going to cause
a disparity.
It might not seem like it now,
but one day you may regret it.
So please give
this some thought.
[Takeda]:
Try to choose the
option you won't regret
5 or 10 years
down the road.
Get lower.
Sure thing.
Guess the finals are...
almost over with.
Yeah...
And so whoever wins gets
to go to the Nationals.
They get to keep
playing more games.
Yeah...
It's not FAAAAAIIIR!
Damn...
DAMMIT!
I wanna win.
I'm never... going to
say I'm sorry again.
And I won't make
a set I regret...
...not ever!
[Shoyo]:
Only the strong...
[Tobio]:
...Stay on the court.
Yeah...
Right.
Let's do better... now!
I think you should
eat lunch first.
Ki..Kiyoko!
Also, I heard you screaming all
the way in the club room...
So please quiet down.
Oh! Right!
[Yu/Ryunosuke]:
Kiyokoooo!
You're looking pretty
as ever today, baby!
I think you're prettier
than he does!
[Yu/Ryunosuke]:
I am all yours forever,
my deeeeear!
Try not to
hurt yourselves.
We're off today. So
why are you guys here?
I could ask you two
the same question y'know.
[Tadashi]:
Hi!
Hey.
Welp. We're all
here.... Almost.
Well maybe the third‐years
decided not to come back.
Hey, hey, hey!
[Ryunosuke]:
You know they wouldn't leave us
hangin' like that! Ever!
Huh? Wait, what does
that mean?! Are they...?!
Hey, the third‐years didn't
quit the team, did they?!
They're still going to Spring
Nationals with us, right?!
Hurry... we're late!
Yes. They're staying.
What kept ya nerds?!
Let's do this... okay?
YEAH!
Well, here I am. Wonder if
those crazy kids showed up.
[Asahi/Kazuhito]:
Nice kill!
You got that one!
[Team Karasuno]:
Coach!
How 'bout that?
Hard at work, huh?
Thank you sir... We hope that
you will continue coaching us!
Thank you!
[Keishin]:
We did the best
we could and lost.
Seijoh beat us... That
proves they're the better team.
You can like it or not, but
that's what happened out there.
I'm sure you're all interested
to know who the winner
of the Inter‐High
final was.
[Keishin]:
It was Shiratorizawa.
(final whistle)
Are you telling me that...
...Seijoh lost?
So Seijoh's NOT the best
in our prefecture.
We need to step it up!
I'm sure you already know
what our next focus is.
[Keishin]:
Spring Nationals...
And obviously, that'll
be the last game
for the third‐year players.
I can't wait to play in the
same place the Tiny Giant did!
Actually, I'd like to hear
some inspiring words
from the
captain himself.
The venue...
is Tokyo's Orange Court.
[Daichi]:
Karasuno's only been once.
Let's go back...
and do it again!
ALL RIGHT!
[Keishin]:
Take five!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes sir!
[Shoyo]:
Kageyama.
We're gonna win
it this time.
You wait and see.
You and me... and our team!
Yeah.
[Keishin]:
Break time's over, love birds!
Sir!
[Shoyo]:
There's a big, tall wall in
front of me, blocking my way.
[Keishin]:
Practice your spikes!
Yes sir!
Here we go!
[Shoyo]:
I'll never be able to see
over that wall on my own,
not without
my teammates by my side.
You're up next, Ginger!
Ready, sir!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it to me!
I get it now!
That's the view from the top!