[SHOYO]
Come on! Gimme another one!
[TOBIO]
Alright, shut up,
I get it! Ready?
[SHOYO]
Yeah!
Ah!
[SHOYO]
GAH! That felt so good!
And once I reach the top of my
jump, the ball hits my hand...
And when the weight of it...
sorta leaves a sting in my
palm... I love that!
[SHOYO]
Sweet! Those cats won't
stand a chance against
our quick‐attacks!
[ASAHI]
Huh? (internal) Cats? Are
they playing against Nekoma?
[DAICHI] We've got ourselves a
practice game... It's the last
day of camp.
[ASAHI] (startled) Aahh!
Hey what's your problem?!
Don't run away from me!
I'm getting out of here.
You scare me when you get mad!
Well it's not like
I'm mad all the time!
We weren't expecting this...
We know nothing about them...
And the rivalry feels
like an old folktale...
I mean it was the generation
before us... So it was never
really relevant to us.
But now... ... it's time to
face off, crows versus cats!
It's so strange to think that
we're about to have our first
rematch with Nekoma in years...
I gotta say I'm pretty
psyched about it.
It's just Suga ...
and well of course
Nishinoya, too...
I can't face them.
You know what, Asahi...
You really are pretty timid,
especially for such a big guy!
And Nishinoya's the
opposite of that.
[ASAHI]
And you could stand to
be a lot less blunt...
Anyway, it'll be fine...
Nobody else on the team
has a problem with it...
Unlike you, they're
pretty open‐minded.
Uh, Daichi? I thought I
remembered you being nicer.
I'll be nicer when you
stop being such a wuss.
[ASAHI] (offended)
[DAICHI]
I don't care so much
about you skipping out
of club activities for a month
and then feeling awkward
about finally coming back.
[DAICHI]
Because if you still
love volleyball...
...that's reason enough to play.
[ASAHI] (surprised)
[DAICHI]
Not just that...
... but we've got this new kid
whose dream is to be the ace.
(ASAHI thinking)
[DAICHI] (punch)
[ASAHI] Ah... Hey!
[KEISHIN, singing]
On the banks of the Hirose
ri‐i‐ver...
Memories afloat...
on the stream...
Dancing lights... over the
rapids‐
(freak out)
Hey! What're you
doing here?! (annoyed)
[TAKEDA]
Uh I'm sorry!
I was just seeing if
you had any customers...
(whimper)
Are you Here to ask
me to coach again?
[TAKEDA]
Yes.
[KEISHIN]
It's not that I don't
still love to play.
I even put together
a neighborhood team.
I can't be a coach
'cause I'd drive myself
crazy wanting to play.
[TAKEDA] Oh...
[KEISHIN] And besides... I can't
go anywhere near that gym.
(surprised) Uh.. did
something tragic happen there?
Not in the least! All my
best memories are there.
[TAKEDA]
Then why can't you?
[KEISHIN]
I don't care if it's
totally different or
exactly the way I left it.
I can't go into that gym or
the club room ever again.
[KEISHIN]
The short time I spent
there was so unique...
If I went back, it'd feel like
opening a time capsule.
Oh, so it's a nostalgia
thing... 'Kay I get it‐
Shut up!
And anyway... It's still a 'no.'
[TAKEDA] Even if Nekoma
High's on the schedule?
[KEISHIN] (shocked)
[TAKEDA]
The last day of Golden Week.
It's our first time facing them
in five years.
Ah... You have got
to be kidding me.
Coach Nekomata... the man that
your grandfather used to be
such good friends with...
He just came out of retirement.
Once I heard that... I asked
them for a practice game.
(KEISHIN speechless)
Back when you were still
in high school...
that was when Karasuno had the
strongest ties with them, right?
[KEISHIN]
Yeah.
And by the way...
Their current coach...
He is the same guy who
played the setter position
about 7 or 8 years ago.
(surprised)
[NAOI]
This is our last shot, Ukai.
I want to see you at Nationals
this year, alright?
[KEISHIN]
Sure! I'll be there!
[TAKEDA]
That was back when you
were active in the club...
So I was thinking... that maybe
you two might know each other.
[KEISHIN] Hey...
[TAKEDA] Hm?
[KEISHIN]
Are you trying to mess with me?!
[TAKEDA, freaking out]
I'm sorry! I'm really
sorry! (manhandled)
[KEISHIN]
This is bullshit! You
just came here to push
my buttons!
Did you really think that
would work?! What time is
practice today?
I said I‐ Huh?
You mean you...?
[KEISHIN]
I'm not letting those
pathetic underclassmen embarrass
our school in front of Nekoma.
Stay right here,
I'll go get changed.
Okay! Great!
[KEISHIN]
Hey Ma, can you watch the store?
[TAKEDA, happy]
Yes!
[KEISHIN]
Hey, uh, Tatsu? It's me.
[TAKEDA]
(surprised) Huh?
Hey.. Noya?
Yeah?
What kinda training did you
do while you were suspended?
Hm... I focused on
blocked ball retrieval.
[YU]
So the ball doesn't hit the
floor after they block!
I haven't gotten it
down perfect yet...
but if I manage to get
really good at it...
then you spikers won't
have to worry... And
you can just spike.
[RYUNOSUKE, internal]
Man... every time I see this
guy, he's got more bruises.
Noya! How are you such a
badass all the time?! (sobbing)
(huh?) It's nothing
to cry about!
(door opening)
[TAKEDA] Um excuse me!
[DAICHI]
Alright come over here, guys!
(surprised)
This is Ukai...
As of today, he'll be your
coach! Say hello everyone!
[ALL]
Huh?
(thinking)
Whoa, are you serious?!
We have a new coach?!
Just until after
the Nekoma game.
[DAICHI] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey wait...
Isn't that the grumpy guy who
runs the Sakanoshita store?
HE'S coaching us?
He's actually used
to go to this school.
He's the old Coach
Ukai's grandson.
[ALL]
HUH?!
But your store's called
Saka‐noshita, right?
You shoulda called it Ukai,
dude! I mean, sir!
It's named for my mom's
side of the family.
[KEISHIN]
Anyway, let's not
waste any more time!
I set you up a game for 6:30..
So c'mon let's see what you got.
[SHOYO] Huh?!
[KEISHIN] They're
gonna be here soon.
[DAICHI]
Who will?
Our friendly Neighborhood
Association team.
[DAICHI]
Because if you still love
volleyball, that's reason
enough to play.
(phone ringing)
[CHIKARA] Going in!
[TOBIO]
Okay! Hup!
[SHOYO] Coming your way!
[KEISHIN] Damn..
He won't pick up.
[HISASHI] Go!
[KEISHIN]
I guess it was too short notice
to get 'em all together on a
weekday.
[CHIKARA]
Heads up!
[SHIMADA]
Here.
Um... Thanks I
appreciate it.
[TAKINOUE]
What's up!
Hey.
[UCHIZAWA]
Oh, man!
[MORI]
Takes me back!
Uh, hi?
We're the Neighborhood
Club Team.
Let's do this!
[KEISHIN]
Hey! Thanks for comin' out
at the last minute!
[KEI] The Neighborhood
Association huh...
[TAKINOUE] That's cool,
you can owe us one.
[KEI] I was picturing a bunch
of old guys.
[KEISHIN] Eh, whatever!
[TADASHI] Me too.
[TAKINOUE] Ha, you
think I'm joking!
[KEISHIN]
Alright! You boys ready to play
or what?
[ALL] Yeah!
[SHOYO] Yeah! Here we go!
[KEISHIN] Hm? What's
with you? You sick?
[YU] Hm? (look)
[DAICHI]
Oh... sorry... He's
not ready to play yet.
Why not? Is he injured or
something? What's wrong?
No, it's not really as
straightforward as all that.
So he's not gonna
participate then?
Well whatever it is..
you can play with us if
you want... Our libero's
been pretty tied up with
a buncha work stuff.
Do... you want to?
(frown)
[KEISHIN]
Hm, we're still short a couple
guys. You have more members,
don't you?
[SHOYO] There's Asahi! Look!
(YU shocked)
(gasp)
[SHOYO]
Asahi! Hey!
Agh! It's that
short guy again!
[ASHAI] Listen, I was
just here to uhhh...
[RYUNOSUKE] Asahi?!
You gotta be kidding! Late
on the coach's first day?!
What position do you play?!
[ASAHI, startled]
Uh‐wing spiker?
Whatever, I don't care,
we need some more players!
Get your ass in
here and warm up!
(ASAHI stunned)
[KEISHIN] Chop chop, man‐bun!
(RYUNOSUKE SHOYO excited)
(watching)
So we just need a setter...
I would do it myself, but I
really should watch the game.
[KEISHIN]
Hey, do me a favor and let me
borrow one of your setters,
would ya?
(BOTH surprised)
(surprised) Sugawara!
Listen you're not doing
this for me, are you?
Because if the only way I can
rise up the ranks is at your
expense... I'm not doing it.
[KOSHI]
You know what... whenever
you joined the club...
I knew that I had to fight you
for the setter spot... but it
was kinda... it was a relief.
[KOSHI]
The setter is the attack
axis for the whole team.
A setter has to be composed
and steadfast... But I...
I was too nervous to put
the ball in the right spot.
[KOSHI]
After what happened to Asahi,
I was so afraid that my
tosses would cause another
spiker to get blocked...
So I was content to just
hide in Kageyama's shadow.
It was... easier.
[KOSHI]
Just the thought of a spike
getting shut down like that
terrifies me.
[KOSHI]
But... Please let me... set
for you one more time... okay?
(surprised)
[KOSHI] I'm playing on their
side... Oh and...
[TOBIO] Hm?
I am not losing.
And me neither.
Now give me some of your
famous receives, okay? (grin)
Oh you know it.
[DAICHI] Okay, time
to start the game!
[SHOYO] Asahi decided
to come... See?
Yeah well... is
he gonna stay?
(whistle)
[ALL]
Thank you!
Looks pretty threatening
standing over here.
[TAKINOUE]
Alright, kids...
Don't poop your pants
[SHOYO, internal]
Let's see the Ace in action!
[SHIMADA]
Nice receive!
(whistle)
[TAKINOUE] Hey, that was a
great set there, buddy!
Really nice job!
(happy) Wow!
Thank you so much!
Sugawara's
killing it! Uh?
Well of course he is! Suga's
our official setter, after all!
[RYUNOSUKE]
He's so happy...
(TOBIO annoyed)
Hey, nice going, Suga!
[KOSHI]
Thanks... but I didn't do
anything special;
it's only because they're
adjusting their whole dynamic
to suit my play style...
These people are real
vets of the game.
[TAKINOUE] Yeah!
[KOSHI] My setting still
needs quite a bit of work.
(listening)
[KOSHI]
Still... We have to start
playing hardball...
and get a good handle on those
fast attacks too...
If we don't, the game'll ride on
just one player like last time.
You know... you're
actually kinda cool.
What? Really? Wow, coming
from you, that's kind of
a huge compliment.
[YU]
Huh? Why's that?
[KOSHI]
Well uh... (laugh)
[ASAHI, internal]
Suga, you've become much more of
a leader than I remember.
[ASAHI, internal] And Nishinoya
is as constant as ever.
[YU] I'm serious; you've really
upped your cool factor.
[ASAHI, internal]
And here I am, coming out of
nowhere and just drifting back
onto the team...
I'm so pathetic...
But even so...
[MORI]
You can do it!
[UCHIZAWA]
One more!
[ASAHI, internal]
I really... I really
do love being here.
[TAKINOUE]
(stunned) Whoa! That was nuts!
[SHOYO] Haha! We did it!
[TOBIO] Yeah!
[UCHIZAWA]
He really got some air!
[SHIMADA]
And that set was scary accurate.
(TAKEDA quiet rejoicing)
(KEISHIN floored)
[DAICHI]
That was excellent, you two!
[SHOYO]
Thanks to Kageyama's amazing
sets I can get past anybody now!
[SHOYO]
The wall just fades away, and
then the view of the other side
is totally clear!
[ASAHI]
The view of the other side...
(gasp) (spike)
(whistle)
(CROWD cheers)
[DAICHI]
We're good!
[KOSHI]
One more try!
That's a bluff!
[RYUNOSUKE] Good job, Noya! Hah!
[KOSHI] Asahi!
(CROWD cheers)
(angry)
[GUY A]
Well they did flub that one...
but their libero's a superstar.
[YU] My bad! I'll
get it next time!
[GUY B] Yeah, he definitely
knows what he's doing.
[GUY A]
Too bad their
attacker's no good.
[ASAHI, panting]
Blocked again... How many times
has that happened to me now?
[ASAHI, internal]
I've asked for so many
chances. I promised I would
make them count.
[ASAHI, internal] But then I
was paralyzed by my fear...
[DAICHI] I'm open!
[ASAHI, internal]
...and I didn't want to
call for them anymore.
What's going on?
Asahi?
[DAICHI]
Suga, aim right!
[KOSHI]
D‐Daichi!
Uwwwaaah!
(whistle)
(DAICHI frustrated)
(long whistle)
(CROWD cheers)
[YU]
Dammit!
I was worthless out there...
I couldn't save a single
blocked ball!
(ASAHI choked up)
[ASAHI]
Nishi! Why won't you
blame ME for this?!
I am the one who cost us
the game!
Even if you could have saved
one, it'd be pointless because
I couldn't make it count‐
[DAICHI] Asahi!
[YU] What exactly do you
mean by pointless?
[ASAHI] (breath)
And while we're at it,
why didn't you call for
the ball at the end?
Come on you were in
the perfect position.
(ASAHI speechless)
[KOSHI] Hey! Just lay
off him, Nishinoya!
It was my fault for sending
him too many sets in a row
before that‐
[ASAHI]
Even if you did Suga... it
wouldn't have mattered anyway.
[YU]
(angry) You never know until
you hit the damn thing! You
know that!
[YU]
The next spike might be
the one to break through!
[KOSHI]
(concerned) Hey! (startled)
Don't you ever give up on a
ball... not while I'm keeping
it in for you!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Noya! Take it easy!
[YU] (grabbed)
I am the libero!
[YU] I am the last defense!
The team needs me!
[RYUNOSUKE] (struggling)
But... I can't score us points.
(shaky sigh)
[YU]
And I can't even attack
either... So...
I don't care how many spikes
get blocked... I'd never blame
you for that.
But quit... and I'll never
be able to forgive you!
(ASAHI choked up)
[RYUNOSUKE] A‐Asahi!
[KOSHI] Asahi! Wait, don't go!
[ASAHI]
Ah...
Tell me... Why weren't
you there yesterday?
Did you forget
or something?
The Inter‐High
tournament coming up.
Yeah where's the fun in hitting
spikes that don't mean anything?
[ASAHI, internal]
What am I saying?
That's not how I feel.
You must be sick of
retrieving balls for no
reason... aren't you?
[ASAHI, internal]
Stop it. Nishinoya doesn't think
that way either!
[ASAHI]
I know Suga feels guilty
every time I get blocked‐
[YU]
Oh who gives a damn what anybody
else thinks about it?!
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
What on earth is all the racket
about out here?! Stop shouting
in the halls!
Asahi!
Young man‐
[YU]
Don't touch me!
(vase crashing)
(GIRLS gasp, concerned)
(VICE PRINCIPAL gasping
and freaking out)
[GUY C]
Uh‐oh, someone's in trouble.
(VICE PRINCIPAL exasperated)
[YU]
Don't you want to make
a spike that matters?!
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice one, Hinata!
(ASAHI surprised)
[SHOYO] Thank you!
Hinata.. It's
your serve.
[ASAHI] I was wrong.
[YU] Huh?
[ASAHI]
I know I got stopped
by the wall...
but I want to... I want to
keep trying to break through it.
[YU] And that's all
that matters.
[ASAHI] Hm?
That was all I needed
to hear from you, Asahi.
(ASAHI speechless)
(YU preparing breath)
[YU, internal]
My job... is just to
keep the ball in play.
[CHIKARA]
Do your best, Hinata!
[TAKINOUE]
It's in!
[SHIMADA]
Agh!
My bad! Cover me!
[UCHIZAWA]
Hey, bun‐head! Finish it off!
(nervous)
(surprised)
[YU, internal]
The sky belongs to the spikers.
I can't compete in their space.
[RYUNOSUKE] (panicked breath)
[TOBIO] Shut him down!
[KEI] Yeah I don't take
orders from you.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Come on, man, we're
playin' for keeps!
[YU, internal]
...but if I can just keep
the ball up in the air...
[ASAHI]
I know I got stopped by the
wall... But I want to keep
trying to break through it.
[YU, internal]
I know I can trust
the ace to nail it.
[TOBIO] Damn!
(focus)
[SHIMADA]
Whoa! It's up!
[UCHIZAWA] Nice follow‐thru!
[RYUNOSUKE] (shocked)
[YU]
I focused on blocked ball
retrieval, so the ball doesn't
hit the floor after they block!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Great job, Noya! (sob)
[KEI] Huh?
[YU]
Even if the ball
rebounds off the wall...
I WILL keep it in
play! So please...
You have to ask the setter
for another chance, Asahi!
You're the ace!
(shocked)
[SHIMADA] Cover me!
[KOSHI] Right here!
[KOSHI, internal]
Woah! Who do I send the ball to?
The left is open, so it's
probably our best bet, but...
...what if I cause Asahi
to get blocked again?
[TOBIO] Sugawara!
(KOSHI surprised)
Keep throwing it to him...
until he scores!
Oh that's just cruel,
Your Majesty.
[TOBIO]
Quiet!
[KOSHI, internal]
When the chips are down
and the receives are
all over the place,
you're supposed to trust
the ace with the last ball.
(internal) I know
that... but still...
[KOSHI, internal]
I can't send Asahi a ball he's
not expecting and make him deal
with a triple block.
[ASAHI] A spiker can only go
for a kill... after a setter
sends him the ball.
[KOSHI]
Please... let me set for you
one more time, okay?
[ASAHI]
And the set only exists because
the libero kept the ball in
play.
[YU]
Don't ever give up on a ball...
not while I'm keeping it in for
you!
[ASAHI]
So when I go to do my job, I'm
not alone.
[ASAHI]
Everyone else was doing theirs,
but I... I...
[TOBIO]
It's impossible to win all by
yourself.
[SHOYO]
I mean, come on. That is why
they call you the Ace!
[DAICHI]
Because if you still love
volleyball...
[YU]
You have to ask the setter for
another chance, Asahi! You're
the ace!
I'm free!
[KOSHI] Shimada!
[ASAHI] SUGAAAAAAA!
(gasp)
Over here!
[KOSHI, internal]
Right... our ace is waiting. He
wants me to send it his way.
(internal) I'll set high,
not too far from the net.
Asahi's favorite toss, the one
I've given him so many times.
[KOSHI]
It's a simple one,
but I'll send it with as
much accuracy as I can.
Why would you bother
encouraging them to do that?
You know we have
to block him.
Obviously; it's meaningless
if we just let him through.
(panicked wail)
[ASAHI, internal]
My team has my back.
And my setter knows exactly
what works best for me.
[ASAHI, internal]
Who could ask for more?
(internal) Somewhere
along the way...
I let myself forget the most
simple and natural thing about
this game.
That I'll never have
to fight alone!
(internal) I will land this hit.
(happy)
(focused)
(breathless)
[ASAHI]
Because I'm the Ace!
[KEI]
Tanaka, would you stop crying
and focus on blocking, please?
[RYUNOSUKE]
What?! I‐I'm not crying,
stupid! This is just‐
[KEI]
Right, it's sweat, you've
said that a thousand times.
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's just a runny nose.
[KEI]
Whatever. Next Haikyu!!
"The Dream".