[Ikejiri]:
Check it out!
I've got the pairings
for the Inter‐High
Preliminaries right here!
Cool!
Sweet!
[Chaya]:
So, who do we play first?
[Haga]:
Let me see...
Tori.. Torino?
[Chaya]:
Torino? That's
in England!
[Ikejiri]:
Try Italy. And you're
reading the kanji wrong.
[Chaya]:
Whatever, dude.
Oh!.. Karasuno,
I've heard of that school!
Uh... if I
remember right...
[Chaya]:
A lot of people call them
like, the "wingless crows."
[Haga]:
Wow, that's a
messed‐up nickname.
[Ikejiri]:
Their team used to be pretty
good though, right?
I think they went
to Nationals one time.
[Chaya]:
Yeah, well, but apparently
they're nothing
to write home
about these days.
Hey, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
We might actually
win this game!
We'll get past the
first round for once!
Not if you don't get off your
butts and start practicing.
C‐Captain!
Now go run
some laps!
[Team Miyagi]:
Yes sir...
[Ikejiri]:
You know...
This guy I played volleyball
with back in middle school,
ended up going
to Karasuno High.
Oh yeah? Well, that ought
to be an interesting reunion...
You know, I don't think we've
ever played them before.
Yeah, that's right...
He said that he saw Karasuno
play in the Spring Nationals
on TV and couldn't get
the place out of his head...
But I'm sure living close
to the school had something
to do with his
decision too, though.
[Ikejiri]:
Wonder how he's doing?
Good old Daichi.
Don't just stand there,
follow through!
Get it
together!
I'm sorry!
Go after every ball...
as if it's the last the
last piece of meat on Earth!
Don't take a play off.
If you do, that'll be
the one you cry about
[Keishin]:
after the game's done!
First of all, you guys
did a great job
playing against
Nekoma today.
Next order
of business...
The Inter High Preliminaries
start next month,
June 2nd
to be exact.
There's no regional prelim here,
so it's straight to prefectural.
[Keishin]:
Out of 60‐some teams
in the prefecture,
only one gets to advance
to the nationals...
Lose one match and
that's all she wrote.
[Keishin]:
If you want revenge
against Nekoma,
you have to get
number 1 in Miyagi.
Second place won't do.
Well, that's assuming
they can prove themselves
as the greatest high
school team in all of Tokyo.
I guarantee you
they can do it, coach!
Yeah! They're
gonna make it!
I want... to
challenge Nekoma again.
One more time!
[Keishin]:
You're ain't done, Ginger!
On your feet!
[Shoyo]:
Yes sir! Keep
'em coming!
[Daichi]:
Front!
[Shoyo]:
Hiya!
[Koshi]:
Cover it!
[Yu]:
Dude, that's nuts!
It's like a whole page!
Right?!
Let me see.
Hey, what's the matter?
What are you guys
so excited about?
Look.
[Ryunosuke]:
That's Ushiwaka from
Shiratorizawa Academy.
They named him one of the
three players to watch
in this year's Nationals.
That's the school
Kageyama didn't get into!
WOULD YOU SHUT IT?!
(snickers)
[Tobio]:
What are you two
losers laughing at?!
So, who's Ushiwaka?
You seriously don't
know who that is?
Of course not; he only cares
about the Tiny Giant.
Ushiwaka is his nickname.
[Ryunosuke]:
His real name is
Wakatoshi Ushijima,
and he's the number one
ace in the prefecture.
Yeah, just look at him.
[Daichi]:
Now that is what an ace
is supposed to look like.
Whoa! H‐hey why's everyone
staring at me?!
Is Ushiwaka the reason
you wanted to go
to Shiratorizawa
Academy?
Let me guess,
you wanted to march right up
to that legendary ace and go...
"Move it, you clumsy dumbass!"
like you tell Hinata!
Of course not!
So we can't play Nekoma...
unless we defeat them first?
[Keishin]:
Remember, boys...
Shiratorizawa's not
the only good team.
[Koshi]:
They're the biggest threat
based on last year though.
Thank you for stating
the obvious...
but there's a whole lot more
than just them.
[Keishin]:
Wakutani South has
great defense and solidarity.
Date Tech's been called
the "iron wall"
because their team has higher
blocks than anyone else around.
They're big guys.
From what I understand, these
guys beat us two to nothing
in the public prefectural
tournament back in March.
Wait a minute. Why does
that sound familiar?
In one game... every single one
of Asahi's spikes was shut down.
[Tobio]:
Was that the game Sugawara
was telling us about
before Asahi decided to
come back to the team?
Date Tech's team has
been top‐four material
for a good
long while, but...
[Keishin]:
Last year, they only
ranked in the top 16
after losing in round 3
to Shiratorizawa,
who won first place.
That's why they're not
seeded this year.
So depending on how
the brackets are laid out,
we could end up having to face
them in the first round.
The next team is...
oh that's right...
I heard you guys played
a practice game with them
not long ago.
[Keishin]:
Their captain possesses the
most offensive power on the team
on top of being an
excellent setter...
He might even be the top overall
player in the whole prefecture.
Aoba Johsai,
led by Toru Oikawa.
Oh yeah, the
Great King!
[Keishin]:
They ranked in last
year's top four too.
Now last but
definitely not least...
...Shiratorizawa, headed up by
that famous ace, Ushiwaka.
That's the short version.
I'll give you more
detailed info later.
[Daichi/Koshi]:
Wow, Coach Ukai's
got his stuff together...
You two smartasses
wanna pay attention
or you wanna share your thoughts
with the class?
Anyway, those are the four teams
I think we need to look out for.
That said, if you spend too much
time staring at the top,
you'll get the rug pulled out
from under you.
[Keishin]:
Don't let yourselves make
the mistake of thinking
we're the only team who's there
to take the number one spot.
We're not.
Sure, we're going to
be training our asses off,
but remember all
those other teams
will be training
their asses off too...
No matter who won last year
and who lost, everybody's aiming
to win it all...
Never forget that.
One more thing.
Don't let those bastards
call us the wingless
crows EVER again!
Right!
You all are still in here?!
[Takeda]:
I'm so sorry I'm late, I got
stuck in a meeting. Anyway...
I've got the bracket
for the Preliminaries!
[Yu]:
If our team and Date Tech
both clear the first round,
we'll be up against them
in round two.
We shouldn't get ahead
of ourselves you guys.
[Kei]:
Aoba Johsai's seeded
in our block this year.
That's not good.
[Ryunosuke]:
Ugh... come on!
[Tobio/Shoyo]:
I don't like
those odds...
Hey...
Did you already
forget what I told you?
[Keishin]:
If you focus
on the top‐
Yes we know, sir.
[Ikejiri]:
Which school
did you pick?
[Daichi]:
Karasuno.
Which one is that?
You know, the one
from Spring Nationals.
Oh, nice.
So uh where are
you headed?
I chose to go to Tokonami...
Sorry about that.
It's cool.
[Ikejiri]:
I dunno, dude...
I guess if I keep playing
volleyball in high school...
[Daichi]:
You should!
[Ikejiri]:
Maybe we'll get to play
against each other.
But, hey, Make sure
you're ready for my team
to wipe the floor
with yours, alright?
(chuckles)
[Daichi]:
Go on and try it.
C'mon, pick up the pace, dude,
it's gettin' late!
[Daichi]:
We'll stay focused...
One game at a time!
Um, hey, Daichi!
Oh... Hey there,
Michimiya.
I just thought you might
want a copy of the program
for the pep rally...
Volleyball's 5th.
Thanks a lot.
So do you have a speech
prepared for it?
Eh, not really.
I can't believe the Inter High
tourney is so close.
I hear the boys are getting
super psyched for that!
What was the name
of that other school
you guys used to play
practice games wi‐?
Sorry.
Nekoma?
That's the one.. I heard
you played them again.
Yeah.. So how's
the girls' team?
Being in separate gyms keeps
us pretty much out of touch
with each
other.
Eh... Everything's about the
same as always.
I can't get a lot of the girls
to come to morning practice...
so I guess I'm not much
of a captain, huh?
Oh well, we'll probably lose
in the first round anyway.
Oops.
Michimiya... You told me
you were going to win
for sure
this time.
Remember...? It doesn't matter
how strong or talented
your opponent is.
You won't win unless you try.
O‐oh, I'm sorry!
I'm sure you didn't come here
for me to lecture you...
Sorry it's what I do.
(giggles)
It's funny, that's exactly
the same lecture you gave me
back in
middle school.
I got my butt kicked in a
pre‐tournament practice game...
I was starting to give up
on winning for real.
Even if you're not confident
that you can win...
and even if everyone around
you says that it's impossible...
no matter what...
"Never say never... Don't admit
defeat 'til you've tried!"
Remember?
Sorry! I just have a habit
of chickening out
right before a tournament!
(whines)
I hate it!
I guess I shouldn't
be telling you what to do.
But we ARE both captains...
so I've always got your back...
Feel free to talk to me
anytime, okay?
(laughs)
You're so weird... Ha!
Okay! I'm good!
See ya, Daichi.
Thanks a lot!
Listen carefully...
my special protégé...
I want to crush you fair and
square at an official game,
where we both play the setter!
What's his deal?
Hell if I know.
(final whistle)
Hey, Asahi!
Club! Time to go!
That was
kinda rude.
Yeah, he's
not a dumb dog.
You don't have to do that
every time, Nishinoya...
I'm not gonna
run away.
[Asahi]:
I understand
everyone's got my back.
I will hold
my head up high...
and show everyone that
I'm Karasuno's ace!
Hinata!
Oh Sugawara.
Perfect timing...
I have something for you.
I made copies for
all the first‐years.
Signals.
My technical skill's not
as good as Kageyama's is,
so I can't always toss perfect
sets... but hand signals might
help us communicate our
next move during a game.
It might take some time but
it'll probably help for you
to memorize
all these.
Are you kidding me?!
This is gonna be so awesome;
I can't wait!
Great... I'm sure we'll have
to work out the kinks
before we can use
them in a game...
so let's practice
as much as we can.
Sure! I promise I'll learn
to hit any set!
Give me some time...
I can master it!
We use a triple front decoy...
and a back attack.
Keishin? Did you get any more
Mirin in stock yet?
Be right with you‐
Ahh...
[Keishin]:
(yelps)
[Old Lady]:
Well don't just throw it
So uh what's the matter
with you Tanaka?
The tournament's
almost here.
Yeah?
And tournaments are supposed
to be all dramatic
like we're marching into battle,
you know what I mean?
Uhh... sure.
And the most important
part of that
is having a
cute girlfriend.
Isn't your big sports
thing is tomorrow.
Yes, darling,
it is.
Isn't this the one you've
been practicing so hard for?
Yeah, baby, I can't thank you
enough for supporting my dream.
Oh, I don't mind at all!
(giggles)
Nothing makes me happier
than watching you play, baby!
Do you mean it?
[Ryunosuke's "girlfriend"]:
I really wanted to do something
for you before the game...
so I... um... made you this.
[Ryunosuke]:
Is that a
good luck charm?
That's right...
do your best, okay?
[Ryunosuke]:
See, I want to be more
fired up about the game...
but first I need a
girlfriend... one that's sexy!
Keep the crazy talk
to a minimum
or I'll tell the coach
to give me your spot.
Huh?!
[Chikara]:
Nice kill!
[Tobio]:
Excellent!
Hey Man‐bun.
Sir!
Would you say you're pretty
decent at back attacks?
[Keishin]:
Over here! I want
to try something.
So do boys think
you can handle that?
Well first we need to find
the right hitting height.
That looks tricky.
We'll do our best. Thank
you for your advice, Coach.
[Keishin]:
Hinata, keep diving
in just like before!
[Shoyo]:
Yes, sir!
[Daichi]:
Keep it up!
[Team Karasuno]:
Right!
[Tobio]:
Asahi, would you mind practicing
with me a little more?
You know... you're looking
really tired lately, Coach.
Come to think of it,
I noticed you've been showing up
right when our practice
starts every day.
Is everything going
okay at your job?
Mhmm... Up until recently the
store was all I had going on.
But now I've started
tending crops
in the early
morning hours,
so I've had to work
night shifts instead.
I've been thinking maybe
it's about time I stopped
relying so much
on my folks, you know?
Th‐thank you so much! I owe you
a nice bottle of sake!
Oh yeah?!
[Takeda]:
Wow, this is a lot of different
attack patterns to practice...
Are you planning
to use all of them?
[Keishin]:
Well... that depends.
It's important to make sure
these guys stay focused
on the game in
front of them.
That's not to say it's a bad
idea to go ahead and prepare
ourselves for all
the other games, too.
Don't tell 'em
I said that.
[Koshi]:
Great job, Hinata!
You did it!
That Hinata‐Sugawara quick
attack's looking good!
Oh I like that. The way you
did it that time felt perfect!
[Ryunosuke]:
Sweet!
Hey Asahi! What did you think
of that last one?
Too high? Too low? How was it?
C'mon you can be honest with me!
Uh, it was fine..
mhm.. good‐
Don't hold back!
Whatever criticism you have,
I can handle it!
Just tell me!
Uhhh, huh...
Okay, then, maybe aim it
a little higher?
And you could try sending it a
little further from the net too.
Right, thank you!
10 more tries!
[Tobio]:
Not enough?
How about 20?!
The tournament's
there's no time to start
changing things up.
Don't forget the
timing we practiced.
Right!
Oh, okay I get it; you want to
practice another pattern now.
[Daichi]:
Alright, let's go,
it's getting late.
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes, sir!
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
Haaaaa!
[Daichi]:
Could you two stop competing
and mop like normal people?
Hey Kiyoko. Daichi's gonna treat
I'm sorry... I have
something else to do.
[Koshi]:
Oh, okay. See ya.
Goodnight.
[Daichi]:
One for everybody.
[Tobio]:
Thank you.
[Shoyo]:
You're the best, captain!
[Yu]:
Yeah, thanks Daichi!
Everybody eat up so
we can go home.
Hey Tsukishima, the captain
bought everybody a meat bun,
you want one?
Sure, thank you.
Hey, did Tadashi
leave already?
He said there was somewhere he
needed to go on the way home.
[Tadashi]:
Um...
Uh sorry, we're actually
closed for the day.
I'm Yamaguchi from
the volleyball club.
Right! So that's
where I know you from.
Look... The jump
float serve...
Do you think you can
teach me how to do it?
[Shimada]:
Oh, yeah...
I used it when we played
each other, didn't I?
I would, but the Prelims
are right around the corner
aren't they? If you're
wanting to learn before then,
I don't think you
have enough time.
You're probably right.
Odds are I won't get
to play in the game, anyway.
First‐years don't usually
have a chance to play
if there are third‐years
on the team... But still...
Despite all that... I never want
to be the only first‐year
on the bench again!
[♪♪♪♪]
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheers)
I say we call it early
and get some rest.
Right!
Okay...., let's
go home‐
W‐Wait, don't leave yet!
We have one more comment.
It's from Kiyoko.
(surprised gasps)
I'm not very...
good with words...
So I kinda
did something.
[Kiyoko]:
If you please, Takeda.
[Takeda]:
Of course.
[Kiyoko]:
Ah! Wait, sir... Please,
let me take that up there.
[Takeda]:
I got it.
What is
that thing?
[Takeda]:
And, go!
Whoa!
[Koshi]:
We have a banner?
I found it while I was cleaning
up, so I thought I'd wash it.
YEAH! I'm
fired up!
You're awesome, Kiyoko!
Thanks for everything!
We're ready now!
Let's win this thing! Huh?
Not yet... Listen guys...
[Daichi]:
I think there's more.
Huh?!
You...
Huh?
You can do it.
Uh...
Kiyoko! She's never done
anything like this before!
Him, too?
Kiyoko! She's never done
anything like this before!
I don't get it; why are
they so freaked out by this?
Most of the time,
you can't shut them up.
[Upperclassmen]:
(dramatic sobbing)
[Kei]:
What the hell?!
Calm down already!
We can win!...
The first round is all ours!
Yeah!
(collective cheering)
I'm the first one here!
[Shoyo]:
Hey, get back
here, Kageyama!
You like that?
I beat you this time.
[Tobio]:
Now the score's:
31 ‐ 30 with one tie.
That's wrong.
Hell no, it's not!
I'm ahead of you!
Yeah, you are...
but that makes it 30 ‐ 32.
I lost to you this
time last year, too.
You beat me bad.
You might be the king who
rules the court for now...
But I'm gonna win!
One day I'll stay in the court
longer than you!
Listen to me.
I'll beat you! If it takes 10
or even 20 more years, I WILL!
Wait a sec... You think one day,
your dumb ass'll be on my level?
Yeah... That's right!
Even the best in all of Japan?
And the world?
The world?!
[Shoyo]:
U‐um ... Obviously!
And I told you,
not to call me the king.
Let's go.
That hurt...
The real journey
begins today.
Yeah!
[Ryunosuke]:
(blubbering)
[Kei]:
[Ryunosuke]:
Kiyoko said
it's okay to cry!
[Kei]:
Yeah... but that
was yesterday.
[Yu]:
Dammit, don't
make me relive it!
[Kei]:
Ugh. You guys
are pathetic.
[Kei]:
Next Haikyu!! "We're back."