[TOBIO, internal]
Be extra alert.
Ball... blocker... spiker.
Observe every single move.
[TOBIO, internal]
Line up your timing with
the spiker's optimum
hitting height...
[TOBIO, internal]
And shoot!
(surprised)
Wow.
They did it again!
[HISASHI]
They turned it around!
One more point and they're
gonna take the first set.
His timing's better...
It's improving by the second!
[KOSHI]
Impressive, this must be
Kageyama's setting ability
at its best!
[SHOYO] Yeah!
[RYUNOSUKE] Yeah! That
was freakin' perfect!
[KOSHI] But the person who
brought it out of him...
was Hinata.
[SHOYO] Thanks!
[SHOYO] (laugh)
Alright! We're on a roll!
(whistle)
[KOSHI, internal]
The kid does have some patience.
[SHOYO] (smacked in the face)
[TOBIO] Oops.
[KOSHI, internal]
I've never seen anybody take
a set directly to the face
before...
[KEI] You're not getting past me
this time, kid!
[KOSHI] (surprised)
Oh really?
Yikes... He'd better keep
a close eye on Tanaka too.
(set ending whistle)
Dammit.
Ohhh! You like that?
'Sup, Tsukishima?! Not talkin'
so big anymore, huh?!
[SHOYO]
Yeah, what he said!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Ooh, I wish you'd
try something, boy!
[SHOYO] Yeah, go ahead and try!
(RYUNOSUKE growling)
[KOSHI] Why are you doing more
trash talking than Hinata is?
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?
Exactly! Without the
first‐years, you never
would have made that hit!
Yeah, don't get
all cocky!
Keep your clothes on!
Look, I don't need any
more smart remarks
from the peanut gallery!
[CHIKARA KOSHI] (surprised)
[HISASHI]
You know... Tsukishima's
team doesn't have
a lot of initiative
on their side...
So the best thing they can do
is try to block all those
aggressive attacks.
(whistle)
[KAZUHITO] Time for the second
set!
Ready!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Yeah!
[TOBIO] Alright!
(smacked) (fall down)
[RYUNOSUKE] (stumble)
(determined)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Not today! Suck it, nerds!
[SHOYO TOBIO] (panting)
[HISASHI] Whoa...
Kageyama's pretty amazing. And
man, all those precision sets!
He's really gotta stay focused.
Not to mention Hinata's running
around even more than usual.
Yeah... but...
[DAICHI] (slide)
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Yesss!
They're having fun.
(whistle)
[SHOYO TOBIO]
(heavy breathing)
[KOSHI]
Good game!
[DAICHI] (gulp) Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey... Quick
question, you guys.
After what you both said
before, it's like you already
knew they were able to master
that move... You're telepathic?!
[DAICHI KOSHI]
Huh?
Let them work on a few
combinations,
and Karasuno will
have the perfect team!
It's up to you to use his
talents more effectively!
What?! That is ridiculous!
All I was telling Kageyama to do
was start setting Hinata up with
something he could hit!
Yeah, sorry... I'm afraid
I'm not a psychic either...
I just thought Hinata could
adapt to his crazy sets.
Anyway... I gotta
admit I'm happy.
(confused) What?
(heavy breathing)
[DAICHI]
Basically... I was hoping for
something like THIS...
...and it turned into THIS.
[DAICHI]
He may be green, but
Hinata's got raw speed
and jumping power...
Kageyama's advanced
techniques are a perfect
complement to that.
And When you pair them up,
they bring out the best in
each other.
[DAICHI] Turns out... we got
even better results
[TOBIO] Just forget it...
Nobody cares.
[DAICHI] than I had hoped for.
[SHOYO] It's important,
okay? See? Look.
[SHOYO]
Tsukishima!
[TADASHI]
Huh?
[KEI]
What now?
You're supposed to shake hands
before and after a game...
I guess we sorta skipped the
first one...
And even though I may not
really like this at all...
you're my teammate now.
(annoyed)
Just do it! Hey look,
I know it's awkward...
but take it from me, if you
can't play nice with your
teammates, these guys'll kick
you right out of the gym!
Look, I know I wasn't around
when it happened or anything...
but I'm pretty sure that was
because you disobeyed the
captain, picked a fight...
AND knocked the Vice
Principal's toupee off.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
(startled)
Y‐you don't have to
get into the details.
[SHOYO]
Shake my hand!
(jumping, roughhousing)
[KEI]
Hey! Gghh... Stop
that, you idiot!
So dramatic...
First‐years, right?
[KEI] (horrified)
[TADASHI] I am SO sorry
that happened!
[DAICHI]
Tsukishima.
So what'd you think?
Did you have some fun?
It wasn't a big deal?
They've got a star from a great
school...
A bunch of lowly commoners
like us never even stood a
chance and you know it.
[DAICHI]
Really?
It seemed like a
big deal to you.
You fought pretty hard
out there... Here.
(annoyed)
[SHOYO]
Captain!
[TADASHI KEI]
(startled) Hm?
[DAICHI]
(startled) Yes?
[DAICHI] Kiyoko! They
should be here, right?
Hm? Mm‐hm...
Huh? What?
[SHOYO]
Hm?
[SHOYO] WHOAAAA!
[TOBIO] (startled)
(excited laughter)
I'm fairly sure I got the
right sizes for you...
Let me know if you
need replacements.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Thanks!
Go ahead, why don't
you try it on?
I can just try
it on later‐
Put it on, bro! Get over
yourself, would ya?
(KEI annoyed)
(EVERYONE chanting)
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
[KOSHI RYUNOSUKE]
Whoa!
(SHOYO containing excitement)
(SHOYO excited prancing)
[RYUNOSUKE] Whooaa Lookin'
good, my man!
[KOSHI]
Yeah, I agree, it
really suits you!
[DAICHI] On behalf of the
Karasuno Volleyball Club...
[RYUNOSUKE KOSHI TADASHI] Hm?
[DAICHI] Welcome...
[ALL]
...to the team!
[TADASHI SHOYO TOBIO]
(moved)
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Thanks!
[DAICHI] (sigh)
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey, strike a pose!
[DAICHI] Well, that's
the first step.
[SHOYO] Like this?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Not bad! Now try this way! Bah!
[DAICHI] I take it you
and Tanaka gave those two
[SHOYO] Yeah, Like that?
[DAICHI] a little extra
help, didn't you?
[KOSHI]
Huh?! No.. Why would
you think that?!
[DAICHI] Anyway, for
now, I'm just glad
[RYUNOSUKE] Now we're talkin'!
[DAICHI] everything worked
out... Thanks a lot, you two.
[RYUNOSUKE] At this rate
we could start
[RYUNOKSUKE] a badass
volleyball street gang!
[KOSHI KIYOKO] Hm?
[KOSHI KIYOKO]
Good work.
[DAICHI] (shocked)
I didn't do anything.
Hey, Hinata! Less talking,
more practicing!
[TOBIO]
Let's run through the quick
attack again while you're
still remembering how!
[SHOYO]
Okay!
[TOBIO]
Throw the ball over here,
Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?! Aren't you guys tired?!
[TAKEDA] (running)
(door opening)
[TAKEDA]
Hey! We got it!
We got something!
(TAKEDA panting)
[TOBIO SHOYO] Huh?
A practice game! With one
of the area's top 4!
Aoba‐Johsai High School!
Those guys?!
[KEI] Come on...
[TADASHI] No way.
We get to play against
one of the top 4?!
Aoba‐Johsai, huh?
[TAKEDA]
Oh, it's you two! You must be
Hinata and Kageyama, right?
Uh... Who's that?
No idea.
My name's Ittetsu Takeda...
Your club advisor.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Hey.
I'm clueless about this game...
so I can't coach you
on your technique...
But I promise I'll try to
help you guys out wherever
I can.. okay?
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Uh, sure.
So what's up?
Oh yeah, the game...
Aoba Johsai, or Seijoh,
as some people call it,
was the only school
who said yes.
That's crazy! So how'd you get a
game with a team like them?
Wait, did you
beg again?
No, not this time!
I AM good at begging...
but I didn't have to.
(relieved sighs)
Although...
there is one
little condition.
What's that?
[TAKEDA]
Kageyama has to be the setter
for the whole game.
[TOBIO] (surprised)
Huh?
What the hell is that?!
So they're not interested in
playing against Karasuno,
but they've got some kinda
special beef with Kageyama, huh?
What are we, just a joke to
them? What's their deeeeal?
(nervous) Um... No... I don't
think that's the case...
[KOSHI]
Let's do it... It's an
opportunity.
You sure about this, Suga?!
You're the official setter..
Doesn't this bug you, man?!
[KOSHI]
Well... It's a chance for
us to use Hinata's and
Kageyama's attack...
Now we can see how good it
truly measures up against
a really good team.
(surprised)
(unsure)
Okay... what are
the details, then?
Well uh... let's see...
The schedule's a little tight,
but it's next Tuesday.
[TAKEDA]
There's only time for the one
game since it's after school.
[SHOYO] It's a real game!
[TAKEDA] We'll borrow a school
bus and head straight there
[SHOYO] A real freakin' game!
My very first one
[TAKEDA] after homeroom's over,
[SHOYO] since I came to Karasuno
High and joined the team!
[TAKEDA] so make sure you have
all your stuff ready to go.
[TAKEDA] Don't be late.
[ALL]
Right!
[KAZUHITO]
Good work, guys!
[CHIKARA HISASHI]
Thanks!
[TOBIO]
Suga!
[KOSHI] Huh?
(TOBIO panting)
I know it's not fair... that
I'll be in the starting
line‐up...
but I promise to you I'll
earn my spot from now on!
[KOSHI] What?
[TOBIO] (confused)
Oh.. Sorry... I guess
I'm just surprised
that you care how I feel about
the whole thing.. That's all.
Hm? I don't follow.
[KOSHI]
You've got more stamina and
raw talent than me anyway‐
Who cares?! That's great and
all, but they're not the same as
having experience! Besides...
[DAICHI RYUNOSUKE] Suga!
[SHOYO] Sugawara!
Um... you see, the rest of
the team... um... they...
well, they trust you.
[KOSHI, internal] (startled)
Whoa... That one bad game in
middle school must have really
screwed with his head...
[TOBIO]
Anyway... I swear...
I won't lose!
Yeah... I'll do my best too.
(SHOYO laughing)
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey Suga! Daichi
said he was gonna treat us to
some food!
[KOSHI] So
uh, I was thinking...
[KOSHI]
Most players from Kitagawa First
end up going to Aoba‐Johsai High
School, right?
[TOBIO]
Yeah, as far as I know.
[SHOYO, internal]
Does that mean we'll be up
against Kageyama's old
teammates?
Yeah, that's what I thought...
So, uh, you think you're gonna
be okay with that.
Huh? Well, I guess it
might be weird if we
were on the same team.
But since we're opponents,
I'll fight them with
everything I've got.
Okay... Good to hear.
[TOBIO] Thanks.
Are you sure you're okay
with this, Suga?
I mean, c'mon... How can you
just sit here and take this?!
(sad smile) I'm not thrilled
about it... but...
We gotta show those guys how
much Kageyama's changed
since middle school...
It'll be fine.
[DAICHI] That's right.
[RYUNOSUKE KOSHI TOBIO] Hm?
[SHOYO]
(happy) (thrilled)
And Kageyama's not
the only one of us
that they'll have to watch
out for. Right, Hinata?
[SHOYO] (mouthful)
Sorry, what was that?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Why are you stuffing your face
before the rest of us?!
[TOBIO] You're such a pig!
[KEISHIN]
Hey, volleyball loser!
No fighting in
front of my store!
[BOTH] Sorry, sir.
[SHOYO] (dropped)
[SHOYO, internal]
That's right... we're the
volleyball club!
Everyone here is a part of the
same group. The same team.
Wow, thanks... Any
curry buns in there?
Save some room for
dinner, would ya?
Hey! Come get your food!
[TADASHI]
Thank you!
[SHOYO, internal]
We are a team!
[DAICHI]
Kageyama, could I have a word?
[TOBIO] Uh, sure.
[KEISHIN] Keep the noise down.
[KOSHI] Okay.
I've been brainstorming about
what Hinata's position should be
for the practice game.
[DAICHI] What do you think?
Well...
[DAICHI]
Let's talk positions
for the practice game.
Here's the plan I came up with.
[DAICHI]
I'd like to have you
two work as a pair.
[SHOYO TOBIO, internal]
A pair?
[DAICHI]
And Tsukishima is
our tallest player,
so I want to see how much
of an advantage that gives
us over Seijoh.
Fiiiiine.
[TADASHI, internal]
All the other first‐years
are special...
Wait, why is Hinata in the one
position that needs a tall guy?!
Huh?! He's right; why are
Tsukishima and I both playing
the middle blocker position?!
Time out... I‐I think I
need to do a quick review
of all the positions.
[TAKEDA]
The setter... That's the control
tower, the one who sets people
up and starts the attacks.
The wing spiker... He's the
all‐rounder that sort of
maintains the balance between
offense and defense.
The middle blockers... They
block the other team's attacks
and score points using quick
attacks.
They also act as a decoy to lead
the opposing blockers astray.
Does that sound about right?
Well, there's another one that
specializes in defense...
but we'll skip
that part for now.
[TOBIO]
Listen up, Hinata.
Let's call you...
Number One Decoy!
[SHOYO]
YEAAAAHHH! I'm the
number one... decoy?
(dejected)
Man, that sounds lame.
We'll use you as a distraction
while we rake in points.
We'll be using quick attacks...
That way, the other spikers can
do some damage!
[SHOYO] Huh?!?
You take the tall
Tsukishima guys...
But you can lead them
right into our trap like
the idiots they are.
How cool is that?
(excited)
That sounds so awesome!
Hey! You better not be
implying Tsukki's an idiot!
Shut up, Tadashi.
Oh, sorry, Tsukki.
[TOBIO]
On the other hand,
if you're not at the
top of your game,
then all our other
attacks will fall apart.
(gulp)
Stop it!
You're gonna put too
much pressure on him.
Don't fall apart...
[DAICHI] You broke him!
Yeah, but blocking is the
most important thing here.
[RYUNOSUKE]
No matter how high he can jump,
he's still a shorty pants...
By the time he gets to his
highest point, the taller
guys'll already be there.
[TOBIO]
Already thought of that. Hinata
won't be focusing on blocking...
Instead of trying to slap
down a spike, he can just
give it a tap...
We'll use his ridiculously
fast reflexes to their
fullest potential.
[TOBIO]
If he taps an enemy spike, it
should slow down enough.
[DAICHI] I got it!
[TOBIO] Then we just collect
the ball and counterattack.
You think he can pull that
off without practice?
[DAICHI] I doubt it.
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?
Well, not on the
first try at least.
But you know, sometimes the
attempt is what really what
matters...
It is a practice game, right?
Right.
Besides... The only ones on
our team who can beat him
in airborne combat are
Tsukishima and Kageyama.
So I just want you
to do your best.
RIGHT! I won't mess up!
I'll earn lots of points and
be the perfect decoy!
I'll serve, I'll block, I'll do
quick attacks,
whatever else you want
me to do! Wahhh!
[DAICHI] Whoa! Hinata,
calm down!
[DAICHI]
We've lost him! I think
he just short‐circuited!
[RYUNOSUKE] (freak out)
Oh crap, we killed him!
(school bell ringing)
[YUI]
Huh?! Daichi!
Huh? Hey, Michimiya...
What's up?
Are you guys really
playing Seijoh tomorrow?
That's so weird.
[DAICHI]
(laugh) Yeah, Takeda really
worked hard to get that matchup.
Aren't you nervous?
Huh?
It's just that those guys were
in the top 4 in the whole
prefecture last year...
Don't you think they'll
wipe the floor with you?
[DAICHI]
(chuckle) You just think that
because you haven't seen these
crazy first‐years we just got.
[YUI] Hm? Oh, I heard!
[DAICHI] (surprised)
They're the ones who knocked the
Vice Principal's toupee off his
head the first d‐
[DAICHI]
Ahhh shushushushushush!
Ssh!
(muffled nod)
(sigh) They still have a lot
of work to do...
but if they keep trying...
I really believe Karasuno High's
gonna have the perfect
volleyball team one day.
Ohhh.
[TOBIO]
Are first‐years allowed
in the club room?
[KOSHI]
Sure, why wouldn't they be?
Good afternoon!
[ALL]
Hey, dudes.
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Hey guys.
[SHOYO] (amazed)
Yeah, it's not that amazing,
Hinata... It's just a club room.
But I've never had a chance to
be in one before! Uh!
And I beat this the same one
used by the Tiny Giant.
[RYUNOSUKE]
You must be excited about
your debut game tomorrow.
[SHOYO] (startled)
[RYUNOSUKE] Well.. practice
game, but who's to judge!
[KOSHI] (listening)
[RYUNOSUKE] Seijoh's gym
is freakin' huge!
[RYUNOSUKE] And their guys
are just as big, so don't
freak out when you see 'em.
What's up?
Hey.
Boss!
[SHOYO] No!
[RYUNOSUKE] No?
I'm not gonna freak out, okay?!
I'm gonna play my
best game ever!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh, dude... You do know your
jacket doesn't belong on your
legs, right?
[DAICHI TOBIO] (stunned)
(RYUNOSUKE laughing)
[DAICHI] Kageyama... can he
survive tomorrow?
[RYUNOSUKE] Man, you're a mess!
[RYUNOSUKE] You're freakin'
out even more than I thought
you would!
[TOBIO] Hm? What do you mean?
[DAICHI] The only game
experience he's got is that one
tournament in middle school.
[RYUNOSUKE] (laughter)
Seriously, just take a chill
pill, would you?!
[SHOYO] It's not what
it looks like!
[DAICHI] He must
be panicking and
[DAICHI] obsessing pretty
bad over this.
[SHOYO] I did it on purpose,
I swear!
[RYUNOSUKE] Doesn't
look like it!
[DAICHI] I'm kinda worried...
I hope he'll be okay.
But everybody gets nervous
once in a while.
Shame on you! You shouldn't pick
on the poor guy just because he
has a little case of the
first‐time jitters!
[TOBIO]
(startled) Huh?!
Anything I say to him turns
into more pressure.
Hinata... The club room key‐
(startled) Y‐yeah sure, I
can take it, no problem!
No, I just wanted to show
you where we keep it.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm
sorry! I'm sorry! I'm
sorry! I'm sorry!
Well, what do you expect
right before his big debut?
Yeah, it's probably best
to leave him alone.
Probably.
[SHOYO, internal]
I have to be on top
of it tomorrow!
It's not middle school or
the 3‐on‐3 game anymore.
If I suck...
[SHOYO]
They'll just replace me!
(internal) Agh, no! I can't
get swapped out!
I get to stand in the court
with some big‐time volleyball
players!
I want to stay in
for the whole game!
(stomach gurgling)
[SHOYO]
I can't mess this up.. I can't
mess this up.. I can't mess this
up... (bumped)
Oh, I'm sorry, you're just so
short, I didn't see you there.
(snickering)
[SHOYO] Oh... yeah.
[BOTH] Uh?
[SHOYO] I can't mess this up...
I can't mess this up... I can't
mess this up...
What's with him?
Beats me.
[KOSHI]
By the way... Could
you do us a favor
and take a break from
messing with Hinata.
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey, I
can't find my jersey!
[KOSHI] You're pressuring him.
[TOBIO] (taken aback)
Messing with him?
[TOBIO, internal]
When have I ever
messed with him?
I think I'd remember that.
(TOBIO thinking)
[ALL, internal]
He doesn't know...
[RYUNOSUKE]
(running) Hinata!
(GIRL startled)
[RYUNOSUKE] Are you wearing
my uniform pants, you little
doofus?! (growl)
[SHOYO] Huh?
[GIRL] Tanaka, you pervert,
put some pants on!
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?!
[GIRL] God, you
are such a creep!
(RYUNOSUKE embarrassed)
[TOBIO] Hm?
(dogs barking)
Darn iiiiiit!
[SHOYO]
I can't sleep!
But I gotta get some rest before
the game tomorrowwwwww!
What do I dooo‐
[NATSU] Shut up, Shoyo!
[SHOYO]
(surprised) Uh, sorry...
(NATSU annoyed)
[TAKEDA]
Ready?
[ALL]
Ready!
[TAKEDA] Good!
(laughter) Hey, Hinata, you
should have a little snack!
(worried) Whoa! You
don't look so good, pal!
Huh? Oh no, I'm fine, I just
didn't sleep much last night...
(about to puke)
Sorry... Do you... mind
if I open the wi‐ (gag)
(SHOYO hurls)
[RYUNOSUKE] (scream) STOP THE
BUS! STOP THE BUS RIGHT NOW!
[SHOYO] (sick)
[RYUNOSUKE] (freaking out)
[DAICHI]
Did he...
[KOSHI]
Uh‐huh...
[TOBIO]
We're in trouble.
[DAICHI KOSHI TOBIO]
Oh no...
[KOSHI]
Is he gonna be okay, Daichi?
[DAICHI]
Uh, yeah...
[KOSHI]
Wow, you don't look too hot.
[DAICHI]
Yeah, I think the smell is
making me sick too... (gag)
[KOSHI]
Oh god, open all
the windows, now!
[KOSHI]
Next Haikyu!
"An Interesting Team."