Oooh!
[Koshi]:
We have a banner?
Y..you can do it.
[Upperclassmen]:
(loud sobbing)
[Kei]:
What the hell?!
Calm down already!
We can win!
The first round
is all ours!
Yeah!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Huh?
Hey.
So... looks like
it's time for‐
Don't say it.
Uh..do not say it.
You were about to start
talking about something
really sappy,
weren't you?
Yeah, something about this
being our last tournament...
Who wants to hear
that crap?
I guess this shall truly
be our last tournament.
Yeah.
It's so crazy...
We've all been through
so much together.
That kind of talk
makes me feel like
we're planning for it
to be over. Stop it!
Aw come on, what's
so bad about it?!
I had this whole big plan
to boost you guys' morale
yesterday, by getting all of
the third‐year players together
after practice for a quiet
talk under the stars,
so we could get ready...
But then you guys
just up and left!
That surprise from Kiyoko
more than doubled
the team's
morale though.
Well... yeah...
I guess that's
true, but...
[Koshi]:
All we need to worry about today
is winning the first two rounds
so we can make it
to day two.
I don't want to talk like
the year is finished.
Let's just play
the game... and win it!
[Daichi]:
Don't sweat
the other stuff.
Yeah.
[Daichi]:
We're counting
on you, Ace...
[Shoyo]:
Morning!
Just... play hard.
Daichi being nice
is freaking me out.
Yeah, it doesn't
suit him does it.
Oh I'm sorry, I can be
mean if that works better.
[Shoyo]:
Good morning!
[Tobio]:
Morning!
Hey!
Good morning! We'll unlock
the room for ya.
Time to go.
Yep!
[Shibuya]:
What do you think
Karasuno's like?
Hopefully... they're
not a bunch of giants.
[Chaya]:
Eh, don't worry
about it, man.
I heard they haven't
been too hot recently.
[OFU Member 1]:
Shiratorizawa's
gonna clean house.
Nah, Aoba Johsai's a
bigger threat this year.
Now that Oikawa's a
third‐year, they're even
tougher than
they were before.
Plus their first‐years
are improving really fast.
But, that's
Seijoh for ya.
Eh... I dunno...
Y'think they can win the
block against Date Tech?
All I know, is I'm glad
they're not in Block A.
Let's see...
Who is in Block A?
[OFU Member 2]:
What does the
kanji say?
[OFU Member 1]:
Karasuno? Oh, yeah!
They might have a shot.
Aren't they supposed
to be tough?
[OFU Member 2]:
Yeah, a few years
ago, maybe...
Now they suck so bad they've
even got a lame nickname.
[OFU Member 1]:
Oh really? So, then,
what are they called?
[OFU Member 2]:
Uh, something about how
they're fallen champions.
Oh! "The Wingless Crows."
Maybe you should
keep it down.
What did you just say?!
"Wingless crows?" Well‐
Cut it out, now...
I'm really sorry.
Uh, it's cool.
Do I need to
get you a leash?
Ugh... no...
[Attendee 1]:
They're kinda scary.
[Attendee 2]:
That guy looks like
a grown man.
Wait! Is that who
I think it is?!
Yeah, that's Asahi!
Wait... what?...
Who's that?
You mean you
don't know?!
[Brown‐haired Student]:
He made his goons beat
up some guys from North High.
Let's teach these
fools a lesson.
Oh no, a fight!
Stay here!
I'll go call
the authorities!
[Brown‐haired Student]:
Then he got caught selling
stuff on the street.
Fifty thousand.
Miss, did you drop
your handkerchief?
I'm so sorry!
[Brown‐haired Student]:
He got held
back five years.
[Black‐haired Student]:
Dude, he's old!
Oh boy, here we
go again, Daichi.
It's hard to avoid that
with your looks.
Wh‐what's the matter
with the way I look?!
I'm a taller guy, so
what's wrong with me wanting
to look all tough
and wild?!
Okay, yeah, you see...
Nobody who's tough or wild
would ever say
that, dude.
(laughs)
What's the big deal, dude?
Who cares how you look?
See, this is what
wild looks like.
[Attendee]:
Hey, check that out.
I guess the banner
really did the trick.
Do you really think so?
I mean, it did a lot more
good than anything I said.
She is smokin'...
Hey, I dare you
to talk to her.
Oh man, you think
she could handle it.
Cut that out.
She just hit me...
That was awesome...
Hey, see that short
guy over there?
[Brown‐haired Student]:
I think that's Nishinoya
from Chidoriyama.
He won "best libero"
back in middle school.
That's all the strength I need!
Whoa... really?
And that's not all.
Y'see that guy there?
He's that scary‐looking
setter dude
that everyone's been
talking about.
[Brown‐haired Student]:
The King of the Court
from Kitagawa First!
[Black‐haired Student]:
But why Karasuno?
[Brown‐haired Student]:
Beats me...
I heard he got a bad rep
in middle school though,
so maybe that's why.
Okay, then who's
the carrot top?
[Black‐haired Student]:
Is he some kind
of living legend too?
Whoa!
Um... I don't
think so...
He's weird.
[Shoyo]:
Wow, there's
so many people!
Hey, the summit!
That's exactly
where I'm headed!
Stay outta my way!
What's with you?!
You can't say things like that!
I'm so sorry he's a little off!
Okay...
This place is huge!
It smells like Air Salonpas!
What are you
talking about?
That is what makes a tournament
smell like a real tournament!
I know, right?!
Mm‐hm...
[Attendee 1]:
They're here!
[Attendee 2]:
Whoa, they're tall!
It's Date Tech!
Where are his eyebrows?!
Who the hell are y‐
[Moniwa]:
Hey! Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, dude!
Please don't do that!...
I am so sorry
about him, everybody!
Um, can I get
a little help here!
Yeah, yeah, please excuse
our giant friend here.
He has a way of automatically
picking out the ace
on every team he sees.
[Futakuchi]:
Anyway... hope
you're ready...
'cause you're about
to lose miserably.
[Moniwa]:
Why do you guys always
have to be so rude?
That's not good
sportsmanship at all!
Well that
was something...
I wasn't really
sure how to respond.
Yeah.
I'm impressed you were
able to look him in the eye‐
Oh man... That
was really scary.
How are you a badass
on the court
but a wimp
everywhere else?
Damn Noya,
that was cold!
[Ikejiri]:
Sawamura.
Been a while.
Oh, Ikejiri! Hey, uh...
I'll catch you guys later!
[Team Karasuno]:
Okay, see ya!
[Daichi]:
Long time, no see.
[Ikejiri]:
Yeah... You look
bigger now.
[Daichi]:
Really? I'm the same
height as before.
Uh, that's not
what I meant.
So I'm fatter?!
No, not that.
[Ikejiri]:
His build is different,
and he looks more intense.
I'm sure he's
training harder too.
I saw you at the entrance
a while ago...
but I was too intimidated to
say something to you.
Wait what,
are you serious?
Well no, I understand.
I guess some of our guys
don't look very
approachable, do they?
It's just... they all seem
really tough... And so do you.
You think so?
The thing is, my school
has kind of a small‐time team.
Listen uh‐
Wait, forget
I said that!
Look, it doesn't matter
how big we are...
or how big we
used to be...
'Cause we're
here now, so...
fact is, we're gonna wipe
the floor with you!
[Chizuru]:
I'm so nervous!
[Manami]:
I know. Me too.
Was it just me, or were
their spikes really on point
during practice
before?
Yeah they did make
the top 8 last year...
Well, maybe hopefully we
won't get matched with them!
[Chizuru]:
We should have showed up
to morning practice more.
[Daichi]:
Remember... it doesn't
matter how strong or talented
your opponent is.
You won't win unless you try.
If you look back now...
we had more than enough time.
[Yui]:
We could have practiced
a lot more than we did.
We didn't have our
priorities straight.
Yeah well it's too
late for that, Yui‐
But none of that matters now!
We've got 45 minutes 'til
the starting whistle blows.
All we can do now is make sure
we're properly warmed up,
then play to the best of our
ability 'til the very end!
And maybe... we can win!
Gather 'round, everyone...
Let's huddle!
You heard the
Captain, ladies!
What?
Karasunoooo... fight!
Yeah!
Hinata... You better not
be about to puke again.
No! I'm mediating!
What is that
supposed to mean?!
Um, I think he means
"meditating".
Nah... Looks like
he might pee himself.
You must be freaked out over
what happened with Date Tech.
I‐I no‐ I'm NOT freaked out,
I'm just finding my chi.
[Ryunosuke]:
Your chi?!
Oh great...
He's losing it...
We're gonna have
to do something fast.
[Tobio]:
Or else it'll be the
Seijoh game all over again.
Wow, Asahi, you're just
as much of a coward,
but you don't seem
to be that nervous.
He just called
me a coward?
Well I have a trick for
getting rid of pre‐game jitters.
Just think about something
totally awful that happened
in your past...
The more terrifying
the better.
[Asahi]:
And then you think, "This isn't
the worst thing there is;
I can handle it."
Something in my past
that was really scary.
Hmm... Hmm... Hmm...
Hm? Hinata?
Yup... I think
I'll be okay.
Snap out of it,
we need you!
If you had this
amazing coping strategy,
then why did you get all
bent out of shape last time
we played
Date Tech?
Listen Noya, that's the
kind of thing you think
but don't actually
say, understand?
Uh, well I didn't really have
time to think of anything
scary that day.
I couldn't concentrate,
and it takes a lot of effort to
come up with the mental image!
You guys get that, right?
Lame excuse.
Everybody ready?
This is our first game...
Now, let's go get warmed up.
Right!
It's finally happening!
[Shoyo]:
Whoaaaaa!
This place... It's huge!
Could you pick your jaw up
off the floor, please?
You're too serious!
At least I'm not
having a freak‐out!
H‐Hey, let me
go, Kageyama!
Ready, boys?... 'Bout time to
get in a few practice reps!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
[Irihata]:
Let's go get a
closer look at 'em.
I want to see those
two Karasuno first‐years
do that quick
attack of theirs.
Yeah.
Aoba Johsai's here.
Man, those guys
are tall...
They look like they're
pretty tough, too.
Well it depends; a big
part of how good a team is,
is their setter...
Wait, where is he?
Where'd Oikawa go?
Uhhh...
he's uh...
Tell us; we
don't have all day!
Wow you're
like so tall!
Yeah, and you're
so handsome too!
Iwaizumi.
Got it.
These are amazing!
You really made them yourself?
Yeah, I stayed up really
late last night baking!
Well that makes me feel
really special; thank you.
Ah! I‐It was nothing!
Could I please take a quick
photo with you, Oikawa?
You want a picture of me?
Absolutely‐ ahhh!
(shrieking)
Poor Oikawa!
Unbelievable! Not even
the coach has ever HIT me!
Sorry ladies, have to take a
rain check on that photo.
Aww...
[Shoyo]:
It's onion head!
What the hell's
an onion head?
You're the only one
it could be.
Huh?!
[Toru]:
Yoo‐hoo!
Kageyama and Small Fry!
How's that cute little
combo move comin' along?
[Shoyo]:
Great King!
Would you please
stop doing that?
[Toru]:
So you got a libero. He wasn't
with you at the practice game.
Throw me one more!
[Hajime]:
I think that
big guy's new, too.
I want to try that again!
Hey...
That coach... I don't think I've
ever seen him around before.
Make every second count!
Ginger, move your ass!
O‐Okay!
So they have new players
and a new coach to boot...
Wonder if that means Karasuno's
improved their game, any.
[Takeda]:
Well, today's the day.
I can't believe it...
our team's about to play here...
in this giant venue.
It's making me... nervous just
watching from the sidelines.
But that's why...
it's important to do
everything we can,
to the best
of our ability.
Yes.
And... go!
[Shoyo]:
I'm ready!
Date Tech...
[Yu]:
Asahi!
[Shoyo]:
Right here!
Listen I'm worried
about Date Tech too...
but I won't be defeated...
Because my mind's on
victory... And remember...
[Shoyo]:
Got it!
We have to remain focused
on the opponents in front of us.
Yeah.
Captains!
Thank you for the game.
Alright, you guys!
[Daichi]:
Line up!
[Contestants]:
Thank you for the game!
Go, go, Date Tech,
Date Tech, here we go!
It's the first
game of the season.
And that kinda pressure can
make anybody nervous enough
to throw off their game. So our
job is to shake the nerves off
quicker than they do.
The best way to get in
the groove is to score
the first
point!
[Team Karasuno]:
Sir!
I don't say this to flatter
you guys; I really mean it.
[Takeda]:
You are all very talented.
We've got a great team!
Let's show this whole stadium...
these crows can still fly!
Whoa! Take's making
a big speech!
I bet those jerks still call us
by that dumb nickname...
Man, they don't know
how wrong they are.
People call them
the Wingless Crows.
It's time to
stand up and say...
That's not true anymore!
The old warhorse is back!
Yessir!
Wait! Was that
too cheesy?! I'll stop!
No, no, no!
That was great!
Hey, what's
an old warhorse?
I never understand
what he says.
I think what Takeda was trying
to say was that we were known
for being stronger
in the past.
Can we just
worry about today?!
[Daichi]:
Karasunooo, fight!
Fight!
[Toko Coach]:
Just get that
first point, boys.
Don't lose your head...
All that practice
is going to pay off.
[Toko Coach]:
And don't forget to
watch those receives.
Yessir!
[Tamagawa]:
No way! That little Number 10
is their middle‐blocker?!
I bet he can't be any
taller than 5 foot 5.
Why do they have those
taller guys on the bench?
Hilarious... Those guys
look totally confused...
And well, I guess
they should be.
[Hajime]:
The middle blocker position
is usually all about height.
Is that short guy part
of their starting lineup?
He's not a libero...
Laugh now, but you'll
pay the price later.
(laughs) Well, you
would know, wouldn'tcha?
I am not letting him make
a fool of me next time.
(starting whistle)
Here we go!
[Ikejiri]:
Your serve, Komaki!
Asahi!
Got it!
First shot...
Where do I send it?
Who can intimidate the other
team and boost our morale?
What is the best move
to start the game?!
I know... Perfect!
Awww yeahhhh!
Nice one‐
Okay, you can
stop now‐
SHUT UP! NOW!
Karasuno already got
themselves a warning!
Wow, these guys
are a freakin' joke.
Hey, don't sweat it! Switch
gears and pay these guys back!
Yeah, take
back that point!
(whistle)
[Daichi]:
Take it to
'em, Tanaka!
[Spectator]:
Pshhh, good luck,
cue‐ball!
Here!
[Tamagawa]:
Nice receive!
Ikejiri!
How did he even
get to that ball?!
That libero's
got reflexes!
Damn, it's too far
from the setter!
Here, Asahi!
Alright, Here comes
the left! Triple up!
It's up to you, Ace!
(cheers)
[Spectator 1]:
Damn, that's
a grown‐ass man!
[Spectator 2]:
I hear he's been
held back 5 times!
[Spectator 1]:
He's gotta be
at least 30!
[Spectator 2]:
That's crazy.
Try not to let it
get to you, Asahi!
No way... Did you
see that momentum?
Uh‐huh.
That's right, don't mess
with our left side!
[Keishin]:
Oh, and... that's not the only
weapon we've got up our sleeves.
(evil cackle)
Don't you dare
wimp out on me!
(whistle)
[Daichi]:
Same thing again, Tanaka!
I'm open!
You're all very talented...
We've got a great team!
[Takeda]:
Let's show this whole stadium...
These crows can still fly!
He's flying.
[Takeda]:
Alright...
Prepare yourselves...
...for the Karasuno warhorse!
[Shoyo]:
It's finally time, guys!
[Ryunosuke]:
Listen carefully,
young one...
[Yu]:
In Sendai, Miyagi
Prefecture...
[Ryunosuke]:
When someone says
"the old warhorse"...
[Ryunosuke/Yu]:
They mean Karasuno!
[Shoyo]:
Next Haikyu!!
"Winner and Loser."