Oooh!
That's our dynamic duo!
[Komaki]:
Oh, well...
Good try, man!
[Haga]:
Hang in there!
Hm... looks like they're
not doing that quick attack.
The one where he
closes his eyes.
They still need work...
but it looks to me as if
they're able to execute
a normal quick
attack now instead.
It's sloppy, but at
least they've got control
over the trajectory.
That's a big
difference...
Those kids must have had quite
a productive practice game.
[Irihata]:
They've learned their
weapons, built them up,
and figured out how
to use the right attack
for the
right situation.
Hmmm... Well,
how about that?
They used to rely on raw power
to score their points.
[Irihata]:
Now they're
getting smart.
[Tamagawa]:
One more!
Yeah, but they still make
a lot of rookie mistakes.
Can't argue with that.
But receives are the one thing
you can't perfect overnight.
[Ikejiri]:
Your serve, Chaya!
[Tamagawa]:
One more!
[Ryunosuke]:
Noya!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
Are these guys actually
about to win the set?
Yeah, that libero's
not playing around, dude...
And not just that...
I think that guy with the
stubble is really helping
support Kageyama's sets.
It's alright.
Yeah... let's just
get ourselves a point.
Okay!
[Daichi]:
One more, guys!
Give us a good serve, Hinata!
[Shoyo]:
Yes, sir!
[Ryunosuke]:
We got this!
[Shoyo]:
Yeah!
(final whistle)
[Team]:
We did it!
[Ikejiri]:
It was our biggest tournament
in middle school.
We won the first
game by dumb luck.
But in the second round, we
were up against a team we knew
we couldn't beat.
And just as we were giving up,
do you remember what you said?
They're middle schoolers
just like we are...
There's no reason
we can't win this!
We still have
to try, okay?!
Wow, you just never
give up, do you?
I can't give
up now...
It's my last
tournament.
They're middle schoolers too,
huh? Yeah, good point!
And plus we just cleared
our first round one!
He's right! Let's win
our first round two!
Yeah!
[Ikejiri]:
Our spirits were high,
but obviously that wasn't enough
to make us suddenly improve.
I‐I'm sorry...
No. We're gonna take
the next point!
We lost that game,
but we were expecting it...
so it didn't really
get us down that much.
Actually, we were kind of
relieved, because it meant
we wouldn't have to do any more
intense training the next day.
But you... You were the
only one who was upset by it...
I didn't understand why, but
part of me was a little jealous
that you could
feel that way.
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes!
Um... are you okay?
[Daichi]:
Do it, Hinata!
It's all yours.
Hey, very nice
receive, Tamagawa!
Come to the left, here!
Here, Ikejiri!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
So much for the
"wingless crows."
That's not what I was
expecting at all.
They're on
a different level!
Whenever there's
a net between you,
it doesn't matter what
anybody's ranking is anymore.
We can't win
unless... we try.
Well, I just mean... It's like
my friend used to say...
(whistle)
[Komaki]:
Time to go.
[Tamagawa]:
Yeah.
Jeez, I should've known it
wouldn't be as persuasive
[Ikejiri]:
coming from me.
I totally blew it...
Man...
(starting whistle)
[Daichi]:
Kageyama's up!
He got an ace!
Looks like Karasuno's starting
to get in the groove
after winning that
first set, huh?
[Team Karasuno]:
Got it!
Damn...
That's high!
We did i‐
Yeahhhhh!
Come on. It's one point.
Is it really that big a deal?
Of course it is! This
is the kind of play
that could change
everything!
Maybe you're right.
You guys...
Can't win unless
we try... you know?
And we're
not giving up!
Even small‐time teams know
they need to stick to it.
[Komaki]:
Let's win
this!
Yeah!
Look out!
Get it, Yui!
Right!
Let it go!
[Team Shirato]:
L, U, C, K, Y!
L, U, C, K, Y, lucky!
[Daichi]:
Even if you're not confident
that you can win...
and even if everyone around you
says that it's impossible...
no matter what...
"We can't allow
ourselves to say 'never!'"
[Shirato Girl 1]:
Heads up!
[Team Shirato]:
Let's go!
[Yui]:
Get it!
[Team Shirato]:
We did it! (cheering)
Don't let it
get to you.
It's my fault we
missed that, Yui.
Sorry! I just...
can't stop
messing us up!
Now's not the
time for that stuff.
On your feet... It's not over!
(whistle)
[Team Karasuno]:
Alright!
Match point, and it's
in their favor...
It won't hurt Karasuno at all
if they lose the next point.
But for us...
One more point.
This isn't over!
[Team Tokonami]:
Bring it, Karasuno!
Sakurai!
Ikejiri!
We haven't lost yet!
This is not the end!
Here!
YEAH!
DAMN YOU!
Next time... you're all mine!
[Daichi]:
Right! Take it back!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
Whoa, they're taking
this seriously.
[Ikejiri]:
No one else in this whole
gymnasium is concerned with us
or sees us as a threat.
[Ikejiri]:
The only team playing
us for keeps...
...is them.
Get your head out of
the clouds, dumbass!
It's time to‐
We won.
Uh‐huh...
So... That means
we get to play again.
Yeah... that's
how it works.
We won.
We won...
We won!
[Shoyo]:
That means we can play
some more volleyball!
We get to stay in the court
for a little while longer!
[Takeda]:
That little guy's been
dying to play a real game...
and now he's finally getting
his first taste of victory.
Yeah.
[Yutaro]:
What're they thinking?
Don't these amateurs know
they have another game to play
this afternoon?
Hm? Well... They were gonna
win that game either way...
They should've saved up
their energy for the next one‐
I disagree.
They gave
it their all...
But we didn't see that
special quick attack, did we?
The other game's done too...
And Date Tech dominated.
[Yutaro]:
Ahhh... Karasuno
versus Date Tech.
Now that's
more interesting.
We should go... If we miss our
next game, it won't matter.
[Yui]:
Aw, don't cry!
It's fine!
I'm sorry... they went
after all my serves.
I gave them so
many points...
The point is to keep
the ball in play...
They were just better at
that than us... so we lost.
It's not anyone's fault!
Captain... The
teacher needs you.
Okay... I'll
be right back.
Michimiya's really...
strong.
She practiced the hardest...
But she doesn't
seem all that upset.
She is.
[Mao]:
It's true. She just puts
on a brave face whenever
she's in
front of us.
It's almost time
for the next game.
[Mao]:
But I'm sure, as soon as
she has a moment to herself,
it'll all
hit her.
I didn't do too bad, really...
I didn't miss many practices.
After I saw the game on TV,
I said I'd be playing
to represent Japan one day.
Even though I said it jokingly,
part of me was serious.
But once I got into all
that resistance training,
my enthusiasm
fizzled out.
Is this it? It's only June...
How could it end so quickly?
If only... I'd worked
just a little harder
to improve while
I had the chance.
If only I'd pushed myself
more during practice.
If only I'd been
a better captain...
If only I'd wanted badly enough
to make one more receive...
If only I'd made the time
to run one more step...
Maybe I would have
gotten to play volleyball
for just a little
while longer.
[Ikejiri]:
Sawamura!
Ikejiri?
Listen to me... Please keep
winning! For my team, too!
Sure. We'll
do our best!
[Ikejiri]:
To think, tens of thousands
of players around the country
are ending their seasons
early, just like we are.
To get to the Nationals, you
have to win every single game
in the
preliminaries.
If this was a TV drama...
the guys going to Nationals
would be the main characters,
and our team would be
extras or something.
But hey...
...we still got to play.
At least we
could still play...
[Ikejiri/Yui]:
Volleyball.
Karasuno was awesome.
Yeah, that short guy
really surprised me!
No kidding.
Did you see those
quick attacks he did?
Wh‐What?! Can't I just
be happy about this?!
Nobody's ever made a big deal
out of me like that before!
(seething)
(cowering)
I haven't said
a word, Hinata...
In fact, I'm glad to see
you getting some recognition.
The more the enemy teams
pay attention to you
and feel intimidated...
the greater the damage
you'll be able to do.
Uh... So I don't know
what that means...
but your face says
it's something evil.
That's right, Kageyama.
We're building
a great reputation
with everybody out there talking
about our little, red 10...
So we need Hinata
to shine out there.
[Keishin]:
So bright, the other team's
blockers are gonna be
too blinded to
know what's goin' on.
Just so you know, we'll be
using the same starting lineup
for round two as
we did for round one.
The next game will
be starting at 1:30...
Let's stay
loose you guys.
Now go get yourselves
a light lunch.
[Keishin]:
Don't fill up though.
[Team Karasuno]:
Yes, sir!
[Shoyo]:
Next is that "Iron Wall" school
with "No Brows," right?
[Tobio]:
Date Tech.
Yeah yeah,
that's the one.
Listen... I think the game back
in March where Date Tech beat us
[Tobio]:
was the reason
Asahi quit the club.
Ah! Really? You think
that was it?
In one of our games... every
single one of Asahi's spikes
was completely
shut down.
They've got blockers...
and they can stop Asahi.
Sorry to interrupt.
You guys got a minute?
[Daichi]:
Asahi.
We should go.
[Koshi]:
Listen to me, you guys. There's
something I want to address.
Date Tech is a very
tough opponent...
I'm sure you know
three months ago,
that iron wall block of theirs
completely obliterated us.
[Koshi]:
But now we have
our special decoy!
You have blazed a trail
so Hinata could succeed.
[Koshi]:
So... Please blaze
a trail for Asahi too!
Okay! Time to win round two!
Ooooh.. wuh?
Go, go, Date Tech,
Date Tech, here we go!
Date Teeeeech... let's fight!
Yeah!
[Moniwa]:
Run some laps!
Well, they've got the scare
tactics down, don't they?
Date Tech really
scares me...
That'd be like sharing the court
with a bunch of monsters.
Seriously, man! Did you see
that team they played against
in round one? Dude, I felt
really bad for their spiker.
[Spectator 1]:
Yeah, no matter what they did,
Date Tech shut 'em right down.
Captains!
Thank you for the game.
[Takeda]:
Oh boy... I get the
feeling this entire gym
wants Date Tech to win.
[Daichi]:
Looks like we're on
the receiving side...
You ready, sir?
Yep.
[Daichi]:
Receiving drills! Let's go!
Sir!
Alright!
Let's do this!
Right!
It's been three months
since Date Tech destroyed us.
Our team's definitely
been getting better...
but I think the third‐years
might still have the last defeat
stuck in their minds.
And we can't let that linger.
Best course of action right now
is to stop 'em from
obsessing over Date Tech.
Rollinggggg...
Thundeeeeeer!
Again!
(chuckles)
There ya go.
Nice! Killer
receive, Noya!
I mean, that was perfect!
Except for the name...
You wanna say that
to me again, baldy?!
Ooh, teach me!
Teach me the Again too!
[Tobio]:
How was that different
than the last one?
[Koshi]:
At least he got it.
[Daichi]:
You never quit, do you?
[Asahi]:
Tone it down, dude;
Daichi might get mad again.
Alright listen here!
You guys have nothing to
be afraid of at all!
[Yu]:
Focus on what's in front of you!
I promise I'll
always have your back.
Whoa... HE'S AMAZING!
Pretty cool.
That's great! Everybody's acting
like their usual selves again!
Yeah.
He may be short,
and his hair, ridiculous...
but he's reliable.
The libero's not
just there for defense...
Another big part of his job
is to support the team
from behind
the scenes.
We've got ourselves
a hell of a libero.
[Captains]:
Line up!
Thank you for the game!
[Tobio]:
So, No‐Brows got in your
way once before, Asahi?
[Asahi]:
Uh, yeah...
[Shoyo]:
Shouldn't HE be
scared of YOU?
[Tobio]:
Yeah, you look so
much older than he does.
[Asahi]:
Oh, come on!
[Koshi]:
Great job, guys...
Next Haikyu!! "The Iron Wall."