[Tobio]:
When I started middle school,
I met a great athlete.
Seeing him play made
me think middle school
must be the big leagues.
But it wasn't middle school
that was impressive.
No, it was HIM.
If I can surpass him...
I'll be the best setter
in the prefecture!
(crowd cheering)
[Spectator 1]:
Wow, check out
Karasuno's setter.
Most first‐years can't
stand up to Oikawa can they?
Yeah, it's like Clash
of the Superstar Setters.
That was sweet!
You're just as good
as the Great King!
Pow! Pow! Pow!
POW! Pow! Pow!
I swear... Even if I face
someone who's better overall...
I'm still the
best setter.
Doesn't matter,
you're up to serve now.
You'll be in the back...
so you can't do
it again, right?
Setter dumps are
illegal from there.
I KNOW!
I'll do it when I'm up
front again, alright?!
[Daichi]:
Serve it up, Kageyama!
Dammit!
That's out.
He put some real
strength behind that.
Somebody sign him up
for the baseball team.
[Daichi]:
Let it go!
I'm sorry!
(fangirls squealing)
Well then. Shall I show you
boys how it's done?
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
[Koshi]:
He hit it right to him!
Straight on... Nope, curve.
He just controlled
an Oikawa serve!
[Black‐haired Guy]:
That libero's incredible!
Aw... that's no fair!
How about that?
He's got some skill.
How did he retrieve that?!
It's like it was nothing to him!
I know, right?
Bring it!
[Hajime]:
Number 10!
Yeah!
Did you see that?
Over on the right?
Uh‐huh. Reminds me
of how Nekoma's setter
[Takinoue]:
could throw people off
with a look.
Those magical sets of his
should be illegal... Am I right?
I'm kinda surprised Nishinoya
could save that one... Wait..
Unless you think maybe Oikawa
sent the ball that way
by accident; could that
be what happened?
Nah... He meant it
to be for Nishinoya.
[Keishin]:
If he HADN'T been
able to save that one,
it would have done some serious
damage to our team's morale.
I think that's probably
what he was going for.
That was close... You really
saved our asses, Nishinoya.
Hey uh I'm sorry...
It's just...
they keep confusing me.
Well, Karasuno did a number
on Date Tech, after all...
Just give it a few
minutes or so.
It's not going to be
much longer now.
Anyway, I pity you.
You were Kageyama's partner...
Now he's gone and replaced you.
And with that little neophyte.
No, it's okay‐
You bet it is...
So what if Kageyama saw you
as... "just a subpar servant"?
That was back
in middle school!
[Toru]:
So what if we don't
have a legendary
quick attack
like theirs?
Let's show him he never should
have driven you away, Kindaichi.
You're clear to jump.
Um.. yes sir!
[Koshi]:
Alright, Tanaka!
[Tadashi]:
Do your best!
[Hajime]:
Watari!
Okay!
[Hanamaki]:
Nice receive!
Center Ball!
An A‐Quick!
[Crowd]:
Kin‐Dai‐Chi! Kin‐Dai‐Chi!
Geeeeet thaaaaat POINT!
[Crowd]:
Kin‐Dai‐Chi! Kin‐Dai‐Chi!
Geeeeet thaaaaat POINT!
Am I crazy?
Because I think their number 12
is jumping higher
[Daichi]:
than he did in the
practice game. I mean, right?
[Toru]:
Your serve, Iwa!
[Daichi]:
Sorry, cover!
I got it!
Give it here!
A‐ha.
I need a
time‐out, sir.
Wait why is Seijoh calling
a time out? This is weird.
Yeah, didn't seem like Karasuno
was about to take the momentum.
[Toru]:
Okay... pay attention
to his choice of words.
"Bring it.. and "Give me."
Are you serious?
Did they already figure it out?
How'd they crack
it so fast?
[Toru]:
My first thought was, "Wow, that
little guy screams something
every time he goes in
to hit a set."
I just assumed
he was an idiot.
But then I noticed,
when they do that insane quick,
he'll say "bring it here"
or "bring it"
something with
the word "bring".
And for a
normal quick...
[Yutaro]:
He says "give it here" instead.
[Toru]:
Yes.
However... he is
their greatest decoy.
And this is
his strength...
They want us
to lock onto him...
So we're going to employ
a strategy to counter that.
[Toru]:
Whenever the shorty
says "bring it",
we'll put
one mark on him...
If he says "give me",
we'll wait to see where
the ball goes before we jump.
Okay?
[Team Seijoh]:
Sir!
One thing though... We called
a time‐out pretty early
in the game for seemingly
no reason at all...
Won't they realize
we're onto them?
So let them realize it!
That can only benefit
us in the end...
If those Karasuno clowns
think we've got their number...
[Toru]:
it's sure to make their poor
setter lose his mind.
Hey! That dumbfounded look
doesn't suit you, dude.
Nah, that's where
you're wrong...
I see this fool make this face
at school all the time.
[Ryunosuke]:
Mostly when he can't
make a decision
on what to get from
the vending machine.
[Tobio]:
I‐I don't do that!
Anyway, Noya... I can't
believe you hit that serve!
Well, I had to deal with it
back in middle school.
So I'm used
to it.
It was a killer serve whenever
it actually went through...
[Yu]:
but the success rate
was pretty low,
and it wasn't as controlled.
He must have really
been working on it.
It takes quite a lot to
stay in the top 4...
more than just great setters...
or only one player with some
above‐average serving technique.
Don't let 'em off easy...
Give 'em hell!
Yeah!
D'oh!
[Tobio]:
Did you just say "d'oh"?!
It happens; just
keep your head up!
Excellent, guys,
let's set the trap...
I assume you know where you
should be aiming, Kindaichi.
Yeah!
One point!
[Toru]:
Behind any strong setup...
is a solid initial receive.
[Hajime]:
Kindaichi's serve!
That's bizarre...
It didn't seem to be a
particularly powerful serve
that time, did it?
These are tricky.
[Keishin]:
Wait a second...
are they shooting for
when the setter moves up
from the back row?
That guy's not as good
at serving as Oikawa,
so why's the other team
having such a hard time
hitting the ball?
Ahem! Yeah, well,
here's the thing, ladies.
[Takinoue]:
When the setter
is in the back row,
he can't get as close to the net
as the people in the front row
until the serve goes up.
That's why he has
to move very quickly
to get to the
net side position
the second the other team
puts the ball in the air.
There's a tiny delay
in the receive
as the players intersect,
which makes it easy
for mistakes to happen.
But as long as everyone knows
where the serve is headed...
...they can still
get it done.
[Tobio]:
Nice receive!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
Who knew this game
could be so complicated?
Thanks, random
old guy!
Wait what?!
Aw man...
Heh.
[Takeda]:
Oikawa's in
the front row now.
Watch number 3!
We'll have to look out
for that setter dump.
C'mon!
Just serve!
[Tobio]:
Damn, this is a
lot of pressure.
There's already
a 4‐point gap.
Like the coach was saying,
these guys know what's in
our bag of tricks.
We need to switch things up!
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive!
Setter dump!
You shouldn't rush a
setter dump, you know...
It's too easy
to shut down.
HAAAAAAA... BAM!
YEAH!
Woooo!
Just 4 more points
to turn this around!
Yeah, yeah!
You are so positive!
And it's really kinda
getting on my nerves.
Give it here!
We'll wait to see where
the ball goes before we jump.
[Yutaro]:
That's it!
[Daichi]:
Yes!
They figured it out...
[Ryunosuke]:
Kageyama's serve!
[Yu]:
You got this!
[Tobio]:
This time, I won't miss!
It's too far forward!
Good.. He adjusted
for a softer serve!
Damn!
You don't honestly think
I'll let you get away with that?
Kageyama made the first touch!
Now he can't make the set!
Here!
No way!
He turned a tight spot
into an opportunity...
The kid sure is
cool under pressure.
[Keishin]:
He's not thinking like
the other guys.
[Koshi]:
It's okay, guys!
[Tadashi]:
Yeah, keep it u... uh‐oh.
The next serve...
is Oikawa.
[Toru]:
Nothing shakes a
team's confidence more
than when their big talker
suddenly goes quiet.
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
[Toru]:
Watch and see!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
[Team Seijoh]:
(cheering)
Shake it off!
Get the next one!
[Toru]:
The best way to build
pressure is ruining several
serve‐receives in a row.
First step is silencing
that loud skinhead.
Then the ace.
Breaking the two left players
who are crucial to the attack...
will nullify
the decoy's efforts.
That was quick! Why is Karasuno
already calling a time out?
They probably did it because
Seijoh has all the momentum...
And if they can't
fix that soon,
they'll never
be able to catch up.
[Spectator 1]:
They keep going after that
same guy. Sucks to be him.
Look... Send the ball
to the setter...
And if you can't do that...
then at least keep it up high.
Yessir!
And you,
Mr. Serious Pants.
Yeah that
setter dump...
What the hell
were you thinkin'?
I'm sorry...
I snapped.
Okay, as long
as you know...
But it's more
than that, though.
[Keishin]:
It's good to
show our opponents
that we have a variety
of offensive techniques.
But once they're onto you, it's
easy for them to stop a dump.
You have to be extremely careful
about how you time those.
[Tobio]:
Sir!
Listen, do not forget who
the opponent is here...
It's Aoba‐Johsai,
not just Oikawa.
[Keishin]:
And you're not the only one
fighting them. It's all of us.
Yes, sir.
Oikawa!
Let's go!
[Crowd]:
Oooooooolé
There it goes!
You're doing fine! Just keep
the ball in the air, Tanaka!
Uh‐huh.
[Yu]:
Tanaka!
Hey, cover!
[Hajime]:
Number 5!
Tanaka!
Time!
Right!
It's kinda early to use up
both of our time outs,
don't you think?
Then again, we've gotta
do something
to get the momentum
on our side.
Yeah, that's the thing
about volleyball...
Everything hinges on
keeping the ball in play.
[Shimada]:
Nothing's worse than the guilt
from repeatedly screwing up.
[Takinoue]:
Yeah...
And then they add
insult to injury
by going after
him like that.
Number 5 is having
a rough day.
Maybe I should say
something to him?
After all, Tanaka's always
got an encouraging word for me
whenever I start
to doubt myself...
Yeah, I will. Hey‐
[Ryunosuke]:
I'M SO STUPID!
I'm sorry!
Tanaka! Some things you
just can't help, okay?
That last set was ridiculous,
AND they triple‐blocked you!
I should've
followed through‐
Shut it! I didn't
call for the ball!
I just... I lost my focus!
And I'll be kicking myself like
hell when the game is over!
I'm not gonna drag
you guys down!
And I won't have you
wasting your time...
crying over MY
stupid mistakes!
[Ryunosuke]:
I'll... do better.
Ha! The fact that
you can say that
is good enough
for me, buddy!
Uh.. thanks.
Make sure to use both
your arms AND your feet,
or it'll bounce
right off you.
You could stand to be more like
Tanaka; you know that, Asahi?
I'm doing my
best here, okay?!
Huh... this is the second
time I've noticed it.
[Brown‐haired Guy]:
Oikawa is looking
really off.
[Black‐haired Guy]:
Yeah, well I heard it's his
little ritual to keep himself
from breaking
concentration.
A lot of teams
call time‐outs
just to throw off their
opponent's groove.
We'll see
if it works.
Bring it on!
[Yutaro]:
It's all you,
Oikawa!
[Hanamaki]:
[Keishin]:
Man, he's really got
his head in the game...
It's up to you guys
to take control now.
[Crowd]:
Ooooooooolé!
[Ryunosuke]:
If it hits the
ground, we're dead!
[Asahi]:
Tanaka!
Crap!
Don't let it fall!
That's what
I'm talking about!
And in the best
possible spot.
Here!
Get it, Hanamaki!
Nice receive!
Someone cover!
LEFT, NOW!
Tanaka!
Tanaka makes his
share of mistakes.
And he takes the bait every time
someone pushes his buttons...
but...
[Keishin]:
His power's second
only to Asahi's...
and he's got the mental
fortitude to keep trucking
and play his best, even when
he's near his breaking point.
No doubt about it...
...he could be an ace.
Whoa!
Looks like the bald kid's
got it goin' on, now!
He pulled the rug right
out from under 'em.
YEAAAAAAAH!
[Spectator 1]:
Not bad!
Well, that's alright; I suppose
I can let go of a point or two.
Whoo, that was the best look
at a block I ever had!
I just mean... sometimes I can
see the other team's block
in midair, clear as day,
like it's in slo‐mo.
[Ryunosuke]:
With a bright ray of light
shining through it.
That sounds
so cool!
You'll see one day!
It's your
serve, jackass!
Right!
Their flow's been broken.
[Tobio]:
And there's still time...
We can come back!
[Daichi]:
Nice one‐touch!
Chance ball, baby! Woo!
Bring it here!
Gotcha!
He's too fast even
when we expect him!
Look, you... Please don't
tell me you STILL can't beat
that kid's sets.
Kageyama's? Of course
I can't...
You really think I can do
a pinpoint set like that?
Please don't
be mad!
[Toru]:
I may not have as much talent,
but I'm more in tune
with my teammates' capabilities
than he'll ever be.
So, I'm just as good
a setter as he is.
It got past
the block again.
Aw, don't look so shocked,
little guy.
Striking right above
the blockers
is what Kindaichi
does best, after all.
[Daichi]:
Forward!
[Tobio]:
7 points. That's way
too big a gap!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it!
Wow, they're really bringing
their A‐game today, aren't they?
I'm impressed!
We do NOT need to deal with
a double‐block right now.
If we're not careful, they'll
take back the momentum...
I have to shake
one of those blockers.
During my second year of
high school, I heard about
a middle schooler who was
a legend in his own time.
[Toru]:
"The King of the Court?"
I thought. "He must be
wonderful at what he does."
But when I saw him play, I knew
the name meant something else.
He's got power, and talent, and
he craves victory more intensely
than anyone I know.
All those qualities make up
Tobio Kageyama's strengths...
But...
they're also his weaknesses.
No man is an island,
little Tobio...
You may have been at this
for two months now, but...
It takes longer than that
to break a bad habit.
Nice kill, Hanamaki!
Yeah! Way to go!
Woo!
Hey, Hinata!
It's time to change it up...
Do you remember the signals?
Remember?
You mean we're gonna use the
signals that we talked about?!
[Daichi]:
Cover!
[Hajime]:
Now that's a block!
Ah! It's mine!
[Daichi]:
One more time!
Y'know... I've been watching
Karasuno's attacks...
I think they're
gradually speeding up.
I don't like how
fast this is going.
We don't have any
time‐outs left.
Slow it down, fellas!
Stay cool out there!
That's not very
wise of them...
They're so desperate
to outrun our blockers...
they're valuing speed
above all else.
But they're losing
their accuracy.
[Irihata]:
Whether they realize it or not,
as their speed increases...
the number of mistakes
will increase as well.
You really are
something, Tobio Kageyama.
[Toru]:
No one but you could
pull off that combo move
with the short kid...
But it's not all about him.
Don't you think your Number 3
would have what he needs
to overcome our blockers
if you would only set to him
a little slower
from now on?
Wouldn't it help if Four‐Eyes
actually trusted your sets
when he hit them?
Every spiker has his
own unique quirks.
The player who can take
those quirks and use them
to their
potential is...
...a true setter.
[Tobio]:
This is bad!
The gap isn't shrinking!
I'll do whatever
it takes to fix this!
[Daichi]:
Over the net!
Push it back!
You know, Kageyama doesn't seem
like himself anymore does he?
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive!
[Tobio]:
I won't lose this game!
I refuse to!
I have to win
and stay on the court!
[Yu]:
Nice follow thru!
Get ready!
Chance ball!
Oikawa's got horse sense, and
he puts in a decent effort...
But compared to a wiz‐kid like
Kageyama who's two years younger
than he is...
[Irihata]:
He's got skill, but he's
far from a genius.
Still, with the way
things are currently,
I can confidently say that the
more proficient setter...
...is Oikawa.
[Takinoue]:
A swap? Right now?
[Shimada]:
Man, that's
brutal...
It's hard to
keep your head up
when you have to leave
the court like that.
[Takinoue]:
How would you know, Shimada?
You're a a benchwarmer.
[Shimada]:
Next Haikyu!!
"The Talented Upperclassman."