[TOBIO] Damn!
(focus)
[SHIMADA] Whoa! It's up!
[UCHIZAWA] Nice follow‐thru!
You have to ask the setter
for another chance, Asahi!
You're the ace!
(nervous)
[KOSHI] Shimada!
[ASAHI] SUGAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
[KOSHI] (gasp)
Over here!
[KOSHI]
Asahi!
(happy)
(focused)
(breathless)
(ALL amazed)
[TAKEDA] Did you just hear that
noise?! It was like BLAHW!
(KEISHIN surprised)
Nice one! You should
be proud! Both of you!
Thanks a lot... Uh great ball...
Suga... And Nishinoya's
receive was perfect.
(BOTH chuckle)
[SHOYO]
So... That's the Ace.
[TOBIO] Hey.
[SHOYO] Hm?
I know you wanted to see
the ace and everything...
but don't freak out!
What?! I‐I'm not freaking out!
[SHOYO]
I may not be as tall or strong
as him, but I've got spirit!
Next ace... is me!
[YU]
The average hand is
approximately 3 quarters
of an inch thick...
I have slightly smaller
hands than most people
in my age group...
But that three‐fourths of
an inch between the ball
and the floor...
makes all the difference in the
world... to keep the ace alive.
This is what happens when
you skip club for a month!
You can't jump worth a crap!
Oh... I'm sorry.
Haha, don't you think
that's a bit harsh?
(happy) Reunited!
So not only are we up
against a veteran team
from the Association
but Asahi's with them?
We've sure got our work
cut out for us now.
(laughter) What are you
going on about, Daichi?
[RYUNOSUKE] You know you've
got me on your side‐
[SHOYO] You've got me
on your side!
Uh.. What?
Hinata! Mind your
own business!
I was just about to be a
badass and then you popped
up and ruined everything!
That was freakin' incredible!
Nishinoya's like a pro!
If we can retrieve
blocked balls, then we'll
be unstoppable for sure!
[KEISHIN] Don't bank on that...
He's not gonna be able to do it
every time.
[TAKEDA] Huh?
[KEISHIN]
The ball falls downward at a
speed of 60 miles an hour.
And that's from just 6 to 8 feet
away. Nobody could save all
of them; it's impossible.
[TAKEDA] Oh.
[KEISHIN]
Listen... The best thing we
can do is get it into these
boys' heads
that a blocked ball isn't
the end of the world.
Just keep getting blocked
and I'll get every single
one of 'em!
Huh?
[KEISHIN] Once you figure
out that your teammates
have your back,
[KOSHI] No way, Asahi's the ace.
[KEISHIN] your frame
of mind totally changes.
[KOSHI] He'll never
get blocked again!
[TAKEDA] That makes sense.
[ASAHI] Don't say that!
[MORI] Go for it!
(whistle)
[DAICHI]
Ennoshita! Cover it!
[KEISHIN] They could stand to
work on their receives as a
team. [CHIKARA] Hey Kageyama,
cover me!
[TOBIO] Got it!
[KEISHIN] That setter's got a
knack for gauging distance from
the point of impact.
[KEISHIN, internal]
If I remember right,
he's a first‐year.
(internal) Wonder
which setter I'll use‐
(KEISHIN surprised)
(SHIMADA & ASAHI shocked)
(whistle)
(KEISHIN stunned)
That's what I'm
talkin' about!
[SHOYO] Thanks!
(YU & ASAHI stunned)
It's all thanks to
Kageyama's sets... I can
get past anybody now!
Oh wow, I guess he wasn't
kidding around when he
told me that.
Dude, that was unbelievable!
How'd you do that?!
I couldn't look away!
(shy laugh)
[KEISHIN, internal]
They didn't give each
other any kind of signal...
How did they time it so well?
(serious) You!
(SHOYO startled)
[KEISHIN] What made you jump
over there... huh, Ginger?!
Huh?! Uh... 'Cause it'll come
to me wherever I am... uh, sir!
[KEISHIN, internal]
(surprised) The shorty obviously
jumped without even LOOKING for
the ball.
[KEISHIN, internal]
Does that first‐year setter
automatically adapt to
everything the little guy does?
[KEISHIN
KEISHIN] How's that kid so sure
that the set is coming? Who in
their right mind goes full‐swing
What are you guys,
a couple of weirdos?!
(SHOYO & TOBIO taken aback)
Weirdos?
Are we?
I dunno.
(KEI snickers)
[TOBIO] Wipe that smirk
off your face, Tsukishima!
[KEISHIN] I have no what those
two have going on,
but I'm not going
to discourage it.
[KOSHI]
So... I content to just hid in
Kageyama's shadow... It was...
easier.
[TOBIO] Let's try for another
one like that, Hinata.
[KEISHIN] Man, that first‐year
setter's gotta be some kinda
[SHOYO] Okay! (whistle)
[TOBIO] Go for it!
[KEISHIN] In fact, he seems like
he's got superhuman abilities.
[KEISHIN]
Still...
[SHIMADA]
Ooh! Straight spike!
And this is after he's
been out for a month,
marvelous bastard!
You are way
too excited.
That split‐second timing between
the toss and the spike...
It's the kind of thing that
can only be accomplished after
you've been through a hell of a
lot of training.
[KOSHI & ASAHI]
Yes! (laugh)
[KEISHIN]
A bond of trust like they have
can't be built in a day.
[KEISHIN]
We have a first‐year setter
with amazing talent...
And another pair with an
incredible connection with
each other. We have weapons.
(grin)
(nervous)
[DAICHI]
I'm free!
This ain't a bad team
you've got here!
(TAKEDA slapped)
[KEISHIN] Why didn't
you tell me, Specs?
(straighten up)
Yeah I've told you
several times, actually.
(ALL celebrate)
[KEISHIN]
But the Ginger...
I don't understand why
he's a middle blocker...
He's got pretty good quick
attacks, but can that peewee
actually block?
[ASAHI, internal]
(question) He's staring at me...
Oh... that's
right, I forgot!
This is Hinata's chance
to go head‐to‐head with
the current ace.
[KEISHIN] Huh?
[TAKEDA] The thing is... Hinata
enrolled at Karasuno
because he wants to be
just like the Tiny Giant.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah. That's right. That
little guy was an ace too.
That's why he's always so
fired up... He's trying to
be the same thing.
This'll be huge for him...
a chance for him to test his
abilities against Asahi.
Heh, well isn't that special?
Although it's kinda like a kid
against a grown man.
(TAKEDA awkward)
[ASAHI, internal]
Parallel ball.
[SHOYO, internal]
I can't believe I'm marking
the ace right now.
(internal) The ace of
Karasuno High School!
[CHIKARA]
Get ready!
[TAKINOUE]
Nice receive!
[ASAHI]
It only took him a
split‐second to catch me!
(SHOYO gasp)
(long whistle)
[ASAHI, internal] I knew how
high that kid could jump...
[SHOYO] I'm sorry!
[DAICHI] It's fine!
You were pretty close...
[ASAHI] ...but it's amazing to
[DAICHI] Maybe next time.
[SHOYO] Right! I'll try!
[ASAHI] I mean, how is something
like that even possible?
[SHOYO] He's great... And he's
been out for a whole month!
[KOSHI] Nice one, Asahi.
(ASAHI laughs)
You've been holding your
hands in the wrong position
when you block...
This how you do it
here! Like this!
Are you listening?
Look at me!
[KOSHI] Let's keep it up, you
guys.
[TOBIO] Hey!
[SHOYO, internal]
He was always covered in
sweat and looked like he was
hurting...
but the Tiny Giant never
stopped jumping.
I didn't really understand it at
the time...
but I think that's what it
means to be in a position
[YU] I'm gonna be
counting on you, Asahi.
[SHOYO, internal]
where your teammates
Everybody on the team had faith
that he could score the point...
so they did everything
they could to get the
ball over to him.
(internal) That must be what
it's like to be Asahi too.
[TOBIO] Hey.
[SHOYO] The ace is awesome!
Even if they're blocking him,
it doesn't matter
'cause he's got enough power
to break right through 'em!
[SHOYO]
What?
Nothing.
Hm?
[KOSHI] Forward!
[RYUNOSUKE] Cover it!
[ASAHI]
Hey, left side!
(internal) If I was tall
and powerful, I could be
just like him...
[DAICHI] We need to boost our
defense on the left side!
[SHOYO, internal] No,
[DAICHI] Hinata, move closer to
the back! Move to the back.
[SHOYO, internal]
the Tiny Giant was amazing
without being tall! But still...
(internal)
I wish...
[DAICHI] Hinata!
(SHOYO startled)
(SHOYO smacked)
(shock)
GAHH!
[ASAHI]
(panicked running) Hinata!
[SHOYO] (groan)
[RYUNOSUKE] Well, he's alive.
(ASAHI panicking)
[YU]
Are you okay?
[ASAHI] I am SO sorry, Hinata!
[KEI] You shouldn't feel bad,
it's his fault for spacing out
like an idiot.
[KEISHIN]
It's gonna be okay, Specs.
[SHOYO]
Uh... Sorry, guys... I'm okay.
[DAICHI]
Are you sure? Maybe you'd
better sit out a bit‐
I swear I'm okay!
Don't worry about me;
I just didn't move out
of the way fast enough,
that's all.
[SHOYO]
I get hit in the face a lot.
Uh, that's not good...
(awkward laughter)
(shock)
Huh?
(ALL shocked)
(ASAHI scared)
[TOBIO]
It's the middle of a game.
What could you possibly
be spacing out about.
(SHOYO scared)
(backing up)
[SHOYO, internal]
Oh crap. Kageyama's not
yelling... which means he's
REALLY mad.
This is just like that
time I hit him in the
head with the ball.
[TOBIO] I know what it is.
(SHOYO gasp)
[TOBIO]
You wish you were the ace don't
you...
You don't want to just be
the team decoy... You think
it's lame.
[TOBIO]
You want to be as big and
important as Asahi so you can
be the ace instead, amiright?
[SHOYO, taken aback]
That's not how I feel!
Well... uh... maybe...
[TOBIO]
Now that you know we
have an ace...
it's not just something you
dream about... You're jealous!
(SHOYO surprised)
Think about that garbage on
your own time from now on!
[SHOYO]
(upset) Okay, so I'm jealous...
Is that so awful?
How could you understand
how I feel? You've always
been really tall!
(pissed)
[DAICHI] Look‐
[JANITOR] Hey, uh fellas!
[DAICHI] Huh?
[JANITOR] It's time to
close down the gym for the
night... Put your stuff away.
I'm sorry, sir!
Our game's not over yet.
Do you know what
time it is?
[TAKEDA]
Yes, I'll be sure to lock up.
[SHOYO, internal]
It's my fault for holding up the
game. And now Kageyama's mad.
Don't doddle.
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
[DAICHI]
Sorry, Takeda!
We'll hurry it up.
[TAKEDA]
(affirmative)
You tell 'em, Take!
[DAICHI]
Right... Let's pick up
where we left off!
[ALL]
Yessir!
(whistle)
[KOSHI] One more!
[UCHIZAWA]
Let's go!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hope you punks are ready!
[TAKINOUE]
Hey... Based on what we've seen
so far,
it looks like the high schoolers
are in their best rotation now.
We better keep our eyes peeled
for the shorty's quick attack.
[ASAHI] Yeah.
[TOBIO] Listen.
[TAKINOUE] Huh?
[ASAHI] Hm?
My next set... goes
straight to this guy.
[TOBIO]
Block him with
all you've got.
Yeah... I'm gonna send it
to him... Just thought you
should know that.
[TAKINOUE ASAHI]
(confused)
[TAKINOUE]
Oh yeah? You daring us?
[TOBIO]
Sure. Call it what you want...
But it's going to Hinata.
[TAKINOUE ASAHI] Huh?
[TAKINOUE] (laugh) You're funny,
kid! That's really good!
Alright... Thanks
for the heads up.
You're welcome.
(ASAHI surprised)
[KEISHIN] Is he crazy? The whole
point of a quick attack is the
fact that your opponent's not
expecting it...
So There's no way Ginger can
get through a head‐on block
now...
[KEISHIN] not with all
the cards on the table!
[TAKEDA] I agree.
[TAKINOUE] Better shut 'em down.
[TAKEDA] His height already
gives him a disadvantage with
blockers as it is.
[UCHIZAWA]
No doubt. Can't lose
to a buncha kids.
[SHOYO, internal]
What the heck is Kageyama's
problem? Why'd he have to give
our plan away?
Those blockers are way too
big for me to spike through!
[TOBIO]
All you are now... is a clumsy
little turd who just happens to
be fast and good at jumping.
Someone like you could never
be the ace of this team.
(SHOYO taken aback)
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey now.
[ASAHI] That's not cool.
[TOBIO]
But... With me around,
you are the greatest!
[SHOYO]
What?
[TOBIO]
Look at Asahi. His spikes
are forceful enough
to cut straight through
a triple block.
[ASAHI]
Huh?! W‐well not
every time, but uh...
[YU]
Whoa, calm it down, buddy!
You might not have what he
does...
but how often do you really
get blocked? when you hit
one of MY sets?
Hm?
(whistle)
[TAKINOUE] Go for it!
[CHIKARA] I got it!
[DAICHI] Nice receive!
[SHOYO, interal]
They're too tall...
[TOBIO] Go around!
(SHOYO gasp)
[TOBIO]
What other option do
you have, you idiot?!
[SHOYO, internal]
If you can't get through...
[SHOYO, internal] ...go around!
[ASAHI TAKINOUE]
(shocked)
(KEISHIN shocked)
[SHOYO, internal]
I hate being blocked.
I hate being pushed back!
[SHOYO]
I don't have a chance of winning
with these blockers in my way.
[SHOYO]
I can't break through them
like the ace does.
[SHOYO, internal]
But...
[TOBIO, internal]
With me around...
[TOBIO]
...you... are the greatest!
(ALL astonished)
[TOBIO]
You might not be the
ace of this team...
[TOBIO]
But with your speed and
jumps... and my sets...
you can take on anybody!
[TOBIO]
The ace powers
through for a point,
and you dodge for yours.
But a point is a point!
[TOBIO]
You don't need a crown
with "ace" written on it!
You just need you to
score all you can!
[TOBIO]
That's why our opponents
will be marking you!
Your decoy skills will free up
our other spikers to score
points too...
[TOBIO] including
the ace! Right?!
[RYUNOSUKE] (startled) Uh‐huh!
Look this guy is
right, you know!
Having you as a decoy could
make a major difference
in our success rate every game!
It's an advantage.
So tell me, Hinata...
Do you still feel like the
job of a decoy is useless?!
(panting)
[SHOYO]
No.
Huh?!
Of course it isn't!
Good!
(SHIMADA YU stunned)
(KOSHI laugh)
That last hit you did...
it was great.
(happy)
[TOBIO]
I'm sorry for interrupting
the practice game, sir!
[DAICHI]
Oh.. that's... uhh...
[SHOYO]
Yeah, sorry!
If it's okay with you...
[BOTH]
Let's keep playing!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Alright! We're gonna
catch right up!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Yeah.
[KEISHIN] Hey, specs. Those two
there.
[TAKEDA] Huh?
[TOBIO]
Anyway, just because you
happened to nail it that time
doesn't mean you should keep on
jumping in the same direction.
[TAKEDA] You mean Hinata and
Kageyama?
Did they meet during
middle school?
Or were the two of 'em close in
elementary school or something?
Huh? Oh not at all, actually the
two of them just met recently...
We had a lot of trouble with
them at first because they
didn't get along.
[KEISHIN]
Hm.
Um, why do you ask?
[KEISHIN]
Whaddya know.
(whistle)
(ALL celebrate)
These high schoolers
really know their stuff...
I think we're gonna have
to kick it up a notch.
[DAICHI, internal]
A jump float!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hinata!
[SHOYO]
Alright, I'm open!
(SHOYO gasp) (slide)
[RYUNOSUKE] Uh?!
[SHIMADA]
(laugh) Face plant!
You are kind of a jerk.
[TAKEDA]
Hmmm? Hey...
I've never seen a serve
like that; didn't seem to
have much momentum on it.
That's called a
jump float serve.
[KEISHIN]
Without any spin, it's
got a shaky trajectory.
It could swerve or
drop at any second.
[TAKEDA]
Ah.. it's like a knuckle
ball... Interesting!
(TADASHI astonished)
[KIYOKO]
Uh Tadashi... they
just got a point.
[TADASHI]
(surprised) Oh, I'm so sorry.
[MORI]
One more!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Whoa! (whistle)
(whistle)
(whistle) [UCHIZAWA] Excellent!
(TADASHI stunned)
[SHIMADA] Sweet!
[KEISHIN] That's four in a row.
[KEISHIN] Those two first years
have a good combo worked out...
[TAKINOUE] What's wrong, high
schoolers?
[KEISHIN] but the receivers
do need some work...
[TAKINOUE] What happened to all
that enthusiasm from before?
[KEISHIN] Make sure you write
that down.
[SHIMADA] That's match point!
[SHIMADA]
Heh. You kids are all mine now!
[TOBIO] Nice receive!
[TAKINOUE] You're not gonna get
away with it again, short pants!
[TAKINOUE] Ha! Gotcha!
[ASAHI] Uh‐oh!
[TAKINOUE] Ack!
[RYUNOSUKE]
'Sup, scrubs?! Remember me?!
What?!
[KOSHI]
Nice save!
[ASAHI]
Suga!
[KOSHI]
Asahi!
(whistle) (long whistle)
(ALL cheers)
[RYUNOSUKE] Aw man! My bad,
dude! They weren't even trying
to mark me either were they?!
[SHOYO] Oh! No!
[RYUNOSUKE] That
was awesome though..
You must've had every set of
eyes on you by the end of it...
Must say I'm a little
jealous of you.
[RYUNOSUKE] Keep it up next
game! (laughs)
[SHOYO] Ah... um.. okay!
[SHIMADA]
Man, that game made me feel like
I was in school again!
Those were some good times
right? All the girls! All the
drama...
"With me around, you're the
greatest!"? You kiddin?, I wish
I could say crap like that...
Man, high school was fun.
[YU TOBIO]
(groan)
[TAKINOUE]
You kids really made us feel
like some dinosaurs in there.
[KOSHI]
Uh.. sorry, sir.
Well Anyway... you might
not have everything
figured out just yet...
but once you do, I think
you guys are really going
places. I mean it.
(ALL excited)
[DAICHI]
Thank you for coming!
[EVERYONE]
Thank you!
[KEISHIN]
Okay. Receiving... That's the
biggest issue right now.
[KEISHIN]
So we'll be working
on that tomorrow!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[DAICHI]
Thank you!
[ALL]
[KEISHIN]
Now... don't forget to stretch.
[DAICHI]
Let's stretch out guys!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[DAICHI]
Rotations! 1, 2, 3, 4...
[ALL] 5, 6, 7, 8!
[TAKEDA] Is their receiving
really that awful? You seem
stressed out.
[KEISHIN]
No... that's not what I'm
worried about most.
I never really thought about
it that hard when I was up for
selection during my time in high
school...
[KEISHIN]
...but the guy doing the
selecting has his work cut out
for him.
[DAICHI] Let's
put all this away!
[TADASHI] Yessir!
[KOSHI] Yamaguchi, bring the
balls over there... Okay, you
ready?
[TADASHI] Coming!
[ASAHI] (exhale) (huh?)
[SHOYO] Asahi?
[DAICHI]
Let's pick up the pace,
everybody!
[SHOYO]
I may not be the ace...
...but I AM one of the guys who
clears the way for the ace...
I'm a great decoy.. the best!
[ASAHI] (surprised)
[SHOYO]
Ah! But I can't really do that
without Kageyama's sets...
[SHOYO]
So... What I'm saying is...
"I'll do my best" sounds kinda
cheesy... but "Let's do our
best" sounds even worse, so...
[ASAHI]
Hinata? That IS... your name,
right?
Listen, "ace" is just another
name for a wing spiker in left
position... You do understand
that, right?
[SHOYO] Uh‐huh.
[ASAHI] When it comes to
breaking through a triple
block...
or hitting the ball when the
timing's tight... those things
are definitely the ace's job...
With your speed and jumps...
and my sets... you can take
on anybody!
But still, to have a setter say
something like that about you...
well, that's pretty impressive
in and of itself.
Huh?
[ASAHI]
A‐anyway... I guess...
what I'm trying to say is...
whether you're a decoy..
or you're the ace...
I'd say the coolest player is
the one causes the most panic
for the opposing team.
Like, "Watch that
mid‐blocker; he's crazy!"
That kinda thing.
Uh‐huh,
uh‐huh!
(smile) Let's do our best.
(surprised) Will do!
Oh! I guess that all depends on
whether or not they let me back
into the starting lineup, huh?
(surprised)
[KOSHI] (laughter)
Man, for such a big guy..
you really are a softy.
[DAICHI]
It's real good to see you back
in action again, Suga.
[KOSHI]
Yeah, sorry I got all obsessive
and weird about everything.
[DAICHI]
(surprised) I didn't
say you did...
[DAICHI] It's good
to have you back too.
[YU] Aw yeah!
[DAICHI] But try not to
assault the Vice Principal
anymore... got that?
(YU stunned)
And finally ... I'm glad our
soft‐spoken wing blocker is back
from his little vacation...
right, Asahi?
(deflated)
Let's get everything
squared away
and call it a night!
[DAICHI]
Keep it up, guys! Alright?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Almost time for training camp.
[YU]
Ch‐Yeah, I can't wait to
be under the same roof with
Kiyoko‐ Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Noya!
[YU]
Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Noya! Noya!
[YU]
Tanaka!
[SHOYO]
Uh, what's happening?
[KIYOKO]
Just ignore them...
Next Haikyu!! "The Decision."