[TOBIO]
(heavy breathing)
(sprint) (set)
[TOBIO]
You're not fast enough!
Can't you jump any higher?!
[TOBIO] More.. more.. more!
(gasp)
[TOBIO] Why? Why
didn't you jump?
[OTHERS] (scoff)
[YUTARO]
'Cause we've had enough of your
crap... Mr. "King of the Court."
Gah!
(ALARM beeping)
[TOBIO]
(gasp)(breath)
[TOBIO] Tch!
[KIYOKO] Good morning,
everybody.
[RYUNOSUKE] (gasp)
[CHIKARA] Hello, there.
[SHOYO] Hey look!
It's that pretty girl!
[RYUNOSUKE] You're looking as
beautiful as ever, Kiyoko!
[SHOYO] So do you think she's
the team manager or something?
[RYUNOSUKE] Ah yeah,
ignoring me!
[DAICHI] Alright,
let's get started.
[SHOYO] Huh?
I'll play on Tsukishima's team
to make it three‐on‐three.
[SHOYO]
Huh?! Is that
fair though?!
(laugh) Don't worry,
of course it is.
Tanaka's got a lot more
attack power than me.
[DAICHI] I won't go
easy on you though.
[RYUNOSUKE] (annoyed)
Well, ahem... The buzzcut or
the shorty, Who to crush...
I mean, challenge first?
[TADASHI] (nervous)
[SHOYO] (shocked)
[RYUNOSUKE] (listen)
So hard to choose...
but I do know I'd like to
save His Highness for last.
[DAICHI] (sigh)
[TADASHI] Uh... Tsukki?...
They can hear you... Be careful.
I know, genius, I want them to
hear me... I can't wait to watch
the King fall apart out there.
Well now... You've got
quite a personality
there, don't you?
[KEI]
It'll have to be a pretty great
show to top watching him
get abandoned by all of his
loyal subjects last year.
[TOBIO] (annoyed) Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE] Well, well!
Didja hear that, you guys?
They're talking trash now...
That jerk had better..
just.. stepppp oooooff!
(RYUNOSUKE growling)
[TOBIO] (shocked)
[RYUNOSUKE] Or he's dead meat.
[SHOYO] Blegh!
(whistle blowing)
[RYUNOSUKE]
(battle scream)
[SHOYO] (thrilled)
[HISASHI] He just got it right
past that giant first‐year guy!
[SHOYO, internal]
He's even stronger than usual!
YYYEAAAAAHHHH!
(wild cheering under)
[KOSHI] Put your shirt on!
[CHIKARA] Yeah, calm down!
[HISASHI] Nobody wants to see
This is what happens when
you get Tanaka too worked up.
Tch!
[KEI]
Heh, so little...
[TOBIO]
Front!
Got it!
(internal) Hey,
I can do that too!
[TOBIO]
Hinata!
[SHOYO, internal]
That's my set!
This'll be my very first spike
in a high school game!
[KIYOKO] Hm?
[HISASHI CHIKARA KOSHI]
(watching)
[SHOYO, internal]
I'm gonna score!
There's another wall in my
way... a big.. big wall.
You took me by surprise
before... You have a really
nice jump there...
Now if only you were about a
foot taller, you'd be a real
superstar.
[SHOYO] (annoyed) (grunt)
[KEI] Better start taking your
vitamins.
[SHOYO, internal]
He's only one guy!
Whatever! One more!
[SHOYO]
I got this one for sure!
(surprised)
[KOSHI] Blocked again.
[CHIKARA] How many times
is that?
[TADASHI] Nice one, Tsukki!
[HISASHI] Tanaka's getting
a lot through, though.
[DAICHI] Nice block, Tsukishima!
[SHOYO] Ah, man.
[KEI] Thanks.
[TOBIO, internal] Damn...
He's better than I thought.
You better snap out of it,
buddy, or you're going to
keep getting blocked.
Why not give him one of your
royal sets... The kind that
wipes out your opponents...
[KEI]
AND your teammates
at the same time!
[TOBIO]
Shut your mouth.
[DAICHI]
Your serve, Tadashi!
(whistle)
[TADASHI] (serve) Agh!
[KEI] Tch!
[TADASHI] Uh...
oops... Sorry, Tsukki.
(whistle)
[DAICHI] Shake it off!
[TOBIO]
We don't need quick attacks.
Time to win.
Alright you got this! Do it!
[KOSHI, internal]
I remember Kageyama's jump
serve, it was pretty amazing.
[TOBIO, internal]
I can score all the
points we need!
[TOBIO] Ha!
(receive)
[SHOYO]
(shock)
[KEI] Tadashi!
[TADASHI] Leave it to me!
(fumble)
[TOBIO] (pissed) Damn.
[TADASHI] Nice toss, Tsukki!
[RYUNOSUKE] Steady receives
like that are Daichi's
specialty.
[DAICHI] You're doing great.
[RYUNOSUKE]
They've got mad defense.
Did you think I would
be a weak spot?
(TOBIO surprised)
[DAICHI] I may not have as much
raw talent as you,
but I've been training on
receives for a lot longer
than you have.
(surprised)
You won't break
through that easily.
[SHOYO, internal]
Wow, he sounds cool.
[TOBIO] (seething) Hm?
[KEI] Your Grace!
Shouldn't you be
taking this seriously?
Dude, what's the matter
with you?! Why do you
keep picking on the guy?!
Chill out with the
freakin' nickname!
What for? Do you even know
why everybody started calling
him the King of the Court?
[SHOYO]
(confused) I thought his
enemies called him that...
because he's really good
player... and well everybody
was so afraid of him.
[KEI] (laugh) That's a
commonly misunderstanding,
but it's just not true.
[SHOYO] (surprised) Huh?
Well, if the rumors are to be
believed, then his nickname
King of the Court...
was given to him by the other
players of Kitagawa First...
Yeah, that's right, by his own
teammates... The truth is...
[KEI]
They were not paying him
a compliment, but calling
him a tyrant.
I've been hearing about it for a
long time... but now that I've
seen him play, I'm convinced...
He got benched at the finals
because he was a domineering,
power‐tripping dictator.
[SHOYO RYUNOSUKE] Hm?
[CROWD](distant) Kita Go!
Kita Go! Kita Go! Kita Go!
(TOBIO hit)
(whistle)
[KOUSEN] Alright!
(CROWD cheers)
[TOBIO, internal]
Grr, they block so high!
(KOUSEN cheering)
[TOBIO] I'll have to use a
faster attack to shake them off.
[TOBIO] Something they won't
be able to get to in time.
[AKIRA] Hey, it's okay.
[YUTARO] I guess.
[TOBIO] Move faster!
[YUTARO] Tch!
[KOUSEN 7]
Our serve!
[YUTARO]
Go right!
[SCORER] (surprised)
(whistle)
(cheers)
[KOUSEN 7] Nice!
Cut it out!
Can't you set it like
a normal person?
[YUTARO]
What's the point if
we can't hit it?!
[KOUSEN 4]
One more to go, you guys!
[TOBIO, internal]
If I can't shake their blockers,
we'll never win!
Is this the end? Is this
how we're gonna lose?
No! I have to go to nationals!
If your sorry asses ever
expect to win anything,
you'd better learn to
adapt to the way I set!
(realize)
Huh?
(sigh)
[TOBIO] End of the first set.
Set point for the opponent.
I set the ball up.
(gasp)
But no one was there to hit it.
[TOBIO]
We had messed up several
combinations that day...
but that was not a mistake.
[TOBIO]
It was a rebellion.
They wanted to make it
absolutely clear that
they were done with me.
Kageyama.
Huh?
[COACH]
It's time for you to go back to
the bench.
(shaky breath)
[KEI]
That's why you won't
try a quick attack.
You're still shaken up over
what happened that day.
[RYUNOSUKE]
You know what, I've had
enough of your smarmy ass‐
[DAICHI] Tanaka.
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?
(sigh)
Well, why bother
setting if there's no
one there to spike it?
[TOBIO] You're right.
[RYUNOSUKE KEI] Hm?
[TOBIO] (exhale)
The thought of nobody being
there to back me up...
it terrifies me, alright?
[SHOYO]
Yeah, but that was
back in middle school.
Your sets are gonna reach
me... no question about it.
(quiet surprised)
After that..
the only problem is how to
get it past this jerkhole!
[DAICHI] (laugh)
[RYUNOSUKE] (chuckle)
You need to kick Tsukishima's
ass, join the volleyball club
and become the setter,
just like we planned! Then you
have to send the ball to me!
It's not that complicated!
(annoyed)
Oh shut up... That over‐the‐top
annoying little attitude of
yours... is disgusting.
[RYUNOSUKE] Hm?
[DAICHI] Hm? (concerned)
(whistle)
[KEI] And enthusiasm won't
make you any taller.
If you think trying hard is
all it takes to succeed...
...you're sorely mistaken.
[RYUNOSUKE] I got this, to you!
Give it back, give it back!
[SHOYO] Tanaka!
Give it to me now!
[TOBIO] Who do I send it to?
[SHOYO] Over here!
[RYUNOSUKE] I'm open!
[TOBIO] I don't know that
Hinata can beat this guy.
[RYUNOSUKE] Come on, this way!
Tanaka!
[SHOYO]
Kageyama!
(surprised)
[TOBIO]
No one... was there.
I'm here!
Gah!
Arglgh!
(whistle)
(grunt)
That was close...
Almost jumped at nothing...
But it's out.
[TOBIO] (shocked)
What the hell was that for?!
[SHOYO] The ball came
right towards me!
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[SHOYO]
I don't care about what happened
in middle school!
I'm grateful for any
set that comes my way!
I just want the ball!
[SHOYO]
I'll jump anywhere! I'll hit
any ball! Believe me!
Give me a set...
And I'll hit it!
[KOSHI, internal]
Kageyama planned to throw
that to Tanaka, I know it.
But when he picked up on
Hinata's voice and movement,
he tossed to him with perfect
accuracy.
[KOSHI, internal]
He might have a sharp tongue
and a bad attitude...
but he really is something else.
You guys can do quick attacks
and you didn't tell me?!
What's that?
That crazy‐fast
attack you just did!
Uh? Uh‐uh... No... The
only sets I've ever hit
were way up in the air.
You literally just did it!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Look, remember in middle school
when that rookie setter messed
up that set and you hit it
anyway? Like that!
[SHOYO]
Huh? But I don't even
remember how I did it.
[RYUNOSUKE] (sigh)
Whatever, I'll still hit
any set that comes at me!
You just wait and see!
[TOBIO] (uneasy)
You've never done combos before,
so that's impossible for you.
[SHOYO, internal] (shocked)
Impossible?! Does he even hear
himself right now?!
Don't be ridiculous! YOU
don't get to act like a
wimp! Just stop it!
Ugh.
Uh...
Not very regal of you, sire.
(angry) You're gonna pay
for that I promise you!
Look at that... getting all
bent out of shape again.
[KEI]
You can't just bulldoze
your way through everything.
You know that, right?
Hm?
Not everyone's a good fit
for every job, you know.
[KEI]
I mean, you're clearly not
cut out to be a spiker.
[SHOYO]
(surprised)
[RYUNOSUKE] (enraged)
[DAICHI] (grab)
[RYUNOSUKE] (listen)
[SHOYO]
You're right.
In middle school...
even now... no matter how much
I jump, I always get blocked.
[SHOYO]
Height is important
for volleyball...
You can't always just jump
real high to make up for
being short like me.
[SHOYO]
But still...
...that never stopped me from
wanting to be a spiker.
[SHOYO]
I don't care whether
I'm cut out for it or not.
[SHOYO]
I'll do the best I can with what
I've got and I'll win!
I'm on this court and
I'm not going anywhere.
[SHOYO]
No.
[TOBIO]
I'm not leaving...
[SHOYO TOBIO]
I want to stay on
the court the longest!
[KEI] (sigh)
Have you even listened
to a word I've said?
It doesn't really work
that way, shorty.
[KEI]
You can't substitute
spirit for height.
Unless you want to be
a libero, that is.
[SHOYO]
Give a set and I'll hit it!
[TOBIO]
I open up the wall and
block the spiker.
That's the setter's job!
(surprised)
(confused)
(yanked) Whoa, what
gives, Kageyama?!
[SHOYO] Gah, let go!
You're hurting me!
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey man,
could you chill?!
[SHOYO] (released)
What the‐Gah!
[TOBIO]
Listen up. If you
can't make the shot...
then I want you to go
around them and hit my
sets with all the power
and agility you've got.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?!... That's how you explain
quick attacks?!
[SHOYO] Got it.
[RYUNOSUKE] There is
no way you got that!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
We have to give it a try!
What's with you? Not 2
minutes ago you were
nothin' but doom and gloom.
I was not.
You lie!
[SHOYO] Okay...
Ready to go!
[TADASHI] Serve it!
[TOBIO, internal]
He should have the speed and
reflexes to hit a quick set.
[SHOYO, internal]
Bring it on, Kageyama!
Show me what you've got!
[TADASHI] Go, Tsukki!
[TOBIO, internal] We haven't
established any signals,
so for now...
[SHOYO, internal]
Got it, so he's gonna
set it that way.
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice!
[SHOYO, internal] That's weaker
than Mrs. Yoshida's serve...
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice receive!
[SHOYO] Once it comes my way,
I'll just‐ Ggh!
Ah...
[SHOYO]
Oh. Faster than I thought.
[TOBIO]
How'd you miss that!
You have to‐
(troubled)
Nice ball, Your Highness!
(angry)
Nothing ever works out
on the first try!
[KEI]
Hey, that's what losers say.
[SHOYO]
Hwph! Gaaah!
Gwah! I touched it that ti‐ Oof!
(gurgling struggle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
You look like a fish!
(weary) I can't guess
your timing at all.
[TOBIO]
You have lightning‐fast
reflexes! You just need to give
it more "pow!" More "oomph!"
[SHOYO]
Is it oomph or pow?!
Make up your mind!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Don't get caught up
in the terminology!
[KOSHI] Kageyama.
[TOBIO RYUNOSUKE] (look)
[SHOYO] Hm?
You need to make sure you don't
let history repeat itself.
Uhh... What I mean is, uh...
He's got super fast
reflexes and uh...
he can jump! He can learn
how to quick attack!
That's not really what I'm
getting at though...
I think I know how you guys
can be more effective.
Hmmm?
Hinata doesn't really
know what he's doing.
[SHOYO] (stunned)
That's kinda harsh...
He doesn't have technique or
experience
like a lot of the people
you competed against in
middle school.
[SHOYO] (bummed)
[KOSHI] But he's a rare asset.
[SHOYO]
Huh?! Really?! Aww come on, I'm
not like a genius or anything...
[RYUNOSUKE] Who said THAT?
(SHOYO awkwardly laughs)
[KOSHI]
If I had your skill...
I mean, think about it...
Maybe YOU should
try adapting to more of Hinata's
characteristics instead of the
other way around,
don't you see what I'm
saying? Then...
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[RYUNOSUKE] Take it easy, Suga!
It's up to you to use his
talents more effectively!
(thinking)
[KOSHI]
I'm a setter like you, so I was
honestly pretty freaked out when
I saw you play last year.
You've got incredible talent and
control over the ball...
But most of all, you're good
at analyzing the opponent's
blocking moves and you make
decisions on the fly.
I've got... none
of those things.
Don't you say
crap like that‐
Hold on... Just
let him talk, okay?
(uneasy)
[KOSHI]
You're good at what you do
and have almost TOO much
determination...
but your ability to assess
your surroundings is your
most important skill.
So pay closer attention
to your allies!
Hm?
Hup!
[TOBIO, internal]
Use HIS talents more
effectively?!
The ball came right towards me!
[TOBIO] (glare)
[SHOYO] (startled) Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE]
("I‐don't‐know" mumble)
[TOBIO]
Listen...
Uh! Uh‐huh?!
I'm jealous of your crazy
reflexes, alright?
Huh?!
That's right...
That's why you piss me off;
it's such a waste!
[SHOYO] HUH?!
[TOBIO]
That said!
All I can do now
is use your talent
to the fullest!
(stunned)
What the?
(focused)
You're gonna run at full
speed...
and you're gonna jump
as high as you can.
[TOBIO]
I'll deliver the ball to you!
(confused) What do you mean
by... "deliver the ball"?
[TOBIO]
All you have to do is jump at
max height and max speed
wherever there's an opening..
and swing at full power.
Forget adjusting to the
ball... You don't even
need to see the ball.
Huh?! How can I hit if
I don't even see it?!
[TOBIO] I don't know!
[SHOYO] What?!
Just... try, okay?
Alright.
What are those two
plotting over there?
I mean, no one wants to deal
His Majesty's selfish ways.
[TADASHI] Exactly.
[KOSHI, internal]
Hope they've got a plan...
Hinata's not gonna be able to
adjust to those tosses without
some practice.
[TADASHI]
Let's go! One point!
(inhale, exhale)
[RYUNOSUKE]
He's in the zone.
(whistle)
[TOBIO, internal]
See now.
[TOBIO]
Where are the blockers?
Where's the ball?
Where's the spiker?
What's his next move?
Where will he jump,
and how high is he going to go?
[TOBIO]
Now! This position!
This angle! This moment!
[KEI]
(gasp)
Yes!
(breath)
[SHOYO]
Ah... Whoa...
I... I touched the ball!
(blissful laughter)
It wasn't that great...
[DAICHI] Guys...
He just did that...
with his eyes closed.
[KEI RYUNOSUKE TOBIO]
Huh?!
What?! No way!
[DAICHI]
From the moment his feet
left the floor to the
second he swung his arm,
Hinata's eyes were closed.
Kageyama just made a pinpoint
toss into Hinata's hand,
but Hinata wasn't even
looking at the ball!
I don't know how he did it,
but his timing was perfect!
Huh?
[SHOYO]
That's awesome!
You guys! I dunno what happened,
but I just hit something!
Did you see that?! Huh?!
Hey! What'd you do?!
Your eyes weren't really
shut, were they?!
Um, well you're the one who told
me not to look at the ball!
[SHOYO]
If I kept my eyes open,
I knew I would look at it.
I wasn't telling you to...
[SHOYO]
But... but it worked, right?
What's the big deal?
[TOBIO] I
know it worked... but what
kind of person acts totally
on trust?!
I can't help it! Trust is the
only way I know how to do it!
[TOBIO]
What have you been wasting all
your time on for three years?!
[TOBIO, internal] His mobility
and jumping power...
[RYUNOSUKE] That was crazy!
Nice one, dude!
[TOBIO, internal] My sets can
enhance that!
[RYUNOSUKE] (laughter)
Tanaka, if we can score with
Hinata's spike, then our
marks'll scatter and make it
easier for you to strike too.
[SHOYO] Yeah!
[RYUNOSUKE] Right on!
Look, I know we don't have
any special trust built
up or anything...
[SHOYO] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] Hm?
...but I'll deliver the next
ball to you. So jump, okay?
(nod)
[TOBIO]
Here!
(swing, fall)
[TOBIO]
Sorry.
[CHIKARA]
Hmm... I guess that first time
was a fluke.
Yeah, but I can tell
their precision's already
starting to improve.
Uh? You really think so?
Mm‐hm.
[CHIKARA] That was a
nice one, Hinata.
[TOBIO] Man...
[TOBIO] Too far away
from the net that time.
[SHOYO] Oh hey, thanks a lot.
[SHOYO] That hurt...
[TOBIO]
This really is tough...
Keeping up with
everything that happens
[KIYOKO] Are you okay?
on the court is
exhausting... but...
[SHOYO] Ah! Y‐yes ma'am!
[TOBIO]
...it's fun!
What're you smiling about?!
This is the second time I've
been smacked in the face!
I'm not buying it... That had to
be a one‐time thing... why
are they even still trying it?
Well guess what... Hinata's
probably gonna jump
without looking at the ball
about a million more times.
[SHOYO] I'm starting to think
you do this on purpose.
[DAICHI] You're right though,
it is pretty unbelievable...
[SHOYO] You do know
we have to win, right?
[DAICHI] It's difficult
to trust another person 100%.
[TOBIO] Of course I do!
[DAICHI]
Especially your sworn enemy.
Aw maaaan, it's
not working... But...
[SHOYO, internal]
I definitely felt
it that one time...
I felt the heaviness of
the core of the ball.
[SHOYO, internal]
I really like that feeling.
Just one more try.
[TOBIO, internal]
More carefully this time. A set
that gives the spiker the chance
to use maximum force.
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Got it! Here!
[TOBIO] Nice receive!
Looks like he gave it to
short‐stack by mistake...
Let's just keep our eyes
on the skinhead fella.
(gasp) Hey Tadashi!
[TADASHI]
Oh!
[SHOYO]
The wall!
Listen up... If you
can't make the shot...
[SHOYO]
Go around!
(surprised)
[SHOYO, internal]
I'm shorter than the
tall players.
So I need that extra inch,
that extra second...
[SHOYO, internal]
...to reach the peak!
For this one single
moment in time...
I'm at the highest point!
[SHOYO, internal]
There's a big, tall wall in
front of me, blocking my way.
I wonder what's waiting on the
other side? What's the view like
over there?
It's something I'll never
be able to see on my own.
It's the view...
[SHOYO, internal]
...from the summit.
[DAICHI] (slide)
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Yes!
[RYUNOSUKE]
You can't just spike with your
eyes closed! Who ARE you?!
[KEI]
I don't believe this.
[KOSHI]
This is getting
kinda crazy, huh?
[SHOYO]
Send me the next one too,
would ya? (smacked)
[TOBIO]
Calm down!
[SHOYO]
Aww... Anyway, next Haikyu:
"The First Time Jitters."