(long whistle)
(CROWD cheers)
[SHOYO]
My first and last real game
in middle school... we got
our butts kicked.
[SHOYO]
We lost to the King of the
Court, and I swore I'd challenge
him to a revenge match.
[SHOYO]
After all that happened,
I enrolled at Karasuno
High School.
[SHOYO, internal]
But now... (stunned)
[SHOYO]
No... wait...
[SHOYO, internal]
Why? What is this guy
doing at Karasuno?
[SHOYO, internal]
No... it's gotta
be somebody else.
Why did you come to this
tournament anyway? Not giving up
is a lot easier said than done!
I'm gonna be the one in
the winner's court!
What did you waste your time
on for three years, huh?!
[SHOYO, internal]
Nope, it's him; that jerk really
is here! Tobio Kageyama.
We met last year.
I forgot your name.
(stunned) Uh! M‐my name's
Shoyo Hinata, okay?!
But I'm sure you don't even
remember who I am. I mean,
you destroyed us in one game!
I remember exactly
who you are.
[SHOYO]
Huh?
[TOBIO, internal]
He's got amazing reflexes,
he can jump high, and he's fast.
[TOBIO, internal]
But he doesn't use those
abilities to their full
potential.
[SHOYO]
Ugh, what's with the
silent treatment?!
[SHOYO]
What, you wanna fight
or something?!
Oh, don't be a dumbass!
[SHOYO]
(shocked) Er...
Don't make fun of me!
I might've lost really bad
the first time we met...
But never again!
[SHOYO]
(taken aback) Look! I came here
to get my revenge
and now I find out you're gonna
be on the same team as me?!
How am I s'posed to kick
your butt that way?!
[SHOYO]
There's tons of better schools
you could have gone to!
Why'd you have to pick this one?
Why didn't you go to
one of those instead?
[TOBIO] (annoyed)
[TOBIO]
I applied to the school
with the best team...
[SHOYO] (gulp)
[TOBIO] But...
Didn't make it
Huh? You didn't?
[SHOYO]
They rejected the
King of the Court?
[TOBIO, angry]
Never call me that... ever!
(confused)
[DAICHI]
Who knew the setter from
Kitagawa First would end
up at our school?
[RYUNOSUKE]
He better not be too cocky.
Or I'll have to pound him one.
[KOSHI]
Give it a rest, Tanaka...
You don't have to threaten
everybody.
[RYUNOSUKE]
What are you gonna do
about it, huh? Yeah,
that's what I thought.
Uh... Hello.
[RYUNOSUKE]
(menacing) Well, well, well...
Now what do we have here‐
[DAICHI]
You Kageyama?
[TOBIO]
Yeah.
[DAICHI]
It's nice to meet you.
[KOSHI]
Pretty tall,
aren'tcha?
First impressions are
everything, Suga!
You're a third‐year, so you
have to establish dominance!
(threatening)
[DAICHI]
Stop it, Tanaka...
You look stupid.
[SHOYO, internal]
Huh? Kageyama's a little
taller than them...
but wow, these high schoolers
are all pretty huge!
[SHOYO, internal]
I can't believe I'm really here!
This'll be great!
[SHOYO] Hey guys!
[DAICHI] So how tall are you?
[SHOYO] Uh.. hey dudes?
[TOBIO] Six feet.
[KOSHI] Whoa.
[RYUNOSUKE] Six feet?
That's badass.
[SHOYO] Excuse me?
[SHOYO]
Hey!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? Hey.. it's you!
[SHOYO] (startled)
[RYUNOSUKE] You're the shorty!
[KOSHI] (amazed)
[DAICHI] (surprised)
Wait a minute...
So the other applicant goes
by the name of Shoyo Hinata...
I guess that's you?
[SHOYO] Uhhh...
[DAICHI] It's just... kind of
surprising, that's all...
But hey! You guys
both chose Kurasuno!
Guess so...
Didn't mean to freak you out;
it's just you made a big
impression last year.
Yeah, you were tiny and all
over the place, but you
really had some spunk!
[SHOYO]
Wow, thanks a lot!
Not to mention
that jump of yours.
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's too bad you haven't hit
a growth spurt yet though.
[SHOYO]
(taken aback) (grunt)
I know! I may be small,
but I've got talent!
[SHOYO] I'll be Karasuno's
ace before you know it!
[TOBIO] (surprised) (annoyed)
[RYUNOSUKE] Hot damn! Already
got your eyeballs on the ace
position, do ya? Somebody's got
cajones.
[KOSHI]
Well, there's nothing wrong
with shooting for the stars,
is there? Right?
[SHOYO] (hopeful)
Yeah! I'll do my best!
Okay then... Now that you've
sworn to become the ace...
you'd better be prepared
to back it up.
[SHOYO] (surprised)
[TOBIO]
If you're not careful, you'll
waste another three years.
Excuse me?
[DAICHI]
(sigh) Was that really
necessary, Kageyama?
I did everything I could!
[SHOYO]
I did!
(determined) Look... I've done
a lot! Stop putting me down!
[SHOYO] (snarl)
Relax, guys... You know you're
not enemies anymore, right?
Volleyball supposed to
bring people together‐
[SHOYO]
I want you to play
me right now!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Whoa, watch it, punk;
don't you know Daichi's
talking to you?!
What are we
gonna play?
Volleyball, what the
heck else is there?!
[TOBIO]
How do you plan to play
volleyball one‐on‐one?
[SHOYO]
Like, passes and stuff!
[TOBIO]
How does anybody win at that?
[SHOYO] (seethe)
[RYUNOSUKE] The kid's
got a point!
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
What's all the noise in here?
[DAICHI]
Huh?
Oh turds, VP...
Be quiet!
Why don't you be quiet!
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Are you boys fighting in here?
[DAICHI]
No, we're just working hard as
always, Vice Principal, right?
We gotta watch ourselves
around the Vice Principal;
that guy's always waiting
for us to slip up!
[SHOYO] Serve it to me!... I can
handle whatever you send!
[RYUNOSUKE] Dude!
Listen, jerk... I only received
one serve from you last year...
[SHOYO, internal]
Granted it was with my face.
But since then I've practiced
with everyone I could!
I am not the same
person I was!
[TOBIO]
Hmph. Not the same person, huh?
Well, I've improved a bit
in the last year too.
Alright, alright... That's
enough smack‐talk, you guys.
They're both
first‐years,
aren't they?
[SHOYO, internal]
Don't let him get to you.
Remember everything you
learned from practicing
with the ladies' team!
[TOBIO]
Get ready.
[SHOYO, internal]
A jump serve?! That's new.
(gasp) (knocked down)
[KOSHI] (amazed)
[RYUNOSUKE] Whoa... Not
even I could catch that!
[SHOYO, internal]
Whoa I never saw a serve like
that from any of the ladies I
played with...
[TOBIO]
Pathetic. How's that
different than last year?
[SHOYO]
(surprised) Tch!
One more try.
Okay... Now cut it out.
I see the new recruits have no
respect for their captain.
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[KOSHI] (shocked)
[KOSHI, internal] Nice reflexes!
[KOSHI] He got right behind it,
now he can control it.
[SHOYO] (smacked)
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
If this keeps‐ (smacked)
[DAICHI] (shocked)
[VICE PRINCIPAL] (pained)
[KOSHI] Or not...
(panicked)
[TOBIO]
Oh man, that was a toupee?
[SHOYO]
You just now figured that out?
I noticed it at the entrance
ceremony.
[DAICHI] (growling)
[RYUNOSUKE] Dude!.. Shut up!
(crack up) It's not even that
funny! (laughter)
[KOSHI] You shut up, moron!
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Captain... a word please?
[DAICHI]
Luckily, we're not in trouble.
He doesn't even want an apology.
(relieved sigh)
[DAICHI]
But we have been
sworn to secrecy.
(surprised)
[SHOYO TOBIO] (glare)
[DAICHI]
As for you two‐ (annoyed)
[TOBIO]
If you'd handled the serve, it
wouldn't have happened in the
first place!
You're the same klutz you were
last year. I can't believe I
thought you'd be a challenge.
[SHOYO]
You don't know when
to quit, do you?
[DAICHI] Can it! There's
something I want to tell you.
(ALL surprised)
[DAICHI]
I don't know what your reasons
were for choosing to come to
this high school...
but... I assume you came to win.
[SHOYO] Yeah!
[TOBIO] Yes, Obviously.
[DAICHI]
Up until a few years ago,
Karasuno's volleyball team could
compete with the best of them...
They even made it
to nationals once.
But these days we're 8th in
the prefecture. Not terrible,
but not good either. And people
talk. They call us...
[DAICHI]
The wingless crows.
I remember when Karasuno played
in the Spring High national
tournament...
I was a student at a nearby
school who just happened to
be in the neighborhood.
Watching them fight those
tough opponents in that
huge gym in Tokyo...
[DAICHI]
It gave me chills.
[SHOYO] (OM gasp)
(cheers on TV)
Let's go back..
one more time!
(cheers)
[SHOYO] (surprised)
(cheers surge)
[SHOYO]
We're going to play on the same
court the Tiny Giant played!
[TOBIO]
The nationals, huh? Plenty of
high schools talk about making
it there one day...
Doesn't mean they'll go.
Wha‐?! You little...
[DAICHI]
I know what you mean.
But I'm dead serious.
[TOBIO] (straighten up)
[DAICHI] If we want to
get there, we need to be
a cohesive unit.
[DAICHI]
That means no more run‐ins
with the VP, for one thing.
[RYUNOSUKE KOSHI](uncomfortable)
[DAICHI] It's not like I'm
telling you to be best friends
or anything like that.
[RYUNOSUKE] (uneasy)
[DAICHI] I know back in middle
school you two might have been
adversaries
on opposite sides of the net...
but let me be clear... You're on
one side now and you need to
make peace with that.
Is that clear?
[SHOYO TOBIO] (shocked)
[DAICHI] I don't care
how good you are.
[TOBIO] (gasp)
[DAICHI] Or how determined
you are to play hard.
[SHOYO] (gasp)
[DAICHI] Anyone who lets a
petty rivalry get in the way
of the team's success...
[KOSHI RYUNOSUKE] (watching)
[SHOYO TOBIO] (slapped)
[DAICHI] ...gets the boot!
[DAICHI]
You two are banned from
participating in club activities
until you learn to think of
yourselves as teammates!
[SHOYO TOBIO] HUH?!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
What?!
[SHOYO] "L‐learn to think of
ourselves as teammates"?!
What's that mean?!
[TOBIO] Beats me!
Please let me in, Captain!
Please let me play volleyball
with you!...
I'll find a way to get along
with Kageyama, I promise!
[SHOYO] Come on, I'm really
sorry! I'll do anything!
[KOSHI] You sure this is wise?
I mean We need players.
[KOSHI] You can't build a team
by threatening people to
cooperate; it takes time.
[SHOYO] I wanna play volleyball!
[DAICHI] Yeah I know... but...
[TOBIO] Move, you idiot!
[SHOYO] (knocked over)
I apologize! I won't pick any
more fights with him!
Please let me be on the team!
(hopeful, into scared)
[DAICHI]
You mean that?
(nervous)
(discomfort)
[TOBIO]
I can do it. I'll share the
court with him if I have to...
but I still want to
do it all myself...
every spike, receive
and set in the game.
What is wrong
with you?!
(laughter)
I wasn't expecting you to be
THAT honest with me...
Hey, well, it's good enough
for now... But you know...
[DAICHI]
In volleyball, it's against the
rules to drop, carry, or touch
the ball twice in a row...
In other words, this game
is impossible to play alone.
[TOBIO] (frown)
[DAICHI] (smile)
[SHOYO] So are you mean...
or just stupid?
[TOBIO] (annoyed)
(volleyball efforts)
[DAICHI] Go right!
[DAICHI] Tanaka, follow
through with your block!
[RYUNOSUKE] Sure thing, boss!
[SHOYO]
There's a court and a ball
right in front of me. It's
such a tease.
Ugh! This is such a stupid
waste of time! I have to
get back in there!
But we're not
teammates yet,
are we?
I have a lot of potential!
[TOBIO]
That should be more than
enough for them to let me
join the team.
[SHOYO]
(stunned) Spoken like a true
Ki...(stifle) Uh.. so what
are you gonna do?
We'll challenge them to a
two‐on‐two and if we win then
they have to let us join...
That way we can at least look
like we're working together as
teammates... It's foolproof.
(surprised) Y‐you mean we have
to beat THEM?! What if we lose?
We won't lose...
I'll make sure.
[SHOYO, internal] (shocked)
Whoa, is he serious?!
Does he even hear himself?!
You need to do the you best you
can. No screw‐ups.
[TOBIO] Do not drag
me down, understand?
[SHOYO] (surprised)
Huh?! Don't talk to me
like that! Who's ever
gonna listen to you if you
treat them like trash?!
[TOBIO] Then what's your plan?
[SHOYO] (seething)
[TOBIO] Just sit here and watch
through the window forever?
[SHOYO] (surprised)(deflated)
[SHOYO]
My first game...
and my only game...
was the time we
played against you.
[SHOYO]
We never had enough players for
tournaments before that,
and I had no place to play, so I
used to practice in the corner
of the gym or in an empty
hallway, or wherever I could.
[TOBIO]
Really?
[SHOYO SHOYO]
So when I got to play
my first game...
and I stood in the middle
of that huge gymnasium...
[SHOYO]
I felt like the main
character in a movie.
It was like, "whoaaaa!"
[TOBIO]
"Whoa?"
I wanted to stay forever.
But only the strongest...
[TOBIO]
...get to stay on the court.
Anyway... they're not gonna let
one of us in without the other.
[SHOYO]
If I get to play volleyball...
(focus) then nothing's too much
to deal with.. not even you!
If I try not to look at you..
I don't have to see your dumb
face!
[TOBIO] Keep talking,
short stack!
[SHOYO] (startled)
[KIYOKO] Excuse me.
[TOBIO SHOYO] (look)
I... need to get through.
[SHOYO] (awkward)
[TOBIO] (step back)
Hey Kiyoko! Thanks for your
hard work! Let me get that...
[KIYOKO]
No, thanks. I can
carry it myself.
Okay then... You look
super gorgeous today.
Ohhh man, she's so pretty
when she ignores me! (bliss)
[SHOYO] (flustered)
[TOBIO] (startled)
(whistle)
[TEAM] Good work, everybody!
You know what I bet those
two goofballs are thinking
right now.
That if they can beat us, then
they'll make the team, right?
Yeah sure... but all they really
have to do is cool off
and prove to everybody that
they've learned their lesson.
[SHOYO TOBIO] Captain!
[DAICHI] (surprised)
[RYUNOSUKE KOSHI] (startled)
[SHOYO TOBIO]
We challenge you to a match!
[RYUNOSUKE] (laughter)
[SHOYO] If we win, you have to
let us join!
[RYUNOSUKE] Guys, I'm psychic!
[SHOYO TOBIO] Now!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
We want to prove that we finally
understand how to play together
as teammates!
How many times did
you rehearse that?
(laughter) This is gold!
I could get used to having
these clowns on the team!
If you lose?
[SHOYO] (nervous)
[TOBIO] Then you get
to choose the penalty!
[DAICHI]
Huh...
Club application form.
Here's an idea...
We have two other first‐years
joining the club soon.
[DAICHI]
You'll play against them
in a three‐on‐three match.
[SHOYO TOBIO] (surprised)
[DAICHI] We do this game every
year with our new club members
so we can get an idea
of how they play.
But if it's gonna be
three‐on‐three... then whose
going to be our third player?
[DAICHI]
Tanaka... you're with them...
Make sure they behave, alright?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Aww man, why me?
[DAICHI]
Well you seem to like them.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Don't drag me into their mess!
[TOBIO] Uh...
[DAICHI] That's too bad.
[DAICHI]
I was thinking you'd be the only
one tough enough to keep these
delinquents in line.
[RYUNOSUKE]
(giddy) Aww well, why the
heck not? When you put
it like that...
[SHOYO] (startled)(wincing)
[RYUNOSUKE] Just stick with me,
little man!
[DAICHI]
Anyway, here's the penalty if
you lose. For the remainder of
my time here at Karasuno...
[DAICHI]
...Kageyama cannot
be the setter.
[TOBIO] Huh?
[SHOYO] (confused) Is that the
only penalty we have, sir?
If the setter is aggressive,
self‐centered, and driven by his
own ego... the team can't win.
(pissed)
[DAICHI]
What? I'm not saying I'll reject
your application to join.
[DAICHI]
I'm sure you'll be well‐suited
to a different position.
[TOBIO] (gasp)
No way, I'm a setter!
Then win the game.
[DAICHI]
You're the one who thought you
could win without help, right?
[SHOYO] (startled)
Hey, uh.. but what about me?!
We play on Saturday.
Come on! I'm over
here too, you know?
Don't worry! Your cool
upperclassman's gonna show
you the ro‐waahh!
[KOSHI]
See ya!
Daichi... Are you being
a little too harsh?
He's right, boss, you're acting
a lot more strict than usual.
[KOSHI]
Yeah, Is there some special
reason you're doing this?
[TOBIO] Dammit!
[SHOYO]
What's wrong?
Are you mad because you're the
only one who gets penalized?
[SHOYO]
Even if you're not a setter, I
bet you'd figure out a different
position just like that!
[TOBIO] (annoyed)
[SHOYO] Plus... (hop up) Spikers
are cooler than setters anyway!
They get to go up
and slam the ball!
[TOBIO, annoyed]
(grunt) Stut up!
[SHOYO] (yanked)
The setter is the
team's control tower!
[TOBIO]
Plus, it's the position
that gets the most contact
with the ball!
It's the greatest position
there is because you get to
be the ruler!
[SHOYO] (confused)
[TOBIO] Without a setter to
toss the ball, there wouldn't be
any spikes for you to hit!
I know, but even though the
setter has an important job,
you don't really stand
out very much, do you?
[TOBIO] (grunt)
[SHOYO] (shoved)
I'm guessing you've never seen
a major volleyball tournament
in person, have you?
[SHOYO] No.
[TOBIO]
You can't tell by the
angle they show on TV,
but pay attention to
the end of the court...
From there, you can see how
fast the setter tosses the ball.
[TOBIO]
It flies straight across the
court... Whoosh!
The ball passes right in front
of the face of the other team's
blockers... Then!...
Just when you start to think
"No way! He's never gonna hit
that one!"
[TOBIO]
There's a spiker just waiting
to strike... and he smashes
the ball in just in time!
[SHOYO]
Y‐yeah...
[TOBIO]
The spiker's job may be
flashier... but...
the spiker can't get
through without the setter
to get the opponent to
block and break the wall!
It's the most important, cool,
and challenging position on
the court, okay?!
Yeah sure, fine, I get it,
you wanna be the setter.
[DAICHI]
Kageyama cannot be the setter.
Dammit! What's with that guy?!
All you have to do is win.
You seemed pretty confident
when you challenged them to
a match earlier.
[TOBIO, internal] (irked)
He's right. Not that he'll be
any help.
I'll just focus on setting
up tosses for that creepy
second‐year.
Okay! We've got until
Saturday to work on
your crappy receiving!
[SHOYO]
Crappy?! Uh, but we
can't get into the gym...
[TOBIO] (surprised)
[RYUNOSUKE] AHEM...
[TOBIO SHOYO] Uh?
[RYUNOSUKE] I forget...
We start practice at 7 AM
tomorrow, don't we?
[KOSHI]
Uh, yeah...? Is that a problem?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Ah! Not at all... A‐anyway,
do you think the Vice
Principal's nappy rug
made it out alive?
[SHOYO TOBIO] (listening)
[DAICHI] We're not supposed
to talk about that...
Alright then.
5 AM.
Don't be late.
I won't.
(grunt)
(grunt, run efforts)
[SHOYO]
Ah, wait! Hang on,
I forgot my bag!
[SHOYO]
Shoulda seen that coming.
[SHOYO] It's locked.
[TOBIO]
Okay, let's go
through the window.
[SHOYO]
Are you crazy?! We'd end
up getting expelled!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Man, 5 AM is too early...
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOBIO] Hm?
[SHOYO] Tanaka?!
(RYUNOSUKE yawns)
You got 2 hours...
and then beat it!
[SHOYO] You're awesome!
[TOBIO] Thank you!
[RYUNOSUKE] (laugh)
Yeah, who's your hero,
first‐years? Call me Sir Tanaka!
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Sir Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE]
(laugh) What was that?
[SHOYO TOBIO]
Sir Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE] (laughs)
Okay, punks, let's get crackin'!
[SHOYO] (excited)
[RYUNOSUKE] He's right, boss,
you're acting a lot more strict
than usual.
[KOSHI]
Yeah, is there some special
reason you're doing this?
Well, sort of... You
saw those two play last
year... Think back.
[DAICHI]
Kageyama had exceptional talent
for a middle schooler,
but now he's got almost
nothing to show for it...
If nothing changes, that
lone wolf personality of his
will hold him back in high
school too.
[DAICHI]
I don't want him dragging
this team down... The big
difference now is...
[DAICHI]
...that he and Hinata are
on the same team.
What, Hinata? Oh yeah, I
guess he's kind of a crazy
ball of energy and agility.
[DAICHI]
Right, but he hasn't
reached his potential.
[DAICHI]
He's got incredible speed and
quick reflexes, not to mention
that jumping power...
but he never played with
a real setter before.
[DAICHI]
Kageyama, on the other hand,
wants a spiker fast enough to
hit the sets he makes.
[DAICHI]
Separately, their abilities
are limited. But put them
together...
[DAICHI]
and let them work on
some combinations...
[DAICHI]
Karasuno will have
the perfect team!
[DAICHI]
It's gonna be fantastic.
[SHOYO]
Outta my way! I'm gonna be
the first one on that court!
[TOBIO]
(struggling) You can't be first
if Tanaka's already in, dumbass!
[SHOYO]
Then why don't you let me go!?
[RYUNOSUKE] We don't
have time for this...
[TOBIO SHOYO] (fall over)
[RYUNOSUKE, internal]
Sorry, boss, we've got a
long way to go on those
combinations. (grin)
[SHOYO] Wow, check it out!
[RYUNOSUKE]
You were just here yesterday.
[SHOYO, internal]
This is the same gym where the
Tiny Giant used to practice.
[SHOYO, internal]
Alright! Let's do this!
[TOBIO]
Leave it to you to ruin
things from the start.
[SHOYO]
What?! You're the one who thinks
you can play without a team!
[TOBIO]
I'd rather go it alone
than work with you!
[SHOYO] Why are
you so stubborn?!
[RYUNOSUKE] Clock's ticking!
[RYUNOSUKE] Less yapping,
more practicing!
[SHOYO TOBIO] Right!
[SHOYO] Next Haikyu,
"The Most Powerful Ally."