[MAKOTO humming]
[MAKOTO]
Breakfast is ready, Haru.
[HARUKA]
'Kay.
Not hungry? It's gonna get cold.
[HARUKA]
You're right.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
Haru?
[MAKOTO]
Wait! Where're you...?
[gasps]
Stop! Don't go! Haru!
[MAKOTO yelps]
[gasps]
[sighs] Crazy dream.
You all right, Makoto?
Let's go.
Uh--
Just dozed off. Thanks, Haruka.
There you go again.
Don't call me that.
Now let's see...
Which way's our train?
Got it!
Well, all that's left is
finding you a place to live.
Yeah.
[RIN]
What?
You're kidding. You mean
Haru still hasn't
got an apartment
lined up in Tokyo?
[NAGISA]
'Fraid not.
Mako found one right
after the University
told him he was accepted.
[RIN] And just decided
to keep Haru company
while he went
apartment hunting, huh?
Kinda.
Except that he said
he had to pick up
the key to his place anyway.
Hey, Rin, do you think
you're gonna have some time
to spare to help us
with the Swim Club's video?
Oh. Hey. You're
there, too, Gou?
Did you say Gou?!
Yeah, plus one more.
The three of us are
preparing to head over
to Iwatobi for the
Swim Club's spring practice.
Quick question, Gou--
do like praying mantises
or giant water bugs more?
[REI]
What? Praying mantises?
Uh--!
[RIN]
You've had your fun.
Be a good boy and
give me back...
[MOMOTARO]
Why are you so stingy, Rin?
So, first off, yeah,
I can work on the video.
But I have a meeting with Ai
so I can only help
out for one day.
[REI]
That would mean a lot!
Also, when you talk to Haru,
remind him that he
needs somewhere to sleep
so he better bite the bullet
and settle on a place soon.
That's some big talk
from the guy
who can't even fall asleep
without his own pillow!
[sighs]
Starting tomorrow, you're
switching up Momo's regimen.
Number 33 Training from Hell.
[BOTH gasp]
You don't mean the workout
my brother created?
No. Anything but that!
[RIN]
Too late!
Whoa, sounds like
Momo and the others
are training hard!
Right.
Guess that means we'll have
to train even harder then!
Yeah! I'm pumped to test
out Gou's new regimen!
Let's get started already!
[REI]
I concur!
I've been wanting
to focus on drills
that will increase
the speed of my turn.
[GOU] I wonder what Haruka
and Makoto are up to.
They should have
reached Tokyo by now.
[MAKOTO] I know graduation
wasn't really that long ago,
but doesn't it feel
like we've both
come pretty far since then?
Nah, Tokyo isn't that far away.
[chuckles] Not if you're
comparing it to Australia.
[MAKOTO] Rin. He's trying
to go even further.
[HARUKA] I need to hurry.
Find a place to live.
Yeah.
For sure, and since our
bus home's tomorrow,
we've got just one day, huh?
Yeah.
[SASABE] Oh. There's absolutely
nothing to worry about.
He'll end up finding
a great place.
Seeing how yours truly
set him up with
one of the best
realtors in Tokyo,
what could possibly go wrong?
That was nice of
you to do, Coach.
Miss Amakata, I'm sure
you have great depth
of knowledge when it
comes to Tokyo as well.
Me?
[NAGISA]
Oh, yeah.
You used to work for
a swimsuit manufacturer
in the city, right?
Well, that is true but...
Then I imagine you have
several wonderful memories
of your time spent there.
Yes. I do.
If I were to distill
them into a saying,
it'd be "Reality is often
different from reputation."
A parched city.
A concrete jungle.
The city is weeping.
And one day, even those
tears will dry out
in the Tokyo desert.
[REI] I thought you agreed
they were wonderful memories!
[GOU]
So, uh, anyway, Coach Sasabe,
how do you know a realtor
currently working in Tokyo?
Uh, actually, it's not someone
I've formally met before.
They just happen to be
a relative of someone
from the Swim Club
that also works
in apartment real estate.
[LITTLE GIRL A]
Good morning!
Huh?
Morning, kids!
Hey! And speak of the devil!
How's it goin' Hayato?
[giggles]
[MAKOTO]
This looks like the place.
Wonder what Kisumi's
uncle is like.
If they're twins,
we're going home.
Sir, could you help us?
Maybe so.
They are twins!
Back home it is.
[MAKOTO]
Not so fast!
[laughs]
Hey, guys! I missed you, too.
Kisumi! What're you
doin' working here?
[HARUKA]
Yep. Definitely going.
[MAKOTO]
Hold up a minute, Haru!
[KISUMI]
Guess I forgot to mention it.
Which part?
Well, that I'll be going
to college here in Tokyo
in the spring, and
staying with my uncle.
Makes sense, you know?
All my stuff should be
arriving sometime today.
That's great to hear!
Customers!
You must be the
Haruka and Makoto.
I've heard so much
about you two!
Allow me to welcome
you both to Tokyo!
The city where love
and lust intertwine.
And to Shigino Realty.
where dreams and
ambition do the same.
This is my Uncle Katsumi.
U-Uh, hello.
I set some places
aside just for you,
so no need to worry.
So what do ya say, Kisumi?
You wanna play realtor?
Okay!
[BOTH laugh]
[chuckles nervously]
Got your license and everything.
Same as you, right?
All my time was eaten up
with entrance exams.
But, Haru, you got
yours already, yeah?
Uh-huh.
[laughs] Plenty of time
to get a license.
But you wait to
find an apartment.
Why am I not surprised?
[HARUKA]
Just drive.
[KISUMI]
Up ahead! On the right.
Here's the first place
I'm supposed to show you.
It's slightly old,
but in great condition,
right by the station
and rent's a steal.
So, verdict?
The tub is small.
A three-in-one bathroom
has its tradeoffs.
Unfortunately, a small tub
is kind of a deal breaker.
[KISUMI]
Hm. How about this place?
It's a little bit further
from the station.
But practically brand new.
[MAKOTO] The bathroom's
got plenty of space.
Pretty nice apartment,
right, Haru?
[KISUMI] And it comes
with a modern kitchen.
The latest induction
technology. No gas burners.
What if I wanna grill mackerel?
Huh? You can still
grill on this.
[KISUMI huffs]
Option number three!
[gasps] Spacious. Clean.
And a great view of the city!
Tons of natural lighting
and the kitchen
comes with a dishwasher
and gas grill.
The bathtub has
a reheating function,
and all for this price!
What a deal!
So why is the rent so cheap?
It's... a psychologically
defective property.
[gasps] Psychologically
defective? You mean it's...
'Fraid so.
This apartment's history
is kinda sordid.
[MAKOTO yelps]
[KISUMI]
Actually, last month,
the person who
used to live here...
[MAKOTO] I don't wanna
know what happened!
No way you're living here!
You're superstitious.
Am not!
But do you really wanna
risk a haunting?
[KISUMI]
Seriously, what's the big deal?
Haru will be the one renting it.
I know.
But I'll be creeped out
every time I come to visit.
[laughs] The two of you
are inseperable, huh?
We're friends. Deal with it.
[KISUMI] Hm. You're a pretty
particular guy, aren't you?
I bet the only thing
he mentioned to you
was the price range
and the train line.
Uncle Katsumi gave 100 percent
trying to find a good
property for you.
I appreciate the effort.
So that uncle of yours
really seems like
a lighthearted kind of guy.
Heh. You bet!
Get us together,
and it's nonstop joking.
--Kiss me!
--[KISUMI] Catch me!
[KISUMI] It's hard to
tell us apart, right?
Even our names are a lot alike.
Getting back to business.
I've got one final
property to show you.
What do you think?
The bathroom comes with
a full-sized tub.
Not to mention a gas
stovetop in the kitchen.
I won't know till I see it.
[KISUMI]
One small catch.
We can't go inside the unit yet.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
Everything should be moved
outta the apartment by now,
but we haven't received the
key back from the tenant.
[phone vibrates]
It's Uncle Katsumi.
What? Already?
I gotta run!
He said my moving truck arrived!
They were supposed to
show up this evening.
Man, they're way
ahead of schedule.
Don't worry. I'll take
care of the check.
That way you two
don't have to rush.
[MAKOTO]
You sure?
I'm helping with work
so it's no problem.
I can expense it. Later!
He can expense it.
Kisumi's matured since
he moved out here,
like he's always
belonged in Toyko.
Hopefully we'll be able
to fit in as easily.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[GOU]
Take your marks!
What do you wanna do now?
Check out the unit
even if we can't go in.
Well, then let's head over.
The neighborhood's just as
important as the apartment.
[phone vibrates]
[NAGISA]
Give me an update.
How's the apartment hunting?
Afraid the search continues.
How are things there?
Great. Rin said he
could help us, you know,
with shooting the
invitation video.
[MAKOTO]
Really? That's terrific news.
And how's practice going?
[NAGISA]
Bet you wish you were here.
We just finished up
at Iwatobi Swim Club
trying out the new
training regimen.
And now we're having
a meeting at the beach
and eating lunch.
A meeting?
[NAGISA] We're trying
to decide what to do
at the New Student Welcome
thing coming up in April.
So, remember how
last year our deal
was showing off each
members' best muscles?
On that occasion,
the muscles ended up
dominating the presentation,
but this year,
we're gonna take a
different approach.
We're planning to
showcase this year's
trendiest muscle,
the latissimus dorsi,
with its best move, the
butterfly! Live on stage!
Someone's gonna swim the
butterfly across a wooden floor?
[GOU]
That's the thing! We're gonna--
Sorry, Gou! Our
train's pulling up!
[GOU] It'll probably be
easier if I just send you
the video we shot.
[REI] Tell Haru good
luck finding a place.
By the way, based on the theory
of securing an apartment--
Nagisa, wait!
[NAGISA] I'll check back later.
Tell Haru we said hi!
Sure. Bye.
That is smart.
You can totally see
the butterfly stroke
without needing water.
[REI yelps]
[MAKOTO laughs]
You guys. At least you're
trying your best.
[laughs]
[MAKOTO] Let's do the same.
And try our best, too.
Looks like it's about
a ten minute walk from here,
so, this way?
That looks right.
Wow.
It's in a gorgeous part
of town, don't you think?
[HARUKA]
Mm-hm.
[MAKOTO gasps]
Hey, look, that's the place!
[HARUKA]
I think so.
[MAKOTO] Good thing it wasn't
that difficult to find.
[MAKOTO] Is it just me or does
this park look like the one
by Iwatobi Elementary School?
[HARUKA]
You mean where you fell off
the monkey bars in kindergarten?
[MAKOTO laughs]
Yeah! Right? That park!
[HARUKA]
Here we are.
[MAKOTO]
No nameplate.
But Kisumi did say they
were pretty much moved out.
Doesn't that building
look a little like...
[HARUKA]
Yeah. A natatorium.
Think about it, a pool
that close to you!
You couldn't find
a more perfect spot.
If this place worked
out, you could swim
whenever you wanted to,
no obstructions!
Yeah, but, there's the
university pool, too.
[MISAKI]
Hey!
I saw you two.
You wanted to get into
this room didn't you?
Well, more like...
Out with it!
Are you friends
with Coach or not?
[MAKOTO]
"Coach"?
[NITORI sighs]
[door clicks]
Hey, looks like you're
almost finished packing.
And what about you?
I don't think you've
even started, have you?
[SOSUKE]
I actually plan on spending
a little more time here.
That reminds me.
Didn't you say you're moving
back to your family's house
before heading
over to Australia?
Yeah. Guess I have to be the
good son once in a while.
Aw, man, I wish I could
move into your house!
Also, I've been
dyin' to ask you--
whenever you go home,
who gets the top?
Is it you or Gou?
What're you talkin' about?
Don't play dumb!
I'm talkin' about the
whole bunk bed situation!
You know, top and bottom!
We don't have bunk beds.
We're not kids.
[MOMOTARO]
Are you kidding?
Not again!
Stop sneaking books
on how to raise beetles
into Rin's stuff!
Ha, ha! Think again!
This is a present for Gou!
I'm gifting her the
entire five-book set!
Sosuke.
Right.
[MOMOTARO yelps]
My relative's kid likes insects.
I'm sure he'll get
more use out of it.
No! He doesn't love them
as much as I do!
[laughs]
I'm sure Gou will be happy
since she gets to
spend time with you.
Even if it is just
a short while.
Oh, he's more excited
and just won't admit it.
Am I right?
Shut up.
If you're done psychoanalyzing
me now, lend a hand.
[HARUKA]
So that apartment was where
your coach used to live.
Yeah.
He only taught swimming
at the district pool though.
I was out sick for a while
and when I came back,
he had quit.
[MAKOTO] Wonder what his
reasons for leaving were.
[MISAKI] Who knows?
I wanted to get better.
He said he'd teach me. It's not
fair, he just up and left!
Now I'll never learn
to swim faster.
And why do you
wanna swim faster?
[MISAKI] 'Cause I don't
want to lose to him.
Who's "him"?
A guy who was in my class.
He transferred out
at the winter break.
He had amazing speed,
and I could never
beat him, not once.
Just wait!
I'm gonna race
against him one day.
And this time, I'll win!
We made a promise!
We would meet at
an upcoming swim meet!
So we could swim together again!
[MAKOTO] Hey, kid.
What should we call you?
Oh, uh, I'm Misaki Kuramoto.
I see. I'm Makoto Tachibana.
[HARUKA] And I'm Haruka Nanase.
Nice to meet you.
Question.
You wouldn't happen to be
heading over to the pool?
Yeah.
Even with Coach gone,
I gotta train to get faster.
When you swim, what
stroke do you use?
[MISAKI]
Uh? Me? The best one!
Free!
And one day, I'm gonna be
the fastest in the world!
In that case,
you think it'd be okay for us
to tag along with you?
Huh?
Look at him go!
He's a little rough, but the
kid definitely has talent.
That's obvious.
Just goes to show you
what a difference
a good coach can make.
Doin' pretty good.
Looks like you have
the basics down.
[MISAKI]
Yeah. Thanks.
[MAKOTO]
But I'm noticing sometimes
you're tensing up
and breaking form.
Relax and you'll move faster.
Your recovery phase is
fantastic, just make sure
you don't bend your elbow
underwater too much.
[MISAKI]
Like this?
[MAKOTO] You got it! Let it
naturally enter the water.
[MAN A]
Who is that?
[MAN B]
Whoever he is, he's amazing!
Too cool! Is he
a friend of yours?
He swims front
crawl beautifully!
Who are you guys? Pro swimmers?
[laughs] It'd be nice to
swim together some day.
Of course, with your friend
who transferred, too.
[MISAKI]
Yeah.
[GOU]
There you are!
What're you doin' here so early?
I managed to finish all my
shopping ahead of schedule.
And I also picked up some
not-too-sweet cake for you!
Guess what we're going
to have for dinner!
You're favorite, steak!
Mom's going all out
while she's got you.
[RIN chuckles]
Doesn't sound like Mom at all.
[GOU] It's been so long.
You can't blame her!
Plus you'll be flying back
to Australia in no time.
I think she's allowed
to go a little overboard.
Did you finish packing up
everything at your dorm?
I did.
On that subject, did you
hear any news about Haru?
Whether he found a place or not?
If it's weighing
on your mind so much
why don't you just pick up
the phone and give him a call?
It's not like it
was bothering me.
I was just curious.
Plus, I'm sure he's fine
with Makoto there.
Yeah.
[GOU] You gotta admit,
it's kinda sad.
[RIN]
What?
[GOU] Just how everyone's
slowly separating.
Moving away.
[RIN] Ha, ha. What are
you talkin' about?
We're not driftin' away.
Everyone's setting off
on new journeys.
No matter where we go, our
hearts will stay connected.
Stronger than they've
ever been before.
[giggles]
[RIN]
What's so funny?
[GOU]
You, trying to act cool.
[RIN]
Shut up.
[GOU giggles]
Come on in, check it out.
This is the place I'm renting.
No furniture yet, but why
don't we rest a little?
Sounds good.
[MAKOTO] I really need
to buy some curtains.
We'll be pretty busy.
[MAKOTO]
Listen, Haru.
[HARUKA]
What is it?
[MAKOTO]
To be honest,
I started today feeling
completely unsure.
Not convinced I could
make the transition
to a brand new place.
But when we went
to the pool earlier,
and I was coaching Misaki,
I was reminded that
what I really wanna do,
what gives me purpose,
is teaching kids how
fun swimming can be.
Remember what you
told me in junior high?
How I need to just be myself?
This is it.
I don't know how far,
or where the path leads,
but I know I wanna
do the best I can.
And in my own way.
Good.
[MAKOTO]
Besides, just watching Misaki
reminded me of Rin
when he was that age.
And made me think of how hard
I need to be working, too.
Rin wasn't that
honest with himself.
[MAKOTO laughs]
I have to agree with you there!
[phone vibrates]
[KATSUMI]
All right, gents.
Here's the key to the apartment.
The unit hasn't
been cleaned yet,
but I think it'd be fine if
you went to just take a look.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
We heard the person
who used to live there
was a swimming coach.
Just out of curiosity,
what kind of person was he?
Well, I believe coaching
was a part-time job
because he was still a student.
Speaking of which, when he
came to return the key,
he accidentally left
his phone behind.
He called to say he'd
come back to pick it up.
So, if two wanna wait
around a little while,
you could probably
end up meeting him.
What do ya think? Wanna say hi?
No thanks.
Very well.
Kisumi's outta the office,
so you guys okay
lookin' at the apartment alone?
You can even borrow my car.
[MAKOTO]
Guess I'll have to get used to
all the cars everywhere.
Everything okay over there?
Busy streets make me nervous.
Look out! Car! Stop! Stopping!
[MAKOTO yelps]
[sighs] That was amazing.
It's gonna take some
time for me to adjust
to driving around these roads.
Wow. Katsumi said it
hasn't been cleaned,
but it looks great!
It's weird but I feel a kind
of connection to the person
who used to live here.
Me, too.
This is the one.
[MAKOTO]
You know, since he was a student
and a part time coach,
I wonder if he swam
for the school.
[HARUKA]
Who knows?
[NAO]
Excuse me!
Huh?
[NAO]
I called earlier.
I'm the goof who left
his phone in your office.
Oh. Hey! He missed ya.
[NAO]
Awesome.
I don't know what I'd do
if I couldn't find it.
[KATSUMI]
If you ever need anything,
feel free to come back.
Sound good, Mr. Serizawa?
Thank you for everything.