[sighs]
[GOU]
You in there, Rin?
Do you need a hand unpacking?
No thanks, I'm good.
All that's left is the stuff
I'm taking to Australia.
Hi, Steve.
Somebody's put on
a few pounds, huh?
The cold shoulder, as usual.
[MIYAKO]
Rin! Gou! I made us tea!
[RIN] Hm? You brewed Japanese
tea to drink with cake?
They go well together.
Come on and give it a try.
It's only the latest fad
in the Matsuoka household.
--[RIN] Uh...
--[MIYAKO, GOU] Right?
[GOU] Mm! So delicious!
Can I have another slice, Mom?
[MIYAKO]
Sure, but don't blame me
if you end up
looking like Steve.
[GOU]
But everyone loves Steve!
[MIYAKO, GOU laugh]
[GOU]
I think I will have another.
[MIYAKO] You know, that's
exactly what the cat would say!
[GOU]
Mom!
[NITORI]
That concludes today's practice.
Great work!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Sir!
[NITORI]
Morning practice is at 7am.
And don't forget to check your
personal training regimen.
That's all! Dismissed!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Good work today!
[MOMOTARO]
Wow, Ai!
You sounded just like
a real captain today!
It was way cool!
[chuckles] C'mon,
it's no big deal.
I'm still just acting captain.
Not the way I see it!
In my eyes, you already own
the role of swim captain!
That's nice of you to say,
but more importantly...
"More important" what?
[NITORI] I want to give
something to Rin and Sosuke
since they're graduating.
I haven't decided what yet.
We were on a relay team
together after all.
Right behind ya! Like a present!
The latest and greatest
in swimsuits or goggle wear!
Those could both work,
but I was thinking
more along the lines
of something
no one would be expecting.
They'd totally be
surprised by that!
A stag beetle larva raising kit!
To clarify, not
something you'd want.
A gift Rin and Sosuke would--
[gasps] Wait a minute!
[PRIZE CLERK A] Step right up!
Greetings, young man.
You get one chance
for every five tickets.
You don't happen
to have any tickets
I could borrow, do ya?
Huh?
I think I received a few when
we were shopping earlier.
But we don't need the stag bee--
[MOMOTARO]
You don't have to worry!
'Cause I'm feeling super lucky!
I scored seven points on
a quiz we got back today!
Lucky number seven!
What were the most points
you could've scored?
[MOMOTARO]
One hundred! Your tickets, sir!
[PRIZE CLERK A]
Okay, you got one shot.
[yells] Stag beetle nursery!
No! I didn't get it!
Our first prize winner!
Congratulations!
You get two tickets
to stay at a hot spring!
Hot spring?
You did it, Momo!
[MOMOTARO]
I did?
[MINAMI]
So. White Day. What now?
Hang out here, what else?
Since we didn't get anything
for Valentine's Day
to begin with!
I need to stop delaying
and pack my stuff soon.
[MINAMI] ...I'm saying is, even
though we didn't get anything,
we should bring presents
to the girls' school anyway.
Boom. We create a revolution
and shake up the system.
I mean, it's the
least we can do.
Yo.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Hey, Yamazaki.
--[UOZUMI] 'Sup?
--[MINAMI] Yo.
Did somebody happen
to leave these
in my room by accident?
Any of you guys?
Whoa, we've got cookies here!
Who're they from?
I don't know.
That's why I'm asking.
Hold on. Let's take
a closer look.
Have they got writing on them?
[gasps] The cookies
spell out of a message
if you find the right order!
[MINAMI]
Brilliant!
[MOMOTARO] Looks like our plan
will go off without a hitch.
When he finally
solves the puzzle,
he'll find a surprise
hot springs vacation!
[UOZUMI]
Mecha salmon roe!
[MINAMI]
"The mecha salmon roe is inside
the morning crabs."
Is it a metaphor?
The key here is
Mecha Salmon Roe!
Sounds difficult to
eat inside a crab.
No, you're missing the point!
We're talking about
Mecha Salmon Roe!
It doesn't really matter
if you can eat it or not!
"Mecha salmon"? Whatever
it is, sounds cool!
Hey, Momo.
Nothing about this
should be impressive.
And weren't you supposed
to make it obvious what order
the cookies should be placed in?
[gasps]
[NITORI]
I heard everything!
You! Leave the puzzle
solving to an expert!
Stand back, you might get hurt!
[NITORI]
This looks correct!
[SOSUKE] "The treasure is
inside the red shark's mouth."
"The treasure is inside
the red shark's mouth."
Obviously a hint to point us
in the direction
of the treasure!
[MINAMI]
But what's this "red shark"?
Now that I think about it,
there's that one kid,
Akai, in Judo Club.
Well, let's bring him here!
[MINAMI]
Wait, why?
Why would this guy have
a prize in his mouth?
[UOZUMI]
Mecha salmon roe.
Oh!
Could it maybe have something
to do with the giant statue
of the shark in
the courtyard? Huh?
That may be a good
place to look.
But it's not red, dude.
[MOMOTARO] Well, why don't we
take a look just to be sure!
Wow! Think I figured it out!
The color of the sunset is
sure turning the shark red!
Then the treasure must
be inside its mouth!
How? It's mouth's not open.
Something's buried.
[UOZUMI]
The mouth's shadow!
Clever as always, Yamazaki!
[SOSUKE]
Two tickets for a hot spring?
[BOTH]
Congrats, Sosuke!
So what is this?
[laughs] I went to the
shopping district with Ai
and won them in a
lottery! Awesome, huh?
Please accept them!
Okay.
[SOSUKE]
So now you're up to speed.
What do you wanna do?
Anago Hot Springs.
They went through all
the trouble so why not?
Although...
I'd kind of feel bad if it was
just the two of us going.
[MIYAKO]
We have tickets to stay
at the Anago Hot
Springs, you know.
I bought some from
the newspaper salesman.
Ta-dah! Why don't
you invite those
underclassmen of yours along?
Hello, hot springs!
Tatami mats, yahoo!
Life is wonderful! Yahoo!
Could you calm down?
How can anyone remain calm?
Let's put our bags away
and go sightseeing!
Oh, yeah! I heard
there're capybaras here!
And I'm gonna take
a photo of one
to make my brother jealous!
Wanna tag along?
Momo! If we see a capybara,
I'll take the picture.
[MOMOTARO]
Yahoo!
These hot spring buns
are so addicting!
How many of those
things have you eaten?
Look out. A capybara.
No way!
It is real!
You have to take a picture!
You promised me!
Come on, Ai! You're
in this photo, too!
Why do I have to go?
[RIN]
Ready? Say cheese!
[MOMOTARO] Next up, both of
you need to get a shot!
--[RIN] Uh--
--Onward! Hurry up!
And what if we don't want to?
We're here, so how
about just one?
Okay.
Why are you looking
so grim, Sosuke?
Give us a smile!
I'm gonna take the photo!
--Cut it out!
--[NITORI] Say cheese!
[NITORI]
You're good! I snapped it!
[RIN]
Ouch!
Hello!
My life has been incomplete
without this sword!
[whispering] Hey, Momo.
Even though we were trying
to give Rin and Sosuke
a relaxing get away, we ended up
coming along and
having fun, too.
Can you think of anything else
we could give them as a present?
As a matter of fact, how
about giving this to Rin?
I don't know if that's the sort
of thing he'd appreciate.
Aw! But he brought
me a back bommerang
as souvenir present
from Australia!
A wooden sword is what
he should get in return!
You haven't entirely
convinced me yet.
Fine, I'll buy it and
give it to Gou instead.
I'm kinda doubtful
she'd like it either.
[gasps]
[MOMOTARO]
Am... Am I hallucinating?
Or do I spy a capybara?
Rin! You have take
a picture for me!
It's an emergency!
[RIN]
Let-Let go of me!
Momo really looks like
he's having a good time.
Yeah.
[MOMOTARO] The capybara was
so cute, it nearly killed me!
[laughs]
[NITORI]
Who're they?
[RIN]
I recognize some of their faces.
They're the Sofukan
High School Swim Club.
[RIN]
They're champions.
Regulars at the nationals.
Are they here training?
I'm going for a closer look!
[NITORI]
Don't go charging in!
Put the sword away.
We can't afford a fight!
[NATSUYA]
Attention.
Those of you who've been called,
go to the lobby in order.
Don't block the doors.
[SOFUKAN STUDENTS]
Sir!
[AMAKATA]
Take your marks.
[knocking]
Hey, filmmakers!
How are preparations
for the movie?
Anything you could use
our help working on?
Hey! Wait till
you see the props!
We brought snacks
if you're hungry.
Couldn't come at a better time!
Wait a sec. Wasn't
Rin stopping by?
He's at the hot springs.
Sosuke and some others
went along with him.
[REI] Hot springs?
That's out of character.
Yeah well, he said Nitori
and that Momotaro guy
were taking them
there as part of
a surprise graduation present.
What? That is so cool!
Well, Nagisa.
Might I suggest we give
our upperclassmen
a surprise gift for graduating?
We can't anymore.
You just ruined
the surprise element.
Oh, no!
[laughs]
[chuckles] Thanks,
but we're good.
However, maybe something for Rin
before he goes to Australia.
Let's put our heads together.
A gift for you.
Wow! Surprise Bread!
Drizzled with limited
edition mackerel miso cream!
[GOU]
You're so thoughtful.
Why don't we take a break?
I think we've earned it.
[NAGISA]
Pass me a strawberry milk!
[REI]
And I'll have a barley tea.
[MOMOTARO]
This looks super delicious!
Should we stop
staring and dig in?
Why not?
Wait! First.
I'd like to say a few words
before we start eating.
This trip was supposed
to be a gift thanking you
for everything you've
done and to celebrate
your graduation, but then
you invited us along
and we both truly appreciate it.
Maybe...
I felt guilty tagging
along at first, but now,
I'm happy the four
of us were able
to make this trip as a team.
I'll cherish our time together!
That was a 10.0 on the
serious scale, man!
I have something I would
like to add to that, Ai.
Cool?
[NITORI]
Uh, yes, sir!
You're still just
acting captain as of now,
but come April,
it will be official.
I'm counting on you.
Sir! You won't be disappointed!
I'll do my very best
to fill the large shoes
you'll be leaving
behind, Captain!
Now that might be an 11!
You gotta loosen up!
Then let's set aside the
formalities and enjoy this meal.
Uh, before we do, a toast!
Here's to you. Rin and Sosuke.
Thank you for all
your hard work.
[ALL]
Cheers!
Don't mind me.
Where'd Momo go?
[NITORI] Looks like he got
carried away and ate too much.
He said he'd come in
after he rested a bit.
So, um.
Have you seen Rin?
He said the heat was
making him feel dizzy.
Seems like the both
of 'em had too much fun.
If you don't mind me saying,
I'm glad, 'cause it looks like
you're having fun as well.
Last time I thought about
anything but swimming's
been too long.
Does the mind good
to relax with friends
every once in a while.
I mean, we wanted to
say thank you to Rin.
But I don't know if you
realize how grateful we are
for everything you've
done for us, Sosuke.
So I'm glad to hear
you're having a good time.
[SOSUKE]
There you go, all serious.
I know you'll be able
to swim again some day.
You love it too much to give up.
A big part of why I was
able to come this far
was because of all
your encouragement.
[NITORI] What you did
for me, I want to pass on
to everyone else from now on.
So please, even though
you've graduated,
come and visit Samezuka,
because you're always welcome.
And if you're interested,
we'd love for you
to teach us again.
Sure thing. It's a deal.
[MOMOTARO]
I can't believe them!
Leaving me behind was way mean.
[BOTH grunt]
Sorry. Uh--
Ah. Hey, I remember you.
Heh. You better!
Samezuka Swim Club, first
year, Momotaro Mikoshiba!
They call me the otter
from the Sea of Japan!
[USAMI] Hmph. Sofukan High
Swim Club, first year.
Usami Aoba! Alias, the capybara.
King of the rapids!
Capybara?
Listen here!
That capybara plushie
you were holding earlier?
I've been looking for one.
That's too bad!
'Cause yours truly
got the last one!
You gotta gimme yours then.
First come, first serve!
Sorry, I can't help ya!
You callin' me slow?
[NITORI sighs]
What a nice b--
Whatever's the problem,
I'm sure we can work it out!
[MOMOTARO] Oh, you bet
we're gonna work it out!
I'm challenging the
"Capybara of the Rapids"
to a match over my capybara!
[shrieking]
[RIN moaning]
[SOFUKAN MEMBER C]
What's the matter?
[SOFUKAN MEMBER D]
Usami's having a match
with the Samezuka guys!
Seriously?
A match? Don't tell me!
[RIN]
Damn it!
Even though I'm here,
we're still outnumbered!
[yelling]
Now, Ai!
[grunts]
[SOFUKAN MEMBERS]
Whoa.
Victorious!
[BOTH laugh]
One more! Let's go
again, damn it!
Jeez, guys. I'm supposed
to be relaxing here.
[NITORI]
Are trying to get us killed?
[NATSUYA]
I take it you're a swimmer, too?
[SOSUKE]
Huh?
You're on the Sameuzka
Swim Team, huh?
I'm an alum of the
Sofukan team myself.
Appears one of our club members
is causing a scene in there.
[NATSUYA]
Did you hurt your shoulder?
[SOSUKE] My own fault. I did
too much reckless training.
So yes, I used to be a
swimmer. But now I'm not.
One of my friends
had an accident,
injured his eye,
and was forced to stop
competing for a while
because of it.
So, he's been
pouring his passion
into sports medicine at college.
For him, loving
swimming doesn't mean
he has to go to tournaments.
He knows there are
other ways to show
his love for the sport.
But still.
One day, I hope we'll
swim together again.
Ha. Sorry, you didn't ask
to hear all that, did ya?
Anyway, good luck
with everything.
[MOMOTARO snoring]
[SOSUKE]
Trouble sleeping?
[RIN]
Yeah, who wouldn't.
[MOMOTARO] Hey! Hands off him.
The capybara's mine.
Someone needs to
have a talk with him.
This was a nice vacation.
It's been a while since
I had this much fun.
Ditto.
I made some good
memories to take back
with me to Australia.
We only have Ai and Momo
to thank for that.
Listen. Sosuke.
What up?
--After this, what'll you...
--[MOMOTARO yells]
That's not a capybara!
That's an alpaca!
What the hell are
you dreaming about?
Well. What were you gonna ask?
Ah, not anything important.
Tomorrow, let's take a dip
in the hot springs.
Good night.
Okay. Good night.
[MOMOTARO]
That was the best!
Let's do this again sometime!
Some place that has alpacas!
You can see them anytime
you want at the zoo.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey! That reminds me.
I dreamt about alpacas
all last night!
[RIN]
Ah, a shrine. Wanna make a stop?
[NITORI]
Sure!
[MOMOTARO] Ah! Guys! They're
selling charms! Charms!
No question, we're
buying something!
Whoa, so many to choose from!
Which one are you thinking
of getting, Sosuke?
None.
I know!
Listen, why don't we totally
get them some charms
as their goodbye present?
Hey, not a bad idea!
[laughs] I'll leave it
up to you to choose
the best one for Rin!
And I'll pick Sosuke's!
[NITORI]
Right. Which one?
For you, Rin. A gift.
Me? Really?
I love it, Ai. Thanks.
[laughs]
I chose the perfect one for you!
Bet I can guess.
[gasps]
[REI groans] Feels like we're
nowhere close to finishing.
I sure hope Rin
gets to wear this.
That could be difficult,
considering his schedule.
Agreed.
Like today he had to
drop back by Samezuka.
Why's that?
I thought he moved out
of the dorms already.
Apparently, he's helping
Sosuke pack up his stuff.
[RIN chuckles]
Got a lot of gifts, didn't ya?
[SOSUKE]
Guilty.
Wha...? What is this?
[SOSUKE]
A Mecha-Salmon Roe from Uozumi.
[RIN]
Okay...?
Transforms into a salmon.
Ah...
Anything the matter?
I'm fine.
I guess I have to win.