[gasps]
After all these years.
I found it! The
legendary magic lamp!
How I've waited for this!
[laughs]
Speak any wish you desire
and I will grant it for you!
My wish is for
countless new members
to join Iwatobi Swim Club!
Your wish is my command!
So! In conclusion.
[ALL] Iwatobi Swim Club
eagerly awaits your arrival!
[STUDENTS cheer]
I figured there'd
be more. Darn it.
[REI]
We failed.
What did we do wrong?!
Wha...? Yikes.
[REI] What an ominous dream.
Is it already morning?
[NAGISA]
Who you trying to fool?
That's not Iwatobi
Surprise bread,
it's just regular...
[REI]
Rise and shine.
I hate to disrupt REM sleep
but Haruka and the others
should be arriving soon.
--[REI] Hm?
--[phone vibrating]
[REI] Good morning, Makoto.
Are you close by?
[MAKOTO]
You sound wide awake.
We should be at your apartment
building in a little bit.
I take it you're
both ready to go?
Are we? Never more ready!
Ready!
[MAKOTO] Hey, Rei. Which car
should I put this in?
[REI] You can set that
in Miss Amakata's vehicle.
You got it.
I'm gonna put this
one in Rin's car.
Great.
Whoa! Check out this
good looking car!
It's not mine. I borrowed it
from my mom for the day.
[NAGISA] Doesn't take away
from the coolness!
[REI]
Rin, Ms. Amakata.
Thanks for helping us out
this early in the morning.
It's my job as your faculty
advisor to be on time.
One of Confucius's
proverbs comes to mind.
"If I hear the Way
in the morning,
in the evening I'm
content to die."
Aw, yeah, I'm feelin' pumped!
[RIN humming]
[NAGISA] Wow. You're a
responsible driver!
I wouldn't call it impressive.
Hah! You wanna talk technique?
I'd leave you in the
dust anytime, anywhere,
no matter the ride.
[HARUKA]
So prove it.
[MAKOTO]
Now, now.
Everyone knows you're both
excellent behind the wheel.
I saw first hand when
you drove through Tokyo
the other day, remember?
True.
Also, there were far more
cars on the road there
than there are here but
you're right, no big deal.
Now you've done it.
Hah! Think Tokyo's a challenge?
I'll be livin' in Sydney.
Lemme show you how
the Aussies do it, mate!
[AMAKATA]
Hey.
Look at Matsuoka hugging
the curve like that.
Pretty smooth!
[REI, GOU yelping]
[yelps] Slow down! This is
equipment is rented!
Please be more careful!
I don't know what came over me!
Jeez, Rin, you sure bring out
people's competitive side.
[RIN]
Not a bad job.
You guys went all
out making these.
'Cause we're gonna be
projecting the video
on stage during the
new student welcome!
You're treatin' it
pretty seriously.
[RIN]
What's up, Rei?
Huh? Nothing. I'm fine.
[NAGISA] You aren't worried
about your dream?
The one from last night?
[RIN]
Wait, what?
He had a dream that zero new
members joined the club.
Zero? You don't think that's
really gonna happen?
[REI]
No! What a ridiculous notion!
Dreams are illogical!
How could something
irrational be bothering me?
That in and of itself
is illogical!
[laughs]
[REI]
Let's get started!
First item on the agenda is
rehearsing the introduction
performance for the
Iwatobi Swim Club!
We open up with Rei doing
air swimming on stage,
showcasing the latissimus
dorsi with the butterfly.
Suddenly, out of nowhere,
a huge wave splashes in!
--[REI] Whoa!
--Splash!
Sending him into the world
of Arabian Nights!
At which point, cue the
movie we're filming today!
That's a pretty
elaborate performance.
One part live stage,
one part video.
Just the sort of bold and
aggressive production
our Swim Club needs.
[HARUKA]
Then we enter.
I'm playing a mysterious peddler
who guides our swimmer
through the desert.
I'm the evil king
who's after the lamp
for his own selfish reasons.
And yours truly will
be playing the genie
of the magic lamp!
[REI] Uh, we were originally
gonna cast Coach Sasabe
to be in the role, but there
was a scheduling conflict.
Don't you think Nagisa
is a little young to exude
the prestige needed for a genie?
You say that now, but look out!
Add a fake moustache! Voila!
[RIN]
Well, I'm sold.
Since you're already here,
why don't you make
a special appearance as the
evil king's loyal henchman!
We even have a costume
ready for you!
Not doin' the movie.
It'd look bad if someone
outside of Iwatobi
was in a video for the school.
[NAGISA]
Aw.
Plus, you know I only
agreed to help transport
your gear to the set.
You're not leaving when
you just got here?
I've got a meeting
with Ai to discuss
him taking over as swim captain.
Besides, once you finish up with
filming, the trains and buses
will be running,
so you'll get home fine.
[MAKOTO]
Thanks for helping out, Rin.
[REI] We couldn't have
gotten here without you.
We won't forget it.
No sweat.
[NAGISA]
One last thing!
You better come visit us!
[chuckles] You guys look
really good in those costumes.
Do your best and I'll
see you 'round, okay?
Quiet on the set!
Ready? Action!
[REI grunts]
[REI]
Wh... What happened?
It must have been
my butterfly stroke.
It was so magnificent,
nature grew jealous.
And sent a tidal wave to
bring me to this strange land.
Cruel fate!
[NAGISA]
Okay, cut!
He's a pretty good actor, huh?
Yeah, a perfect take.
Natural talent is what he's got!
He's doesn't hold back--
hard to believe he's
a newbie. However...
The lighting on his
skin needs something.
What?
I'm thinking more suntan
oil will do the trick.
Paired with the
silver reflector.
The reflector?
[AMAKATA gasps]
Yeah!
Isn't that what this round
thing is called, maybe?
As expected, Miss Amakata!
You have tirelessly studied
a list of technical terms
to help us make this into
a first rate production!
[AMAKATA]
Yeah! Sure!
[REI] Then we must meet that
level of professionalism
and have our most prefect acting
on full display for the camera!
[NAGISA]
But first,
Nagisa's gonna have
to put suntain oil on you.
You stay back!
I did it myself earlier!
That amount of oil
is in no way beautiful!
[NAGISA]
Stop struggling and hold still!
[REI] Too much will
diminish the beauty!
[NAGISA] Remember, it's
adding production value!
The next scene is
where I, Rei Ryugazaki,
wander through the strange
world of Arabian Nights.
Only to find that
my path crosses
with the mysterious
peddler, Haruka.
[MAKOTO muttering]
Within those bundles,
the mysterious peddler
carries a lamp.
[REI]
You all set?
We don't have much time,
so lets get this next shot.
Yes, I'm ready.
[NAGISA]
And action!
Who did you say you were?
[HARUKA]
I am a mysterious peddler.
I travel carrying
mysterious bundles.
While riding atop my
mysterious partner,
Chappy the Camel.
[NAGISA]
And cut!
Ah! Your acting has an
unexpectedly natural air!
[GOU] Up next on the schedule,
we shoot your scene, Makoto.
Uh-- Okay!
Wi-Within those bundles,
the mysterious peddler
carries a lamp.
A magic lamp that holds
a genie who grants wishes.
I must have the lamp,
no mander whaa...
[NAGISA]
Cut!
[MAKOTO]
I'm a terrible actor!
You can do this!
Just relax as you
deliver your lines!
Makoto.
When I'm nervous,
I think about mackerel.
[MAKOTO] H-How is that
supposed to help me?!
Fish should be the last thing
on an evil king's mind!
[NAGISA] Maybe he should think
about a pumpkin instead?
[REI]
Why a pumpkin?!
[NAGISA]
I'm just trying to collaborate.
[RIN]
All right, Ai. Let's start.
This meeting is to discuss
your transition to captain.
Okay! Where do you
think we should begin?
We definitely need
to revise the entire
first-year training regimen.
Will do.
[RIN]
Hm? What's this?
Oh. That's a Lucky Meal
and apparently they come
with a toy in each one.
The cashier said ordering
that was the better deal.
Looks like somethin' Momo
would fall in love with.
[laughs] It's true,
he probably would.
[gasps] Momo?
Sorry?
Oops! I thought you
were another person!
Hey, Asahi what's the problem?
No problem, be right back.
You still there?
[ASAHI]
Sorry about that.
Anyway, what are you doing
all the way over in Tokyo?
Didn't you get my message?
I said I'd be coming in March.
[KISUMI]
March? I don't think so.
As I recall, your message
clearly said May.
[ASAHI]
What, seriously?
Then I guess it was a typo.
I kinda suspected since
it was a pretty weird time
for you to be on a break.
Dammit, Kisumi!
Ugh! You mean you
knew it was a mistake
and never said anything?
[RESTAURANT CROWD]
I already bought
millet dumplings
and other souvenirs
for when I came to visit!
[NAGISA]
That was so delicious!
[MAKOTO] Wow, Miss A,
you even went to the trouble
of making lunches for us.
We can't thank you enough.
[AMAKATA]
No worries.
The one thing you can't
skimp out on during filming
is craft service for
the crew and actors.
The food was great,
but if only we we had
Gou's chocolate-flavored
protein rice balls,
this would have been
the perfect afternoon.
I was thinking of
making some but I didn't
have all the ingredients.
[MAKOTO, REI sigh]
[clears throat] Despite the
absence of chocolate rice balls,
lunch was fantastic and
we finished our shoot!
Once the edit's
complete and projected,
I'm sure the club will be
overflowing with new members!
[laughs]
[REI]
Nagisa. Gou.
There's still a lot of
work left to be done.
Let's put the finishing
touches on it
and recruit more students!
Team post-production!
[GOU, NAGISA]
Yeah!
[SASABE]
Take your marks.
[REI]
As long as I have this...
It is I, the genie
of the magic lamp!
Who has summoned me and
disturbed my slumber?
[REI grumbles]
You show off.
Your acting is pitch perfect.
And your portrayal of
the genie is commendable.
[laughs] The moustache
is doing the work.
Still. I can't help but feel
like something's missing.
Something I can't
put my finger on.
Yeah. You feel the same way?
Yes.
In terms of a self-produced
invitation video,
I don't think we could have
achieved greater success.
And yet...
It feels like there's an element
we're not fully conveying.
What could it be?
[yelps]
Huh?
No way!
[REI]
Hm. What are we missing?
What are we missing...?
You know what?
We could try asking Haru
and Mako what they think.
We could.
But we can't continue to
rely on the upperclassmen
to help us forever.
In order to prove ourselves,
we have to solve this
problem without their help.
Otherwise, after
they move to Toyko,
they'll be worrying if
leaving the club in our hands
was a mistake.
There's gotta be
a solution though.
[ASAHI] The most important
part is never giving up.
[gasps]
I know it's gonna sound cliché,
but no matter how remote
your chances are,
as long as a
possibility remains,
you've just gotta keep trying.
[FRIEND A]
Hang on a sec.
So you're planning on
going to Tokyo right now?
[ASAHI] No, but I thought
I could at least drop off
the souvenirs at
his parents' house.
[FRIEND B]
The dumplings?
[ASAHI] Shut up! They were
going to expire today!
I can't think
of anything good!
Yeah, same here.
[GOU]
Rei! Nagisa! Guess what!
[NAGISA]
What's up?
[GOU] I found something
amazing! Take a look!
It's an old Iwatobi Swim Club
new student
invitation guidebook!
And what makes this
so remarkable?
Okay, try not to be too shocked.
Earlier today, I checked
the history of the club
in the faculty room.
And you are never going
to believe how many
new students decided to join
the year it was established!
The most in history!
A total of 30!
[BOTH]
Thirty new members?!
[GOU] And inside it tells
how they made it happen!
[NAGISA]
Quick! Open it!
[NAGISA] What's going on
with the number four?
What's that about?
[GOU]
Right? Aren't you curious?
[NAGISA] Of course! Where's
the page explaining it?
[GOU]
Unfortunately...
That part is missing.
What? That's so unfair!
What good's saving
the book then?
Because the other
pages are intact,
so maybe we can still get
a record number of students...
The most important part
is never giving up.
Except the ice cream thing
does seem like bribery.
I don't think I'd complain!
[REI]
Then it's decided!
What an interesting
turn of events.
Quite obviously, the only
choice we have is to search
until we locate
that missing page!
Are you sure you wanna
spend time looking
for something you may not find?
Now while you might find
this to be bit cliché,
no matter how remote
your chances are,
as long as even a
possibility remains,
you've just gotta keep trying.
Agreed? Now who's with me?
[SASABE] Hm, afraid I'm at
a loss. I'm no spring chicken
but this was way
before even my time.
[NAGISA]
That is old.
However, I feel as though
I've heard about this
PKH business at some point.
[REI]
Do you remember where?
Nah. Not enough to be a help.
[GOU] Anything at all
would be amazing.
[SASABE]
Hm...
Hey, the equipment you ordered
finally arrived, Coach Sasabe.
[SASABE]
Terrific. I'll be right over.
If I remember anything,
I'll let you know ASAP.
Later!
[NAGISA] All caps.
It's gotta be an acronym.
[GOU]
PKH.
[NAGISA] Maybe it's some kinda
technical swimming term?
[GOU]
I've never heard of it.
Then another sport, like soccer?
Or related to baseball maybe?
[NAGISA, GOU groan]
We won't make
progress by guessing.
Tomorrow, the three of us will
conduct a thorough search.
We'll leave no stone
unturned and won't quit
until we recover
the missing page!
--Let's go!
--[GOU] Yeah!
[NAGISA] So, we'll start
by emptying everything
out of the clubroom!
[REI]
Sounds like a plan!
[NAGISA, GOU]
Yeah!
[NAGISA]
Nothing here either.
I don't know if
we'll ever find it.
[REI]
Those are the last two.
That's all that's left?
Except... There is one last
room we haven't checked yet.
Great news!
My optimism's restored!
[HARUKA]
You guys taking inventory?
[MAKOTO]
What's going on here?
[NAGISA]
It's kind of a long story.
[REI] We're currently on
the hunt for a misplaced item.
What are you both up to?
You know, just stopping by.
Is there anything we can
help you guys out with?
[REI]
Absolutely not!
It's nothing I would
ask the upperclassmen
to trouble themselves over!
[GOU]
Nagisa, Rei, look what I found!
Oh, hey, guys! You're
helping search, too?
You said you
found something out?
New developments!
When I took a look at the
old minutes, I figured out
that the Swim Club has
so many people who joined
that first year, they had to
operate out of a separate room
in the activities building!
[BOTH gasp]
It's there! We'll need a key!
I'm positive Miss Amakata
could provide us with one!
[AMAKATA] Apparently, this
clubroom hasn't been used
by anyone in over
ten years. So get ready.
It's turning.
[NAGISA]
So, Mako.
You feelin' worried about
the way Rei's been acting?
[MAKOTO]
Was it that obvious?
Ever since the filming,
Haru and I noticed
he's not his usual self.
So, we came by to
make sure he's okay.
I'm starting to get it.
He's on a mission to
find this missing page.
But typically, he'd view this
as a wild goose chase,
so something is bothering him.
It's crossed into obsession.
He thinks the dream
was some kind of warning
that if we don't get any
new members to join up,
then the Swim Club we went
through all the trouble
of reviving will be lost again.
But you got no reason
to be stressed out!
Gou and I are here
to help anyway we can.
[MAKOTO]
Well, all right.
No way.
You seem to have found a box
of former members' swim caps.
Why save those?
Look over here.
A training regimen
from way back when.
[REI]
Such a wealth of information.
Everyone was definitely
giving it their all.
They had over ten times
the members we have currently.
But I don't doubt each
was doing their best
whether at practice,
or while competing
in tournaments.
[phone vibrates]
It's Coach Sasabe.
[SASABE]
Hey, great news! I remember!
The true meaning behind PKH!
Get ready for this.
P is for "Perfect,"
K is "Killer Muscle,"
and H for "Handsome."
Back in the day, there
was this hunky swimmer
named Azuma who
embodied the acronym.
He was the Swim Club's
secret weapon!
[GOU] Here we go.
This is the right year.
[BOTH gasp]
[REI]
I take it he's Azuma.
[GOU] To call his abs the
epitome of male physique
wouldn't be an exaggeration!
And suddenly, the PKH
plan becomes apparent.
Basically, a tactic to lure
a considerable amount
of new female members
into the club
by using this Azuma.
[GOU] Now that you
mention it, looks like
more than half the
members are female.
And they're wearing school
uniforms instead of swimsuits.
Were they all managers?
[NAGISA]
What?
Are you telling me that was
the secret meaning behind PKH?
I'm afraid it was
all for nothing.
Sorry, I'm going
to have to disagree.
I think the three of
you should implement
your own version of it.
Oh, yeah, I gotcha!
Like a PKH Rei variation!
I'm standing right here!
[GOU] Mm... I dunno if I would
call Rei PKH material.
He's standing right here!
Listen everyone.
Since all the boxes are out
why don't we go ahead
and clean up the clubroom?
It's a little early,
but I say we scrub
the pool as well.
[sighs]
Uh--
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Merely reflecting back to when
I first joined the Swim Club.
That day,
after I watched you
swim so beautifully,
I wanted to move through the
water as freely as you did.
You're the whole reason
I joined the club.
Guess what? You already
are free, Rei.
[REI]
Yes!
[NAGISA]
Talk about nostalgic!
You found the little
mascots Haru carved!
[GOU]
I didn't know we had any left.
If you need more,
I have some at home.
[NAGISA]
For real?
Hey! Maybe we can pass
'em out this year, too!
What do you have there?
Oh. A cassette tape?
Yeah. What do you
say we take a look?
[GOU]
This takes me back!
Everyone was trying so hard.
This was from right before
the tournament, wasn't it?
I'm sure past Swim Club members
practiced equally hard.
And now here we are, keeping
that legacy alive and well.
[gasps] All these years later,
history repeats itself.
Nagisa!
Inspiration struck me
like a lightning bolt!
I believe I've discovered
the missing piece.
I know the final edit
we need to make
to the invitation video!
Let's finish it up
then. Can't wait!
And, why don't we hold a
private screening right after?
[REI]
Uh...
Inside the pool! Cool?
[NAGISA] It is I, the genie
of the magic lamp!
Who has summoned me and
disturbed my slumber?
[REI] What the mysterious
peddler said was true!
I can ask for anything!
Come now.
And tell me what
it is you wish for!
I wish for many
new members to join!
In the past,
we were young and formed bonds
with the upperclassmen.
Now we're the upperclassmen.
Looking to develop new ones.
Forging memories
with new friends.
[REI] I want those bonds to
continue. Forever and ever!
Your wish is my command!
We decided we should add
the voiceover at the end.
I couldn't have
said it any better.
Agreed. Good job you guys.
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa.
Rei.
Gou.
As long as the three
of you are here,
Iwatobi High School Swim Club
will be in good hands.
And Makoto and I can graduate
without any worries.
Leave everything to us!
[MAKOTO] Rei. I'm counting
on you as the captain.
Thanks.
[laughs]
[NAGISA] Don't forget,
the live performance
is still yet to come!
[GOU] I already feel
myself getting nervous.
[REI]
There's no point in stressing
before we're even on stage.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, no worries!
[NAGISA]
That's just like you, Gou!
[GOU]
But what if a new member
with incredible muscles
joins? What'll I do?
[NAGISA]
Full on panic!