[MAKOTO]
I'm sorry.
I wish I didn't have
to quit Swim Club.
[IKUYA]
It's not you fault.
You have to take care of your
little brother and sister.
[MAKOTO]
I do. Thanks, Ikuya.
I hate how things turned out.
For the team to
break up like this,
and right before the tournament.
Between me and Asahi leaving...
And Haru... What really
happened to him anyway?
I thought we were close,
but now I'm starting to think,
maybe I'm never going
to understand him.
[gasps]
Makoto. I've made up my mind.
I'm going to America
with my brother.
[MAKOTO]
What?
[IKUYA] I wanna keep
swimming, and get faster.
I never thought I'd like
competing this much.
But I've fallen in love with it.
Ikuya.
[IKUYA] When you see Haru,
give him a message.
Tell him...
[REI]
The meeting will come to order.
I'd like to start off by
proposing the following.
Before Rin leaves for Australia,
we should throw him
a surprise party.
As you'll recall,
he gifted us a pool
full of cherry blossoms.
And we were all touched
by the gesture.
So in my personal view,
we should return this kindness
with a surprise of equal
or greater value.
However, bear in mind Haruka
and Makoto will be--
Gotta keep it short and sweet.
Anyway, who here at
this table has an idea
and wants to start our
brainstorming session?
[NAGISA]
I'll go first!
Picture this: fireworks
shooting off and exploding
the moment Rin dives
into the pool!
That exceeds well beyond
the club's budget.
What if the four of you
sneak into his room
and perform a
choreographed muscle dance
as he's waking up
in the morning?
Back up. What the heck
is a muscle dance?
Uh. I'm thinking we
should keep the surprise
centralized to the pool.
I gotcha, then we can carry Rin
to the pool while he's sleeping!
Then commence with
the muscle dance!
Zero dancing will be involved!
What do you think we
should do for him, Haru?
[HARUKA]
Give him a grilled mackerel.
And it turns out it's
cured in vinegar.
Then, surprise, it's actually...
...Carpaccio.
I think we need
a little bit of fanfare!
In Haru's eyes, that is fanfare.
[MAKOTO laughs]
I'm starting to get hungry.
Why don't we break for lunch?
[GOU]
You got my vote.
[NAGISA]
I vote we order pizza!
On that day,
during the experiment,
a mouse slipped into the
matter transference device.
[alarm blaring]
[VERONICA] David. It doesn't
matter what form you've taken.
Our memories, our love
will never change!
[DAVID]
I'm sorry, Veronica. But...
[gasps]
[DAVID]
We can't.
Since you adore cats,
we can never be together!
[VERONICA]
David! Your face! No! No!
[DAVID]
Forgive me!
[RIN] Ugh. How David had
to give up his love.
And then Veronica,
knowing they couldn't
see each other anymore.
Do you need me to
bring you a tissue?
I'm not crying, Sosuke.
I'm gonna go use the restroom.
You should be allowed to
lose yourself in a movie.
There's no shame in it.
[RIN] Wha-- What part of
"not crying" don't you get?
[RIN]
Gou?
[RIN] That's funny, she
didn't mention anything
about goin' out today.
[MOMOTARO]
Honestly.
Being here,
at this place and getting
to eat a Lucky Meal with you,
um, what I'm saying is
it's a dream come true!
Momo?
[RIN]
Hold the phone.
Is this a date?!
My sister with him ?
[phone vibrates]
Hey, Sosuke. What's up?
Where are you right now?
Sorry, man. 'Fraid I got lost.
[RIN]
Surprise. Okay what do you see?
Are there any
landmarks around you?
Up ahead there's a sign
that's marked "South Exit."
That's the opposite direction
you were supposed to go!
No worries, just hang tight.
I'm gonna come
and find you, okay?
[SOSUKE]
Will do.
[NAGISA]
Sorry about the wait!
Despite being advertised
as a fast food restaurant,
the Super Deluxe Burger takes
a surprisingly long
time to cook.
[MOMOTARO]
What gives?
Who comes to eat here and
doesn't get a Lucky Meal?
Only Lucky Meals give you fries
and a toy with
your burger, y'know?
Think about it: fries and a toy!
And since Gou bought one,
too, they're the best!
[NITORI]
O-Okay. I get it.
Could you please dial it back?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But do you think we
could get started?
[NITORI]
Right! Apologies! Yes! Go ahead!
[REI]
Actually, it's a crucial matter
that requires your assistance.
Oh, don't tell me
you're thinking
of trading Lucky Meal
toys with us?
[NAGISA]
Maybe next time we meet.
Cutting to the chase,
we're interested in throwing
Rin a surprise party
before he leaves
and returns to Australia
and we could use your help.
[NAGISA] 'Cause, you see,
we haven't been able to come up
with any good ideas on our own.
So we thought we'd ask
you two if perhaps
you had some insight into
what we should include
regarding the
decorations or food.
Sure, we'd definitely be
interested in helping out.
There was a welcome-slash-
send-off party
with the team at Samezuka
the other day,
but it wasn't a big
surprise or anything.
Don't surprises make you think
of like, stag beetles?
We should totally give Rin one!
He'd love that!
Man, I know I would.
I think there're laws in
place that would keep him
from bringing a stag
beetle into Australia.
That reminds me!
I brought along some
presents for everyone today!
An explanation is needed.
Stopping kidding around!
It's food for stag
beetles of course!
I brought one for
each of you guys.
How thoughtful of you.
Wow, thanks! This was
really unexpected!
[MOMOTARO]
Oh, and um, Gou.
I have a special value
size pack just for you!
Here! It's all yours!
Oh, that's terrific.
I'm so glad I came out today!
[RIN]
I'm home.
Oh, welcome back.
How was your day?
Um. Great.
And did you go anywhere today?
Me?
Uh, yeah, I had a sudden
meeting pop up
with Nagisa and Rei
earlier, but that's it.
Completely normal!
[RIN]
Meeting? About what?
Well. Too many things to list.
Why are you asking?
Uh, I, you know, was
just curious, but, uh,
since you're the one
who brought it up.
You're not hiding anything
from me, are you, Gou?
Huh? Why would I be hiding
something from you?
I mean, if I did,
it'd have to be important!
Come on. You're
acting so paranoid!
[MIYAKO]
Don't pry, Rin.
Why can't a girl
have her secrets?
Whatever she's up to
is her own business.
You make it sound like
I have a double life!
Nothing's going on, Mom!
[MIYAKO]
If you say so.
I am saying so.
[RIN]
No. T-Tree sap for stag beetles?
Then Gou and Momo really are...
[GOU]
Everything okay?
You don't look so hot.
I'm perfect.
[gulps]
[RIN]
Gou, are you and Momo--
I mean. No, what I'm
trying to say is, Momo...
"Most peaches and chestnuts
take three years,
Persimmons, eight."
Do you know that proverb?
Huh?
I mean, I've heard of it before,
but why bring that up?
Never mind. It's not important.
Later.
He's sure acting strange.
For real.
[RIN]
It's no good.
I couldn't bring myself
to ask her to her face.
Anyway. Gou's not a kid anymore.
It's not my place to tell her
who she should
or shouldn't date.
Still, it's hard to
believe. Of all people.
Are her and Momo
really a couple?
[MAKOTO]
Fill me in.
How'd your meeting
with the others go?
So good! Momo even gave us
tree sap food for beetles!
[MAKOTO]
What're you talking about?
And the rest of the time,
the weirdo talked endlessly
about his love for
Dangerous Ookuchin Hosoeson.
If it were me,
I'd be super stoked
to find a Dangerous
Ookuchin Hosoeson
waiting inside my lunch!
What's the appeal behind this
Dangerous Ookuchoo
whatcha-call-it?
Only that it's
a super rare toy
that comes with Lucky Meals!
Really?
If it's an ugly fish,
I'm pretty sure Rin got one
with his lunch the other day.
[RESTAURANT CROWD]
What?! Are you kidding me?
[REI] More curious,
Rin bought a Lucky Meal?
It was a recommendation
by the cashier.
Was he happy? Did it
work its magic on him?
Not especially.
Well if Rin doesn't
want it, do you think
he'd let me have his prize?
A Dangerous Ookuchin Hosoeson
is my life goal!
I promise to give
it a good home!
So they...
They were no help at all.
[GOU sighs]
Maybe we'll have better luck
if we try and
brainstorm with Sosuke.
[RIN]
What's the big deal?
I should just ask
him if it's true.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey, Rin! Glad I ran into you!
What's goin' on?
[RIN]
Oh, uh, hi, Momo.
There's something I've
been meaning to ask.
What a coincidence!
There's something I wanted
to talk to you about!
There is?
You bet!
Actually, to be honest,
it concerns something I want.
[RIN]
Something you want?
Then my suspicions were dead on.
It's true? Gou--
So she already
told you everything?
Well, no, not exactly,
but I pieced it together.
Wasn't too hard.
Then, please understand!
It's my life goal!
I need this, Rin!
I've never seen
you this serious.
So it's okay?
First off, it's not place to
say whether you can or can't,
so asking won't
make any difference.
And secondly--
If you can't make up your mind
then the two of us
will hafta race!
If I win, you're gonna
gimme my heart's desire!
[gasps]
Very well. If that's
how you feel.
Obviously, your passion
can only be settled one way.
If it's through a duel,
I gladly accept the
terms of your challenge!
Tomorrow night, at Iwatobi
Swim Club Returns, we race.
Be there!
Thank you! You don't
know how excited I am!
You're gonna lose,
but I won't let you down!
Yahoo!
No way. The gauntlet's thrown!
[UOZUMI]
What? Seriously?
[MINAMI]
I saw it with my own eyes!
Neither of 'em were joking!
A race against Rin with his
little sister on the line
is unbelievable!
But then Momo saying
"Give me my heart's desire?"
Yeah.
Guess if he wins, the guy's
gonna propose to her.
In high school and already
thinking about marriage.
Momotaro Mikoshiba is a
man who lives by passion.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Are you kidding me?
[MINAMI]
Uh, hi, hello, sir!
[UOZUMI]
Didn't see you there.
Doesn't the Spring Break
Training from Hell
start tomorrow?
I couldn't wait to see you guys,
so I came back early only
to find Momo's gone crazy?
How'd he end up like this?
I don't accept it!
And I won't allow it!
[MOMOTARO]
Even if you don't like the idea,
Rin said it was okay, so I
don't see what the problem is!
The problem is it's not enough
to win against Matsuoka!
You're trying to surpass
your older brother!
I think someone's
a little jealous
they didn't come up
with this plan first.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Stop acting like a child!
If Matsuoka says it okay,
then I won't stop the race.
But you should know
you're gonna have to
out swim me as well!
Beat you? Are you
outta your mind?
[MIKOSHIBA]
How do you expect to win
with that kinda attitude?
Huh?
Everything I've ever done
has been for your sake!
I'm always on your side!
This doesn't change that!
And in terms of a competition,
I view it as you and
me versus Matsuoka!
You do?
Did I just hear them
say they're teaming up
to race against Rin?
How did things get
to this point?
[MIKOSHIBA]
Take your marks!
[REI] Even though we're only
asking Sosuke for advice,
is it okay that we're showing
up without an appointment?
[NAGISA]
We're good! Plus,
I know for a fact he
isn't supposed to have
moved outta the dorms yet.
Hey, guys, what are the
two of you doin' here?
[NAGISA]
Nothing!
We, uh, came to ask
Sosuke for advice
regarding our, um,
training regime!
Yes! That's it!
[RIN]
Oh. Really?
[NAGISA] He wasn't
answering his cell phone
so we decided to just show up.
Do you happen to know
if he's around?
He said he was goin' over
to the hospital today.
But if it's about your training,
I'd be more than happy
to help you out.
[NITORI]
Emergency! It's bad! Really bad!
[REI]
Mikoshiba and Momotaro?
So both brothers are
teaming up against me.
[NITORI] What's going on
between you three?
Well, actually, a lot of stuff
has happened recently.
You are gonna accept their
challenge--you have to!
I'm going to.
Be logical about this!
Swimming solo against
two guarantees defeat!
You know he's right!
If it was just Momo
it'd be one thing,
but you're also
going head-to-head
with our old captain,
a college student with serious
training under his belt!
[NAGISA]
Doesn't matter!
You'd never run
from a challenge!
Even if the odds
are against you!
No. Of course
I'm gonna race 'em.
Then I propose you at least
follow the theory of contests.
And have the match
be equal odds.
Two teams, two swimmers.
Haru! He would totally
be on your team!
Look, this is personal matter
and the last thing I want
is for him to get wrapped up
in all this drama.
Could you clarify what
you mean by personal?
[RIN]
Uh, j-just forget about it!
But... I know that if I lose
this race, I'll never be able
to go back to Australia
with a clear conscience.
[NAGISA, REI gasp]
[GOU] I wonder if Nagisa
and Rei had any luck
talking to Sosuke.
If they did,
I'm sure they came up
with some good ideas.
[phone vibrates]
Nagisa?
Hey, we've got problems!
Ask Haru for a favor!
Check if he can swim
in Rin's match!
Huh? Rin's match?
[NAGISA] Yeah! 'Cause he
said if he lost the race,
he couldn't bring himself
to go to Australia anymore!
[MAKOTO]
What?
Anyway, if Haru's
there, just ask him!
This is serious!
Wait! Don't hang up the phone!
What's going on?
[MAKOTO]
Well, if I understand right,
Rin wants a match with you.
And if he doesn't win, he's
not going back to Australia.
You have to be joking.
Years of training, and he's
ready to quit just like that?
It can't be true!
He never mentioned
anything to me!
But... now that
I'm thinking back.
When we talked the other day,
he did say something weird.
[MAKOTO]
What?
Let's see. A proverb.
"Most peaches and chestnuts
take three years.
Persimmons, take eight."
What do you think it could mean?
Maybe it's a code.
[MAKOTO] It takes peach
and chestnut trees
three years to bear fruit.
And persimmons take longer.
So, maybe what he was
getting at is this.
If you wanna succeed at
anything, it's gonna take time.
But, eight years?
Actually, from the time he
first started swimming to now,
it's been way longer than that!
Does he maybe think it's
taken him too long?
That he's less than a persimmon?
That big idiot.
Rin would never lose
to a persimmon, ever!
You can't give up!
Scratch the surprise party!
He needs our help! Now!
[phone vibrating]
Uh.
Haru?
Whatever's wrong,
it must be important.
When's the last time you
called me? So, what's up?
It's about the match.
I heard from Nagisa and Rei.
Those blabber mouths can't
keep anything confidential.
It's a personal problem,
which is why I explained to them
not to get you involved at all.
It's a personal problem?
Very. But, you shouldn't
worry about it.
[HARUKA]
How can you say that?
Huh?
How does this issue
not concern me?
I don't understand why
you're gettin' so worked up.
Don't tell me you
and Gou are also...
[HARUKA]
This isn't about Gou.
Don't change the subject.
[RIN]
That is the subject!
[HARUKA]
Listen.
The only reason I was able
to move towards the future
was because of you.
So what gives?
You just decided to put
your dreams on hold?
[RIN]
What?
How can you say you're
going to quit swimming
after all this time!
You are not less
than a persimmon!
[RIN] Whoa, I don't know what
we're talkin' about anymore!
I never said I was gonna
stop swimming, okay?
You're not quitting?
[RIN]
Are you insane?
Nagisa said Australia hinged on
winning a match against me.
And if you lost,
you weren't going back.
Where'd that come from?
Besides the race is me
versus Momo and his brother!
Can you even believe it?
And if the creep wins,
I have to give him Gou.
I didn't realize
they were a thing.
Neither did I, but I saw them.
They both met yesterday.
Looked like they were
on a lunch date.
[HARUKA]
Yesterday?
Yeah.
Over at the hamburger joint--
the one they built a year ago?
What you saw... wasn't a date.
[RIN] Seriously? You were
planning a surprise party?!
Yeah, and when Momotaro
challenged you,
I don't think it had anything
to do with your sister.
Bet he wants your
Dangerous Ookuchin Hosoeson
What the heck is that?
It doesn't matter.
The more important thing is,
do you think it was okay
for you to tell me
about the party?
Don't blame me if Gou
and the others get upset.
[laughs] I'm sure they won't.
Things could have gotten weird
if you hadn't called me.
And anyway,
I may know about the party,
but finding out
I get to swim with
you one last time
is a good enough surprise.
Are you sure about that?
Why wouldn't I be?
If those brothers are looking
for a real challenge,
I don't think we should
disappoint them.
[SASABE] All right, gents.
The rules are simple.
Two teams. Two
swimmers. Freestyle.
Everyone ready to get
this match started?
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
Thanks for racing
us today, you guys.
Absolutely!
How this came
together is bizarre,
but a race is still a race!
And when we win,
Dangerous Ookuchin
Hosoeson is mine!
[RIN]
Haru.
[gasps]
[MIKOSHIBA]
Hey, before we start,
I'm glad I have the opportunity
to swim with you again.
But I won't hold anything back.
Good, 'cause neither will I.
[laughs] That's what
I like to hear!
[SASABE]
Swimmers, get ready.
Set.
[whistle blows]
[MOMOTARO]
Holy moly!
He's always been amazing,
but look at my brother go!
Yeah, I mean I know
he's giving it his all
on this short
distance, but still.
He's on a completely different
level from high school!
Look at Haru, though.
They're neck and neck!
[MOMOTARO]
Going in for the turn. Aw yeah!
[SASABE]
Haruka's right behind him!
They're both exceptional,
but Mikoshiba's technique
really stands out.
He, he. You know me losing
to you isn't an option.
Heh. I'll let you
get a head start.
Just make sure no one comes up
from behind you and bites.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Go!
Rin!
[MIKOSHIBA] As usual, Matsuoka's
leg propulsion is on point.
But my brother's givin'
him quite a challenge.
He must really wanna win
that toy, am I right?
[SASABE]
Look at Rin go.
Totally focused.
Swimming with all his heart.
Just one glance
and anyone could tell
how much he loves the water.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Almost there, Momotaro!
[SASABE]
Twenty meters remain!
Yes!
Aw! Why are you so fast, Rin?
Your swimming has
come a long way.
[MOMOTARO, RIN gasp]
[MOMOTARO]
What? Who killed the lights?
[gasps]
[ALL cheer]
Surprise!
[laughs] I admit it, I didn't
see this one coming.
I'm surprised! You guys got me.
[laughs] Just
returning the favor.
In exchange for the
pool of cherry blossoms.
Your friends at Samezuka
helped us organize this, too.
What about me? No one
mentioned any party!
[UOZUMI] Yeah, 'bout that.
We thought you'd let it slip,
so we kinda didn't
tell you. Sorry.
Can you ever forgive us?
[MOMOTARO]
Look at all the animal floats!
You got us an otter!
And even a capybara?
You guys!
For some reason, I really
don't think he's gonna mind!
We planned it for
Rin and turns out
Momotaro's the most surprised.
Nagisa thought the
inclusion of balloons
would be a welcome addition.
So how do you like them?
We all worked together last
night to get everything ready.
All of you?
It's cool if you need to cry.
If you stay in the pool,
no one will ever
notice your tears.
[RIN]
Idiots! Shut up, I never cry.
[AMAKATA]
I believe there's a saying.
One can only truly move forward
when tears have
cleared their vision.
I've also got some
words of inspiration
for you to follow.
Have fun with
everything you've got!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[RIN]
Hey, Momo.
Huh?
Take care of this
for me, will ya?
[gasps] I can keep him?
Even though I lost?
Consider it a parting gift.
[MOMOTARO]
Yahoo!
[laughs] Out of everyone here,
Momo sounds the most excited.
You can't blame him.
He didn't know to
expect this either!
[REI] You'll be departing
for Australia next week?
Want us to come see you off?
[RIN]
Nah, you don't have to.
Setting off on a
journey is something
that should be done solo.
How is it possible for
one person to be so cool?
The guy's got
poetry in his blood!
[RIN]
Give it a rest.
[RIN] You know, it's gonna
be a while before we can
all hang out like this again.
That's true.
[RIN]
I gotta be honest.
Being able to spend this
last month with you.
I wouldn't trade
it for anything.
Looking forward to the
next time we can do it.
You bet.
[MOMOTARO] Let's get this
party fired up again!
[RIN]
Agreed!
[HIYORI] Seriosuly?
That's all you're gonna eat?
[IKUYA] And you're eating
too much, as usual.
You forget we've got time trials
as soon as college starts.
[laughs] Diligent
as always, Ikuya.
Yeah, well I suppose
one of us has to be.
[HIYORI]
Come on. I know you're excited.
We're gonna have a lot
of tournaments comin' up.
They'll give us a better idea
of who'll be competing
at the world level
after next year.
Look. Here's a picture of you.
[IKUYA]
I don't care.
As long as I can swim
the way I want.
Okay. Anyway.
I'm looking forward
to the future.
[HIYORI] But in the meantime,
I have to do my best.