[JUZO]
My name is Juzo Inui.
I resolve problems
involving the Extended.
That's why folks call
me the Resolver.
Recently, this kid,
Tetsuro, needed my help.
I took him to see Mary,
an extension engineer
in my part of town,
the Kyusei Pit.
After I refused an offer from
Huang, a higher up in the mob,
Tetsuro used a technology known
as Harmony to take over my body.
Honestly, this situation
snubs my barrel.
Listen.
They said they'd change
your body back to normal.
But before they do, we have to
finish the job we were assigned.
The company has no use for gears
that do not fulfill
their assigned role.
[gasps]
[TETSURO]
These are children!
Not soulless gears!
[ANNE]
But how? You should be dead.
Did the poison not work on you?
[TETSURO] Yeah, it did,
but I guess this body
has some sort of
built‐in resistance to it.
I am a little numb, though.
[CUNNINGHAM] One of those
wretched Kyusei Extended?
So unaware, you didn't even
realize you were being followed.
My goodness. You couldn't
be more useless if you tried.
[snaps]
[TETSURO gasps]
[TETSURO groaning]
[CUNNINGHAM gasping]
[CUNNINGHAM laughing]
[CUNNINGHAM]
Juzo Inui!
[laughs] It appears you've made
me eat my words from before.
You've proven to be
some unexpectedly
useful gears after all.
What a pleasant surprise.
Lucky for you, our
company rewards those
who can demonstrate their worth.
[ANNE gasps]
Anne.
This will be your final
chance to do just that.
Disassemble this
overgrown peashooter
and we'll allow you to live.
A faulty gear can
gum up the works
and wreak havoc on
an entire production.
Prove your worth
right here and right now
and you can be a part of our
efficient machinery once again.
What? You want us to fight?
But using her power
again will kill her!
[ENDE]
Anne.
Please don't worry.
I'll be fine, I swear.
Because your embrace
will hold me together.
[ANNE]
Ende!
Oh, no.
[gasps]
[TETSURO]
Wait!
Stop this!
Listen to me!
Don't you realize you're being
used by some heartless company?
Is that what you really
want for yourselves?
You don't have any idea
what you're talking about!
All you're doing is
shooting your mouth off!
We wanna survive.
And if somebody else
gets hurt along the way,
then too bad for them.
We do whatever
the company tells us
because that's
just how life works!
Ya see?
It's self‐preservation,
so if we wanna keep on living,
then we have no other choice!
[TETSURO groans]
[TETSURO gasps]
[gasps]
[TETSURO]
Oh, no!
[CUNNINGHAM]
Well, what do we have here?
Master Tetsuro.
Has the little troublemaker
been with you this entire time?
No. Wait a tick.
I think I know what's
really going on here.
The boy's not just with him.
I believe he's actually
controlling Juzo Inui.
Master Tetsuro, is that you?
It's amazing.
He's using Harmony!
Oh, my! [chuckles]
So many surprises today!
You didn't have to do
all this for us, you know.
Not only did you render
our biggest nuisance
and your only
protector powerless‐‐
you served him
to us on a platter.
No matter how
powerful a tool may be,
it becomes a blunt instrument
in the hands of a child.
Actually, it's more
like he's become the rope
you're using to hang yourself.
[CUNNINGHAM chuckling]
Master Tetsuro, despite
all your protesting,
you've proven to be just
another tool as well.
[TETSURO]
I got too cocky.
I thought if I just
took over Juzo's body,
I could solve my problems.
I thought all I needed
was physical strength.
But I can't ignore it anymore.
The fact is, deep down,
I'm a weak person.
It's like Juzo said...
[CUNNINGHAM]
Hmm?
[TETSURO]
...achieving justice without
putting your life on
the line is a pipe dream.
[TETSURO] Even so, I still
wanna save those children.
I won't stop doing what's
right‐‐what I believe in.
That's the only way to
prove I'm my own person.
That I am not a tool!
[ANNE grunts]
Ha! You're nothing but a child
spouting off utter nonsense.
And this Gun Slave Unit
is a worthless hunk of trash
with a child using
it as their puppet.
Girl, why are you just
standing there slack‐jawed?
Go and secure that
boy's body at once!
[gasps]
[ANNE]
Don't take it personally.
We're only doing
this to survive.
But, Anne...
So what?
[ANNE] What's wrong with being
a tool for others, anyway?
'Cause free will is completely
meaningless in this world.
We really don't have
a choice in what happens!
Shit! Damn it to hell!
Ende, do it.
Hurry up and kill him already!
If you don't, you know
what'll happen to us.
[ANNE crying]
[ENDE]
Anne. I'm lost.
[ANNE gasps]
Anne.
Please hold my hand.
Ende.
[ENDE]
These aren't my arms.
This isn't my body!
Where did I go?
Please, Anne. I need your help.
Please tell me where I am.
I'm lost, Anne. Where am I?
[ANNE] Remember what
that fake Sister told us?
To hold hands.
That way we won't get lost,
and we'll still be
connected to one another.
I promise I'll always
hold your hand, Ende.
So you'll never get lost,
and I'll never lose you.
[gasps]
[TETSURO groans]
[gasps] Ende!
[CUNNINGHAM] I'm sick
of all these childish games.
I gave you two a second chance
out of the goodness of my heart
and you've just wasted it.
I'm extremely disappointed
in both of you.
And since showing you
mercy didn't seem to work,
I had to resort to
more extreme means
and force your disobedient
hands to do my bidding.
[ANNE]
Ende!
Hang in there! Please, Ende!
[CUNNINGHAM]
I didn't kill her, per se.
The drug I shot her with
will put her brain
into a comatose state.
[gasping]
Ende.
[CUNNINGHAM]
What little self‐awareness
she once possessed will
now be gone completely.
That was the only
thing in the way
of total compliance, after all.
She'll keep up the
attacks as she's been doing
and simply go berserk until
her sub‐brain fizzles out.
Those primitive
Kyusei Extendeds won't
have a snowball's chance in hell
of stopping a cutting‐edge
model like Ende.
This will give us
the opportunity
to swoop in and save the day,
and for that, they
will owe us dearly.
[TETSURO]
Why?!
Couldn't you just take me back
instead of hurting more people?
Did you forget
our chat, Mister Inui?
Oh. I suppose I'm
talking to Tetsuro.
Anyway, I told the owner
of that body you're in now
what I planned to do.
That bit by bit
and little by little,
I would destroy
everything he cares about.
[TETSURO]
What?
[CUNNINGHAM] So my goal was
not to simply capture you
here and be done
with it. Oh, no.
That pistol‐headed
freak made a fool of me,
so I'm staying true to my word
and slowly crushing
every support he has.
I can't stop doing that
before I'm done, now can I?
Besides, you've caused
quite a bit more trouble
than you can handle,
so sooner or later
they're going to run you
out of the Kyusei Pit.
When that happens,
it's only a matter of time
before you get
snatched up again.
But until then I will sit back
and relax in my
comfortable perch
while I enjoy watching you
panic and flail about in vain.
Hang on! You're just
gonna leave us down here?
[ENDE]
Anne.
Where are you?
[ANNE]
I'm here, Ende!
I'm right here!
Run.
No. [gasps]
[TETSURO]
Watch out!
[ANNE yells]
[BOTH groan]
[grunting]
[TETSURO]
What do I do?
I can't use Juzo's
body very well.
But still, I've gotta try.
I have to find some
way to stop her.
I have to do something!
[ANNE] Do you know
how pathetic you are?
[gasps]
[ANNE] I can see the
dead ring on your neck.
You got it from
trying to control
that gun head, didn't you?
At this rate, your sub‐brain
is gonna fry pretty soon.
Can you do something for me?
Please save Ende.
I can't do it.
I need your help.
She doesn't deserve this.
She didn't do anything wrong.
It was all my fault.
I made her do everything.
Ende. I'm sorry.
I'm too weak.
I let go of you.
[TETSURO]
There's only one way.
But I can stop her.
[ENDE screaming]
[TETSURO]
Harmony's power has dropped.
I can't control her whole body.
If that's the case, maybe
I can take over one arm.
I gotta destroy her sub‐brain!
[ENDE screaming]
[TETSURO]
Come on! One more hit!
[groans]
[ENDE]
Anne, where are you?
I'm so scared!
Please hold my hand.
Or else, I'll... Anne, please!
Save me!
[ENDE wailing]
[TETSURO grunts]
'Cause free will is
completely meaningless.
[TETSURO]
But that's not true!
We do whatever
the company tells us
because that's
just how life works!
[TETSURO]
Your lives mean more than that!
Can you do something?
Save Ende. I can't do it.
I need your help.
[TETSURO] I'm not gonna let
all of this be for nothing!
[gasps]
[JUZO grunts]
[TETSURO]
Juzo.
[JUZO] Pretty strange riding
shotgun in my own body.
But still, I could see
everything that happened.
It's like my legs and arms
were moving on their own,
even though I was conscious.
Jeez. You really are
a crazy kid, ya know?
We're gonna have to have a nice
long talk when this is over.
That means you're gonna
have to listen for once.
[JUZO groans]
[ENDE shrieks]
[JUZO sighs]
[gasps]
[JUZO] This fight isn't
settled yet, though.
[JUZO] I know you can't
use Harmony right now.
So what the hell
are you gonna do
since you can't
move on your own?
You wanna try and use
me like a tool again?
Is that the only way you can
think of to clean up your mess?
Huh?
[TETSURO grunts]
[JUZO] I mean, when you
stop and think about it,
didn't you do pretty
much the same kinda thing
Beruhren does on
a smaller scale?
[TETSURO gasps]
[JUZO] You used me because
it was convenient for you.
Like I was just a tool
to get what you wanted.
[TETSURO grunts]
[elevator dings]
[JUZO] I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt
you didn't meant it that way.
But that's what using
Harmony on someone really is.
[MAILMAN A]
Ah! He's got a gun for a head!
[TETSURO groans]
[JUZO]
So think about that quietly
while ya hide
in here for a bit.
[scuttling]
[JUZO]
Huh?
Wh‐What the hell are you doing?
[TETSURO grunting]
[JUZO] There's only
so much whining I can take!
[TETSURO]
Listen, Juzo.
You're the one who told
me to act like a kid!
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO]
If you're a punk kid,
then try acting
like it for a change!
[JUZO]
You little...
[ENDE screams]
‐‐[JUZO] Shit!
‐‐[ENDE screaming]
[JUZO grunting]
[JUZO]
Damn it.
You really are a
major pain in the neck.
[JUZO] Don't use
Harmony anymore, okay?
Besides all that other stuff,
it'll fry your brain.
‐‐[scuttling]
‐‐[gasps]
[JUZO] She'll catch up
with us any moment now.
[JUZO]
Look.
Don't forget it's your
fault I'm so beat up.
And since I'm not
a hundred percent right now,
we're running out
of options to stop her.
I'm all outta smokes, too.
There's about a 90 percent
chance she'll die,
but I want you to
try your absolute best
to aim for just her
body extensions.
And then... pull my trigger.
[gasps]
[TETSURO]
But if I do that,
I'd be killing her
with my own hands.
[JUZO] If you really wanna
do what you believe is right,
no matter what anybody
else may tell ya,
you've gotta show some resolve!
Save Ende. I can't do it.
[ENDE screaming]
[TETSURO]
Yeah.
I really need to
wipe my own ass for once.
[TETSURO]
You were right all along, Juzo!
[ENDE screams]
[JUZO]
Well, damn.
I guess my days of trying to lay
low in the Kyusei Pit are over.
[JUZO] But thanks to Huang,
at least Mary wasn't kicked out.
Hate to break it to ya, kid.
In the eyes of
the Beruhren Corp,
you've graduated
from prey to enemy.
Don't you dare forget that.
[JUZO] The "poison"
from that poor Ende kid‐‐
it was like a special code
that paralyzes the
sub‐brain of an Extended.
Lucky for me, it wasn't designed
to work on tech as old as mine.
[JUZO] Anyway, Mary's
gonna make a counterprogram.
I'm not the most optimistic guy,
but I think she can
help those kids...
...even that girl, Ende.
[TETSURO]
Be honest.
You could've resisted Harmony
and taken back control
whenever you wanted.
Am I right?
[TETSURO] So you were actually
letting me control you.
[JUZO] No wonder
Beruhren is so desperate
to get their claws
into you again.
Do you know how hard it
was just to move my arm?
Which reminds me...
[TETSURO gasping]
[JUZO] I'm gonna say
this as clearly as I can.
[JUZO] Don't you ever think
about using Harmony on me again!
I helped you out this time
because that's the job
you hired me to do.
But the only people
that are allowed
to touch my trigger are
the ones I've accepted.
And I don't plan on accepting
anybody, you understand?
[JUZO] Walk the rest
of the way yourself.
[TETSURO grunts] Well, I don't
wanna go through that again!
Because walking around
with that head cannon
is like being a
magnet for trouble!
[JUZO]
What did you say?
[TETSURO] And you have
a big 'ol nasty wart
or something on
your left butt cheek!
Haven't you heard of a
little concept called privacy?
I went through all
that crap for you
and this I what I get in return?
[TETSURO] And your big
toe on your right foot...
[JUZO yells]
[OLIVIER]
You've really done it now.
I assume you know what
this means, don't you?
Things just got more
complicated, Juzo.
[MARY] Isn't EMS
finding out a bad thing?
[JUZO]
Calm down.
Just stay quiet and wait, okay?
[TETSURO]
You gotta save us, Juzo!
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Five:
"EMS."