[GIRL A]
Didn't you know?
[GIRL B]
My parents told me to avoid
that neighborhood since
it's full of Extended!
They're such scary creatures.
You can never tell what
those things might be up to.
[ROSA]
You really think so?
Uh?
[ROSA] To be fair,
maybe some of them are bad,
but they can't all
be like that, right?
[ROSA]
My name is Rosa McMahon.
I was a normal
girl going to school
and living an everyday life.
[car honking]
[gasps]
[ROSA] Until an Extended
took my parents away from me.
[gasps]
[ROSA yelps]
[ROSA gasps]
[crash]
[JUZO]
My name's Juzo Inui.
Ever since the Great War,
the city's been
overflowing with Extended‐‐
people who went
through modifications
to fight or survive
or just to change.
It can be difficult to
reassimilate into society,
so I make a living
by cleaning up.
My current client is
this gentleman, Danny Yoe.
These steps are tricky,
so be careful.
[JUZO] Danny works for
the Department of Justice.
He wants me to
stand guard for Rosa.
She's the daughter of his
late colleague, George McMahon,
who apparently used
to own this place.
[JUZO] And, yeah, that
sounds like an ordinary gig...
...except a few days ago,
the family was in a pretty
terrible car accident.
Rosa's folks died on impact.
She got injured and lost
a leg, but she survived.
Since then, strange
and inexplicable events
have started happening.
People are saying
that she's being haunted,
and that a ghostly
Extended is to blame.
Because of that, most of
the house servants have quit.
As you can see there's hardly
anybody left to look
after the poor girl.
[JUZO]
I get it, but are you sure
you called the
right guy for this?
I may be a gun for hire,
but I'm no exorcist.
I think I've found a lead.
I came into contact
with this supposed ghost
and chased it
through the mansion.
Ohh!
[DANNY] Unfortunately, this is
where I lost track of the beast.
Please note the ground below.
[JUZO]
Hmm... Footprints?
[DANNY]
Yes.
[MARY] Wait, so it's
not some evil spirit?
[DANNY] I'm certain the
culprit is actually hunting
for valuable evidence
regarding a criminal case.
Ugh. That's all?
[DANNY]
Anyway,
Rosa's still convinced
there's a phantom lurking about.
However, my theory makes sense.
George and I worked primarily
on legal matters
involving Extended.
And I was hoping you could
at least uncover
the culprit's motive.
With that, we can
hopefully find a way
to put an end to all of this.
Whatever the case,
till we find the truth,
Rosa may be in danger.
You must understand
she is the precious daughter
of my dear old friend.
So please, lend us your
strength and protect her.
[JUZO]
I don't know.
This whole situation's
pretty sketchy.
[MARY] I went ahead and
got you more cigarettes.
And an invoice
for your convenience.
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO]
No dodging this bullet.
Hello, dear,
you awake? It's just me.
I'm coming in now.
She's gone?
[ROSA]
No! Let me go!
Come on. Stop hiding
under the bed!
I have to! I know there's
someone out there watching me!
I keep telling you,
it's a ghost!
[ROSA gasps]
[DANNY]
Rosa?
[JUZO gasps]
No!
Uh, hey. Are you okay?
[ROSA] What is that
monster doing in my room?
Get him out!
[DANNY]
Calm down, it's all right!
I asked him to come here and
protect you for your own good.
Listen, young lady. There's
nothing trying to haunt you.
I've already told you,
it's likely a thief
searching through
this house for something.
Now I'll ask you
one more time, my dear.
Do you have any idea what
they might be looking for?
You're sure your father
didn't mention anything?!
[ROSA]
Stop. That hurts.
[DANNY gasps]
My apologies.
I think it's time we try
a more feminine approach.
[JUZO] No way, hotshot!
This is my job re‐‐
[MARY]
Hurry up and get out!
[JUZO]
Hey, wait!
[door closes]
[JUZO gasping] My chamber's
all wet! I'm gonna rust!
[DANNY]
Forgive me, Mr. Inui.
Ever since the accident,
Rosa's been very suspicious
of anyone with extensions.
[JUZO] I've got a face that
triggers people. I'm used to it.
Huh?
Hmm?
What's the matter?
[JUZO] Our ghost has
already shown himself.
You stay here.
Wait a moment!
[ROSA]
Um, who are you?
You can call me Mary.
Uh, I'm an engineer.
[ROSA]
An engineer?
For Extended.
I work on people like my big
friend Juzo that you just met.
[ROSA]
Get out!
I'm not sure what
Mr. Danny told you,
but I won't have
extension surgery!
You poor little thing.
I bet you haven't had the
chance to wash up properly.
Lucky for you,
I've got a lot of experience
taking care of patients!
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO] I'm gonna have
to sew up my coat again!
[JUZO]
Which means,
you can lend a hand,
since you're obviously no ghost.
Huh?
Well, son of a gun.
So you've got something
against the Extended.
[MARY]
Some of them definitely
let their abilities
go to their heads.
And some do bad things
so they can pay their
maintenance bills.
But still, there
are good people.
Plenty of 'em choose this
life in order to survive.
Is that so wrong?
Whatever the reason,
I can't believe someone
would choose that.
It doesn't make any sense.
And I know what I saw.
That fateful night,
a ghastly arm crashed
through the windshield.
My father was doing work that
made the Extended hate him.
This was revenge.
[MARY] Your dad worked for
the Department of Justice,
am I right?
So that's... [gasps]
Wait! No way!
What the‐‐ Is that
a real Gustav MV 360?
[ROSA] That thing?
It was father's bike.
[MARY] You can't just
call it that thing!
Only five of these
precious speed demons
were ever produced
during the entire war!
The temperature from the
gas turbine engine exhaust
would get so high
after prolonged use
that it would melt
the bike itself!
Uh... uh...
Sorry. I guess
I got carried away.
[ROSA] No need to apologize.
We still have it in storage,
so you can do with
it as you please.
[gasps] Are you kidding me?
[ROSA] I mean... I won't
be able to use it anyway.
[MARY] You've been wearing
that this whole time.
Is it important to you?
Father gave it to me...
right before the accident.
Oh, you don't say?
[ROSA]
It's almost funny.
Who would think to give
a girl such a big, ugly pendant?
It was unlike him.
He seldom gave me presents.
[DANNY] Rosa! The intruder's
here once again!
Don't be so rude! You can't just
barge in on a girl like that!
There isn't time to explain!
Mr. Inui's fighting him off.
We must hurry to safety!
[MARY] Wait! Could you
not yank her around?
[ROSA gasps]
Let's go, now!
Put me down! I refuse
to surrender my house
to the ghost of an Extended!
[DANNY grunts]
‐‐[ROSA gasps]
‐‐Oh, thank goodness!
You're all right!
I was just about to find
a place for us to hide.
[JUZO] Sorry for the wait,
miss, thought I'd have a smoke.
You're awfully calm.
Could it be that you've already
taken care of our
mysterious trespasser?
[JUZO]
Not to sound slow on the draw,
but what would you
do if I told you
that thing really was a ghost?
That's impossible.
You remember those footprints‐‐
Tthe ones outside the window.
[JUZO]
That's a half‐cocked response.
'Cause after all...
[DANNY, ROSA gasp]
[JUZO] ...last time I checked,
ghosts don't have feet.
Huh? [gasps]
[ROSA gasps]
It's that arm... from the crash.
No way! A hands‐only model?
Wait, why is it not
attacking you, Juzo?
[JUZO]
Sorry. You got it all wrong.
It's time you saw what's
really been haunting you.
[JUZO]
Question for ya.
It's pretty obvious you made
fake footprints for
an imaginary culprit.
Why'd you think you
had to take it that far?
[JUZO] This might
be a shot in the dark,
but I think you were trying
to trick her into thinking
somebody was after
something her dad left behind.
All in the hopes
that she'd give it up...
...right, Danny‐boy?
[gasps] What are you
talking about?
Uh, Juzo?
You gonna tell us what's up?
[inhales, screams]
‐‐[DANNY groans]
‐‐[ROSA, MARY gasp]
‐‐[MARY] Are you kidding?
[MARY]
He has the place bugged?!
[DANNY] No, i‐it's not what
it looks like! I promise!
I was only thinking
about Rosa's safety‐‐
[JUZO]
You're way off the mark, pal.
[DANNY]
Huh?
[JUZO] She could've been
attacked at any moment.
Yet you didn't hire
a single guard to watch her.
Not to mention you left her
all on her own when
you came to hire me.
[JUZO] Because you knew
she wouldn't get hurt,
'cause she was never
in any real danger.
[JUZO] Now, if I were you,
I'd hand over the girl.
[ROSA]
No.
You're nothing but
a heartless Extended.
I'd never believe
a word from you.
But Rosa!
[JUZO] Really? Did you
not hear a single th‐‐
Don't touch me!
You decided to become a weapon
so you could murder
innocent people, didn't you?
Honestly, you're not
even human anymore.
You're a monster.
Well, come along.
Hold up. Mr. Danny,
wait a second!
I'm relieved that you
chose not to trust Mr. Inui.
How brave of you to place
your confidence in me, dear.
I certainly hope that
nothing he said back there
was remotely true.
Unfortunately, Mr. Danny,
I'm afraid, I don't
have faith in you anymore.
My firearm?
When did you take it?
[DANNY]
Ah, there it is.
I should've known that
George would pass it on to you.
I admit it.
Mr. Inui was correct.
I resorted to using microphones
and a listening device
to uncover its whereabouts.
But I only did it for the
sake of keeping you innocent.
To protect you!
Your father and I...
As you know,
everything we fought for
was in the name of justice.
The real enemy is overwhelming.
And it's one I must
fight all by myself.
It's the great shadow
that looms over this city.
The data that George
obtained was unmistakable proof.
It warned us of the
dangers of the Extended.
We could have used it for good
and crushed the Beruhren
Corporation once and for all!
Such power... In this necklace?
[DANNY]
Will you give it to me?
[ROSA]
But...
This must have been important.
Why would he have entrusted
it with me instead of with you?
After all,
it's obviously crucial
to your whole life's work.
[DANNY] Why, those are
my sentiments exactly.
I, too, wonder why he chose
to bring his beloved
daughter into this fight.
How I'd love to tell
him off right now!
Once again, I have to get
the short of end of the stick
all because of
your selfish father.
[gasps]
[ROSA pants]
[DANNY]
I'm still not quite certain
how that man ever
got a hold of the data.
[DANNY]
He was a coward for sure.
If only he hadn't
rejected my suggestion
of using the knowledge
to our fullest advantage.
He even planned to run away.
To take you and your
mother out of the country.
If we'd handed it over to
Spitzbergen, we could've
rid ourselves of those filthy
Extendeds once and for all.
We'd be lining our pockets
with the bountiful
fruits of our labor.
[DANNY]
You see, in the end,
I had no choice
but to take action.
Anyway, don't take
this personally.
'Cause at the end of the day,
this is all your father's fault.
So it was you.
You murdered them.
The car accident
was my handiwork, yes.
Those robotic arms,
however... not so much.
If anything, they've
protected you ever since.
[DANNY]
Though I have no idea why.
I even had to hire that
meddling Resolver
because of them.
Well,
luckily your hatred for
his kind made things easier.
Though no one would trust
a man with a gun
for a head regardless.
[ROSA]
No. I'm such an idiot!
[DANNY]
Don't worry, dearie.
I know you despise the idea
of survival by extension,
so I'll make sure to
kill you nice and proper.
[ROSA gasps]
What a pain! It must've
hidden in the car!
[DANNY gasps]
Him again?! Ugh!
How'd he find us?!
[JUZO]
Eleven o'clock! That's his car.
[MARY gasps]
Look out! The train!
At this rate we're gonna
be blown to smithereens!
[JUZO]
Hold on tight, Mary!
[ROSA gasps]
[DANNY grunts]
[ROSA gasping]
‐‐[panting]
‐‐[footsteps]
[gasps]
[JUZO]
It's time to snuff out the ghost
that's been haunting
that poor girl.
A parting shot.
Just as requested.
No, wait! [groans]
[JUZO]
All right. Now let's see.
[JUZO] How the hell am
I supposed to get paid?
[JUZO] Is this under the
Security Bureau's jurisdiction?
Well as it currently
stands, yeah.
Though I'm sure the EMS
will take it away from us
once we get to the
investigating part.
In the meantime,
we'll take a good look.
We're talking about the murder
of a prosecutor
and his wife after all.
[MARY]
I did it!
I figured out how
to open the pendant!
This necklace contains a puzzle.
Now watch my fingers.
You just gotta spin it,
give it a twist,
turn, and presto!
It's some kind of
antique memory vessel.
Is this what the
thief was after?
So that's what it was. [gasps]
[JUZO] Really?
This dinky, little thing?
Hmm.
[JUZO] If this old thing is
more valuable than your life,
I bet it would fetch
a good price if I sold it.
[ROSA gasps]
Huh? Just what are you
trying to get at, Juzo?
[JUZO inhales]
All right, listen up people!
I've decided that I'm taking
this data as my reward!
[POLICE groaning]
Hey, keep it quiet, will ya?!
Why the hell did you do that?
That wasn't pleasant
for us regular folk!
[JUZO]
That okay with you, miss?
Help yourself.
I'm pretty sure I
would've gotten murdered
if you hadn't come to rescue me.
Anyway, I said such
vile things to you!
But you helped. Why?
[JUZO] It's simple.
You weren't my client, princess.
What?
[JUZO]
And besides...
...I was kinda curious
about giving exorcisms a try.
Had nothing to do with you.
[MARY] Don't let that face
fool you. He's an old softy.
Here.
Well then, let me know
if you ever plan on
getting an extension‐‐
safe, reliable,
and super badass.
That's my personal promise.
C'mon, Juzo! Wait up a second!
[ROSA] Maybe‐‐ Maybe
that's what was haunting me.
My own negative feelings
against the Extended.
[MARY] I wonder where
that left hand flew off to?
I think we should look for it.
Thanks so much.
[MARY]
Ugh, it's no use!
This thing is so
old and obsolete
that none of my tools can
extract the data properly!
[JUZO]
Well, son of a gun.
I know you took this
off that girl's hands
so she wouldn't
be targeted again.
That's why you announced
it to the entire world.
But if you can't
turn it into cash,
then that means
you played yourself!
How the heck are you gonna
pay for my maintenance fees?!
Did you ever find out anything
about that hands‐only Extended?
Not really. It disappeared
before we knew it.
It's a shame since
it was a rare model.
I'm pretty bummed I didn't get
to take a better look at it.
You know, this
might just be a hunch,
but I have a feeling
that Rosa's father
might've hired
it to protect her.
[JUZO]
It sounds like a long shot.
Either way we'll
never know for sure.
[MARY gasps]
[JUZO]
Thanks for the light, Tetsuro.
Sorry. Come again?
[JUZO]
Huh?
[JUZO yells]