[HIGH OFFICIAL A]
Olivier, we gave you
specific instructions
to eliminate Gondry
and to do so using
extreme secrecy.
You've not only disobeyed us,
but we've heard
disturbing rumors.
It would appear that you've been
taking action behind our backs.
Please understand.
Gondry's an important witness
regarding the Nightmare
of Norse Scott.
As the director of EMS,
I decided it was necessary
to capture him alive.
[HIGH OFFICIAL A]
Hmm. If I remember correctly,
your father was
involved in that incident.
He was one of the
murdered officers
from the military police, yes?
And here I thought the
idea of eliminating his killer
and getting revenge would
have appealed to you.
[OLIVIER] My feelings
don't interfere with my job.
Doesn't matter.
I have already assigned
someone far more capable
to clean up this mess.
And until this incident
is fully resolved,
consider yourself suspended.
That is all.
[OLIVIER grunts]
[OLIVIER]
If you'll excuse me.
Juzo.
Please, take him alive!
[TOKISADA]
Gondry!
What are you doing here?
[TOKISADA grunts]
Where did he go?
[GONDRY snarls]
[GONDRY groans]
[TOKISADA]
Hmm?
[JUZO]
That's a neat trick.
I didn't expect a renegade
Extended to use a decoy.
Seems a little too subtle.
[GONDRY grunting]
[JUZO]
You okay, old man?
[TOKISADA]
Mm‐hm...
[KRONEN]
He got away.
[JUZO]
Looks like that freakshow
has plenty of
tricks in his chamber.
[TOKISADA]
That form‐‐
I believe they were
called Gun Slave Units.
[JUZO]
Huh?
[TOKISADA]
I saw your type during the war.
Why are you here?
[EMS OFFICER A] Word is Director
Olivier has been replaced.
[EMS OFFICER B]
What should we do now?
[EMS OFFICER A]
Well, I mean,
I think all we can do is
wait for our next orders.
Sounds like there's
major drama going on.
Maybe something
happened to Juzo.
[CHRISTINA]
Don't be ridiculous!
Mark my words, he's the one
causing the problems.
You think so?
[MARY sighs]
[TETSURO]
Is that Juzo's brand?
I had planned on giving
it to him in the morning.
[TETSURO]
But...
...aren't those cigarettes
pretty much the only thing
around that can ease the
strain put on his extensions?
[MARY]
Mm. And by my calculations,
he should be running
low on 'em right about now.
[TETSURO]
That doesn't sound good.
In a word, yeah.
Issue is... I don't think
that's the only problem.
These things ward off more than
just the stress on Juzo's body.
It's like's he's desperately
trying to suppress something.
Keeping the past at bay.
But, then again,
this might be a perfect chance
for our favorite smoking
gun to quit cold turkey.
[TETSURO grunts]
You good?
[TETSURO] Hey! You out there!
Open up this door, now!
Have you gone completely insane?
[TETSURO] What's the matter?
Am I not loud enough for you?
[EMS OFFICER B] Prisoners
will refrain from shouting!
[TETSURO] Just big enough
for cigarettes to fit through.
[EMS OFFICER B]
Say what?
Juzo was caught because of me.
I'm going to repay my debt.
[MARY] Hold on.
You're not thinking of...
[TETSURO]
If Juzo needs those cigarettes,
I'll make sure he gets them.
[EMS OFFICER B]
Huh?
[JUZO]
The name is Juzo Inui.
Somebody asked me
to capture Gondry.
That's why I'm here.
[TOKISADA]
I see.
[JUZO]
You probably haven't heard yet,
but I've got some bad news about
your buddies from Tindalos.
Gondry knocked them off.
[TOKISADA]
He what?
[JUZO] And it seems you were
going to be his final target.
[TOKISADA]
All of them.
How terrible.
[JUZO] You served together.
Why is Gondry after you?
[TOKISADA]
There's no shortage of people
who want to tear
down a hero like me.
However, he targeted the
other members of the unit.
Gondry should have no reason
to eliminate comrades
who fought alongside
him during the war.
Still, I suppose the past
doesn't matter to him
now that he's gone berserk.
[JUZO]
Hm?
[TOKISADA]
His extensions were designed
specifically for assassinations.
The iridophore nano crystals
embedded in his
armored sub‐arms,
as well as the dummy face
on the back of his head,
give him the power to
mimic nearly anything.
[TOKISADA]
Combine that tech with his
exceptional close
quarters combat skills‐‐
he's never failed
to take out a target.
But abilities came at a price
and caused immense
stress on his sub‐brain.
The continued extension
treatments he received
eventually ate
away at his nerves.
[JUZO]
As a result,
the Nightmare of
Norse Scott occurred...
...along with
these recent murders.
[TOKISADA]
And here we are.
[KRONEN]
Mimicry, huh?
Well, that kind of
power explains why
full‐bodied Extendeds are
being murdered so easily.
[JUZO]
What happened earlier, Kronen?
Getting slow on the draw
and miss your target?
I know the trigger points
of nearly every
recent model produced.
Speed and accuracy
aren't the issue here.
Irregular models like Gondry
have unique trigger points
which make them more challenging
to subdue than normal.
In special cases like this,
it's standard procedure
to aim for the sub‐brain.
But the history logs
stored within those
can be useful evidence in court.
So I avoid damaging
them if possible.
On top of that,
Gondry is likely using an older
model sub‐brain that's internal,
meaning it's much more difficult
to pinpoint its exact location.
[JUZO]
In other words,
it's gonna be that much more
difficult to capture him alive.
Huh. Here's some more
good news for you.
I have new orders from
the substitute director.
[JUZO]
Substitute? Meaning what?
It seems that Director Olivier
has been relieved of her post,
and all EMS officers
are to remove themselves
from this case at once.
The top brass want Gondry dead
and the whole affair
swept under the rug.
[JUZO]
Yeah, it figures.
Superiors are all the same.
They get it in their heads that
you can make a problem go away
by killing it and
pretending it doesn't exist.
But once you fire a bullet,
it can't be put
back into the chamber.
And it always ends up leaving
some kind of mark behind.
[KRONEN]
Ex‐Director Olivier no longer
has the authority
to protect you.
There's no reason
to involve yourself
in this case any longer.
[JUZO] You just don't
get it, do you, Kronen?
If I don't hear
from Olivier herself,
then the job isn't finished yet.
Until I do, there's
no reason to quit.
[JUZO]
Not to mention,
if I bring Gondry back
alive and talking,
her superiors may have to
reconsider their position.
Especially once the
truth about Norse Scott
is finally made public.
Huh?
This one time,
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear you say that.
We're even now,
which means I don't owe you
for the information you
supplied me about Gondry.
[clattering]
[TOKISADA] Government
officials never change.
Doesn't matter the era‐‐
they value orders more
than their friends.
[JUZO] That'd be the case,
except we aren't friends.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
[JUZO] We both do
pretty much what we want.
[JUZO]
Ain't that right, Kronen?
[TOKISADA] Have no fear,
my distinctive‐headed friend.
Just seeing the magnificence
of a hero like myself
generally discourages
follow‐up attacks. [chuckles]
[JUZO]
If you say so, old man.
Let's hope.
[GONDRY snarls]
[JUZO gasps, groans]
[TOKISADA groans]
[GONDRY] That needle‐thrower
gave me trouble.
But with him out of the picture,
we can continue
where we left off.
What do you say, "hero"?
I think it's time you died!
[GONDRY] After I kill you,
they'll have to reevaluate me
and realize I'm needed again.
[TOKISADA]
Now I see.
As a fellow experimental
subject during the war,
we were constantly
expected to produce results.
Did you think by killing
your comrades‐in‐arms
anything was going to change?
That you'd somehow prove
your continued value?
Is that it?
[JUZO]
I get it.
[GONDRY gasps]
[JUZO] You're proud of
your high‐end extensions.
Only problem is they
take a toll on the body.
My body's pretty
inefficient as well.
[JUZO] And if I wanna keep it
running, I can't stop smoking.
So what do you say
to a test of stamina?
[JUZO]
Let's do this. Me and you.
And we'll see whose
sub‐brain fries first!
[JUZO grunts]
[GONDRY yells]
[TOKISADA]
Juzo has foregone defense
in favor of overwhelming power.
The only thing is... the man has
such a reckless fighting style.
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO gasps]
[GONDRY chuckles]
[groans]
[chuckles, groans]
[groaning]
[JUZO] If you hadn't
fallen into madness,
you might've actually
been worshipped
and treated like a hero.
But they took advantage
of you, and now look at you.
It's pathetic.
[JUZO] I bet it feels like
you're stuck in a nightmare‐‐
one you can never wake up from.
[JUZO] But this isn't a dream
'cause what you did was real,
and the scars have
already been made.
Now, it's time
for me to wake you up
so you can see
the damage you've done!
[GONDRY grunts]
[JUZO] I guess you
aren't a morning person.
[JUZO]
You blocked that just in time.
But it looks like you won't be
playing hide‐and‐seek anymore.
[TOKISADA]
Oh. As he over‐heats,
the location of his
sub‐brain is exposed.
[GONDRY grunts]
[TOKISADA]
You can do it, Mr. Gun Slave!
Go get him! One last push!
[JUZO groans]
[JUZO] I hate to say it,
but I'm counting on you.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
[JUZO] I'm counting on you
to be stubborn enough to do
what needs to be done,
regardless of the orders
your superiors give you.
[GONDRY groaning]
Prisoner Number 0001.
Name, Hayden Gondry.
You're headed back
to your prison cell
to be judged for your crimes.
[JUZO]
Took ya long enough, Kronen.
If I wasn't waiting here, this
prisoner would've escaped.
Show some gratitude.
[JUZO]
What'd you say?
I left you something to do,
since you're always
going on about your duty.
You should be
the one thanking me.
[TOKISADA]
Hmm.
He purposefully put
himself in danger
to ensure that Gondry
was captured alive.
Huh. You should shut up
before you embarrass
yourself any further, Juzo.
[TOKISADA] Even if he fell,
he believed the needle‐thrower
would stop Gondry once
he could locate the sub‐brain.
[JUZO]
You son of a‐‐
Keep talking.
See if I don't throw
you into Wunder Bender.
[JUZO]
Bastard. You wouldn't dare.
[KRONEN]
Oh?
[TOKISADA]
Hmm. These two are a threat.
[PEPPER gasps]
[SEVEN]
What is it, Pepper?
My connection with Gondry
was interrupted quite suddenly.
By someone who
looks just like you.
[SEVEN]
Like me? No way.
[PEPPER]
This Harmony thing‐‐
it really does let
you control Extendeds,
but the mind of its owner
ends up messing with your own.
[PEPPER] And I was this
close to killing Armed, too.
[chuckles] Guess I shouldn't
have played around so much.
Whoever you are, Mr. Gun Head,
this isn't over yet.
[RECON A] Ex‐Director Olivier,
I implore you to hurry.
You really shouldn't
be making any stops.
We've been assigned to
take you home and protect you.
I heard you the first time.
One more thing.
Your job is to watch me,
so drop the white knight act.
[CORONER] I can see
you're rather agitated.
However, would
you mind saving that
until after you
leave the morgue?
I don't have much time.
Speed things up a bit.
All right then, just don't
open that can. I'm begging you.
The stench is so hard to remove.
Well, then, let's hear it.
It's exactly as
I wrote in the report.
Among the three victims,
the one who stands out
as completely different
in the manner of death
is the delivery driver.
While all three suffered
deep lacerations,
after looking at the bodies,
I determined that
was the cause of death
for only two of the victims.
But the driver was killed
in a different manner‐‐
by an impact to the chest
which caused his heart to stop.
What does that mean?
Are you saying that Gondry tried
to hide how the victim died?
It's possible.
Or somebody else
was responsible.
Shame. If only the
sub‐brain were intact,
we'd be able to know more about
the crime, but alas, it's not.
Someone besides Gondry?
But who?
[OLIVIER gasps]
[RECON A]
Ex‐Director, it's time.
If you'd kindly
follow me to the car.
[RECON A groans]
[TETSURO]
I tried imitating Juzo,
successfully, I'd say.
Um, and just who are you?
[TETSURO]
My name is Tetsuro.
Anyway, I need you to lead
me to where Juzo is, now!
[JUZO]
Pitch in, Kronen.
Stop making an injured man
do all the heavy lifting.
It may seem there's
no end to my talents,
but a human can't
carry an Extended.
[JUZO]
Hey, old man!
Think you could help
me out and lend a hand?
[JUZO] What are you doing?
The door won't open itself.
[TOKISADA]
You don't say.
This must be one of those
doors you open manually.
How quaint.
[JUZO sighs]
Whatever.
Be sure not to damage
the prisoner any further.
[JUZO]
Hm.
He's an important
witness, after all.
Finally, we'll know about
the Nightmare of Norse Scott.
Not to mention
he can possibly help
clear the Ex‐Director
and get her reinstated.
[JUZO] Guess Gondry's not
the only mimic around here.
[KRONEN] Then again, could
be a chance he's useless
and you've been carrying
dead weight all this time,
after you went and
trashed his sub‐brain.
[JUZO]
Didn't your parents tell you
not to play around
with guns, Kronen?
[GONDRY yelling]
[KRONEN]
Tranquilizer's worn off!
Hurry up and hold
him down, Inui!
[groans]
[GONDRY]
Where am I? Wait, the war.
It's over?
All gone. My squad.
That's right.
Those guys and me,
we were...
[JUZO]
What's he talking about?
It sounds like he's in
some state of confusion.
We need to hurry and get him
treated at a medical facility.
If he regains sanity,
we may be able to obtain intel.
[TOKISADA]
How unfortunate.
I never thought it
would end this way.
[TOKISADA] But you've
left me with no options.
If the truth about
Norse Scott had come to light,
it would have
slowed the progress
of extension technology.
And this country's
economic boom
after the war
may have never occurred.
Can you imagine that?
[TOKISADA] That is why
I cannot allow Gondry
to tell the truth about what
really happened ten years ago.
[TOKISADA]
And sadly, why the two of you
must perish alongside him!
Why, you bastard!
[KRONEN groans]
[JUZO]
Kronen!
[TOKISADA]
Don't just stand there.
Show me the power
that I gave you!
[JUZO]
Damn it, Armed!
[TOKISADA]
Funke...
[JUZO]
...Faust!
[TOKISADA] Now do you finally
understand, Mr. Gun Slave?
[OLIVIER] So you're the
one who killed my father!
[TETSURO]
You should be embarrassed
to call yourself an adult!
[OLIVIER]
I'm begging you, Juzo!
[JUZO]
NoGunsLife Episode Eight:
"Will."