[TV CASTER]
At the scheduled...
[phone ringing]
[TV CASTER]
...conclusion of the Great War.
On the other hand,
there is concern about
increases in crime,
particularly in the slum
district known as the‐‐
[JUZO]
Yeah. No problem.
I'll head that way now.
‐‐[crash]
‐‐[GOON A groans]
[GOON A]
Who the hell are you?
[GOON B grunting]
Bastard!
[GOONS groaning]
[GOON A]
We'll remember this, Resolver!
[JUZO] Can't say I will.
Don't come here again.
[JUZO] That eyesore blocks the
view no matter where you are.
After the great war,
two things changed
the landscape of the city.
First was the
Beruhren Corporation
which grew from the
military procurement boom.
It casts a long shadow.
Second was the emergence
of people who underwent
physical function extension
thanks to technology
developed by Beruhren.
We got a name for 'em.
Call them the Extended.
‐‐[JUZO] Wouldn't do that.
‐‐[CLIENT A gasps]
[JUZO]
Don't make me hurt a client.
Aww. Not even a squeeze?
The rumor is that trigger
on your head is your weakness.
Is it true?
[JUZO]
Just two things give me trouble:
Humidity and kids.
So?
[JUZO] The only ones
who can touch my trigger
are the ones
I've come to accept.
Thing is... I don't
plan on accepting anyone.
That's what you always say,
but I get the feeling
you're looking for someone
you can trust it with.
[JUZO]
Don't be stupid.
And next time, call before
you get yourself in trouble.
Since the war ended, those
folks don't have anywhere to go.
However, I can't
turn a blind eye
when they start
dealing drugs in my bar.
Juzo!
[JUZO]
Hm?
Here's your payment.
Also, how about
a drink for the road?
On the house, of course.
[JUZO] Booze and dames
will make a man go mad.
[JUZO]
This is all I need.
Use the money and
get yourself looked at.
[CLIENT A]
One last thing...
[JUZO]
Hm?
[CLIENT A]
Mwah!
[JUZO gasps]
[CLIENT A]
Don't get any ideas.
That was just a "thanks."
[JUZO gasping]
[JUZO]
Damn it.
Like I'd get the wrong idea.
[STREET VENDOR A]
Hey, Resolver!
I got some good parts in.
Look! Top of the line!
[JUZO] I see you're still
laundering for the Kyusei Group.
What's it matter?
This is still top of the line!
[JUZO]
My name's Juzo Inui.
I make a living resolving
problems involving the Extended.
That being said,
my services vary.
I take care of everything
from babysitting runaways
to negotiating peace
between rival gangs.
[ONLOOKER A]
I heard that a renegade Extended
kidnapped some
kid and booked it.
Another Extended?
Not only that, they're
saying that the person
who tried intervening ended up
getting shot through the head.
Oh, how terrible.
Even though the war's over with,
can't say this is much better.
[JUZO]
Amen to that.
‐‐[ONLOOKERS gasp]
‐‐His... His head.
It's a gun!
[ONLOOKER A]
Don't worry.
[ONLOOKER B]
That's the Resolver, Juzo.
‐‐[ONLOOKER C] Wait, that's him?
‐‐[BABY crying]
Yes, ma'am.
[ONLOOKER C] It's all right.
Now, now. Be good.
[JUZO] What's a nun
doing at a crime scene?
[CHRISTINA]
Is that you, Juzo?
You're just now getting back?
[JUZO]
Christina.
I was certain that gun on
your head finally went off.
As your landlady, I've gotta
ask about those loud noises
I heard coming from
inside your office.
[JUZO]
Noises?
[JUZO] Would you
take a look at this mess?
I can barely pay
the rent as it is.
[JUZO]
If you've got business with me,
start over by the ringing
the doorbell first.
[EXTENDED A]
You're... Inui?
[JUZO]
That's right. What of it?
[EXTENDED A gasps]
Your face is a‐‐!
[JUZO]
It hurts when someone
looking like you
reacts that way.
Huh?
The fuss outside‐‐
are you the culprit?
[EXTENDED A] No! I wasn't
responsible for that!
[JUZO]
Tell it to the Security Bureau.
[EXTENDED A]
Wait. You can't! Please!
I'm not a tool!
[JUZO]
Hm?
What's that?
[EXTENDED A] I can't be
caught by those people again!
‐‐[knocking]
‐‐[SECURITY A] Security Bureau!
[SECURITY HEAD A]
Open up!
We know you got a
renegade Extend inside!
[JUZO] They're fast.
I didn't call for 'em yet.
[SECURITY HEAD A] Open this
door or we'll break it down!
[EXTENDED A]
Wait, you can't!
[SECURITY HEAD A grunts]
He oughta be around here
somewhere, so find him.
Right.
What do ya think you're‐‐
[SECURITY HEAD A gasps]
[JUZO] As you can see,
I'm in the middle of renovating.
My place is in no
condition for guests.
But we can talk right here.
The deal is we're chasing
after a renegade Extend
that abducted a kid
from a nearby orphanage.
People have died.
If you're hiding him in there,
you'll be charged
as an accomplice.
[JUZO]
Sadly...
[JUZO] ...I haven't
received anyone like that.
Say, pal, you're
an Over‐Extended.
That certainly changes things.
Seeing as you
got a license from
the Reconstruction
Administration...
...it'd be a shame if you
interfered with our
investigation and lost it.
You wouldn't want
that to happen‐‐
be considered
a violator of Extend Law.
Ya follow?
Now that we understand
each other, step a‐‐
[JUZO]
One problem.
[JUZO] Violating the
Extend Law is a serious crime.
I could be arrested
and taken apart.
In which case, I guess
it won't matter if
I break a few more
laws before that happens.
Well?
What do ya think?
[SECURITY HEAD A grumbles]
But, sir...
Let's search someplace else.
So you know, Beruhren has
an interest in this matter.
With them involved,
I wonder how much longer
you'll be able to cop
that attitude, gun head.
[SECURITY HEAD A]
Snubbed. Shit!
[EXTENDED A]
Mr. Inui?
[JUZO]
We'll talk later.
[JUZO] The Security
Bureau is watching us.
And not hiding it.
[EXTENDED A]
They're all chasing after me?
[JUZO] We gotta find a way
to handle this situation first.
[EXTENDED A]
Why didn't you hand me over
to them when you had the chance?
[JUZO] The Security Bureau's
attitude burns my muzzle,
and long ago, someone
told me a story like yours.
[JUZO]
There's nothing more to say.
[EXTENDED A]
I'll keep them distracted.
[JUZO]
Hm?
[EXTENDED A] Please, he needs
to be taken somewhere safe.
I'm asking you to protect
the kid from those people.
When this is over,
I promise to pay you, so...
...Juzo Inui, I'm hiring you.
[JUZO]
All right. I'll take the job.
Besides, you already owe me
for breaking the window.
[EXTENDED A]
Thank you.
[SECURITY C]
I see him!
[SECURITY D]
Over there!
[SECURITY E]
After him!
[JUZO]
Mary.
I need to hide
someone for a while.
Let me use the usual place.
[JUZO]
Yeah, I know.
Well, then... let's go.
[footsteps]
[JUZO]
Hm?
O Lord, you are merciful.
You must be the one
responsible for saving this boy.
His name is Tetsuro.
The poor child
was under the care
of the orphanage the
other sisters and I operate.
[JUZO]
Well, that's good to hear.
Guess I've got nothin'
to worry about, then.
I am sure it was God's will
that led us to meet tonight.
Now, if you'll hand him over.
[JUZO]
Huh...
Just one thing.
You must've been
worried about this kid
in order to come to
a place like this alone.
[KAREN gasps]
It was worth it.
I consider the boy
to be like a son to me.
[JUZO] How honorable...
that's what I'd like to say.
But there's a renegade
Extend out there
that's been killing people.
Kinda reckless, don't ya think?
Coming out here by yourself.
[JUZO] Then again,
I guess it depends on whether
the renegade Extend really was
the one that abducted this kid.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
[JUZO]
That guy out there‐‐
he didn't kill anyone,
and you know it.
[KAREN gasps]
I swear by the Holy Father‐‐
[JUZO]
As for you, sister,
seems your God's a pretty
harsh disciplinarian,
especially when
it comes to kids.
Look at these legs.
The tendons have been cut
so he can't run away.
But even stranger,
you say you're a nun, but the
entire time we've been speaking,
you haven't looked away
once, despite how I look.
So... who are you really?
[sighs]
[KAREN] It's sad to hear you
talk about yourself like that.
[JUZO gasps]
I bet that intuition of yours
lands you in trouble often.
[JUZO]
Uhh...
[KAREN]
I mean, after all...
[JUZO gasps]
[KAREN]
I wouldn't be forced to kill you
if only you had handed
the kid over quietly.
[JUZO]
That emblem.
You're with Beruhren.
[JUZO] Aren't you trying
to take him back alive?
I will, as long as you don't
make any stupid moves.
And worst case scenario, I only
need him from the neck up.
[JUZO grunts]
[KAREN gasps]
[JUZO]
You've got skills.
I take it you
extended your eyesight.
And judging by your bloodlust,
the victim everyone
was fussing over
must've been caught
in your crossfire.
[KAREN] I've heard plenty
of stories about you.
Like how you're a product of
the Big Ships, Big Guns
Doctrine from the war.
The Over‐Extended that
served in the Gun Slave Unit.
I don't know how someone
like you got involved in this.
But trust me, what
you've stumbled into
is way beyond
a relic like you are.
If you wanna prove me wrong,
please, go ahead and fire
that magnificent gun of yours.
Wait. You can't.
Right. Without someone there
to pull the trigger for you,
you're absolutely nothing.
Just a useless tool.
Sorry, that was uncalled for.
As an apology, I'll make
your death quick and painless.
Oh? Are you all finished
playing hide‐and‐seek?
[JUZO]
Say that one more time.
[gasps]
[JUZO] Maybe I didn't
make myself clear.
I said tell me what I am!
Nothing more than
a relic of the past!
You think you stand a chance
against an agent of
the Beruhren Corp?
[EXTENDED A grunts]
[KAREN gasps]
[KAREN groans]
[JUZO]
What're you doin' here?
[EXTENDED A]
Juzo Inui, now's your chance!
Run!
[EXTENDED A]
Where are you aiming?
[EXTENDED A yelps]
My sub‐brain!
[JUZO]
She shot for the ricochet.
[KAREN panting]
You belong to us!
Your body is our property!
And in case you forgot,
here's the thing about
company property‐‐
it isn't allowed
to have free will!
[JUZO]
Don't shoot!
[EXTENDED A gasps]
[KAREN] Why are you going
out of your way to help him?
It's not like this mess
has anything to do
with you, Resolver.
[JUZO] I always finish
the job and protect my clients.
Especially when
I haven't been paid yet.
You're a funny guy,
but the joke's on you.
Both of you will
end up dying in the fall.
[JUZO] That'd prove
inconvenient for you as well,
I imagine.
Like I said, it doesn't
matter if he's alive or dead.
As long as we follow
the sewer system,
it shouldn't be difficult for us
to locate him and
recover his body.
[JUZO] I have no idea
what you need this kid for,
but like I said earlier,
I never leave a job unfinished.
[JUZO] He's yours for now,
but I'll be back for him.
Count on it.
[KAREN giggles] I look
forward to seeing you try.
[splash]
Now then...
...time for us
to go back home...
...Master Tetsuro.
[EXTENDED A]
Juzo Inui.
Wake up.
Juzo!
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO coughs]
[JUZO yelling]
What the hell?
I gotta dry myself off!
I'm gonna rust, I'm gonna rust!
[EXTENDED A gasps]
[EXTENDED A]
Your head, it's spinning!
[BOTH scream]
[JUZO]
Huh?
Your body... You took
that hit to protect me.
[EXTENDED A]
Don't worry about that.
This form didn't have
much time left anyway.
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO] Maybe you oughta
tell me what's goin' on.
Let's start with that crazy nun
and why she was after
this Tetsuro kid.
Also, given the way you
look, you oughta be dead,
but you're not.
[EXTENDED A] I was a prisoner
being held at a secret facility.
That nun is one
of the employees there.
[EXTENDED A] She's not
a real sister, of course.
They disguised their
headquarters as an orphanage,
but they were really
gathering orphans
to send over to Beruhren Corp
to be used as test subjects for
their extension experiments.
[EXTENDED A]
I'm one of their guinea pigs.
They installed
something in my body‐‐
Harmony, a device that can
control Extended remotely.
[JUZO] Hold on a sec! The
remote control of an Extended?
[EXTENDED A]
That's right.
The ability allows me
to operate a body
like this by force even when
I'm nowhere close to it.
[EXTENDED A] You're looking
at proof my story's true.
I took over this unoccupied
Extended body
with Harmony and used
it to escape the lab.
[EXTENDED A]
In other words,
the person you're
speaking with right now
is me, Tetsuro.
[JUZO] If that's legit,
this goes way beyond
just violating the Extend Law.
[TETSURO] Right. That's
why they were so frantic
to recover me before
I was discovered.
[TETSURO]
My existence could bring
the downfall of the
Beruhren Corporation.
[JUZO]
On any other day
I'd tell you there's no way
I'd buy a crazy story like that.
But after looking
at that shell of a head,
I've got no choice
but to believe.
Your body‐‐where is it?
[TETSURO] I feel vibrations,
like I've been
placed on a vehicle
of some sort.
I'm sorry I'm not more help, but
whenever Harmony is activated
most of my senses are cut off.
[TETSURO]
It doesn't matter.
I don't think this false
body can take the strain
of Harmony for much longer.
Looks like this is it.
I'll be their tool again.
[TETSURO]
I should've known.
It's impossible to
escape from Beruhren.
[TETSURO] In order
to focus Harmony's ability
and control an Extended body,
you have to have a strong desire
to move your own body parts.
[TETSURO]
To make me feel that way,
they took away my vocal cords,
and cut the tendons
in my arms and legs.
Even so, I still
managed to escape.
[TESTURO] I tried convincing the
people in the Security Bureau,
but they didn't
believe a word I said.
I just wanted freedom‐‐
to experience the feeling of
being able to walk around again.
Juzo Inui, you were the only
one who listened to my story.
[TETSURO] It's too bad
things had to end this way.
But you should know...
I'm glad to have met you.
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO]
Damn it.
This is why I hate
humidity and kids.
[OPERATOR A]
Medication administered.
[OPERATOR B]
The subject's consciousness
and physical activity
have dropped.
[OPERATOR C] Sister Karen,
we have locked down
the activation of Harmony.
We'll begin the
transfer of Harmony
as soon as we arrive
at the facility.
Make sure the
preparations are complete
for an immediate procedure.
[JUZO]
Funke...
...Faust!
[JUZO]
I'm back for the kid I lent you.
[KAREN]
I can't believe you really came.
[MARY]
Don't tell me...
[CUNNINGHAM]
I continue to destroy
the things you
treasure one by one.
[MARY]
I told you, don't say my name!
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Two:
"Extended
Remote‐Control Device."