[OLIVIER'S DAD]
Congratulations.
You're at the top of the
academy's incoming class.
I'll get you whatever you
want to celebrate the occasion
as soon as I come back
home, okay, Olivier?
Will you finally quit the force
like I've been asking you to?
What made you decide to enlist
with the military police
of all things anyway?
Isn't work already hard enough
without constantly making
enemies while you're on the job?
Come on, Olivier. Stop worrying.
You really are
just like your mom.
[OLIVIER'S DAD]
I'm heading to Norse Scott.
Just for some on‐site inspection
of augmentation technology.
We're following up on a report
that they've been
abusing the prisoners there.
Several officers were
sent out on reconnaissance,
but we haven't
heard from them since.
[gasps]
Well, someone has to take
care of business, don't they?
That's how it is.
You understand.
Then I have no choice
but to climb up the ranks
till I reach the top.
And then fire you
as soon as I can.
[chuckles]
But until I do, make sure
you stay in one piece.
Gotcha, Princess. I promise.
You know, Norse Scott is famous
for their tinned delicacies.
How 'bout I bring some home?
They're canned?
Yeah, and amazing, too.
You have no idea.
Just you wait and see, Olivier.
Hey, kid. It's Tetsuro, right?
Why don't you go ahead and
put that thing down already?
[OLIVIER] One of my
former subordinates called in.
They made contact with Gondry
at the End of War Memorial Park.
Juzo should be in that area.
He's totally screwed unless
we get his cigarettes to him.
And believe me, if he goes down,
it's gonna be
a problem for me, too.
[OLIVIER gasps]
[TETSURO groans]
[TETSURO]
That explosion.
‐‐[TETSURO] It's him!
‐‐[doors closing]
[JUZO]
You're sure about this?
It's what you really want?
[TOKISADA] You wield such
power despite your injuries.
I'm impressed.
Not bad,
my hammer‐headed friend.
[JUZO groans]
[TOKISADA]
Hmm, what's this?
Hand‐rolled. How rare.
Unlike your beloved
Tanegashima brand,
this is made with
high quality materials.
Considering the
extraordinary amount
of cigarettes
you've burned through,
I'm quite certain your
nerves must be completely shot.
What's more, too many
firefights have left you spent.
You're merely spinning
an empty cylinder.
[JUZO] That's enough,
you slick son of a gun.
What's the game
you're playing at here?
[TOKISADA] Let me help
you gauge the situation.
This is the truth I've
been fighting to protect.
[TOKISADA]
During the Great War,
the members of Tindalos proudly
sacrificed their own bodies
in the name of
scientific progress.
To protect our
families, our homeland,
we led this country to victory.
And yet...
[TOKISADA]
In the end,
we sacrificed our dignity
to the war as well.
[TOKISADA]
For their sake,
I must go on as
a symbol of their heroism.
[TOKISADA chuckles]
[JUZO]
Uh?
[TOKISADA] That is my cause,
my duty, my cornerstone!
[JUZO]
I'm still drawing a blank here.
[TOKISADA]
Are you, now?
[JUZO groans]
[TOKISADA]
Listen closely.
Professor Wachowski was the
father of extension technology.
Using research from
experiments on Tindalos,
he worked closely
with Beruhren Corp.
They created your war‐type
model, the Gun Slave Unit.
Unfortunately,
their enormous power came
at the cost of their minds.
And thus,
all existing models were
decommissioned before
the end of the war.
To think I would ever come face
to... barrel with one like this.
[JUZO choking]
[TOKISADA] All your
actions were far too reckless
to be considered
strategically sound.
It was almost as if you were
trying to prove your worth.
[TOKISADA] In this country,
there are countless
disenfranchised
soldiers like you
who've been unable
to fit into society
after returning
home from the war.
How about it, my wayward friend?
Why not work with me?
Together we can make this world
a better place for the Extended!
[JUZO groans]
[TOKISADA gasps]
[JUZO] Hey. That sounds
like a noble idea,
but you mind gettin'
me some more smokes?
That was my last one.
[TOKISADA]
How unfortunate.
‐‐[JUZO groans]
‐‐[TOKISADA grunts]
[TOKISADA]
And there goes your last breath.
Rest your weary soul,
for I shall bear it
and carry you with me.
[TOKISADA] I won't ask
for your forgiveness, Gondry.
Once more, it seems
you must sacrifice
yourself to the greater good.
[TOKISADA] I'll be merciful.
You won't feel a thing.
[gunshot]
[TOKISADA]
How pitiful.
To unleash the power to
change the outcome of battle,
Gun Slave Units need to
be partnered with marksmen,
also known as Hands.
If only we'd been able
to come to an agreement.
Never mind. Such thoughts
are pointless now.
[VOICE A]
Surrender.
Entrust yourself completely.
Relinquish your muzzle.
Submit your trigger.
From now on, your blood and
your flesh are a living weapon.
You will destroy all enemies
and anyone else who would
endanger our country!
Feel it. Seize it.
Be proud!
This is the exhilaration
of protecting your homeland.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
[ELECTRIC VOICE A] Cephalic
reconstruction complete.
Confirming battle conditions.
[footsteps]
[TOKISADA]
You... stood back up?
[JUZO groaning]
[JUZO yelling]
[TETSURO]
Juzo?
[ELECTRIC VOICE A]
Deploying skeletal compression,
configuration zero.
[TOKISADA]
I see. This must be it‐‐
his true form.
[ELECTRIC VOICE A]
Authorization required.
Requesting permission
to engage combat program.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
[ELECTRIC VOICE A]
Repeating.
Requesting permission
to engage combat program.
[TOKISADA laughing]
[TOKISADA] It doesn't matter
how powerful a weapon is
if the proper hand
isn't wielding it.
In the end,
you're nothing but a tool.
[TOKISADA]
How pathetic, you pile of scrap!
[TOKISADA grunts, yells]
[ELECTRIC VOICE A]
Attack confirmed.
Interception complete.
Restricted combat
mode initiated.
Eliminating target.
[TOKISADA groans]
[TOKISADA groaning]
[yells]
[TOKISADA laughs]
Don't you see?
I'm a walking arsenal!
They don't call me Tokisada
Mega Armed for nothing!
[TOKISADA]
Funke Faust!
[TOKISADA groans]
[TOKISADA]
I see.
This is the madness
of a Gun Slave Unit.
[TOKISADA]
Still,
I refuse to be
defeated in this gutter!
[yells]
[TOKISADA]
How did it come to this?
After taking such calculated
pains to push Gondry
right over the edge of reason...
After eliminating
those meddling officers
who came to inspect
the research facility...
To protect the dignity
of all Extended...
No.
The nobility of a hero such as
myself shall never be sullied!
[TOKISADA]
I must remedy this.
I have to silence Gondry
before he regains his sanity.
[OLIVIER]
Sounds suspicious.
[TOKISADA]
Oh?
[OLIVIER]
And memorable.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
So go on then.
You'd better tell me
every last detail.
[TOKISADA]
Oh, it's you.
You're the acting
director of the EMS.
That means the needle‐thrower
and the gun head
must be your lackeys.
You've caused me a lot
of needless headaches.
Ten years ago, Gondry went
berserk at Norse Scott
during a routine
facilities inspection there.
He murdered 16 officers
of the military police.
My father was included among
the casualties on that day.
It was the Nightmare
of Norse Scott.
At least, that's what
we were led to believe.
Yet you said they
were all eliminated.
Interesting word choice.
What did you mean by that?
[TOKISADA] Every part of
the research that we conducted
was done for the future of
the Extended in this country‐‐
to give hope.
Despite our efforts,
our virtuous mission
was misunderstood.
I simply did what I had to do!
Right.
I see. So then you were
the one who murdered my father!
[TOKISADA]
Causing headaches yet again.
A hero like me should never
have to raise his fist
against a helpless woman,
but you've left me no choice!
‐‐[TOKISADA] Hm?
‐‐[TETSURO] Stop! Listen to me.
[TETSURO] Can you please
calm down already?
Hey! There's no need
to lose your cool
just because you
ran out of cigarettes!
[gasps] Juzo?
[TETSURO] This is embarrassing!
Aren't you an adult?!
[OLIVIER]
That form...
He's gone berserk after
running out of his medication.
[JUZO snarling]
[TOKISADA gasps]
[TOKISADA groans]
[JUZO yells]
[TETSURO]
I said stop it!
[TETSURO groans]
[OLIVIER gasps]
[TOKISADA]
I won't‐‐
[TOKISADA groaning]
I won't give up.
No matter the price,
honor must prevail!
I have faith in my cause.
I will never allow
it to be shaken!
[OLIVIER]
Make sure you stay in one piece.
[OLIVIER'S DAD]
Gotcha, Princess. I promise.
Ya know,
Norse Scott is famous
for their tinned delicacies.
How 'bout I bring some home?
[OLIVIER]
Please...
...finish him.
[OLIVIER]
I'm begging you.
Do it!
[ELECTRIC VOICE A]
Funke Faust.
[TOKISADA]
N‐No‐‐
[crash]
But why?
[JUZO]
His death...
...is that what you really want?
[gasps]
We've also been given a
once in a lifetime opportunity!
After he's caught,
we can drag Gondry to court!
Promise, Juzo! You'll bring
that monster back alive!
He promised.
That's right!
[TOKISADA grunts]
[TOKISADA] Finally, your
sub‐brain is completely fried!
Just as I thought, this is
a sign that the people need me.
No.
That the world needs me!
Juzo!
[TOKISADA]
Could you even imagine?
What if the public
had found out the truth?
The entire country would
fall into utter chaos!
The bridge I worked
so hard to build between
Extendeds and the anti‐Extendeds
would crumble completely.
Distrust would increase
among the people.
The discord sown would plunge us
into deeper segregation
and economic disparity.
In other words,
without me, progress would
simply cease to exist!
Really?
[TOKISADA grunts]
[OLIVIER]
My father was the kind of fool
who gave up his own
happiness without a thought.
He'd do anything to
fight for a worthy cause.
After all,
he was a strong man who wished
for the peace of his homeland.
You'll never come close to him.
You talk a big game
and flash your laurels,
but the only thing you
care about is your ego.
You're nothing more
than a petty criminal.
You're just all
smoke and no fire.
[TOKISADA]
Am I now?
Well, then, you'd better
hurry up and put me out.
Hm?
[OLIVIER] Justice must
be gained under the law.
To think I was
about to lose sight
of what my old man taught me.
But thanks to you,
I was able to keep my eyes
on what truly matters.
Come on, are you about to
let your client die on you...
...Juzo?
[TOKISADA grunts]
[TOKISADA gasps]
[JUZO]
My bad, I dozed off.
All that preaching was so boring
I thought I'd cool
my barrel for a sec.
[TOKISADA yells]
[TOKISADA groans]
[JUZO] Funny thing
about loose cannons‐‐
the louder they go off, the more
secrets they have to hide.
[TOKISADA groans]
[TETSURO]
Juzo! Oh, good, you're back!
[OLIVIER coughing]
[JUZO]
You okay there?
I just inhaled some of
the smoke when I revived you.
I'll be all right.
[JUZO]
Revived? Like with your mouth?
[EMS OFFICER A]
Freeze!
You're under arrest!
Tetsuro, take Juzo and
get out of here. Got it?
[TETSURO]
Right!
[JUZO]
You're Tetsuro?
You did good. Nice work.
All right then, boys.
I'll take it from here.
[EMS OFFICERS gasping]
[EMS OFFICER B]
Odor detected!
‐‐[JUZO] Olivier!
‐‐[EMS OFFICER C] It's gas!
[EMS OFFICER C]
Everyone retreat!
[EMS OFFICERS coughing]
[JUZO]
Damn, kid.
Didn't I tell you
to stop using Harmony?
[TETSURO]
That's not what you said.
[JUZO]
Huh?
[TETSURO]
As I remember,
you told me never to use it
on you and not for nothing.
But this happened
because you had all of us
locked up back there.
I get it, you were worried.
But you gotta learn to trust
Mary and the others a bit more.
[JUZO]
Huh.
You're as obnoxious as
ever now, aren't ya, kid?
[TOKISADA] After eliminating
those meddling officers
who came to inspect
the research facility...
To protect the dignity
of all Extended...
No. The nobility of‐‐
I've already
sent this recording
to one of my connections
in the Department of Justice.
You're gonna be living inside
of courtrooms for a while now.
I'm sure it'll be
quite the scandal.
[TOKISADA]
You really don't get it, do you?
There's nothing that
the Department of Justice
can do about any of this,
let alone your hopeless EMS.
What do you mean?
[TOKISADA]
Stop and think for a moment.
Who do you think set me up
to be a hero in the first place?
Of course, it's
exactly what I thought.
You're merely their‐‐
[SEVEN]
Direct hit on target.
Mission complete, Pepper.
[PEPPER]
I would still prefer to avoid
using your power as
a Gun Slave though, Seven.
Ya know, I always
get a runny nose
whenever I smell
the smoke from your muzzle.
Oh, well.
A hero becomes complete
through death, or so they say.
Congratulations.
Well done,
you little Beruhren puppet.
[CUNNINGHAM] Everything has gone
exactly as you have requested.
[PEPPER] What are you
squealing about, you little pig?
[JUZO]
And Olivier? How is she?
[MATILDA, IMELDA] We are
grateful to our Honorable COO.
[HONEST] At the very least,
we should pay our respects.
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Nine:
"Reverberation."