[OLIVIER]
Yuckie!
[JUZO]
Whoa! That reeks!
What the hell are
you doin', Olivier?
I thought it would be obvious.
My Resolver and subordinates
don't listen to me.
And my superiors are engaged in
shady dealings behind my back.
So I'm releasing the stress
of being sandwiched
between all the drama.
Eee‐yuck!
[JUZO]
How's Mary and the others?
[OLIVIER]
Safe, like I promised.
They're in our custody.
[JUZO]
That helps me out a lot.
[OLIVIER]
Is that so?
Huh?
[OLIVIER] One of your
friends is very interesting.
The young boy without any ID.
Seems he has scars from
an illegal extension operation.
In a weird coincidence,
I heard Beruhren is
searching for an Extended
that recently escaped
from one of their facilities.
Remember one thing, Juzo.
You better adopt the right
attitude, 'cause if you don't,
I'll send you and
your precious client
to Wunder Bender
without a second thought.
This is a warning‐‐
don't take the promise
between us lightly ever again.
I'm telling you
for both our sakes.
[JUZO]
You're one dangerous dame.
No need to worry.
I keep my promises.
[JUZO] Besides,
I can't take you opening
any more of those
cans to burn off steam.
[OLIVIER] Heh! No one
asked, you smoking gun.
[JUZO]
Here we go.
So this is the final escapee
that needs capturing.
[OLIVIER]
Prisoner 0001.
His name's Hayden Gondry.
[OLIVIER]
And he's ex‐military.
Fifteen years ago,
Gondry was assigned to the
western region of Norse Scott
and underwent one of the
first extension procedures.
However,
we lost most of the
records pertaining
to the operation
during the Great War.
[JUZO]
You don't say.
There's no way of knowing
what his role in the war was.
Sadly, the only data
we were able to find
just mentioned the
Nightmare of Norse Scott.
[JUZO]
I've heard stories about it.
[OLIVIER]
Ten years ago,
Gondry went berserk
for reasons unknown.
Murdered the
soldiers in his unit.
All together,
there were 16 causalities.
The military police, before they
were called EMS, captured him.
He was held at Wunder Bender
until the day he escaped.
[OLIVIER]
The family of the victims
never received answers
about what really happened.
Nor was he put on
trial for his crimes.
Since his escape,
we have reason to suspect
that Gondry has been responsible
for three separate homicides:
These unlucky corpses.
First was a delivery driver.
Second was an
unidentified vagrant.
Last one's a big shot with
the Reconstruction Agency.
There's nothing in any of their
backgrounds connecting them.
Even the murders and
locations seem random.
The only commonality
the victims share
is that they have
full‐body extensions.
On top of that,
their sub‐brains were removed
at the scene of the crime.
[JUZO] So no one would be able
to recover their history logs.
Right. Which means we
can't even confirm
an exact time of death for them.
[JUZO]
Then what makes you think
this was Gondry's
handiwork in the first place?
[OLIVIER] This sequence
is carved into each
of the dead bodies.
The code stands for
East, Ward Three, 0001.
It's Gondry's prison number.
We believe there's
a high probability
the delivery driver
was an accomplice
that aided with the escape.
We're looking into whether or
not Spitzbergen was involved,
but no leads have turned up yet.
[JUZO]
There's that name again.
Why would an anti‐extension
group even throw in with Gondry?
[OLIVIER]
The Nightmare of Norse Scott
was the first renegade
Extended case on record.
At the time, pro‐extensionist
groups insisted Gondry's actions
had nothing to do with
the augmentations to his body.
Meanwhile, those with
anti‐extensionist views
were convinced the
technology was to blame.
If the reason for his actions
was definitively linked
to the extension
procedure he went through,
it would've never become
as popular as it is today.
That's the only reason
his existence matters.
He's symbolic enough
for Spitzbergen to target.
[JUZO]
So, in the end, which was it?
We still don't know.
By the time the smoke cleared,
Gondry was sentenced to Wunder
Bender for the rest of his life.
In other words, those in power
tried burying the problem.
Because he was locked away,
no one could get
to him, not even EMS.
I'll shoot it to you straight.
Our number one
priority is to stop him
before he can
kill anymore, but...
We've also been given a once
in a lifetime opportunity!
After he's caught,
we can drag Gondry to court!
Promise, Juzo!
You'll bring that
monster back alive!
[JUZO]
I see how it is.
What?
[JUZO]
Let me ask you one thing.
You're sure about this?
It's what you really want?
Of course it is.
As director of EMS,
I'm giving you an order.
[JUZO]
Fine then.
The bullet's loaded
in the chamber.
Leave the rest to me, Director.
We'll talk soon.
[OLIVIER'S DAD]
Listen, Olivier.
It's one thing to
lead other people,
but you should
never use that power
to satisfy your own motives.
When it becomes personal,
there is no justice.
My actions must always be
guided by one thing alone‐‐
following the law.
[JUZO]
You're sure about this?
It's what you really want?
I've got a ways
to go, Dad, don't I?
[beeping]
[SUBORDINATE A]
Director, you've been asked
to attend the hearing.
Orders from the top.
I'm on my way.
[JUZO] Do me a favor
and hang out here a minute.
[DRIVER A]
Huh? Uh, but I was told to‐‐
[JUZO] Look. I'll pay
you for your trouble.
Just sit tight, okay?
[JUZO] So this was
the third victim's home.
I don't blame him
for living here. Uh, ah!
‐‐[DRIVER A] Someone help me!
‐‐[JUZO] Hey! Wait!
[DRIVER A]
He had a gun to my face!
[JUZO sighs]
[JUZO]
Guess I'm walking back.
[JUZO] Victim's name
was Phillip le Carré.
The owner of this gilded armory.
An accomplished war vet,
which earned him a top spot
at the Reconstruction Agency.
To prepare for his speech,
which he was set to deliver
during the public unveiling
of the Mega Armed Statue,
he holed himself up
in his second house.
[JUZO]
Huh?
His second home?
[JUZO] Looks like that
fancy position of his
reaped a lot of benefits.
[JUZO]
Wasn't much of a fight.
Victim was an Extended
with full‐body extensions.
Yet he was taken down
in the first round.
Hard to get my head around
just how easily he was defeated.
If only I could
uncover some motive.
[JUZO]
Hm?
These guys...
Where have I‐‐
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO] You shouldn't
sneak up on people like that.
I thought Gondry came back, but
instead it's just you, Kronen!
I could say the same, Juzo.
What are you doing here?
Did the director
put you up to this?
She has you wrapped
around her finger.
[JUZO]
The way I remember it,
you're not supposed go
digging around this case.
Orders from the top.
No one stops me
from upholding the law.
Take my advice‐‐
you're the one who really ought
to be leaving this case alone.
Whatever's going on,
an Over‐Extended like yourself
doesn't want to get
caught up in it.
[JUZO] You know, I'd love
to heed your suggestion,
but once I take on a case,
I don't stop till it's resolved.
[KRONEN] Filling the void
left by the war, I see.
Desperate to do the bidding of
others and solve their problems.
[JUZO] No reason to
make it sound heavy.
What about you?
Aren't you holding on to
that sense of duty yourself?
[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO groans]
[JUZO]
What's wrong?
Is that your best shot?
[KRONEN]
You realized it was impossible
to evade all the needles,
so you moved in a way
to ensure they landed
a few millimeters
from the trigger points.
Meaning none of them
had any effect on you.
Stop pretending you're
frozen in place and move.
[JUZO sighs]
If you insist.
[JUZO] Thought about
knocking you unconscious
after you let your guard down.
Decided against it last minute.
Didn't want to
accidentally kill you.
Even so, I've got to
admire how you kept up,
despite being extension‐free.
[JUZO]
How unlike you.
[JUZO] Already given
up trying to stop me?
I'm out of needles.
And without them,
I've no way of stopping
an Over‐Extended
like yourself right now.
But don't forget‐‐
I've always got an
eye on you law‐breakers.
And the second you dip
your hands into crime...
...I swear I'll hunt you down
even if it costs me my life.
[JUZO] Got a real fire in
your soul when it comes to work.
[JUZO]
Guess you'll do.
I need you to drive me
to Gondry's next target.
You got a car, right?
You know where he'll strike?
How?
[JUZO]
It just came to me
after looking at
the people in this photo.
They served together in the war.
That's the connection
between the victims.
They were extension subjects‐‐
soldiers that belonged to
the first generation unit.
Went by the name Tindalos.
And out of all of 'em,
three have already
been bumped off.
Which leaves only two.
One is the prisoner,
Hayden Gondry.
As for the other one...
[CROWD]
Army! Army! Army...
[JUZO] ...he was the first man
to become a full‐body Extended.
[JUZO]
A certain Mega Armed.
Full name, Tokisada Mega Armed.
Offered himself up for the sake
of advancing extension tech.
A real war hero.
These days, he's living
high off the hog,
making a living selling
food for the Extended.
[JUZO] Never has to worry about
running out of smokes, I bet.
Lucky son of a gun.
[KRONEN] It's a car, not
a piece of furniture. Get off.
[JUZO]
Took you long enough.
It turns out our guy's not home.
Made a trip over to
End of War Commemoration Park
to examine the Armed Statue
before its grand unveiling.
[JUZO] Guess our hero's
got a busy schedule.
[JUZO] This thing looks
bigger on the outside.
Feel like a sardine in here.
[JUZO]
Damn it!
Not an ashtray either.
Now listen, this car is vintage,
from before the Great War,
and there's no other
model on the road
in as pristine a condition.
Extended are so ready
to replace parts,
they have no appreciation
for a work of art such as this.
You're in a masterpiece
of engineering.
Go ahead and try
hurting my baby.
You'll get ejected faster
than a spent shell casing.
[JUZO groans]
[KRONEN] I looked into it, but
couldn't find records of Gondry
and any of the victims
belonging to the same unit.
You sure about this lead?
[JUZO] There's only a
small percentage of people
who knew about the
existence of Tindalos.
That's because the
records all deal with
leaders involved
in extension tech.
I'm sure either the government
or Beruhren covered
up the information.
[KRONEN]
Then how can you even be sure?
[JUZO]
'Cause I'm a newer model
based on the data collected
in battle from Tindalos.
And when it comes to my seniors,
I won't forget their
faces anytime soon.
So the short version
is Gondry's going around
killing his few
remaining war buddies.
[JUZO]
Basically.
But as for motive,
I've got nothing.
Huh. Renegade Extended
go berserk, that's why.
It's not like
they need a reason.
The guy's living in the past.
Time hasn't moved forward since
the Nightmare of Norse Scott.
[JUZO]
Wonder if that's the case.
Ugh!
[JUZO groaning]
[KRONEN]
Inui.
Did you just scratch my car?
[JUZO] Don't blame the
victim! You were driving!
[CROWD]
Army! Army! Army! Army...
[CROWD cheering]
I wonder when Army's showing up!
[ANTI‐EXTENDED A] Extension
technology's the devil's work!
More regulations now!
[JUZO] Well, he's certainly
brought people together.
Now, if we only knew
what Gondry's abilities were.
[JUZO] This situation could
get real ugly, real fast.
[BOY B]
Hurry up!
I heard someone say he's here!
[gasps]
[JUZO]
Gotta watch your back, kiddo.
Uhh...
I swear I won't look at you!
But just don't turn on
the waterworks, please!
[GIRL A]
It's okay. I won't cry.
Are you proud of me?
[JUZO]
Folks twice your size
go running when
they see my face.
You're pretty impressive, kid.
[GIRL A]
Know why I'm not scared?
Your face seems
familiar to me somehow.
[JUZO]
It does?
[CROWD cheering]
Huh. Sounds like the
guest of honor has arrived.
Everyone, I need you
to step back now!
Please stand back!
[CROWD]
Army! Army! Army! Army...
[BOY A]
Army!
Could you show us
your famous move?
Don't do it, sir!
If we excite the crowd any more,
we won't be able to
keep the area secure‐‐
[TOKISADA]
I mustn't disappoint my public!
[STAFFER A]
Master Tokisada, please wait!
[BOY A]
Ahh!
[TOKISADA]
Funke...
...Faust!
[TOKISADA]
Achieving this level of power
is no longer an
unattainable dream.
Promise me, boy,
that you'll aim high.
[laughs] I will!
[CROWD cheering]
Guy's a blank.
All noise, zero impact.
To be honest,
I can almost understand
why Gondry would
want to take him out.
[JUZO] After getting
a good look at that attack,
there's not a doubt in my mind.
[JUZO] He's definitely
one of my seniors.
[GIRL A]
Excuse me, sir.
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
Here. For you.
Sorry, but gifts have
to be sent to‐‐ Uh.
[TOKISADA]
It's the duty of a hero
to embrace the
admiration of the young.
Little girl, these flowers
are as beautiful as you,
and I accept them.
[CROWD cheering]
[WOMAN A]
Army! Army! Army! Army! Army!
[TOKISADA]
Hm?
What is this?
[JUZO] I'd advise you to
take this chance to get away.
‐‐[TOKISADA] You're a...
‐‐[STAFFER A] Master Tokisada!
This way, quick!
[JUZO]
So you're Gondry, huh?
[JUZO] If you wanna
attack somebody so badly,
I'll volunteer.
Let's go, punk.
[MAN A]
Don't get in my way!
[JUZO]
Not to worry.
I'll hold back only because I
was asked to capture you alive!
Ugh!
[KRONEN]
Step aside, Inui.
EMS will take care of him.
[KRONEN] You just sit back
and see how it's done!
[JUZO]
With my back turned!
Man, that's low.
Huh?
[KRONEN groaning]
[JUZO] Just what
the hell's going on here?
Whoever that is,
it's not Gondry.
Not by a mile.
‐‐[STAFFER A] This way.
‐‐[TOKISADA] That's enough.
I'm sure we've
reached a safe distance.
Such foolish behavior.
Doesn't he realize
I've spent my life
helping the Extended
be recognized as citizens?
[TOKISADA]
No.
I should be more compassionate.
There's no telling what
sort of life he's lived.
I'm ashamed I wasn't
more sympathetic
and that I was caught off guard.
What's truly miraculous
is this little girl.
So young, yet she
managed to stay calm
throughout the entire ordeal.
For your bravery, you have the
respect of Tokisada Mega Armed.
Beg your pardon,
but the culprit may have
accomplices working for him.
We shouldn't stop until
we make it out of the park,
otherwise‐‐
‐‐[squelching]
‐‐[groaning]
‐‐[TOKISADA] What?
‐‐[STAFFER A] Otherwise‐‐
‐‐[squelching]
‐‐[STAFFER B groans]
[STAFFER A]
Otherwise‐‐
‐‐[STAFFER C groans]
‐‐[TOKISADA] It can't be.
[TOKISADA]
Impossible!
[GIRL A]
I didn't cry.
[GIRL A, GONDRY]
Would you like to know why?
[GONDRY] Because your
face was so familiar.
Are you still proud of me?
[JUZO]
It looks like you're his...
[TOKISADA] Have no fear,
you with a gun for a head.
[JUZO] I'll wake up from
the dream the past left behind.
[GONDRY] Now then,
hero, how about you die?
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Seven:
"Overheat."