It's a pretty simple
external extension,
so the area around
the attachment
may be swollen a little while.
You'll get used to it.
Don't try to rush things.
Unfortunately, I wasn't able
to repair your vocal cords
since Harmony is
interfering with them.
But we'll figure
something out eventually.
[TETSURO grunting]
[RINKO]
Keep running!
[RINKO yells]
Say, "ahh."
[gasps]
Why are you looking
at me so intensely?
I see how it is.
You love being fed by
such a beautiful girl.
Ugh!
[JUZO]
Stop messing with him.
[MARY]
I wasn't hurting anyone!
You on the other hand...
[JUZO] Eat. Then you and
I are gonna have a talk...
...using this.
[thudding]
[HUANG] Juzo Inui!
We know you're in there.
[LACKEY] We're from the
Kyusei Group! So open up!
You better not make
Brother Huang wait.
‐‐[slap]
‐‐[LACKEY yelps]
[LACKEY gasps] Whoa, his head!
It's a gun, just like they said!
Shut yer mouth, idiot!
This is Kyusei Territory.
Extends like him
are a dime a dozen.
Try acting
professional for once.
So you're Juzo, the Resolver.
You're shorter than I expected.
[JUZO]
Huang, was it?
I understand you're a senior
member of the Kyusei Group.
So why are in you
a dump like this?
[MARY grunts]
If you're as good
as they say you are,
it shouldn't be too
difficult to figure out.
I'd like you to
resolve a certain
Extended problem we've got.
[JUZO]
Give me the details.
As of late, there've
been several attacks.
All of them on our turf and
all of them involving children.
While none of them were killed,
each one had their arm and
leg extensions ripped off.
[JUZO]
Pretty heinous.
Yeah. And on top of that, every
one of 'em's unconscious still,
so we can't ask them anything.
But the real problem is this.
The culprit, whoever they are,
keeps displaying the
limbs in public places.
According to witnesses,
the way they're strung up
makes 'em look like puppets.
Based on the attacks,
we're sure it's Spitzbergen,
the anti‐Extended tech group.
They don't like the fact
we control the black
market on extensions.
They're taunting us.
Look, even though they say
they're a political group,
it's really obvious.
These guys are
nothin' but terrorists.
You understand, don't you?
Bottom line‐‐
we need to know about
everything that's going
on in our territory.
[JUZO]
Wish I could help.
[HUANG]
Hm?
[JUZO] What makes you think
I could find out anything?
I don't even know why
my head's like this.
Heh! You gotta be some
kind of loose cannon
talkin' that way to
a senior member of the Kyusei.
You either have some
powerful connections
behind you or don't
care about your life.
[JUZO] Just don't have a reason
to put a high price on it.
Heh. Here's the thing.
It's embarrassing, but
we lost some of our own‐‐
combat‐rated Extended
we sent as lookouts.
Since none of the brats
that were attacked
are conscious yet, we don't
know what we're up against.
[JUZO] You want me to find
the perp and take 'em out.
That's what I'm askin'.
You'd be doin' us a favor.
Oh. Heard you had
a beef with Beruhren, too.
Maybe we could help you
smooth things out with them.
[LACKEY]
Hey, bastard!
You answer him when
he talks to you, got it?
Go smoke on your own time!
[JUZO]
It's funny.
I was having déjà vu, like I've
had this conversation before.
[JUZO]
I do appreciate the offer.
After all, we're talking
about the Beruhren Corp,
the true owners of the city.
And I've been
racking my chamber,
trying to deal with a
problem that's way beyond me.
But my philosophy's always
been "wipe your own ass."
My suggestion:
You oughta protect
your territory yourself.
[JUZO] By the way, you
guys want some coffee?
Tastes like shit, but the
mob's been driving up prices
making it cost a fortune.
Still, you're welcome to a cup.
[LACKEY]
All right, wise guy.
How 'bout my gun
does some talking? Uh!
Brother.
[HUANG grunts]
[MARY gasping]
[HUANG laughs]
You're one tough son of a gun.
I'll give ya that. How am I
supposed to stare a guy down
when I don't even
know where his eyes are?
[JUZO]
Yeah. I get that a lot.
[LACKEY] We're leaving?
Are you sure about this?
[HUANG]
Gun head's got a point.
We'll take care of the problem.
I mean, if we can't
protect our turf,
how're we supposed to
tell others what to do?
On top of that,
I'd rather not duke it
out in this apartment...
...considering
that young engineer
has helped out our
boys in the past.
[MARY nervously chuckles]
[HUANG] You may not realize
it, but I like you, Resolver.
Even so, there're rules
that gotta be followed.
If you want to hide
something valuable here,
it's best not to
start any trouble.
[JUZO] Thanks for the
advice. I'll remember it.
[LACKEY]
This isn't over!
[door closes]
[MARY]
You think it was smart?
Turning down their job?
[JUZO] That wasn't
Spitzbergen's handiwork.
No question, the culprit's
definitely an Extended.
[JUZO] Yeah. And a group
so adamantly opposed
to the technology wouldn't
use one for their dirty work.
Then you mean...
[JUZO] My guess is that it's
Beruhren sending me a message.
[JUZO] They'll probably
continue hurting kids
till they find Tetsuro.
That's insane!
[thudding]
[MARY gasps]
Hey, kid! What're you doing?
It's too soon for
you to stand up!
[TETSURO]
No. I can't let them.
[MARY]
Huh?
[TETSURO] If children are being
attacked all because of me,
I can't stay here.
I have to do something about it.
I won't sit by!
All right, look.
You're a good kid, and I
understand your frustration,
but no good will come of getting
mixed up with up Beruhren.
You can trust me on this.
See, I know a guy
who shall remain nameless,
and they're in
neck deep already.
[JUZO]
So what do you plan on doing?
Sure, your thoughts
are admirable,
but I hope you're not
asking me to risk my life
just because you can't
do anything yourself.
C'mon, Juzo! Why'd you
have to word it like that?
[JUZO] Achieving justice without
putting your life on the line‐‐
that's a pipe dream.
[grunts]
[TETSURO]
You're absolutely right.
And at the moment,
I can't even stand without
somebody helping me.
But does that mean...
everyone who's down and out
should give up hope of
ever getting out of the gutters?
[TETSURO]
When I escaped the facility,
it was hard enough
trying to save myself.
I couldn't help
any of the others.
[TETSURO] No. I didn't
even try to save them.
Where exactly is
this facility located?
[TETSURO]
I don't know.
I was running through
dark underground passages
trying to evade my captors,
and somehow I
ended up in the city.
All I know is that Beruhren
has been taking people
and illegally
experimenting on them.
I have no memory from before
I was sent to that place,
but if I'm the CEO's
son, like you say I am,
then it's my responsibility
to stop what's going on!
I can't allow them to
ruin more innocent lives.
Juzo Inui, I want
to formally hire you.
Will you lend me your
strength one more time?
[MARY]
Uhh...
[JUZO]
So that's what you plan to do
with your hard‐earned freedom?
[TETSURO] If I tried going
to the Security Bureau
or the press, Beruhren
would just erase my existence.
Since I managed to escape,
I have to stop them from
harming any more children.
[JUZO]
I've already come this far.
[JUZO] I'll protect you until
you can stand on your own again.
But you know, I'm not
running a charity here.
I can't be responsible for
saving complete strangers.
[TETSURO]
Your fee... Wait!
There's gotta be a way we can
remove Harmony and sell it!
I bet it'd go for a good price!
[JUZO sighs]
One problem‐‐
we don't even know
if it'll come out.
[TETSURO gasps]
Looks like the device
was surgically embedded
in your medulla oblongata.
If we attempt to remove
it, well, it's dangerous.
[JUZO] Your heart's in
the right place, Tetsuro.
[JUZO] There aren't many
people who'd be as noble
if they experienced the same
things that were done to you.
[JUZO] The sooner you can
come to terms with that,
the sooner you can move on.
[JUZO] Before you start
worrying about others,
you should take
care of yourself.
[JUZO grunts]
It's even worse when it's cold.
[JUZO]
Tetsuro, are you‐‐?
[MARY groans]
[JUZO groaning]
[MARY]
You okay?
What's going on? Hey, Juzo!
[gasps] He's out.
[MARY]
Uh...
Um, what's going on here?
[TETSURO]
You won't have any complaints
if I can stand on
my own, right, Juzo?
[TETSURO] Sorry for causing
trouble. Thank you, Mary.
So that was Tetsuro just now?
And he jumped bodies?
That's how Harmony's activated.
He really can control Extended.
[TETSURO] I feel pretty lousy
having to steal like this,
but it's for the
good of the children.
[TETSURO] If I had stuck
around any longer,
Mary might've forced me to
sever my connection with Juzo.
The downside to all
this is that my body
is vulnerable while I'm
controlling another form.
[WORKER A] Are you
from the Security Bureau?
Nah, not with a head like
that. As if it matters.
Kids get attacked around here
pretty much on a daily basis,
but it's always been that way.
Yeah, this neighborhood
weeds them out.
I remember watching
my kid sister go chasing
after a bug or something
about ten years ago.
She never came back home.
Ah! Here it is!
[WORKER A]
Now let's get a closer look
at that body of yours.
You got some great parts that're
rare even on the black market.
[HOODLUMS chuckling]
[WORKER A]
There's no need to worry.
I promise any leftover scraps
we don't want you can keep.
I really oughta be going!
[HOODLUMS yelling]
[WORKER A]
Hey! Where're you going?
I promise it won't hurt!
[HOODLUM D]
Shit! We lost him!
[HOODLUM E] Don't worry.
With a face like that,
he can't stay hidden.
[HOODLUM D]
I'll keep goin' this way.
The rest of you,
go check out the main stairs!
[footsteps]
[TETSURO]
That was close!
What's with this body though?
It has way too many channels
making it hard to control.
Is it an off‐brand sub‐brain?
Nevermind!
I've gotta hide this head.
If only I had some kind of mask.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[TETSURO]
Amazing.
I can still see
everything even with this on.
[ANNE]
This way!
[TETSURO gasps]
[ANNE, ENDE panting]
Ende! Keep up with me!
I won't let go, Anne! I swear!
‐‐[BOTH grunt]
‐‐[EXTENDED A yelling]
[ENDE screams]
[EXTENDED A groans]
[gasps]
[TETSURO]
Go! Leave this to me!
You can't just use
others for your goals,
then toss them aside
when you're done!
You people... This has to stop!
[EXTENDED A]
I get it.
You're just another
Spitzbergen terrorist!
[TETSURO]
Huh?
[EXTENDED A grunts]
[TETSURO]
Wait! I'm not‐‐
[EXTENDED A yells]
[TETSURO]
Stop!
Ah, uh... What the...?
[TETSURO]
Amazing.
[ANNE]
Ende, are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine, Anne.
Listen.
They said they'd change
your body back to normal.
But before they do, we have to
finish the job we were assigned.
Which means there can't be
any witnesses left behind.
Your strength, I need you
to lend it to me again.
[TETSURO]
Hey, you two.
What're you talking about?
Anyone who sees us
should be killed, right?
Yes, Ende.
[TETSURO]
Just who are you girls?
[TETSURO gasps]
Because after all, we have
no need for any adults.
[TETSURO]
Don't tell me...
...the ones attacking
the children...
...it was you!
[TETSURO]
Wait!
[ENDE grunts]
[TETSURO] You're both
Extended from Beruhren, right?
That body...
I can tell you were a test
subject at the facility.
Who are you?
How could you
know that? Unless you...
[TETSURO] I used to be
one of Beruhren's prisoners
and I know what they can do.
But with some help,
I was able to break free.
And now I wanna help.
I wanna save the two of you!
No thanks. You're crazy.
I have no idea why
you stopped that Extended
from the Kyusei group for us,
but we are not
captives of Beruhren.
That's the only place
we can call our home.
[TETSURO gasps]
[ANNE] Sorry, but now that
you've seen the two of us,
we can't allow you to live.
Kill him, Ende!
[TETSURO gasps]
This body, it moved on its own!
[TETSURO]
Whoa. What's going on?
I can't control him.
Is this poison?
Now I get it. This is why
the kids aren't waking up.
They were... injected with...
You know, people like
you piss me off the most.
[ENDE whimpering]
Ende! Are you all
right? What's wrong?
[groans]
[screams]
[gasps]
Oh, no! She can't stop!
[PEOPLE chattering]
[PEOPLE gasping]
[PEOPLE yelling]
[PERSON A]
A renegade Extended!
[ENDE wailing]
Ende!
[ENDE]
Anne.
It hurts. My head hurts so much.
Please, I need your
hand. Don't let go.
No. Where are you?
Don't let go of me.
Everything's okay, Ende!
I'm right here with you!
Anne?
[ANNE]
You have to listen to me.
We need to lure
this Tetsuro out,
then we can go back
to the facility.
There you'll be
taken good care of.
They'll make you feel better.
Yes. You're... right.
[CUNNINGHAM sighs]
What is the meaning of this?
[ANNE]
I already told you!
Look! Ende's at her limit!
Please, take her to the
facility to be treated!
[CUNNINGHAM] Did you forget
the roles you were assigned?
Her task was to ambush children
in the Kyusei territory in order
to send a message and
lure the boy out of hiding.
Whereas your one job
was to keep this failure
from going berserk and
drawing unnecessary attention.
But it seems this
simple assignment
proved too difficult
for you to carry out.
[ANNE grunts]
Your abilities allowed
you to operate covertly
in the Kyusei Pit
where 90 percent of
the locals are Extended,
yet somehow you still
managed to cause a scene‐‐
meaning the two of you failed
and are complete
disappointments!
But we left messages just
like we were instructed to!
If Ende's treated,
we can go back‐‐
The company has no use for gears
that do not fulfill
their assigned role.
You can't! If you
separate us, Ende will...
[gasps]
Ende!
Let go! She has to
receive her treatments!
[CUNNINGHAM]
It's too late!
Both test subjects are
to be immediately retired.
No...
[TETSURO]
That's enough!
[HENCHMAN A groans]
Hey... How'd you...?
[TETSURO] These are children!
Not soulless gears!
[ENDE] Hey, Anne.
My body, where'd it go?
[CUNNINGHAM] What do
you know, Master Tetsuro,
it seems you're fit
to be a tool after all!
[TETSURO] It doesn't matter.
I want to save these children!
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Four:
"Trigger."