I just wanted freedom‐‐
to experience the feeling of
being able to walk around again.
[TETSURO]
Juzo Inui,
you were the only one
who listened to my story.
[TETSURO] It's too bad
things had to end this way.
But you should know...
...I'm glad to have met you.
[JUZO]
Funke...
...Faust!
What just happened?
[OPERATOR A]
We're being attacked!
[KAREN gasps]
[OPERATOR A] Looks like
some kind of Over‐Extended
with a gun for a head!
But that's impossible.
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
[JUZO grunts]
[HENCHMAN A groans]
[JUZO] Don't you think
you're overreacting a bit?
I'm just a single unarmed man.
‐‐[gunshots]
‐‐[KAREN gasps]
[OPERATOR A] Sister Karen!
We should request backup!
What? And humiliate myself?
I don't think so.
[OPERATOR A]
But what about...
[BOTH gasp]
[JUZO]
We meet again... Sister.
I'm surprised you came back.
A man of his word.
[JUZO] You walked off with the
kid. I'm here to pick him up.
I hate to tell you this,
especially after how
far you've traveled,
but I'm the one who was
put in charge of making sure
this child was safely
returned to the facility.
Your request has been denied.
[gasps] But these are
anti‐Extended bullets.
[JUZO]
You know...
...I really hate kids,
but what I hate more
are obedient ones, Tetsuro.
Hear me?!
[KAREN gasps]
[JUZO]
What did you tell me earlier?
That you aren't a tool.
That you wanna
walk around freely.
Then, afterwards, you said
you were glad to have met me?
Don't make me laugh!
You gave up before
you even tried.
Is this the extent
of your so‐called will?
If you're a punk kid, then try
acting like it for a change!
[grunting]
[OPERATOR A] Subject's
consciousness is rising!
Harmony is being activated!
[KAREN gasps]
[grunting]
Harmony? But how?
[JUZO grunts]
[OPERATOR A groans]
[TETSURO]
Please...
...Juzo!
Save me! Save me!
[TETSURO grunts]
[JUZO]
There you go.
[KAREN]
Huh?
[JUZO] Now, that's
how a kid should act.
I've had enough of this!
Let's see how you
like it point‐blank!
[JUZO] Tetsuro!
I'll grant that wish of yours.
The bullet's been loaded.
[gasps]
[JUZO] Working too much
is bad for your health, Sister.
[OPERATOR A grunts]
[JUZO]
You should take some time off.
The job's finished, Tetsuro,
like I promised.
[JUZO]
Yeah, Mary.
I got tied up, but I'm
bringing him over now.
What's the deal? Don'tcha
got any Tanegashimas?
Fine. Gimme a pack of those.
And thrown in some matches.
No, this isn't a stickup.
[JUZO] Cranked my pain
tolerance too high.
Can't move right now.
Took too many bullets, too,
tryin' to look cool.
It was worth it.
Managed to save the kid.
Didn't plan out where
he's supposed to crash.
[TV CASTER A] Our next
story: Early this morning,
a train owned by the Beruhren
Corporation was derailed.
According to an official
statement released,
the incident was most
likely an act of terrorism
committed by Spitzbergen...
[JUZO]
That didn't take long.
Beruhren's already
covered it up.
Must really wanna hide
this kid's existence.
Spitzbergen is also believed to
be involved in the kidnapping
of Tetsuro Arahabaki,
the eldest son of Beruhren CEO,
Souichiro Arahabaki.
Tetsuro has not been seen since
his mysterious
disappearance one year ago.
The Reconstruction
Agency announced...
[JUZO]
Nah, it can't be. Could it?
[DAUGHTER A screaming]
This is all my fault
for skimping and getting
my sweetie bear a cheap
back‐alley extension procedure!
[MARY]
They ignored part compatibility
and compiled the
extensions abnormally
causing interference
and failure.
These must be parts
from the Kyusei group.
At the rate she's going,
that sub‐brain of hers
is bound to overload.
After that, the actual
brain will be affected.
No way! You have
to help my daughter!
Hold up.
What are you still doing here?
I thought I told you there's no
one allowed in this back room.
I'm paying you through
the nose for this treatment!
Now I want to know,
can you fix her or not?
Can I fix her? What're you
talkin' about, old man?
I've already taken her apart.
So you can stop your worrying.
All the affected areas
have been removed.
[FATHER A gasping]
[DAUGHTER A]
Dad.
Thank goodness. Thank goodness!
The next time you want
extension work done,
do yourself a favor
and come see me first.
I've got better parts.
I also don't charge as much
as the mafia to install them.
You can come on out now,
Juzo. The coast is clear.
[JUZO]
Uhh...
[MARY] What gives?
You've got a guilty expression.
Got a peek of her
naked, didn't you?
‐‐[JUZO] What? I would never!
‐‐I knew it.
That's not even
where your eyes are.
It was pointless to blindfold
you at all, pervert.
[JUZO]
Uh, but, uh, I‐I'm not a...
[MARY] So you want me to keep
this kid hidden, right?
[JUZO]
Yeah.
I don't mind.
Beruhren will think twice
before stepping into
Kyusei territory where
all the immigrants live.
Plus, I'm also
interested in this new
and highly illegal extension
he's been equipped with.
[JUZO] The new gear, it's
called "Harmony" or something.
What is it?
[MARY]
Well, ya see...
...Extended were created during
the war, as you already know.
The intention was to boost
a soldier's strength for combat
by augmenting
their physical form.
To reduce the load
on the normal brain,
auxiliary sub‐brains
were installed to be able
to control all metahuman
functionality.
[MARY] With it, an Extended
can move extensions that
follow certain
programmed actions
without giving
complicated commands.
[JUZO]
I see.
You gotta be kidding me!
With a head like that,
how could you not know this?
[JUZO]
I had a general idea...
...but as a Resolver,
that's all I needed to know.
Think of extensions the
same way you would a vehicle.
The sub‐brain is
the driver's seat,
and the Extended's
will is the driver.
[JUZO]
That's why when the sub‐brain,
or as you call it, the
driver's seat, is destroyed,
the Extended can
no longer function.
Most old models like you
who were constructed
during the war have
internal sub‐brains.
Meaning the likelihood of them
being targeted is minimal.
But while we're on the subject,
where is yours located?
[JUZO]
Who knows?
It's fine if you
don't wanna tell me.
Just remember, whenever you die,
I'll be sure to dissect
your body thoroughly
and find out for
myself. Sound good?
[JUZO]
Hey, now.
[MARY]
Anyway, it's only a theory, but
I suspect this Harmony device
probably allows another driver
to force their way into
somebody else's driver's seat.
But to do that, you need
authentication codes‐‐
three of them.
One from the user, the
manufacturer, and finally, EMS.
[MARY] There're rumors floating
around of some master key
that could bypass all the codes.
Thing is,
this device has the potential to
ruin the Beruhren Corporation.
Why would they make something
like that themselves?
[JUZO] Can you safely
remove it from his body?
[MARY] Mm... The implant goes
up to his medulla oblongata,
so taking it out could leave him
with some permanent
brain damage.
Seems like whoever installed it
didn't care whether
or not he lived or died.
Makes me think maybe he
doesn't have any parents.
You don't suppose
this kid's an orphan?
[JUZO]
How am I supposed to know?
Something bothering you, Juzo?
Huh? Wait. Did you
switch cigarette brands?
[JUZO]
It's not like I wanted to!
Uhh...
[laughing]
You're joking! You're
pissed off because
you can't smoke your
favorite cigarettes?
You're so big, but you
act like a little kid!
You go for Tanegashimas, right?
Pretty sure you left a pack
behind here a while back.
[JUZO]
You have some?
Oh. I threw them out the other
day, now that I think about it.
[JUZO]
You what?
Well, whaddaya expect? It's
not like I'm a smoker, jeez.
And besides, if I had cigarettes
that strong lyin' around,
my patients might start to
get the wrong idea about me.
You probably don't realize it,
but a lot of them
come here just to flirt.
I can't afford to have
a scandal on my‐‐
So like I was saying, it's
absolutely no problem for me
to install limb
and vocal extensions
that'll be good
enough to support
his day‐to‐day functions,
but I can't do anything
until he wakes up.
[JUZO] Roger that. When he comes
around, call me at the office.
[MARY] It's unusual for
you to stay involved
with a case this long.
The job's finished, y'know?
You're not planning on making
him your partner, are you?
Oh! I'm only saying everybody
knows how Gun Slave Units
are supposed to
work in teams of two!
Well, the general public may
not be aware of that fact,
but to anyone on my
level, it's common‐‐
[JUZO]
Take good care of him, Mary.
[MARY]
Huh?
[MARY grunts]
Seriously, would it kill
him to get a sense of humor?
[JUZO] Can't believe
no one has my brand.
Talk about being out of luck.
[TETSURO]
Please! I'm not a tool!
[SUISO]
You're not my tool.
And certainly not
command center's.
What you wanna do is
for you to decide, Juzo.
[JUZO]
It won't happen again. Never.
Shit! These aren't
doing anything for me.
I need Tanegashima!
Huh?
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO]
There they are!
[JUZO giggles]
[JUZO]
You gotta be kiddin' me!
Don't tell me
the damn thing's stuck!
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO]
Oh, come on.
‐‐[crash]
‐‐[JUZO grunts]
[JUZO]
All right!
Hey! What's the big id‐‐
[BOTH snickering]
You're comin' down
to the Security Bureau!
[JUZO]
Hold on! I bought those!
[SECURITY B]
Save it, pal.
[JUZO]
I properly paid for 'em!
It's the vending
machine's fault!
Huh?
I believe you're Juzo Inui, yes?
[CUNNINGHAM] Thank you
for your hard work, gentlemen.
You may return to
your usual duties now.
‐‐[SECURITY A] Sir!
‐‐[SECURITY B] Right.
[JUZO] Looks like you had
business with me from the start.
Name: Juzo Inui‐‐
an Over‐Extended who
received augmentation
courtesy of the military during
the days of the Great War.
Your hobby is housecleaning.
Dislikes: Children and humidity.
No family or memories of life
prior to your extensions.
After the war ended, you began
living in a one‐room apartment
owned by your landlord,
Christina Matsuzaki,
where you currently
make a living
resolving Extended‐related
problems. Heh.
However, it appears
you haven't been
properly compensated for the
last few jobs you've taken on.
I'm curious, how's the
window repair coming along?
[JUZO] It seems you looked
into my past pretty thoroughly.
So how 'bout you try telling me
something I don't already know?
[JUZO] For instance, let's
start with the Tetsuro kid.
Just who the hell is he?
[CUNNINGHAM] You misunderstand.
I'm here on behalf of
the Beruhren Corporation
to negotiate.
Please, call me Cunningham.
The boy is a very
valuable product of ours.
And as his rightful owners,
we would appreciate him
being returned to us.
We have a general
idea of his location,
but it seems he's in
a rather tricky area.
We'd like to resolve
this situation
as peacefully as possible.
Help us and you'll see,
we can be quite generous.
[JUZO grunts]
[CUNNINGHAM chuckles]
[JUZO gasps]
[CUNNINGHAM] Tanegashima
cigarettes for the Extended.
I can be so forgetful.
Remind me, that is your
favorite brand, isn't it?
We've been busy collecting all
the Tanegashimas in the city.
If you're smart and decide
to accept our proposal,
then the entire box
can be yours.
In order to reduce the stress
on their nervous system,
Extended rely on sub‐brains
to help carry the weight.
However, depending on the
degree of the extensions,
wear and tear on the nervous
system may not be prevented‐‐
thus, many Extended
choose to routinely use
"medicine" to suppress
the side effects.
One example being
these cigarettes.
However, the amount of sedative
contained in this brand
is far greater than
anything else on the market.
But there aren't many
who habitually use them,
so they were easy to buy out.
We're also aware that
you haven't been able to
get your hands on any of these
for nearly the entire day now.
Given the degree your
body's been extended,
controlling it
must be difficult.
[JUZO] Why'd you have to go and
do a dumb thing like that?
Take him.
[HENCHMAN C grunts]
[JUZO, HENCHMAN D grunt]
[JUZO groans]
[CUNNINGHAM]
During the war,
you were an Extended feared
by enemies and allies alike.
But look what happens to you
when you run out of your smokes.
I'm thankful every day I have
nothing in common with you.
[CUNNINGHAM]
Listen carefully.
Controlling the city's
supply of cigarettes was easy.
If you keep refusing our
proposal, we'll be forced to
destroy everything
you care about bit by bit.
[CUNNINGHAM laughs]
You see? Like this!
Understand now?
[CUNNINGHAM chuckles]
Hurts, doesn't it?
[JUZO]
The kid is Tetsuro Arahabaki,
the only son of Souichiro
Arahabaki, the CEO of Beruhren.
At first I didn't
think it was possible,
but it's him, isn't it?
Why's he being used as
some kind of guinea pig?
Is that really what
your boss wants?
There's nothing
strange about it at all.
Every employee's a cog
in the company machine.
It makes no difference
whether or not
you're the son of the CEO.
Gears don't have free will.
They simply listen and
do whatever they're told.
Just like you did in the past.
[JUZO grunts]
I can't believe
it's that hour already.
You see, I made plans
to get home early tonight
so I could enjoy
dinner with my family.
So if you wouldn't mind giving
us your answer, Mr. Inui.
[JUZO groans]
[JUZO] Y'know, you
ended up missing something
when you did that
background check on me.
[JUZO grunting]
[JUZO] I don't smoke
Tanegashimas because I have to.
I smoke 'em because
I like the way they taste.
[CUNNINGHAM whimpering]
[JUZO]
Oh, and one more thing.
The kid made it clear.
He already told me
he wasn't a tool.
Which means he's not the lost
property you're looking for.
[JUZO] But if you wanna
keep wasting my time,
then you can
forget about dinner.
Unfortunately, I seem
to be losing control.
[JUUZO] Guess that means
I won't go easy on you.
[CUNNINGHAM screams]
[crash]
[JUZO panting]
Do it now! Why're you waiting?
Hurry up and shoot him!
[MARY] You're asking a lot from
a person who lost their arms.
I know a great engineer if
you ever want them replaced,
Mr. Beruhren Employee.
[JUZO] Looks like you're
out of expendable gears.
Why don't you take them back
to that fine company of yours?
Maybe if you fix 'em up,
they'll help you next time.
I hope you understand the
consequences of your actions.
[JUZO]
Huh?
There's no place in this
city that's safe for you now!
I suggest you start
watching your back closely.
[JUZO]
Hey, hey, hey, hold on!
I didn't mean to take those
back! At least leave me one!
[MARY]
Big surprise.
Looks like you managed to get
yourself into trouble, Juzo...
...yet again.
[JUZO]
Huh?
Disgusting.
[MARY]
Of course they are.
I only copied Tanegashima's
active ingredients.
And I don't know anything about
how cigarettes are
supposed to taste.
[JUZO] So, Mary, why are you
wearing that ridiculous mask?
[MARY]
What do ya think, dummy?
I'm usin' it to
hide my identity,
so don't say my name!
[MARY] I'm not eager to
get caught up in your mess.
[JUZO] Seems to me you're
neck‐deep in it already.
Yeah, well, I called
your office earlier,
but you weren't
picking up the phone.
Not to mention it
looked like you were
going through some
serious withdrawal earlier.
So I came out and
look what I found.
[JUZO]
You called me?
[MARY]
Right, I almost forgot.
[MARY] The kid you brought in,
he finally woke up.
[MARY]
Say, "ahh."
[TETSURO] It's my responsibility
to stop Beruhren's evil deeds.
[ANNE]
Ende, don't let go of me!
[KYUSEI]
So you're Juzo, the Resolver.
[ENDE]
I know, Anne! I won't!
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Three:
"Puppet."