[COLT'S SISTER A]
All this food is ours?
Can we really eat it all?
[COLT]
That's why I got it!
And pretty soon you'll‐‐
No. Starting tomorrow, you'll be
eating this good all the time.
It's only the best from now on.
[COLT'S SISTER A]
Starting...
[COLT'S SISTER B]
...tomorrow?
Yeah. Now, eat up.
Tomorrow. I promise.
[GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL A] We will
never forget the heroic actions
of the late Tokisada Mega Armed!
Or how they led our
country to victory!
Don't let them fool you!
Mega Armed is no hero!
‐‐[thud]
‐‐What're you doing?
[HENCHMAN A]
Come quietly.
But he was working
alongside Beruhren!
Not only that,
he was a suspect in a criminal
case from ten years ago!
I have proof!
[EMS OFFICER A]
Beruhren's private police
are getting cocky.
[PROTESTER A]
This is tyranny!
[EMS OFFICER A] What are they
even doing at a public event?
[EMS OFFICER B]
Ignore them.
We just need to
focus on doing our jobs.
[EMS OFFICER A] Yeah, otherwise
Kronen will chew us out.
[MARY sighs] Today's ceremony
is just for Beruhren
and important political figures.
Why would Colt be
hanging around here?
[TETSURO]
He definitely told me
to meet him at
the park at three.
[MARY grunts] So what're
we supposed to do then?
It's too bad we couldn't
use the transmitter.
[TETSURO]
What transmitter?
[MARY] The one in your pocket
you should've let him steal!
[TETSURO grunts]
[MARY] When Colt's around,
items tend to go missing.
He was acting weird yesterday,
so I planted a tracker.
[MARY] But I didn't
account for one thing:
You taking it back.
[TETSURO]
Sorry, I screwed up.
Nah, it's fine.
You thought you were helping
Colt stay out of trouble
and trying to get back
the property he stole from me.
It's kinda sweet.
This stinks.
No way!
I don't know why‐‐since I think
I took a shower two days ago.
Or the trash is the
culprit. Just a thought.
[MARY]
Yeah. I see your point.
We'll wait for our chance
and clear outta here.
[TETSURO]
You sure?
But he may be able
to shed some light
on your brother's whereabouts.
I can ask Colt about
Victor some other time.
Plus, we can't let
Beruhren find you here.
[TETSURO]
If that extension really was
made by your big brother,
then that means Victor
must have survived the war.
Who knows?
All the parts used in
that piece's construction
were available
while he was enlisted.
I can't be sure of anything yet.
But if my brother is alive
in the city somewhere,
I'll definitely find him.
I'll never stop looking.
We'll meet up with
Colt some other time.
Follow my lead.
They say there's no one more
cautious than an engineer‐‐ Uh!
[gasps]
[SECURITY EXTENDED A]
Trespassers spotted!
Commencing capture!
[SECURITY EXTENDED A]
What was that?
Are you...?
[TETSURO grunts]
Huh?
Don't tell me.
[TETSURO grunts] This body's
difficult to control!
[MARY]
I'm glad you saved us,
but taking over
some random Extended
before we've figured
out Harmony is reckless!
[TETSURO] Yeah, sure,
but more importantly,
what was that explosion?
[TETSURO gasps]
Wait a second.
It's Colt!
‐‐[glass shatters]
‐‐[WOMAN A, WOMAN B scream]
[WOMAN A panting]
[MALE GUEST A]
Ugh! My arm!
[WOMAN A yelps]
[JUZO]
You all right?
Help me! He's‐‐ [gasps]
[gasps] He's gotta gun!
Your face is exactly
how he described it.
So you're Juzo Inui!
Not so fast.
[WOMAN A whimpers]
Bitch. She ratted me out even
though I took good care of her.
No! I swear it wasn't me!
Don't take one step closer!
'Cause if you do, I'll be forced
to use this heated long‐dosu.
The East Side Mafia
loves cutting
through extensions with these,
so imagine what it'll
do to her pretty face.
‐‐[SARYSHAGAN groans]
‐‐[JUZO] Save it.
[SARYSHAGAN groans]
[JUZO]
Saryshagan, right?
[groans]
[JUZO] Got some questions
regarding terrorism.
Specifically, the group
you're involved with.
That so? You mean
today's ceremony.
[JUZO]
Huh?
Look, I only acted
as the middleman.
My role was to arrange a meeting
between the kid and
Spitzbergen. That was it.
Looks like they're using
the train to evacuate.
[BOTH gasp]
[COLT]
Let those two go quietly, yeah?
I‐It's you!
Tetsuro, while
I'm glad you made it,
you shouldn't have brought
médica along with you.
[TETSURO]
Actually, I'm in here.
Huh? Okay. Back up.
Does that mean
you're controlling it?
[TETSURO]
Uh‐huh.
¡Estupendo!
[MARY]
Yeah, amazing.
That explosion‐‐
did you have something
to do with setting it off?
[COLT grunts]
[MARY]
Answer me!
Yeah, that's right.
This is the job I mentioned.
If something happens
during the ceremony,
protocol is for the
Beruhren officials
to board the train
and depart for safety.
[COLT] A train that
happens to have a bomb on it...
...and this switch sets it off.
It's time to cut some branches.
Those huge trees have been
stealing all the nutrients,
leaving nothing for us!
I understand how you feel,
but what you're talking
about is straight up terrorism!
[COLT]
No need to worry, médica.
I'll make sure no
civilians get hurt.
[gasps]
[TETSURO] So that's how you
plan to support your loved ones?
With the money you earn
from murdering others?
[COLT] You explain
it to my family then!
How killing the rich
and corrupt is wrong,
but it's okay to let
them take everything
while we starve to death!
[COLT]
My little sisters‐‐
neither of them understand.
The word "tomorrow"
is foreign to them.
They're not able to even imagine
what good a new day will bring.
[COLT]
Last time we met,
you asked me if this is
what I really wanted to do.
Yes, it is.
What I want
is to show 'em there's
a future waiting up ahead.
The cost doesn't matter.
I will do whatever it takes!
So do me a favor. Let go of me!
[HENCHMAN B]
They're up there!
The target's leaving!
[HENCHMAN C]
Shoot them!
[COLT gasps]
[COLT growls]
[TETSURO]
Colt!
[MARY]
Go after him!
[HENCHMAN B]
They're escaping!
[HENCHMAN C]
Notify the train!
[MARY gasps]
[MARY] Why didn't that
car leave the station?
[TETSURO groans]
[COLT] Seriously, though,
that body's a bad fit for you.
[TETSURO]
There's still time to turn back!
What'll happen to your family if
you're arrested as a terrorist?
Who will watch over them?
[COLT]
We're not getting caught.
I'll arm that bomb
by hand, then escape.
Both of us.
But first off...
...we should do something
about that guy.
[MID‐SECURITY A] Well?
Why didn't you capture him?
Are you forsaking your duties?
[TETSURO]
I'll distract him, Colt!
You make a run for it.
Good idea!
Think I'll take you up on it!
[TETSURO]
I won't let you!
[MID‐SECURITY A]
Traitor!
[COLT] Gotta be quick
and start the timer!
If he calls for backup,
it'll be hell!
[COLT]
Boom.
All done.
Now to go back
and help out Tetsuro.
[COLT gasps]
[MID‐SECURITY A]
Immigrant rat.
You were obviously enticed by
Spitzbergen and blinded by gold.
Repent, sinner,
for acting so capriciously!
[TETSURO]
Colt, I‐I'm sorry.
No. Tetsuro!
[COLT chuckles] So this
is how it's going to end.
I already set the
bomb timer though.
So if you try disarming it,
you can say goodbye to me,
you, and this whole train.
Once your suits die, my family
gets the money they're owed,
regardless of
what happens to me.
That's the only
thing that matters.
Letting my sisters see what
tomorrow can bring them!
[MID‐SECURITY A]
Though you received extensions
thanks to the company,
you stand against us and
lend yourself to terrorists.
You're nothing but
a lackey of Spitzbergen.
Pity for you, your targets
aren't even on this train.
[MID‐SECURITY A]
We knew the terrorists would
create some distraction near
the heavily guarded
ceremony ground.
Then during the commotion,
the evacuation train
would be targeted.
Therefore, we took precautions
and changed our plans.
While our prized officials
boarded the train,
we uncoupled their car
and left them at the station.
After that, we took
them somewhere safe
using an alternate
means of transportation.
No! You're lying!
[TETSURO gasps]
[MID‐SECURITY A] Huh. You're
free to think whatever you want.
Oh, one other thing.
Remember the people you saw
protesting outside the shrine?
And the innocent
choir of orphans
that sang during the ceremony?
What if I told you all
those unsuspecting people
were aboard this train?
After the world hears
how you murdered civilians,
they'll know the truth
about Spitzbergen.
How you're just butchers
without any motivation.
Meanwhile,
Beruhren will be propelled
into an even more
brilliant tomorrow!
[COLT grunts]
[MID‐SECURITY A] Release
the car with the explosives.
‐‐[HENCHMAN D] Sir!
‐‐[COLT] No, you can't!
Innocent people are going
to die! Are you insane?
[MID‐SECURITY A]
Proceed.
I've got to make this right.
[HENCHMEN groan]
[COLT] Enough time to
enter the code and disarm it!
‐‐[gunshot]
‐‐[COLT groans]
[TETSURO]
Colt...
[COLT groaning]
[COLT yells]
[COLT groans]
[COLT] My meds ran out
at a time like this?
[TETSURO grunting]
[MARY gasps]
[TETSURO groans]
[MARY] Hey, kid,
don't those burns hurt at all?
I didn't even notice them.
When did I...?
[MARY]
Never mind.
It was probably when...
[TETSURO] I‐I'm okay,
but how's Colt doing?
[MARY] They must've used
anti‐Extended rounds on him.
See how the bullets
went clear through?
If we don't get him to a
hospital soon, he's a dead man.
Damn! I was sure I was
a goner back there!
[TETSURO, MARY]
Don't do that!
So then it's not
as bad as it looks?
[COLT chuckles]
I didn't get maintenance
from you for nothing!
Not bad.
You're something else, Tetsuro.
Thanks to you, not a single
bystander ended up hurt.
Glad I invited you
along to help me out.
[TETSURO]
Thanks, but I'm not amazing.
This power is‐‐
Ah, so humble! I love this guy!
‐‐[TETSURO] Let go of me!
‐‐[MARY] Colt.
This extension‐‐
I need to know
where you got it from.
Damn, looks like
I've been found out.
[MARY]
Uh...
I stole it. Saw it on the black
market and couldn't resist.
Sorry, médica.
Oh. I see.
Look, I know I've caused a
whole bunch of problems today,
but could you maybe
control my legs for a while
and walk me back home?
I'm having some
problems standing.
That's cool, right, Tetsuro?
Thing is, his sub‐brain's
taken a beating
after everything
he's gone through.
This one time, please.
[COLT] When that old man with
the braids described the job,
I knew it was
too good to be true.
Should've trusted my gut.
Hey, what's up?
Don't feel much like talking?
Oh, I get it. Whenever you
take over someone else,
you aren't able to
speak anymore, right?
That's my bad.
Make a left. It's down here.
[COLT] By the way,
I meant what I said.
You are amazing.
But hey, don't think
I was talking about that‐‐
that power of yours.
You went out of your way to
help a guy you had just met.
Extensions didn't do that.
[COLT]
Don't get me wrong though.
Without that ability of yours,
I would have never gotten home.
I appreciate it, Tetsuro.
[JUZO]
The terrorist attack on Beruhren
ended in failure, Saryshagan.
Even if it was a success,
it would've only increased
discrimination
against the Extended.
If things went south,
they'd just need to
take care of the kid
and say he was acting alone.
Pretty selfish method,
don't you think?
[SARYSHAGAN] Heh. You really
can't see the big picture.
What do you think
is Spitzbergen's goal?
We're trying to eliminate
every last one of you Extended.
Let me assure you of one thing.
We're not gonna rest
until we've succeeded!
Yo.
[SARYSHAGAN]
Rosso?
[laughs] So the Security Bureau
was using you as a pawn!
They were holding the other
end of your leash, Extended!
[ROSSO] Hmph. First off,
I think you misunderstood.
I'm not here tonight
in my capacity as chief
of the Security Bureau,
and if I were, it's not
like we have jurisdiction
when it comes to
their kind anyway!
Still, because of all
the weapons and resources
you've supplied to Spitzbergen,
I ended up losing
a lot of family members!
And believe me, I'm gonna
make sure you pay for it!
[SARYSHAGAN grunts]
Well, Gun Head,
it looks like I owe you one.
[JUZO] The Security Bureau
doesn't owe me anything.
[ROSSO]
Tch.
[JUZO]
One last thing, Saryshagan.
Before, you said I looked
exactly the way he described me.
Who were you talking about?
Give me a name.
[SARYSHAGAN laughs]
[SARYSHAGAN]
Sorry, I just thought
you would've
figured it out by now.
After all,
you must remember Victor.
[JUZO gasps]
[JUZO]
Victor? Can't be.
[SARYSHAGAN] By the way, said he
couldn't wait to see you again!
[SARYSHAGAN laughs]
[JUZO]
Huh.
[PEPPER] Sure took your time.
I was losing my patience.
[JUZO] Sorry, but
I'm closed for the night.
Have a heart, or did
they take that as well?
What about my wish?
Aren't you going to grant it?
Or am I going to
have to order you to?
[JUZO]
That right arm.
[SEVEN] The only one who
can give me orders is Pepper.
[SUISO] Guess I was
the one who was wrong.
[PEPPER] Bad news, it looks
like I've fallen for you.
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Eleven:
"Owner."