[MATILDA]
Good day to you...
[IMELDA]
...dear members of Wurzel.
[HONEST] Good day to you
both, Matilda, Imelda.
The others seem indisposed, so
I shall listen to your report.
[MATILDA, IMELDA]
We thank you, COO Honest.
[MATILDA]
Actually...
[IMELDA]
...there's someone here
who wishes to meet
with the board in person.
[footsteps]
[HONEST] This is a surprise. If
it isn't our chief of security.
How long has it been since
I saw you last, Cunningham?
[CUNNINGHAM] I believe the
last occasion I had the pleasure
was after the unsuccessful
negotiations
with that Resolver
in the Kyusei Pit.
It was, uh, an
inquiry into my failure.
I come before you today,
groveling and
completely unworthy,
hoping that there's
still a chance
I may somehow redeem myself.
And to share that even though
it wasn't part of
the original plan,
I'm pleased to report
we've successfully
decommissioned Armed‐‐
permanently.
[CUNNINGHAM]
The former Mega Armed Tokisada.
As you'll recall, we lavished
him with wealth and power
over the course of many years,
built his reputation
up from nothing,
made him into a hero‐‐
the ideal Extended.
[CUNNINGHAM] However,
everything changed very recently
when a former member of
Tindalos threatened to reveal
the truth and go public about
what actually happened
at the Nightmare of Norse Scott.
In response to
hearing this news,
Armed foolishly murdered
the man, and then asked
for our assistance in
covering up the crime.
We took control of Gondry
and made him kill the others
to frame him for
the original slaying.
And after eliminating Armed,
made it appear as if
he was the final victim.
Exactly as you've
commanded, COO.
[HONEST] His obsession
with honor knew no bounds.
I have to admit, initially even
I was impressed by his avarice.
At least, until he began to
mistake the power granted to him
as his own.
That was his error.
However, Chief of
Security Cunningham,
I do not recall permitting
you to use a Gun Slave Unit,
or ordering you to
involve EMS's director.
[gasps]
[MATILDA] The COO
can be quite malicious.
[IMELDA]
So true.
[MATILDA, IMELDA giggle]
[STRANGE] Even the smallest
misplaced gear within the
grand mechanism of the company
can lead to disastrous results.
[CUNNINGHAM]
Uh! CSO Strange, you're here?
[STRANGE]
The facility has requested
more subjects for
their experiments.
And you'd already be there now
if your body was
even fit for testing.
[gasps]
[STRANGE] Since it's not,
perhaps the best option
is turning you into
an actual gear.
[CUNNINGHAM gasps]
[HONEST]
Fortunately for you,
your failures haven't reached
the ears of CEO Arahabaki yet.
[STRANGE scoffs]
[HONEST] Therefore,
your request will be granted
and you'll have one
last chance at redemption.
Do not fail us again.
[whimpers]
[HONEST] Fulfill your duty,
or face the consequences.
[PEPPER]
What's with that expression?
Someone eat your lunch?
For your information,
I was chewed out thanks
to the second‐rate job
you two ended up doing.
[PEPPER]
Excuse me?
We took care of Armed,
exactly like you asked us to.
So how about you save
your oinking, little pig?
Are you mad? Shut up
before someone hears you!
Jeez. First, that
knock‐off nun failed me,
now her little sister.
Stupid must run in your genes!
Huh? Leave Karen outta this!
[SEVEN]
Come on, Pepper.
You're the one being
rude to him first.
[gasps]
[CUNNINGHAM]
Don't sneak up on me like that!
[SEVEN]
I'm really sorry!
[PEPPER]
It's your damn fault.
For starters, if you want
us to do the job right,
don't give us junk equipment!
[grunting]
A way to control Extendeds?
Don't make me laugh!
It screwed with my own head
more than anything.
Plus it broke after one use!
This thing's complete trash!
What were you expecting
from a replica?
Not like we have access
to the original anymore.
[PEPPER]
Original?
[CUNNINGHAM]
Forget I said anything.
I'll be in contact.
And until you do hear from me,
your only job's to try keeping
your yaps shut, understand?
[SEVEN]
'Kay. Bye!
[PEPPER] Unfortunately,
we can't really do that.
After all, I did find
someone interesting.
[chuckles]
[SEVEN]
Who is it? Do I know them?
What're you planning?
Pepper, we were told
to stay quiet.
[PEPPER]
Shut up, would ya?!
[SEVEN]
But, Pepper, what about‐‐
[PEPPER] How can you be so
humongous and so pathetic?
[CUNNINGHAM] I swear, it doesn't
matter how hard you try,
you can't make simpletons
like them understand!
They have no idea the kind of
people they're dealing with.
We're talking about Wurzel,
the founding executive officers
and roots of the
Beruhren Corporation!
These are the demons
responsible for the creation
of extension technology
and finally putting an
end to the Great War
that lasted more
than half a century!
Even before that,
they were pulling strings
from the shadows.
There are even rumors going
around they were the ones
who started the war
in the first place.
I can't afford to fail
them again, otherwise...
[MATILDA]
One more thing.
In regard to the new
assistive walking devices
that have been distributed,
we've received complaints
from several families
about deaths caused by
problematic sub‐brains.
[BOTH]
What would you like us to do?
[HONEST] I'll remind you of the
Beruhren Corporation's emblem.
I'm sure you two realize
what it symbolizes.
Not only does it represent
the hand of the worker's guild
that founded the company,
it stands for the evolutionary
tree of our species.
That is what the Beruhren
Corporation strives for:
To bring evolutionary
innovation to the world.
However, the sad fact
remains there are those
who are opposed to
such dramatic change.
The least we can do is leave
flowers on their graves.
As always, take care of
their surviving family.
[TV CASTER A]
A few days ago,
a somber memorial service was
held for Tokisada Mega Armed.
The hero extended was killed
after a decaying bridge he was
traveling across gave way.
Those wishing to
pay their respects
have a unique opportunity.
For the next week...
[JUZO]
Yeah.
[TV CASTER A] ...citizens can
visit a special exhibit
at the End of War
Commemoration Park.
On to our next story.
Regarding the accidents caused
by the new extensions
from the Beruhren Corporation,
the family members
of the victims
have dropped their complaints
against the company.
[JUZO]
I know.
The news has been running
the story nonstop.
So how is Olivier doing?
[JUZO]
I see.
[JUZO] Damn it. And here
I was sweating bullets.
[knocking]
[JUZO]
Huh?
It's that time.
The hotpot's cooked
and ready to go.
[door closes]
[JUZO] I thought I already
made myself clear.
I don't play well with others.
[TETSURO gasps]
You gonna stand there
all day or what?
Usually you're good at
saying the wrong thing
at the wrong time.
[JUZO]
You still got business with me?
Juzo! I wanna stay here
and help you with your work!
About the money, I've no
way to pay you back yet.
But... I can be
useful with Harmony!
[JUZO]
Don't be stupid!
Your life's in the crosshairs
because of that thing.
Or did you forget?
And besides, it renders others
as nothing but tools,
which we both despise.
[grunts] I didn't...
[MARY] The only one being
an idiot here is you, Juzo.
[grunts]
Maybe your brain misfired,
but you're only alive
'cause of him!
If he hadn't rescued you,
you'd be sold as scrap parts
in the Kyusei Pit by now.
[JUZO]
Jeez, Mary.
It's still better
to be a pile of junk
than to get help
from some little kid.
[MARY growls]
Just 'cause you're made of iron
doesn't mean you hafta
be hard‐headed!
Why do you act like this
every time anyone tries
to help you out?
Agh! We're getting outta here!
If muzzle‐mouth wants to eat
his mochi‐kinchaku alone,
then we'll just let him!
[JUZO]
Uhh...
[BOTH]
Uh?
[JUZO] After going wild back
there in the tunnels,
getting a bite wouldn't hurt.
I suppose I could eat
the hotpot with ya.
This once.
[MARY] Was that supposed
to be a thank you?
What's wrong? Do two
little words scare you?
I swear, which one is the...
But I absolutely refuse
to eat any mochi!
That stuff shouldn't even
be considered food!
[MARY]
You gun‐faced teddy bear!
[JUZO]
Tetsuro!
For now, you should
start thinking
of ways to defend yourself.
Since word's gotten around
and interested parties
know where to find you.
As a matter of fact,
I wouldn't be surprised
if they burst through that
door at this very moment.
[gasps]
[CHRISTINA, SCARLET groan]
I know, it may look
like we're eavesdropping,
but that's just not true.
We just wanted to warn you
the hotpot was getting cold.
[CHRISTINA, SCARLET chuckle]
[JUZO]
I'll say this once.
Clear outta here.
You're ruining my appetite!
[TETSURO, SCARLET,
CHRISTINA yell]
[MARY laughs]
Oh, by the way...
I'll be moving in.
Starting today.
You're what?!
[CHRISTINA]
Sweepity‐sweep‐sweep.
Sweepity‐sweep.
[MARY] It may have been easier
to get parts in the Kyusei Pit,
but the whole scene is
pretty tense right now
because of how many
anti‐extension people
are around lately.
Good thing I'm done
patching up Ende.
Someone's gotta look
after you and Juzo.
Besides, I know he'll
always need repairs.
‐‐[MARY grunts]
‐‐[crack]
So I'm crashing here
for the moment.
Am I gonna have to do
these maintenance check‐ups
indefinitely from now on?
[MARY] The thing is, since we
aren't replacing any skin,
your body needs to get
regular check‐ups.
Same goes for the parts.
Not to mention, you haven't
finished growing yet.
We gotta stay on top of things.
[beep]
Oh.
You're electrical response
looks right on the money.
Not seeing any problems.
[TETSURO] You should have
amputated my legs.
It's not like they work anyway.
[MARY] Basic extensions put
less stress on the sub‐brain.
Also, once your legs are
removed, they're gone forever.
But if further down the road,
you discover that you
still feel the same way,
I'll handle any work you need.
No problem. I'll chop
your limbs right off.
After that, we can add
some cool extensions.
Hmm... Let's see.
Where'd I put those inner
liner replacements?
[TETSURO]
Mary,
why did you become
an extension engineer?
[MARY]
Mmm... Oh!
Ah‐ha! Finally found them!
Let's switch out the old ones
and get you feelin' like new!
[TETSURO]
Sorry. I asked you why you‐‐
Yeah, I heard you
the first time!
Ugh.
Seriously, you should
know better
than to ask a girl
about her past.
Then again, I guess an exception
can be made in your case.
[MARY]
For a while now,
I've been on a search
for someone.
The guy was a talented mechanic,
but he went to war as
a military engineer.
Like so many others,
he never came back.
Yeah, he might be dead,
but I just thought...
if I kept doing this job,
I'd see him again one day.
[TETSURO]
I hope you do... Find him.
[chuckles]
Yeah, me, too.
Make sure to let me know
if anything feels
off to you at all.
You did an amazing job.
[CHRISTINA]
Mary!
We've got an emergency!
[MARY]
What's the matter, Christina?
Just hurry up, would ya?
An Extended boy collapsed
in front of the building!
Come and take a look at him!
[MARY gasps]
[MARY]
Colt?
[TETSURO]
He sure was heavy.
[CHRISTINA] I should've figured
he was one of your patients.
That ought to do it.
I met him about half a year ago.
His name's Colt.
I found him passed out
and almost completely
out of medicine.
Medicine?
Yeah, believe it or not, lots
of people need them to function,
and not just
Over‐Extended like Juzo.
Colt received an illegal
extension treatment
that fitted him with
high‐output extensions.
Problem is, they put a lot
of stress on the sub‐brain.
But they help out at
construction sites.
That's how he
supports his family.
In this day and age,
there aren't many jobs available
for immigrants with
ordinary bodies.
[TETSURO]
So this was the result.
[MARY] We've pushed the limit
on the number of modifications,
but it looks like
it's about time
I started removing some
of his extensions.
[COLT]
Please, wait, médica!
Not yet. I need this body
of mine a bit longer.
That's all I can pay
you with today.
I know it's not that much.
[MARY gasping]
[MARY]
Check out the craftsmanship!
So clean despite the numbers
of delicate actuators.
You get maximum output without
depending on artificial muscles!
It looks old‐fashioned
on the outside,
but make no mistake,
this is the work of a genius!
How'd you get your hands
on something like this?
Heh. That piece of junk?
[MARY grumbles]
Something big's coming through.
A big job with a huge return.
As soon as it's wrapped,
I'll pay you what you
deserve, médica.
[MARY]
How big is big?
Yeah, the details
aren't important,
but I can afford
Madre's surgery.
Your mother's not well?
What's wrong with her?
Beruhen's new extensions.
You've heard about
them, right, médica?
What about them?
[MARY] Don't tell me.
Did she become a tester?
It paid. And besides that,
she got free extension work.
Madre said once she got better,
she wanted to start
working again.
[COLT] Turns out she wasn't
compatible with the sub‐brain.
It damaged her nerves.
But the news was saying
how all of the complaints
were taken back.
Mentiras!
It's a lie! All of it!
Beruhren Corp, they refused
to compensate us!
They've always
looked down on us!
Thing is, when a door shuts,
a window of opportunity opens.
We'll make it through somehow.
Thanks to this next job.
[MARY]
Don't get yourself killed.
I'll be careful.
Oh, and médica?
What's your size? An A cup?
B, duh. Nearly C.
[COLT]
Oh, yeah?
Working with more
than I thought.
[COLT]
Heh.
[COLT] Sorry, médica,
but to finish the job,
I'm gonna need to borrow this.
[TETSURO] What's your
definition of borrowing?
Return it and I won't tell Mary.
[chuckles]
[COLT grunts]
[gasps]
[COLT groans]
Crap! Too much!
[KAREN] From now on,
this is going to be your home.
[CUNNINGHAM] Due to your
betrayal of the company...
[WACHOWSKI]
On behalf of the organization,
thank you for your assistance,
Master Tetsuro.
We are grateful.
[COLT]
All right! Wake up!
[TETSURO]
What was that?
[COLT]
Hey!
Just now, what did
you do?! Tell me!
'Cause it was nuts! I thought my
sub‐brain was fried for sure!
Sorry if I overreacted
a bit. [laughs]
[TETSURO]
No. This is, um...
[COLT] You seem slow, but I
won't hold it against you.
They call me Colt. And you are?
The name is Tetsuro.
Nice to make your acquaintance.
So now that we're fast friends,
help me with the job.
A‐A job?
Yeah.
Some branches grew too long
and now we gotta cut 'em down.
I'll handle most of the work.
No need to put yourself
in any danger.
[TETSURO]
Why do I get the feeling
you're up to something shady?
Meeting you today and seeing
how rough you've had it,
you must have a lot
of determination,
but this is how you
decide to use it?
Well? You'd rather spend
your life being a criminal?
[COLT]
Is that what you think?
It's not about me.
Sometimes you just gotta give
people something to believe in.
Like a future.
[COLT] Tomorrow, at three,
the Mega Armed Memorial Ground.
Come, if you like.
Well, see ya.
Where did he go, Tetsuro?!
What? Mary?
This extension part
that Colt gave me,
Victor is the one who made it!
[TETSURO]
Who's Victor?
He's the one I've
been searching for!
My big brother!
[JUZO]
Mary. That thief.
She took off with nearly all
the cash I got from Olivier.
[JUZO]
Oh.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
[knocking]
[ROSSO]
Office is drafty as ever.
Did ya get that window fixed?
Hey. You remember me?
Gotta job for you
concerning Spitzbergen.
Figured you could help.
We need somebody to track down a
known associate of their group.
The target's a guy that goes
by the name of Saryshagan.
[COLT] I'm gonna show them
that it's not hopeless...
[TETSURO]
You can still turn back!
[ENEMY]
Damned immigrant rat!
[MARY] That's just an
ordinary boring crime!
[COLT]
Let go of me!
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode ten:
"Phantom Limb."