[TV CASTER A] In preparation
for the grand opening of
the End of War Commemoration
Park in six months,
there will be a public unveiling
of the Mega Armed Statue‐‐
what many consider to be
a symbol of the new plaza.
[JUZO]
The name's Juzo Inui.
I make a living
resolving problems
caused by Extended in this city.
Ever since the incident
in the Kyusei Pit,
the Beruhren Corporation's
been laying low.
However, Tanegashimas
still aren't available
for sale anywhere.
[JUZO] Well, these
fakes aren't half bad,
especially in the
comfort of my office.
[TETSURO]
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Easy!
That hurts, Mary!
The fact it stings means there's
still feeling left in your legs,
so you should be thankful.
Here we go.
[screams]
[MARY]
Hey. I need you to stay still...
[JUZO] If only there
was less screaming.
[MARY] I had to
decrease the output a bit,
but this ought to lighten
the load on your sub‐brain.
On the subject of Harmony,
there're a few tests
I wanna run later,
but maybe we should
save them for another day.
I second that.
[TV CASTER A]
Our next story.
Regarding the mysterious
flying object
that was reportedly seen
shooting out of the Kyusei Pit,
the Security Bureau now
suspects the Kyusei Group
was responsible and
most likely testing out
some illegal weaponry.
We have some‐‐
That was a flashy display
you pulled back there.
Could be bad news if
EMS finds out the truth.
[JUZO]
Could be.
[TETSURO]
EMS?
Yeah. They're a part of
the Reconstruction Agency.
It's a group that plans
countermeasures
against Extendeds.
[TETSURO]
I already know that,
but I thought
the Security Bureau
was looking for
the culprit. Not EMS.
Anyone with weapon
extensions like Juzo
is considered to
be Over‐Extended.
Or to put it another way,
their very existence is illegal.
EMS gives them
conditional immunity
so they can experience
normal lives,
However, it does
come with some rules.
That immunity can be revoked
if they decide to do
something criminal.
They're back to being
considered an illegal Extend.
Then EMS would hunt you down,
and after they caught you,
your body would be processed
and used for scrap parts!
[JUZO] Running your
mouth can be unhealthy, too.
[coughs]
[MARY] Thanks for
killing the atmosphere!
[TETSURO]
It's all my fault.
Thanks for the help.
[JUZO]
Where're you going?
Like she said, you'll
be turned into scrap parts
if you get involved
in this any further!
Not only you, Juzo‐‐
Mary'll be held
accountable, too!
[TETSURO grunts]
[JUZO]
Don't take her so seriously.
For starters,
where do you plan to go?
Beruhren's got
their sights on you.
There's nowhere
in the city to hide.
I'll find a place!
[JUZO]
A client oughta act like one.
The only thing they
should be worried about
is how they're
gonna pay their fee.
[JUZO] Anyway, just
shut up and wait for now.
[gasps]
Seriously. You don't
need to worry about me
or the other people
who live here.
By now, the tenants are used to
the problems Juzo
causes everyone.
‐‐[JUZO] Huh?
‐‐Right?
[JUZO grunts]
That reminds me.
Chris wanted me to tell you
she's got a pot waiting
for you to pick up.
[JUZO]
Of what?
Turns out Mr. Huang was quite
pleased with you stopping
Ende's rampage through
their territory.
So in lieu of cash,
he sent us some crab.
[JUZO]
We're gonna eat it here?
Damn it, my office
isn't a cafeteria.
Chris fixed your window
and put it on your tab.
The least you can do
is try acting polite.
[TETSURO]
All right, then.
At least let me go and
bring the landlady over.
And apologize for
breaking the window.
[MARY] I wouldn't
recommend going alone.
[TETSURO]
Don't worry.
Well, you've never met her.
[TETSURO screams]
[CHRISTINA] There's no need
to be afraid, cutie pie.
Just give in to it.
[TETSURO]
Help me, Juzo!
I can't pay you
if I'm not alive!
[CHRISTINA] A little sweetie‐
pants just barges in my room,
looking for me.
How am I supposed to hold back?
If I had known you
were Juzo's client,
I would've exercised restraint.
Can you forgive me?
[TETSURO]
Not a problem.
You're lucky she didn't
take it any further than that.
Looks like it's just
about ready to serve.
[CHRISTINA] Mm, barely fits and
needed to be crammed inside.
[MARY]
Now that I think about it,
we should've invited
Scarlet and her old man.
[CHRISTINA] Those workaholics
couldn't leave the shop,
so I shared some
ingredients with them.
[TETSURO gags]
Are you all right?
[TETSURO]
I'm sorry.
Seeing the crab
reminded me of something.
Tetsuro, poor baby,
you're not a fan of crustaceans?
How about this?
Try some mochi‐kinchaku.
I have enough for everyone.
Ahh!
[CHRISTINA] One lucky
person gets an egg inside.
[MARY]
Ooh!
[JUZO]
Christina, I'm not‐‐
Come now.
There's no reason
to be antisocial.
[MARY gasps]
My mochi!
Don't let it fall!
[TETSURO]
Juzo?
[JUZO]
Sorry,
but I'm not the type that
plays well with others.
Saved by the five second rule!
[TETSURO]
What was that all about?
[CHRISTINA sighs]
Juzo isn't used to this
much social interaction,
so it can be hard on him.
The two of you are
similar in a lot of ways.
Me and Juzo? You think so?
I agree.
He's worried his
existence will end up
hurting the people around him.
That's the reason he's
always putting distance
between himself and others.
[MARY]
Hey! The egg!
[SCARLET yelps]
[JUZO]
Hm?
[SCARLET]
Please let go of me.
I need to be somewhere.
[SECURITY A]
What's the rush?
After all, we're
giving up vacation hours
to make the rounds.
So the least you could do is
be a little more polite to us!
Yeah, c'mon, girl!
[JUZO]
Damn it.
The way I understood it,
government dogs and dogs in heat
were two different animals.
[JUZO]
Which ones are you again?
‐‐Hey!
‐‐That guy's an Over‐Extended!
[JUZO]
C'mon, now.
You're makin' me seem
like a loose cannon.
I may not look it,
but I'm just an average‐joe
with a license from the
Reconstruction Agency.
It checks out.
A license and everything.
[SECURITY A]
Let's scram. He killed the mood.
[SECURITY B]
Damn. That's a helluva face.
[JUZO] Go back to the office
and chew on some donuts.
[JUZO]
Huh?
Oh, Juzo. I was so scared!
[JUZO stammering]
Scarlet.
I just... wanted...
to say thank you.
[JUZO]
And, uh,
I just happened to have some
business with your father.
Y‐You've got some bad luck,
getting approached
by those goons
right in front of your place.
Aw, my luck isn't all that bad.
After all, you showed up.
[bell rings]
[JUZO]
You in, old man?
Old man?
[SCARLET gasps]
[JUZO] What happened?
Did he choke on his mochi?
Wake up, Dad!
[ANDY screams]
Tell me there's more crab!
Ahh. Welcome back, Zippo.
It certainly has been a while.
[JUZO]
Had me worried.
And would you call
me Juzo already?
Look at that.
You let someone pull
your trigger after all.
So you finally found
a person you could trust.
[JUZO]
No, nothing like that.
But it had to be done.
[ANDY chuckles]
[ANDY] I've had this shop
since the end of the Great War,
five years now,
and you're still the only one
who ever asks me to do this.
[JUZO]
That a fact?
A craftsman of your
caliber? What a waste.
[chuckles]
Go on joking, but you've never
seen me with a pair of scissors.
[JUZO]
I'm being serious.
You should have more customers.
If you closed shop,
I don't know what I'd do.
[SCARLET]
Never!
[JUZO, ANDY]
Huh?
I'd never let our
doors shut permanently!
F‐F‐For your sake, Juzo!
Uhh, yeah.
I kinda depend on you.
[chuckles] All right.
Just gonna lower you so I can
take care of that muzzle.
Hey, scoot down
a little bit more.
You're no small fry.
Would you care for
a warm towel, sir?
[footsteps]
[OLIVIER] I know you're
being hunted by Beruhren.
[OLIVIER] And if this
barrel of yours blows,
the Reconstruction Agency
will sniff around for you.
And when they do, you'll use
us to throw them off the trail,
since we don't get along.
You've got it all worked out.
Damn. You're so clever.
[SCARLET whimpers]
[JUZO] I figured you'd
show up eventually, Olivier.
Time you made good
on your promise to me.
I hope you're ready.
[OLIVIER]
You have been charged
with the suspected use of
a restricted weapon extension.
Thus, your license
has been revoked.
We're placing you
under arrest, Juzo.
[MARY]
Aww...
[TETSURO]
Yeah, well, that's what you get
for trying to eat
all the porridge
right after downing my
helping of kinchaku.
[MARY] You're the one who
said you couldn't eat crab.
I did you a favor.
[TETSURO]
Seriously.
We should've just
shared the hot pot
with everyone else
from the beginning.
Could you try and stop being
logical for, like, two seconds?
Just so you know, that's
not really popular with girls.
[TETSURO] Hurry up
and open the door already.
The porridge is
starting to get cold.
[MARY]
Yeah, yeah. You are like Juzo‐‐
too hard on people.
Uh.
[TETSURO]
Hm?
Guess we didn't bring enough.
These guys are EMS‐‐
Look here. It seems
we have guests.
[bell rings]
Unfortunately, we're currently
in the middle of something.
If you could come back later.
[MARY]
Your body would be processed
and used for scrap parts!
[TETSURO]
Juzo!
[JUZO]
No need to rush things, Olivier.
Besides, the old man
isn't done with me yet.
Come now.
I don't think I need to
explain the situation to you.
If they interfere,
they'll be arrested
for obstructing officers.
[EMS OFFICER A]
Hey, stand up!
[JUZO]
That's right, old man.
The anti‐rusting lubricant you
used last time was pretty good.
Let's go with that again.
Oh, sure.
[EMS OFFICER A]
He's not moving an inch!
What the hell's going on?
I'll give you three minutes.
I won't wait any longer.
By the way, what's
an old gun like you
doin' in a place like this?
[JUZO] I may not look it,
but I like to stay clean.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's finish up.
This may be the last
time I get the chance,
so I want to make sure
to be extra thorough...
...is probably what
a braver man would say.
But I pissed myself
a little just now,
so I should let
Scarlet take over.
Old man!
You're joking, right?
It'd be my honor,
and I'll do my best to give
you high‐quality service!
Uhh...
Why'd we have to be arrested?
Could you stop leering
at us, you perverts?
Or maybe I oughta take
your bodies apart!
[CHRISTINA]
Speaking of which,
you gentlemen do
you have nice bodies.
[TETSURO] If they're actually
Extended under those uniforms,
I may be able to
take control of them.
[TETSURO]
This time, I can save Juzo.
[MARY] Don't think about
trying anything stupid.
[TETSURO]
Mary?
You would be putting
all of us at risk.
Can you imagine what would
happen if they ended up
finding out you had
Harmony installed?
For now, all that we can do is
be patient and trust in Juzo.
[JUZO]
That Scarlet's somethin' else.
Not only did she
not clean my muzzle,
she left oil all over me.
The spin of my cylinder's
off and it's killing me.
[OLIVIER]
Only you, Juzo.
No one could ask me, the head
of EMS, to do such a thing.
I can't believe you convinced me
to shelter ordinary civilians.
[JUZO] You didn't expect me to
just leave 'em behind, did you?
Fine. You owe me another favor.
Maybe I should cash it in
right here in this vehicle.
[JUZO]
Uhh...
I would love to see
you try and refuse me.
And on the subject of oil,
I think it suits you.
[JUZO]
Uh, thank you.
Thank you? You oughta
be kissing my feet
for not deciding to
slap a corset on you.
It would've been
more convincing,
since it can't be made public
EMS cooperates
with Over‐Extendeds.
Especially when there's
suspicion our higher‐ups
have close relations
with the Beruhren Corp.
[JUZO] Working as a
bureaucrat sure sounds tough.
You're planning
on making my life
way more difficult
again, aren't you?
Just send me to prison already.
Juzo, every time I cover
up a problem you cause,
you make it up to me by
following one of my orders.
Wasn't that our arrangement?
[JUZO]
Damn it.
Or if you would rather,
we can send you off
to Wunder Bender.
[JUZO] A correctional facility
used exclusively for Extended.
Also known as the
storeroom for lethal weapons.
Heavy.
Well, can't let myself get
locked in the gun safe just yet.
So... what's the story?
[OLIVIER]
Early this morning,
an EMS prison transport leaving
Wunder Bender was ambushed
and all of the guards
were executed.
Furthermore,
the seven prisoners
that were being transferred
to the Beruhren research
facility managed to escape.
[JUZO]
Beruhren's takin' prisoners?
I thought you
weren't on good terms.
[OLIVIER] That's exactly
why this is such a headache.
The restraints used
to capture Extendeds
and restrict their sub‐brain
are referred to as corsets,
and Beruhren Corp holds
the exclusive rights
to manufacture them.
What a terrible joke.
In order to receive
their cooperation,
we have to send them Extended
prisoners on a regular basis.
Offerings to the altar.
[JUZO] The Reconstruction
Agency has a lot of authority,
but it depends on
borrowed firepower.
[OLIVIER] While it isn't
all that difficult to imagine
what Beruhren is using
the prisoners for,
currently, I lack the power to
change the situation on my own.
Which really pisses me off.
[JUZO] In other words, you need
someone to chase and hunt down
these convicts since you
can't do it out in the open.
You're welcome to refuse.
Then I'll have the pleasure of
doing whatever I want with you.
[JUZO] I swear.
You're cold as steel, Olivier.
Sounds like we have a deal.
I'm a little disappointed.
Why are we stopping?
It looks like an
accident. Apologies.
[OLIVIER] This always happens
when we're short on time!
[JUZO]
So...
...about the information
on the escaped prisoners.
[OLIVIER] Fortunately,
five out of the seven involved
have already been
recaptured by my unit.
And we've located
one of the other two.
[JUZO] Good. Then I don't
see what use I'd be.
The thing is, this
remaining prisoner‐‐
[crash]
[JUZO]
Mary!
[HUG BEAR] EMS bastards!
They don't know when to quit.
[EMS OFFICER C]
This guy's one of the escapees!
Uh, freeze!
Tell me, just how many
of those toy soldiers
do you have crammed
into that truck?
[EMS OFFICER D]
Stop shooting!
The corset's hit!
[HUG BEAR laughing]
Well, that was helpful!
[HUG BEAR grunting]
[BOTH yell]
Get over here!
Allow me to show you
how appreciative I am
for setting me free!
[EMS OFFICERS screaming]
[EMS OFFICERS groaning]
[HUG BEAR]
Don't know my own strength.
Did I overdo it?
Dad, hang on.
Guys, I'll get you out.
Just hold on.
[HUG BEAR]
I knew there had to be more.
You all look like
you could use a hug.
[gasps]
[OLIVIER]
This is a nightmare!
Where the hell is Kronen
when I actually need him?
[OLIVIER gasps]
[JUZO groans]
Juzo, those cuffs were
made especially heavy duty
to restrain Extendeds.
[JUZO grunts]
[OLIVIER gasps]
[JUZO]
Scarlet!
[OLIVIER] We can't have you
moving around in public!
[JUZO gasps]
[HUG BEAR grunts]
What's wrong with my body?
[KRONEN]
Prisoner Number 0137.
Goes by the name Hug Bear.
You're in violation of
line four and line nine
of article three
under Extend Law.
[HUG BEAR]
Bastard! What did you do?
I'm placing you under arrest.
I've pierced various
trigger points along your back
with my needles, cutting off
your power transmission.
I'm afraid your extensions won't
be operating properly
for quite a while.
[KRONEN]
Go back to your cell
and reflect on what
breaking the law gets you.
[EMS OFFICER C]
Section Chief.
I'm sorry I failed you.
Useless garbage.
Have the officers that aren't
scrap put a new corset on Bear.
[OLIVIER]
Kronen!
What's the meaning of this?
Our superiors gave
us explicit orders
to capture them discreetly!
It's of no concern to
me how our superiors will
have to explain themselves
to the Beruhren Corp.
I only follow the law and
fulfill my assigned duties,
Director.
‐‐[JUZO] You all right?
‐‐[SCARLET] Y‐Yes!
Everyone's in one piece.
They're just unconscious.
I can't believe you considered
relying on him for assistance.
[OLIVIER gasps]
[KRONEN]
Juzo Inui.
Just another renegade that
goes around breaking Extend Law.
In case you didn't know,
he's been granted immunity!
In case you forgot,
this is our duty.
We'll take care of the
last prisoner ourselves.
Accepting help from his kind
would degrade our profession.
[OLIVIER]
Are you sure?
His kind's not easily defeated
and he's not our enemy, Kronen.
[OLIVIER]
You should be more concerned
with the final escapee.
Prisoner Number 0001.
Name, Hayden Gondry.
The first officially
recorded renegade Extended.
If we're going to capture him,
we'll need all
the help we can get.
[OLIVIER] Don't take a promise
between us lightly ever again.
[KRONEN] I've always got an eye
on you law‐breaking Extends.
[OLIVIER]
The Nightmare of Norse Scott...
[KRONEN]
Next target, you say?
[OLIVIER] ...renegade
Extended case on record.
[JUZO]
NoGunsLife Episode Six:
"Hero."