[JUZO]
Huh...
[PEPPER] Sure took your time.
I was losing my patience.
[JUZO] Sorry, but I'm
closed for the night.
Have a heart or did
they take that as well?
What about my request?
Aren't you going to grant it?
Or am I going to
have to order you to?
[giggles]
[JUZO]
Punk.
Move your foot.
[SEVEN]
How come?
[JUZO]
That's just great.
You destroyed a
perfectly good smoke.
[SEVEN] Pepper's the only
one who can give me orders.
[JUZO]
Sorry about that.
Guess you better hurry and
ask mommy for permission then.
Brat.
[SEVEN]
Ugh!
Why you!
[PEPPER]
That's enough, Seven.
This room reeks
of cigarette smoke.
One more won't matter.
[SEVEN gasps]
Now that I see you side by side,
the difference is noticeable.
You've got that
classic noir look.
[PEPPER sniffs]
So romantic!
[gasps]
[SEVEN]
I think you just get caught up
in romanticism, Pepper.
[PEPPER]
Huh?
[PEPPER grunts]
[SEVEN]
When it comes to his kind,
they're relics...
and belong in the past.
[JUZO] Huh... Looks like we
have a different set of values.
[JUZO] You two, you're
minions of Beruhren.
[PEPPER] Really?
And what makes you think that?
I don't like the word minion,
but... you're not wrong.
[JUZO gasps]
Know what's funny?
You need a license
from the Reconstruction Agency
just to walk around.
But that's only
half the problem.
I couldn't help but notice that
right arm of yours is a Hands.
A device exclusively
used to release
the control program
on a Gun Slave Unit.
[JUZO] I'm surprised you can
still find 'em lying around.
Thing is, the Reconstruction
Agency would never allow
a Hands and a Gun Slave
Unit to work in tandem.
[JUZO] Unless... you're
employed by the right people
and have Beruhren's blessing.
You said your name
was Juzo Inui, correct?
Your room's looking
pretty barren,
but I guess that's
how you like it.
No anchors holding
you down to this place.
Free to leave whenever.
[PEPPER]
What've we here?
I do love books.
Printed words become an object.
Objects are things.
You can even pick them up
and have complete ownership.
[PEPPER]
Huh...
Didn't write your name inside?
Somebody could
easily steal this.
Won't be me though.
I decided to pay a visit
to your office today
for more personal reasons.
So, who is it?
[PEPPER] You're a tool,
and all tools have owners.
[JUZO]
I'm not following along.
[PEPPER] Unfortunately,
I've fallen in love with you.
[JUZO]
Uhh...
Was I not clear?
I wanna take you
and your owner down.
And afterward, I'll write
my own name inside of you.
That's my request, Mr. Resolver.
Will you grant it?
Knock him to the ground, Seven.
[SYSTEM VOICE 11A]
Activation of combat programming
confirmed by Hands.
Engaging in battle.
[JUZO]
So it's gonna be like that?
[SEVEN]
Hitze Faust!
[JUZO grunts]
[SEVEN groans]
[PEPPER]
So disappointing.
Do you plan on embarrassing
me in front of him, Seven?
[JUZO]
He's fast!
[SEVEN]
Sturm Faust!
So it is true. You really
don't have a shooter, then.
You're gonna die if
you don't get serious.
[JUZO]
I'm losing my patience.
That's the second
smoke he's destroyed.
[JUZO] I only use my
powers for one reason:
To complete a job I've accepted,
and after consideration,
listening to your
worthless request,
I'm choosing to pass on yours.
You're being serious?
That some kind of policy?
Pretty damn cool, I'll admit.
You've got me a little wet.
[PEPPER sneezes]
See what you've gone and done?
I want you even more now.
[PEPPER giggles]
[JUZO]
Tetsuro!
Get outta my way!
Seven? What the hell?!
[SYSTEM VOICE 11A]
Illegal access detected.
[gasps]
There's no way.
[JUZO]
Dammit.
[MARY]
Hey, kid!
Are you crazy? I told you
not to use Harmony too much!
Wait, Harmony? Really?
[CHRISTINA gasps]
No!
What the hell are you doing?
Stop turning my apartment
building into a war zone!
[NEIGHBOR 11A]
Keep it down!
[CHRISTINA]
Who said that?
How about I send them over to
your place and
see how you like it?
Oh? That's strange!
Why're you so quiet?
[PEPPER] That must
be the kid he mentioned.
Shit! Change of plans!
Things aren't gonna end well for
us if we lay our hands on him.
[JUZO]
Uh?
[PEPPER giggles]
[MARY groans]
I call dibs on this one!
[SEVEN]
Huh?
[PEPPER]
Move your ass. We're done here.
I can't believe you let
someone else control you!
No candy for you
when we get home.
[SEVEN]
Huh? But Pepper!
That wasn't fair!
[PEPPER]
Oh, shut up!
‐‐[JUZO groans]
‐‐[MARY] How bad is it?!
[JUZO]
Just... grazed me.
[MARY]
Juzo?!
Get up!
Juzo!
[growling]
Uh...
[CHRISTINA]
I saw that!
Stop trying to tear
my building apart even more,
you idiot EMS flunkies!
Otherwise you'll have
a lawsuit on your hands!
If I wanted a demolition
crew, I'd hire experts‐‐
not a pack of bumbling,
tax‐stealing bitches!
And why exactly are you here
instead of on the streets
trying to catch the culprit?!
[KRONEN]
A farewell to arms, huh?
[JUZO]
Huh?
[KRONEN] Looks like a Gun Slave
Unit working alongside a Hands
is too much for
even you to handle.
Pathetic.
[JUZO] Look, Kronen.
I'm sort of the victim today,
so just shut up and keep
wasting our tax dollars.
Damn straight! If you can't find
whoever's responsible for this,
I'll make sure all of you‐‐
Ooh!
I wasn't referring
to Volfie here, obviously.
Such a handsome,
yummy young man.
You're Juzo's friend?
You don't look anything
like those losers over there,
which must make
you their boss, hmm?
[KRONEN]
You recognize these two?
They're a Gun Slave Unit
owned by Beruhren.
Basically cleaners for anyone
who goes against the company.
[JUZO] Huh. Like I told them,
we've got different values.
That aside,
there's a high probability
they're the ones who attacked
the director a few days ago.
[JUZO]
Why'd they wanna kill Olivier?
Don't think she was the target.
They were really gunning
for Armed and Gondry.
Good luck getting
anyone to admit it.
Beruhren spent a ton of money
covering up the truth.
[JUZO] Sounds like
you're well informed.
Then you wouldn't mind telling
me where they are right now.
[KRONEN]
Hmph.
[JUZO] Just wanna
make a civil house call
asking for repair fees,
otherwise I could be evicted.
As for EMS, they've
got no intention of
looking further
into this matter.
We'll assign lookouts
to the building,
but anything beyond
that is up to you.
[JUZO]
That's outta character.
Get cold feet, Kronen?
[KRONEN]
I'll remind you.
There's the organization
and then there's me.
[KRONEN]
But you already know that.
[KRONEN] Let me warn you
of one thing, though.
The son of the Beruhren
CEO that went missing...
Well...
Seems the request for his search
has been silently retracted.
Suspicious, right?
My guess is it's
related to something
that you've been hiding.
Thanks for giving me
the warning, chief.
[PEPPER]
Change of plans!
Things aren't gonna end well for
us if we lay our hands on him.
[KRONEN] The son of the Beruhren
CEO that went missing...
Well...
Seems the request for his search
has been silently retracted.
Suspicious, right?
[JUZO] It doesn't make sense.
What's Beruhren planning?
[KRONEN] Looks like a Gun Slave
Unit working alongside a Hands
is too much for
even you to handle.
Pathetic.
[PEPPER] You're a tool,
and all tools have owners.
[TETSURO]
Juzo!
I want to stay here and
help you with your work!
[JUZO] Wish I could empty these
voices out of my cylinder.
Damn it.
[SUISO] In spring,
this crap's everywhere.
Feels like a snowstorm.
It's annoying when a
piece gets in your mouth,
but you gotta admit,
it's beautiful.
Just wanted you to
see it for yourself.
[SUISO] You were only following
orders from the higher‐ups.
In no way was it your fault.
[SUISO] Actually,
I was the one in the wrong.
[SUISO] I shouldn't have
treated you like a person.
Gotta remember, you're strictly
a tool, and nothing more.
Isn't that right...
...partner?
‐‐[TETSURO] Juzo?
‐‐[gasps]
[TETSURO]
Something the matter?
If you're sick, I can call Mary.
I'll be right back!
[JUZO]
No.
Nothing's wrong.
Except I can't even take
a nap around here in peace.
[JUZO]
Stop looking at me like that.
I'm not in any pain.
That isn't true!
[JUZO] How're your
wounds? They serious?
I'm fine, really.
[JUZO]
Mary sounded pretty worried.
They're just burns.
At least we think so.
[JUZO] Sounds like you're
not sure how you got them.
Mary's calling what
happened resonance.
If Harmony gets
pushed to its limits,
then I end up
taking the same damage
as the Extended I'm controlling.
[JUZO]
You used it again, huh?
[gasps]
[JUZO]
Thanks for the hand.
[TETSURO]
Juzo...
I'm sorry.
[JUZO] You've got
no reason to apologize.
[TETSURO] It's my fault.
Everything that's happened.
I'm the reason you're
all in so much danger!
The reason you lost your arm!
‐‐[JUZO] Don't start‐‐
‐‐[TETSURO] I know the ones
who were here last night
were from Beruhren!
They were targeting me again!
[JUZO]
You're wrong.
It's me they wanted.
Only thing is...
[JUZO]
...I have no idea why.
[TETSURO]
Don't you see?
This never would've happened
if I didn't come here
in the first place!
And all those kids!
[TETSURO]
If only I was stronger,
things would have
turned out differently!
I could have saved Colt!
[TETSURO]
It's my fault.
I have Harmony,
but what good is it?
[TETSURO] In the end... I wasn't
able to help anyone. [cries]
[JUZO]
I see.
[MARY]
Hey, Juzo!
You around?
Oh, there you are.
Y'know, next time you
could answer me when I call.
Brought up a customer
that wants to talk.
[JUZO]
Customer?
Right this way, sir.
Apologies for the mess.
Nice to meet you.
You're Mr. Juzo Inui, I presume?
[JUZO]
Yeah?
[DANNY]
This is quite sudden,
but I'd like you to
watch over a young lady.
She's being haunted
by an Extended.
[JUZO]
Come again?
[MARY]
Oh, yeah. I could get used to
being chauffeured around
in a convertible!
[JUZO] Strange. I don't
remember inviting you along.
Who's going to watch over‐‐
It's been handled.
[JUZO]
Hm?
The boy won't get
into any trouble.
EMS is keeping an eye
on him, and besides,
it's not as if Beruhren can
afford to make a careless move.
If all else fails, no worries.
The door is rigged to
release a high‐voltage current
if anyone tries to open it.
[gasps] You could've
let me know!
How long ago did you
install that thing?
I wasn't going to stay behind
even if you asked me nicely.
It's my fault we couldn't
salvage your left arm.
So I'm coming as your
personal engineer, got it?
[JUZO]
Uhh...
[MARY]
Not to mention,
I'm dying to get a close‐up
look at this Extended ghost!
I hope they died a long time ago
and they're an older model I've
never seen before! [giggles]
[JUZO]
There's the real reason.
I welcome you, Mr. Inui...
...to the McMahon mansion.
[MARY]
Oh, ho, ho. I could live here.
[doors closing]
[DANNY] If you wouldn't
mind following me.
[ROSA]
Even for the sake of survival...
[MARY] You're talking
about the Extended ghost?
[JUZO]
I'm not a priest.
[ROSA]
No! Let me go!
[DANNY] You mean your
father didn't tell you?
[JUZO]
No Guns Life Episode Twelve:
"Specter."