[NARUTAKI] You've done well to
make it as far as you have.
You've learned
everything I have to teach.
There's nothing left.
[NARUTAKI] I'm going to have to
transfer you to a new school.
You will bide your time there,
waiting until the opportunity
comes to put your skills to use.
[TATSUMA]
Where will I be going?
Magami High School.
[lightening bolts strike]
[distant construction noises]
[jackhammer whirring]
[KISARAGI] I don't know what
hole you just crawled out of...
...but you've got no
business being in this world.
[panting]
[GIRL] Good morning, Aoi!
How are you today?
[AOI]
Good.
Thanks!
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
Good to see you, Aoi.
[AOI]
Good to see you.
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[AOI] Morning, Komaki! Archery
practice is already over?
[KOMAKI]
See, the thing is I didn't
get to have
breakfast this morning,
and since I'm the captain,
I cut out early.
[girls giggle]
[KYOICHI] "Well, good morning,
m'lady!" Yeah, right.
Stupid.
[KOMAKI]
Those guys never learn, do they?
I mean, there's no way
you'll be able to respond
to all these
love letters...
Hey, Komaki!
Oh yeah,
Isn't there a...
a new transfer student today?
[AOI]
Oh, yeah...
[STUDENT]
Nice shot.
[KOMAKI] It's gotta be tough
transferring high schools
at the end of your senior year.
So what do you think?
Is it gonna be a guy or a girl?
[AOI] I...don't know,
I haven't heard anything yet.
[students chattering]
I'm heading out.
I'll see you later.
[gentle breeze]
[groans]
Hmm?
Tch!
[birds chirping]
[water fountain cascading]
[GUY]
Are you for real?
[GIRL]
Yeah, totally serious!
I hear that he's super fine.
Quick, how do I look?
[GUY]
What, you mean it's a dude?
[GIRL] They say
he's from the Asuka Academy.
Don't you know
anything about him?
[GUY]
No, but I don't care.
[GIRL] Well. I can't
wait to see what he's like.
[students chattering]
[footsteps echoing]
[door slides open and close]
[MARIA]
Good morning! Everyone.
Be quiet!!
[MAIA] Now, I realize
it's just about
the end of your
high school careers,
but, nevertheless,
we've got a new student.
He's going to be joining
you in all your studies
from here on out, so try
to make him f-- Sit down!
[AOI]
Kyoichi, don't...
[KYOICHI] Maria, sweetie,
I got a stomach ache,
so I'm just gonna head home.
Now, you listen here!
Oh!
Ugh!
[MARIA]
Misato, wait!
Ugh, high school kids!
Tanonaka.
[TANONAKA]
Here.
Chiyama.
[CHIYAMA]
Present.
Tsunoda.
[TSUNODA]
Yo.
[TONO]
Something's going down!
[INUGAMI]
Ono.
Is Ono here?
Absent...
What, you finally
get tired of running away?
This place is better.
We're not going to
trouble anyone out here.
I don't like you.
Sakurai.
You heard about it, too?
Yeah.
I got a bad
feeling about this...
[gasps]
Kyoichi Horaiji.
Tatsuma Hiyu.
What was all that about?
Hello, scoop...
[birds caw]
Excellent work.
Yeah.
[INUGAMI] Word gets around,
you know...
[KYOICHI] Yeah, I know,
it looks a little shady
but in my humble
opinion--dirtier the bowl,
the better the noodle.
At least,
that's what I always say.
Dude.
You gotta be more subtle
when you check them out...
[TATSUMA]
That girl...
Hunh!
[grunting]
[slurps]
Well?
Pretty awesome, huh?
Humm.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh.
Just listening to the music...
Huh? Well, that stuff isn't
exactly my cup of tea...
[KYOICHI] Shit!
She writes whatever
she damn well pleases...
Son-of-a-bitch.
Oh.
I guess she can't be a
son-of-a-bitch if she's a girl.
Whatever! That son-of-a-bitch...
I'm gonna make her pay for this!
[wind whistling]
[AOI]
Tatsuma Hiyu?
Huh?
[TATSUMA] Oh, you're the class
president, aren't you, um...
I'm Aoi Misato.
[TATSUMA]
That's right.
Hi, Misato.
[KYOICHI] What can we commoners
do for you, madame president?
Ms. Alucard wanted me to make
sure to show him around campus.
I also wanted to
check if everything's okay.
I'd like to make this
transition as easy as possible.
My, but how kind of you!
Why, you...
Komaki.
Thanks for your concern.
But I'm fine, really.
[AOI]
I see. All right.
[AOI] Oh.
One more thing...
[KOMAKI]
Aoi.
[AOI] There've been a
lot of terrible things
happening around here lately
so Ms. Alucard wanted me
to tell you to be very careful.
[TATSUMA]
Terrible things?
[AOI]
Yes.
Some students
have gone missing, and...
and there have been
a couple of murders.
You can see the
number of victims going up
and up every
time you watch the news.
Every day there seem to be
two or three new deaths...
Are you okay?
It is weird, huh?
It's terrible...
Tch.
[KYOCHI] Stop whining
and do something.
Your family's pretty loaded.
Why don't you go ask them
if they can buy a solution
to this problem, princess.
At the end of the day,
it's all the same.
There's no noticeable
difference between people
and animals, anyhow.
There's nothing remotely
"unusual" about any of this.
They kill, devour, rape...
Shut the hell up.
[KYOICHI] But none of that's
anything that a little princess
who lives in a great big
mansion would know about, is it?
[KOMAKI]
Aoi.
[KYOICHI]
What are you lookin' at?
[TATSUMA]
Oh, nothing...
[MARIA VIA INTERCOM]
Mr. Inugami.
Mr. Inugami, wherever you are,
please report
to the teacher's lounge.
I know you just
love making us wait,
but get your ass in here!
[REPORTER] In other news,
it has been reported that
a priceless work of art
was carried off in the
aftermath of an explosion that
occurred yesterday morning on
the Tokyo-Nagoya Expressway.
It is believed the work in
question is one of a collection
that are known as the
"ten sacred treasures".
Some believe the
accident itself may have been
a smokescreen to facilitate
the theft of the item...
[clock tower strikes]
[giggles]
[KYOICHI] Damn!
Transfer Student
turns out to be a ladies' man.
Hey, you mind if I
take a look at your mail?
[KYOICHI]
Hmm?
[KYOICHI] Wha-What's up
with that? Crazy...
Anyway, you up for
some ramen? My treat.
[KISARAGI] The item the
master requested has arrived.
What would you like me
to do with it?
Miss Misato?
[AOI]
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I honestly don't know
what I'm gonna do with Daddy.
Always ordering
new things although
he hardly ever comes home...
What did he send us this time?
[keyboard clicking]
[YANG]
Hey there, boss!
Huh?
[KYOICHI] Well,
if it isn't Old Man Yang!
[YANG] I appreciated
your help the other day.
[KYOICHI] You're not makin'
trouble again, are you?
Aw, c'mon, can't ya
have a little faith in me?
[KYOICHI]
Well, see ya later.
[YANG]
Yeah, later.
Now, you take care, boss!
[FAN] I think we got it
cleaned up, master.
[YANG]
Right. Just keep at it.
[WANG] What do you think
the boss would do to us
if he saw what the inside of
this place looks like right now?
[YANG] He'd beat the
living daylights out of us.
And then our miserable
souls would wander around
in Limbo for eternity,
'cause there ain't no way they'd
let guys like us into heaven.
[WANG]
Man, that'd suck...
[FAN] All I want is
to just die in my sleep.
[Yang cackles]
[KYOICHI]
What's up?
Why, if it isn't Kyoach.
Don't call me that!
[COOK] Sit down
and order, would ya?
Tatsuma Hiyu.
What the hell are
you doin' here, meathead?
[AOI]
A showdown?
[KOMAKI VIA PHONE]
A guy from the Wrestling Club
was telling me that Daigo said
he was going to fight the
transfer student.
[AOI]
But, do you know where?
[KOMAKI VIA PHONE]
At the old school building.
Guys are so stupid, aren't they?
I mean, what's this gonna prove?
Hey, are you still there? Aoi?
[YUUYA] This old
building's been around
since before the War. But
nobody's used it for years.
[KYOICHI] In other words:
no one's gonna bother us.
[YUUYA] Hey.
Who invited you along, anyway?
[KYOICHI] C'mon, you wrestling
guys like it when people watch.
I'll be the ref.
How come it's so
bright in here, anyway?
I told the Drama Club
I'd get them lunch
if I could use
their lights tonight.
[KYOICHI]
That's not what I was asking...
What the hell does it matter?!
[Kyoichi chuckling]
[KYOICHI] You've plastered
talismans all over the walls
like they're a bunch of
centerfolds, Daigo.
What, are you scared that
we're gonna see a ghost?
[YUUYA] We won't!
I say there'll be no ghosts!
No ghosts.
[YUUYA]
Now, let's go.
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[panting]
[YUUYA]
C'mon! C'mon!
What's wrong?
'Fraid to fight me? Come on.
Let's go!
[growls]
[strained groaning]
This is gonna be interesting.
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
[AOI]
Stop it, you guys!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi?
[YUUYA]
Sakurai, what are you--
[TATSUMA]
Misato?
[KYOICHI] Jeesh, she's the
nosiest girl on the planet.
[AOI] I'm sorry,
but you can't do this.
You need a teacher's permission
to even be on this property.
[KYOICHI] What? That's what
you're worried about?
[AOI] At any rate,
we need to get out of here.
I'll help you
guys clean up, okay?
No! Don't come in!
[rumbling]
[cracking]
It's here.
[lightbulbs shatter]
[scream]
[KOMAKI]
Aoi?
The talismans!
Hey.
Don't worry, Sakurai,
I'll keep you safe.
You can always depend on me!
[YUUYA]
Wha?
What the hell's going on here?
[AOI]
Hey, wait!
Wha--?
[GIRL] Good morning, Aoi!
How are you today?
[AOI]
Good thanks.
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
Good to see you, Aoi!
[AOI]
Good to see you!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[TATSUMA]
Who are you?
What is this?
[KYOICHI]
Have you snapped out of it?
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi!
I dunno
what's going on here
but things are
about to get interesting.
[TATSUMA]
Misato, wake up!
Komaki!
Yeah, are you?
[otherworldly groans]
[scream]
[heartbeats]
[otherworldly shriek]
[pained groan]
[AOI]
Tatsuma!
[screams]
[KOMAKI]
No!
[prolonged screaming]
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi!
[screams]
[growling]
[AOI]
Tatsuma!
[Komaki groaning in pain]
[otherworldly growl]
I got her!
Yeah, but she's--
[screams]
Komaki!
[Aoi whimpering]
[Aoi screaming]
What on earth is
the meaning of this?
Hisui, how did you...?
[KISARAGI] So it undid
the seals on its own? No.
That sensation I had earlier...
It couldn't be.
Could they have
summoned this thing?
[otherworldly roaring]
Four heretic
demons block our path
towards achieving
the way of Buddha.
[Ghost screeching]
So we must
equally unite them
the Buddhist and
the realm of demons...
[KISARAGI]
Now!
[roof bursts]
[Ghost wails]
So, is it...is it over?
[TATSUMA] Can you tell me
what just happened here?
[gentle breeze]