The time for revenge
has arrived.
[engine noise]
[CLAIRE gasps]
[cat squeals]
[CLAIRE]
Hello, Lord Yagyu.
[YAGYU]
So, what's he up to?
[CLAIRE]
He has control of some girl
who's supposed to have the
Bodhisattva Eye or something.
He's making some
kind of plan...
[YAGYU]
Let him do as he likes.
[CLAIRE]
Huh? Are you sure about that?
It'll be worth watching...
to see how the Vessel reacts...
It's quiet lately.
Sure is. Nothin' at all
going on around here.
But... no news is
good news, right?
Yeah, well, it's
making me nervous.
[RYUTA] Huh?
[INUGAMI] Repeating the same
things all over again, huh?
Some people just don't learn;
that much seems obvious...
[AZUMABASHI] So do ya think
that guy is gonna be all right?
Yeah, Tatsuma's not gonna
bite the dust without a fight.
Thanks for your help tonight.
Yeah, well, don't be a stranger,
boss, call me anytime!
All right. See ya around!
So it looks
like you're back
with your batteries
fully charged.
That stunt you pulled
back there by the shrine
must've been
pretty impressive.
If that was any indication,
you and your buddies
seem to be better at
using your powers, too.
So tell me, what the hell
are you doing back here?
It's almost like
you're not grateful
that I saved your
asses out there.
Don't you worry. I got
no business with you.
I just figured that
if I followed you around
long enough I'd be
able to find him.
"Him" who?
[MAIKO]
Oh! Oh, Houraiji! Oh.
[KYOUICHI] Hey.
[MAIKO] Hello.
[KYOUICHI]
How's Tatsuma doing?
The Doctor's examining
him as we speak.
But it looks good. She says he's
not in any immediate danger.
[ANKO] Here.
How are you doing?
Oh, I'm fine, thanks.
Shouldn't you be getting
home soon? It's kinda late.
I'm worried too,
so I'd like to stay.
Huh?
Heh. So what's
the story, old bag?
Call me that again and it's
the last thing you'll ever say.
Is he gonna be all right?
[IWAYAMA] I'm pretty
impressed, actually.
Any one of these injuries
would have been fatal
if he hadn't just barely
dodged each of them.
You know, you've
always been lacking
in the brains department,
but you sure do have a knack
for finding guys like this
to have as your friend...
Hmph.
Could it be some
primal instinct at work?
Shut it.
[YUKINO]
What a relief!
[HINANO] Yes.
So what's going on?
What were the two of you
doing there in
the first place?
I'm not sure how we
can answer that...
Uh... How can I put this...?
[RYUZAN] Perhaps you
could allow me to explain.
Master? What is this?
[KISARAGI] Old Man
White Moth... Master Ryuzan!
Huh?
Young Kisaragi. It has
been a very long time.
And Iwayama, you seem
as well as ever.
I don't need your flattery.
[RYUZAN chuckles]
Kisaragi... and Dr. Iwayama?
You mean you guys knew
each other all along?
Aw, just cut to the chase!
[KYOUICHI]
I really hate mysteries.
So, you gonna spit it out
or what... gramps?
[barks]
[RYUZAN] There is an individual
known as the "Bodhisattva Eye."
[ANKO]
Bodhisattva Eye?
[RYUZAN] This person has the
power to read the Dragon Stream
and thereby select the
chosen from all humanity
and lead them to salvation.
However, this person is
also a source of conflict
precisely because they may use
the power of the Dragon Stream.
If one could manipulate
the Dragon Stream at will,
then bringing the world
under your control
would be no great effort.
Since the beginning of time,
those in positions of power
have waged countless
battles over the use
of the Bodhisattva Eye.
If the past is any indicator,
it would be most irresponsible
and unwise not to prepare
ourselves for any eventuality.
[KOMAKI] So what
are you trying to say?
[RYUZA] It is said that the one
who holds the Bodhisattva Eye
also holds a certain
amount of power.
[YUUYA]
What kind of power?
[RYUZA] To rejuvenate the
power of life, so to speak.
The ultimate
power of healing.
[KOMAKI gasps]
It can't be!
Aoi... Aoi's the
Bodhisattva Eye?
[IWAYAMA] The healing powers
of the Bodhisattva Eye
are on an entirely
different level from my own.
Not only can
they heal injuries,
but they can even
restore the dead to life.
On the other hand, they can
instantly advance the age
of a person, older and older,
until that person dies.
[RYUZAN] The Eight-Hands-Breadth
Sword that they stole
is an instrument that
greatly intensifies
the Bodhisattva Eye's powers.
It is one of a collection
that together are called
the ten sacred treasures.
"The ten sacred treasures"?
[YUUYA] If it's only one
of ten, then that means...
[RYUYA] Our enemy has already
obtained the other nine.
On one occasion, we were able
to track him down. However...
[KYOUICHI] Huh. You were no
match for him, huh, gramps?
[YUUYA] Kyouichi!
[RYUZA] Heh. It's quite all
right. He speaks the truth.
The Bodhisattva Eye
only appears
when the Dragon Stream
has been disrupted.
[KOMAKI] So, wait a sec.
If Tendo Kozunu was causing
all those demon attacks
to disrupt the
Dragon Stream...
[gasps] Then...
[KYOUICHI] Right. He only
did it so he could wake up
the Bodhisattva Eye in Aoi.
[KOMAKI] Does Aoi know
what's happening to her?
[KYOUICHI] Good question.
Why don't you answer
that one for her,
Doom 'n Gloom? Asshole...
[KOMAKI]
What is this?
You told her...
You told Aoi, didn't you?
You idiot! If you told her
about something like that,
you know she would... Why?!
Why would you tell her?!
And that wasn't all
you did either, was it?
[KOMAKI] Tell the truth.
Tell me what the hell
you did to Aoi!
I tried to kill her.
[KOMAKI gasps]
[KISARAGI]
The Bodhisattva Eye...
The one with the power
of the Bodhisattva Eye
will bring doom
upon this world.
With that being the case,
I sought to kill her
before she...
[KOMAKI shudders]
[KOMAKI]
You son of a--!
[slap]
[KOMAKI grunts]
[KOMAKI grunts repeatedly]
[KOMAKI shudders]
[approaching footsteps]
[YUUYA]
Sakurai, no!
Stop it! Please stop fighting!
My God! How could you
even consider that?!
Why would anybody
have to kill Aoi?
It just doesn't make sense!
[KOMAKI]
It's not her fault she was
born with that stupid power.
It's not her fault that
those demons appeared!
Aoi always said that we should
try to protect people...
She said we should
do everything we could.
At first I wondered why she was
saying all that stuff to us...
Why she thought we could prevent
people from getting hurt...
All along, she still...
[KOMAKI] I'm wasting
my breath. Someone like you
could never be half as
courageous as Aoi is!
[KOMAKI cries]
[KYOUICHI] Komaki...
I think that's enough.
[RYUZAN] Kisaragi...
Those were your grandfather's
instructions, weren't they?
[KISARAGI] Yes.
Just like you, Kisaragi,
I and the Oribe sisters here
are the last in a long
line of ancestors
who have defended this land
of Edo, this city of Tokyo,
[RYUZAN] from evil forces
down through the ages.
We each have our own missions,
and it is the mission
of the Kisaragi to kill
the Bodhisattva Eye.
[KOMAKI]
But... what about Aoi?
[indistinct murmuring]
[TENDO]
That's a good girl.
[TENDO laughs]
You know, I love your eyes.
[CLAIRE] Hm. So you
can talk to girls
as long as it's
one of your toys.
For a puppet on someone
else's strings,
you've sure got a point
of view. Have you finished
running errands
for your master?
You're not fit to
breathe the same air!
[TENDO] You think so, hm?
Hmph. Well, no matter.
It's time to go, my dear Aoi.
Kisaragi, I will tell
you all the account
of how this strife began.
I'll tell you all.
Everything I know...
[child's voice]
Mother! M-Mother! M-Mother!
[RYUZAN] The house of
Kozunu launched a coup
against the ruling parties.
The reason was that
the shogunate attempted to
kidnap one of their daughters,
who had been born with the
power of the Bodhisattva Eye.
In order to protect the girl,
the Kozunu made use
of the Dark Arts
and used force
to rebel against the might
of the Shogunate.
[ANKO]
So that means...
[YUUYA] It means the
Shogunate are the ones
who started the whole thing.
[YUKINO]
And we're continuing...
[HINANO] Why did we never
know this before, Master Arai?
[KYOUICHI]
That's how war is.
There's no "good" fighting
or "bad" fighting.
Even that fight was
just a struggle for power
when you come down to it.
So, Kisaragi...
What's up? You still
gonna kill Aoi over this?
[RYUZAN] That fight
ended in a bloody defeat
for the Kozunu family.
Decades later,
their descendants
again raised an army
during the Bakumatsu reign,
but once again
they were defeated.
Since that time, the Kozunu
have hidden their lineage,
and lived in the shadows of
history, unbeknownst to anyone.
I don't know how
they managed to do it,
but they escaped
their pursuers,
and continued to
evade people like us
after the Meiji
Restoration as well.
All I know for certain
is that the man who calls
himself Tendo Kozunu
must have lived
quite a life indeed.
[MAN A] I don't believe
you're a Kozunu!
[WOMAN A]
You concealed your identity
so you could sneak
into our family!
[WOMAN B] And then you
gave birth to a child!
How utterly disgusting!
[door locks]
[CHILD] Mother!
This is for you, Mother.
[TATSUMA] I think I...
can kind of understand...
[KYOUICHI] Tatsuma!
[YUUYA] Hiyu!
[KOMAKI]
Hey, Tatsuma!
[ANKO]
Oh! Tatsuma!
You idiot. Goin' overboard,
don'tcha think?
Sorry.
[ANKO] How are you feeling?
Are you... still in pain?
[TATSUMA]
Nah. Thanks for asking.
He was trying...
to look inside my mind
and see all
of my memories.
"He"? You mean Kozunu?
[TATSUMA] But instead
I felt what he felt...
A deep, intense
sadness inside him.
I want to save him, too.
I want to save the soul
of Tendo Kozunu.
[RAITO]
Don't give me that shit!
Save him? What a joke.
That son of a bitch! He's the
only one I wanna see suffer!
Like I told you before,
we fight to protect,
not to punish.
[ANKO] But look at what
he did to Sayo Hirasaka.
[KOMAKI] She's right.
I couldn't save
somebody like him.
Not ever.
[TATSUMA] Aoi also
wanted to protect...
This is what she wants, too.
I've never been
more sure of that.
Hiyu?
Man, you are such a dumbass.
I'm sorry you
think so, but I still...
Okay, I give!
Huh?
Like the old bag said,
I'm not the brightest bulb
in the toolbox. So I guess
we make a pretty good team.
Kyouichi!
Aww. Primal instinct,
like I said...
[IWAYAMA and MAIKO laugh]
[KYOUICHI] So what's that
freak trying to do now?
[RYUZAN]
Well, most likely...
[CLAIRE]
Hey, what are ya doin'?
[TENDO] This very ground is
where my ancestors are buried.
[CLAIRE]
Huh?
[TENDO] My forebears who were
defeated by the Shogunate
committed suicide here.
Members of the Kozunu line
have continued to
sleep here ever since,
never having been granted a
proper burial anywhere else...
[CLAIRE]
What are you talking about?
And now I will
resurrect that bloodline--
the bloodline of my
poor, ruined family!
I'll make everything right...
What's that?
What the hell
was that?
Did you hear something, too?
H-Heard what?
[TENDO] Come now to those
who serve and venerate you
at this shrine; we implore you,
hasten, heal our ills.
Mirror of the Deep,
Mirror of the Shore,
Eight-Hands-Breadth Sword,
Jewel of Life,
Jewel of Perfection,
Jewel of Resurrection,
Jewel of Warding,
Serpent-Repelling Scarf,
Wasp-Repelling Scarf, Scarf of
Multifarious Protection...
Is he bringing back
the Kozunu clan?!
Poor Aoi!
[indistinct murmurs]
[AOI whimpers]
[AOI screaming]
[screams]
Looks like it's already started.
You don't have
a moment to lose;
you've got to
go bring Aoi back.
Easy for you to say.
Where the hell is she, huh?
Well, master?
[RYUZAN] Hmm...
[MAIKO]
Doctor Iwayama!
I can hear her... I can hear
Aoi crying out for help.
Sagaya. You're so
full of it...
I think I can trace
the path of Aoi's mind
to find out where she is.
I'll go too. He mustn't
travel alone.
[IWAYAMA] Don't push
yourself too hard.
[SAGAYA]
Aoi saved my life.
It's time for me
to return the favor.
[MAIKO]
Sure. Now let's go get her.
I wasn't able to protect
you in the end. But I...
[KYOUICHI] Whaddaya gonna do?
Still planning on killing her?
Those were my instructions.
Huh. Your instructions, huh?
Well, if that's what
you're gonna do,
I'm not gonna
waste my breath.
But I'm the one you'll
be facing off against.
[KYOUICHI] I'll protect her,
you'll see.
I'm still going to destroy him.
I promise you that.
I'm not going to let you.
Master, what is this?
The demons.
It seems the demons are out
taking a little stroll tonight.
[KOMAKI]
Anko, this isn't the time!
[ANKO] You'll tell me
everything that happened?
[KOMAKI] Hm?
Promise me, okay, you guys?
That you'll all come back here
and you'll tell me
the whole story!
Sure, Anko.
[AZUMABASHI]
Heya, Boss!
H-Hey! What're you--?
Sorry we're late! I brought
the whole gang with me.
All that's left for us
is to just sit and wait.
Seems to me the kids have
everything under control.
I suppose that, too,
is our star of fate.
[KYOUICHI] Heh. This is
gonna be one hell of a party.
So make sure you're ready
to fight. Now let's roll!