[sighs]
[Woman screams]
[MOTHER]
Takeo! It's dinner time!
[desperate gasping]
[animalistic growl]
[scrapes]
[RAITO] If it's our fate,
I'll see you again.
[KYOICHI]
When it was all over,
we still didn't have a
real good idea what happened,
and Lightening Head
just disappeared.
[YUUYA] Can someone
explain to me how a human
can turn into
one of those demons?
Is it possible
that the other demons
we've fought have
all been the same?
It's not. This one
wasn't like them at all.
It was a human with
a Power, who had been
intentionally transformed
into something else.
Who or whatever did
this to him knew exactly
what they were doing.
My guess is that they
cast a spell on him
that intensified his
malice and hatred.
[KYOICHI] A spell...
Is that what the Dark Arts
are supposed to be?
But who on earth
would do such a thing?
[gasps]
It's that guy.
[KISARAGI] At any rate,
this is not to say that anyone
with the Power is going
transform into a demon.
It's more than likely that
the spell only works on people
who have darkness
in their hearts.
[YUUYA]
Darkness in their hearts, huh?
Is there anybody on
the planet who doesn't
fit that description?
But still... This is our
fight! So we have to win it.
We can't give up now.
And more importantly, we can't
forget our obligation to
protect the innocent
people that this creature
is preying upon
every single day.
[Girl in fire screaming]
[GIRL IN FIRE] Help me, Aoi!
Please! Help me! Aoi!
I want to save them all,
I want to save every person
I can.
Even the souls of
those who have become
those horrible demons.
I have to try.
I won't give up.
I'm going to fight.
[KYOICHI]
Madam President got my vote.
[KOMAKI]
Count me out.
Are all of you people out of
your freakin' minds or what?
You saw what that
thing was capable of!
This isn't a game. You guys are
gonna be fighting for real!
Don't you understand that?
C'mon, Aoi. If a demon has a
chance, it's going to kill you.
[KOMAKI] Let's stop playing
superhero and be normal again.
Can't we please just go back to
being high school students?
W'e've been waiting for the
summer break for a long time.
Remember how we talked
about hanging out by the pool
or the beach all summer long?
[AOI] Komaki... I understand
what you're saying, but this
"thing" has already started
whether we like it or not.
We're the only ones who
can do anything about it.
[KOMAKI] Of course, you're
always such a good Samaritan!
Is saving a bunch of strangers
really that important to you?
You don't even have the power to
do it all by yourself!
[KOMAKI] Tono's not the only one
having a rough time with this.
I... I can't handle all this.
It's too much! I hate you, Aoi!
[YUUYA]
Wait!
[light rainfall]
She'll be alright.
Komaki will understand.
[TATSUMA] So Anko's still locked
herself up in her house?
[DETECTIVE] The witnesses all
confirmed she said something.
Before she collapsed, they heard
her repeating the word 'dog.'
Think that she
could have dreamt it?
[MIKURIYA] She said 'dog' huh?
Sure have been a lot of strange
incidents occuring lately...
[STUDENT LEANING]
Hey, did you hear what happened?
[STUDENT WITH TIE]
Yeah... It got Takeo, too.
[STUDENT LEANING] Yeah. Guess
the curse is real after all.
Man, I'm in deep shit.
[NEWSCASTER]
And now in the news...
There have been a
series of bizarre incidents
throughout the
metropolitan area, in which
high school students have
collapsed into comatose states.
As of now, the police are not
ruling out any possibilities
while they continue
their investigation,
but there are still
many unanswered questions.
[KOMAKI]
Damn it...
[TALL ARCHER] Hey. Looks
like Sakurai's totally lost
her touch today!
[SHORT HAIRED ARCHER] Maybe
something happened to her
over vacation?
[BRUNETTE ARCHER] Do you think
she had a fight with Misato?
[TALL ARCHER]
Yeah, a lovers' quarrel.
[grunting]
[KYOICHI] For cryin' out loud,
it's summer vacation!
What's do you need to practice
your club stuff for?
I swear, I'll never understand
how you muscle-heads think.
Okay, what are you doing here?
Did you want something?
[KYOICHI] Have you been thinking
about what Kisaragi said
the other day?
You know, "darkness in their
hearts" stuff...
I'm sure you don't have
anything to worry about.
[KISARAGI] Mejiro,
Meao, Meguro, Meaka, Meki...
Five small Buddhist
shrines which try to seal
the demons away...
Lady Misato...
[ANKO'S MOM] I apologize,
but Kyoko says she doesn't
want to see you today.
[AOI]
I understand.
[cat meows]
[MAIKO] You like that,
little fella?
So it looks like somebody's
finally adopted you, huh?
What a lucky kitty.
[cat hisses]
[meows]
Is that...?
[barks]
[SAGAYA]
Aoi...
Now this is much more
interesting.
[ANKO'S MOM] Kyoko! She
keeps coming by every day
to say hi, the least
you can do is see her!
I'm sorry for the
way she's been acting.
[AOI] It's me, Anko. It's Aoi.
Look, I'm really sorry about
everything that
happened the other day.
I can understand what
you saw must've been really
frightening for you.
But, uh, don't worry
about all that stuff, okay?
Y'know, like Tatsuma
and Kyoichi flying around.
That's really no big
deal, see, there's a perfectly
reasonable explanation...
And you know Yuuya and Komaki
are normal people just like
you, they're like...
they're... so not normal...
Look. We won't put you through
anything like that again.
We'll do our best to
protect you no matter what,
so don't worry.
Don't worry, okay?
[AOI] The pool opens
tomorrow, and everyone's
looking forward to it since
we haven't seen each other
in a while, so... So
make sure you come, too, okay?
By the way, do you remember...
How you were on
Minami Middle Shool's
newspaper, and I went to
Kagura Middle School
and you interviewed me
for an article?
I was so excited about it!
Up until then, people
just saw me as an honor student.
That was all anyone
seemed to know about me,
and I felt so much pressure.
It was suffocating. But your
article really changed things
for me, and I've wanted
to be friends with you
ever since.
I mean that.
[crickets chirping]
[KISARAGI]
This one too... huh?
[phone ringing]
[AOI]
Hello, Misato residence.
Hisui?
[KISARAGI] I've got some
business I need to take care of.
It may be a while before
I'm able to contact you again.
Have there been
any new developments?
Uh, not, not really.
You don't sound like you're
in your shop now, Hisui.
[KISARAGI] There's a certain
rare vase I'm looking for,
so I'm making the rounds
at the area's antiques shops.
Another one of those requests
from Dad, huh?
Well, good luck finding it.
And you take care.
[SAGAYA]
Aoi.
[crowd cheering]
[KYOICHI] Hey. You're lookin'
kinda bummed today.
[TATSUMA]
Morning.
[KOMAKI] Listen, you two.
I'm sorry about before.
[TATSUMA] It's no big deal.
But I think...
[GIRL] Hey,
long time no see!
[GIRL'S FRIEND] Yeah! You go
anywhere over summer break?
[GIRL]
Is something wrong?
[MARIA] Speak, Spoke,
Speaking, Have spoken, Spoken,
Had spoken.
[KYOICHI] I can't believe we've
gotta take this summer school
on a nice day like this!
This sucks. What are you doing
in here, anyway, Tatsuma?
I am the teacher.
You are the student.
Do they even know how
lucky they are? It's not fair!
How come only the girls are
allowed to go swimmin' today?
I wanna go swimmin' too!
[MARIA]
I don't get it, Mr. Hiyu.
When we tested
you for placement here,
it looked like you should
be in the top of your class,
so what happened?
[light laugh]
[binder smack]
[TATSUMA]
Ow, that hurt.
Hey, guys,
check it out! Over there.
[HANNABATA]
Look, Captain, it's Sakurai.
[GIRL] Stop starin'
at us, ya pervert!
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
Dirty old man!
[girls chattering]
[AOI]
Hey, Anko!
Good to see you!
You'd rather be with her.
Is that it?
[KOMAKI] Answer me!
Who's more important to you,
me or Tono, huh?
[AOI]
Komaki...
[KOMAKI]
Aoi?
[SAGAYA] Hello, Aoi.
It's good to see you again.
[SAGAYA] Come.
Come with me.
Wha--?
Huh?
[MARIA]
Hey, get bac...
You are so gonna
fail this class!
[KOMAKI] Aoi... Aoi! What is it?
What's going on?! Aoi! Aoi!
What's wrong with her?
[KOMAKI]
Snap out of it!
--Somebody call an ambulance!
--What's wrong with you, Aoi?!
I might have guessed...
Hey. Horaiji.
Take her to Sakura-ga-o-ka
Central Hospital.
I'll take full responsibility.
What?! But that place...
Hey, how did you know
we needed your
help here, anyway?
This is no time to
stand around arguing, Horaiji!
We have to do something
to help her right now!
Quick, show us
where to take her.
Right...
Is she okay?!
[TATSUMA] You know I don't get a
good feeling from this place...
So figured it out, huh? See,
that's why I like you, Tatsuma.
What? Is there something
wrong with this place?
It just looks like
an ordinary hospital...
[KYOICHI] Personally,
I'd rather be anywhere
in the world but here.
That's cause
there's someone here
that I'm no
match for, period.
Hello!
There aren't even any patients
here, let alone doctors...
This place isn't
gonna stay open long!
[reverberating stomps]
What's that...
that sound?
[KYOICHI]
Here she comes.
[stomps increase in frequency]
Long time no see, Kyoichi?
I guess.
I heard from Inugami
a little while ago.
He let me know
you'd be stopping by.
[uneasy laugh]
Welcome everyone!
[MAIKO]
It's that girl!
Hey, Tendo. You look
like you're having fun?
[TENDO] Well, there's someone
I gave a new toy to, you see.
Now I'm curious to find out how
he's going to dance for us.
And this one, as well.