[baby crying]
[energy charges]
[screeching]
Who's there?
[helicopter blades whirring]
[footsteps]
[television gunshots]
[blows landing]
[panting]
[fighting]
[zombies groaning]
[intense growl]
[labored inhale]
[screeching]
[thud]
[bystanders gossiping]
[REPORTER] At the moment, no
detailed information has been
released, beyond the fact
that the victim was a student
from a high school in Tokyo...
[helicopter blades whirring]
[MIKURIYA] Just like you
asked for, here's one exactly
as it was found, no
autopsy done on it yet.
Too smokey in here...
[MIKURIYA] What are you talking
about, you're smoking, too.
Anyway... Why don't
you help me move her?
[RYUTA]
Not gonna happen.
[MIKURIYA]
Oh, that's nice.
What kind of an
attitude is that from
a guy who wants a favor?
[RYUTA] Just shut
up and do your job.
[MIKURIYA]
Yeah, yeah...
This one brings
the total to five, huh?
[RYUTA] That we were
able to find, at least.
Anyhow, every last
drop of water's been
sucked from her body.
[RYUTA]
Desiccated.
[MIKURIYA]
That's right.
Kind of a shame, still...
I mean, she was just
a high schooler, you know?
Seems like a waste...
Shut the
hell up and get to work.
[MIKURIYA]
I'm goin', I'm goin'...
Huh?
[cracks]
[MIKURIYA]
What in the hell's that?
I'll leave
her in your hands.
[MIKURIYA] Hey!
What the hell, man?
[PROFESSOR]
And today's lesson...
[shouting plays]
[INUGAMI]
What's the matter?
Don't you wanna
eat any of this?
They're organic.
[MARIA] "He, His, Him".
"You, Your, You".
So, over here
it's, like, all about you!
Putting that aside
for now, in this instance...
It depends on the indirect
object that follows and then--
you!
[awed classmates]
I got him again! Yes!
[chuckles]
[screaming]
[FOUR GREAT]
Get your ass out here!
[FOUR GREAT] Let's settle this
shit once and for all!
Not again.
The Four Great Ones from Sumida.
Those dipshits never learn...
Kyoichi?
Hey.
What about a little
coffee break huh?
I prefer strawberry milk.
Oh, great.
The juvenile
delinquent and the
narcoleptic transfer
student are bonding.
KYOICHI] Maria, sweetie,
I got a little fever.
I'm going home early.
[TATSUMA] Yeah,
I got a stomach ache.
You two listen to me...
Hey! Get back here!
[KYOICHI]
See ya later!
[laughter]
That boring class
was putting me to sleep.
But I'm awake now.
How dare you?!
[metallic rings clink]
[screams]
[splashing]
[maniacal laughter]
[onlookers cheer]
Here we go...
Those idiots!
Komaki?
Huh?
[drawers rattling]
Just as I thought...
It's too weak a link.
I can only assume I'm
overlooking some element.
[WANG]
How?
[YANG] More than
20 in two months.
The other gangs can't
figure it out either...
[FAN]
I don't know, man,
it couldn't possibly be
normal people doin' this stuff.
[YANG] It's not entirely
certain that they're people...
We oughta check with the
boss on this one before
we make any moves.
Huh?
[YANG] Have you two ever
heard of the "living dead"?
What do
you mean all of them?
[MIKURIYA ON PHONE]
I'm not kidding here!
I didn't even finish
my autopsy on that new girl,
before she runs off on me!
I mean, that's gotta
be against the rules!
Hey, you didn't know this
was going to happen, did you?
[RYUTA]
Shut up and do your job.
But all
the bodies are gone...
I'm gonna use this thing to
shove it right up your ass!
[FOUR GREAT] All right,
dickhead, let's play ball!
I guess
I've got no choice...
[light chuckle]
Hmm?
[FOUR GREAT]
Horaji...
You always make me look stupid
when we fight but this time,
I swear to God, it's not
gonna work! I'll kill y--
[crying in pain]
What the
heck are you doing?!
Is this a geology experiment?
If you must know, I was
on the trail of a scoop.
Whatever you're doing.
You have enthusiasm.
The mysterious transfer
student, Tatsuma Hiyu, hooks up
with resident delinquent Kyoichi
Horaiji and the two proceed to
cut class, get into brawls both
on and off campus, buy junk food
to eat on the way home,
and all of this adds up to a
record 26 offenses
in the past two months.
So you you think I'm
"mysterious", huh?
[KYOICHI]
Anko!
Holy shit, you're one persistent
little pest! I dunno if you call
it journalism or what, but in my
book I'd call what you're doing
just plain old-fashioned
spying, ya friggin' stalker!
You're like the pa- pa-
Paparazzi?
Yeah, that's right,
that's the word.
[KYOICHI]
Parapazzi!
It's "paparazzi."
I don't consider that an insult.
But why don't I cut to the
chase and ask what I've been
curious about: what have you
guys been up to at night lately?
I saw you with student
council president Aoi Misato,
the captain of the archery team,
Komaki Sakurai, and the captain
of the wrestling team,
Yuuya Daigo. That's kind of an
odd social circle,
don't you think? I mean,
I've never even seen you guys
talk to each other at school...
I smell a rat!
Listen here, little snitch!
I'd rather die than team up
with a bunch of candy-asses!
[TONO] Oh, would you now?
Man, do I ever smell a scoop!
[KYOICHI] I can't listen to
any more of this crap.
Tatsuma, let's get out of here!
[city traffic]
[crying]
[TATSUMA]
The living dead?
[KYOICHI] I'm telling you,
old man Yang used to know a
thing or two about Taoism.
You're kidding, right?
He happens to be the
leader of the notorious
"Three Wise Men"
of east Shinjuku.
It's always the quiet ones...
Well, it's a
complicated story...
...but now he's supposedly a
fine, upstanding citizen.
[KYOICHI] At least,
that's the story I heard.
And I've got a hunch he may
have a couple of ideas about why
we haven't been
getting any sleep lately.
Wang, Fan, They're here!
[zombies growl]
[screams]
[gunfire]
[FAN]
Oh, shit.
[fight noises]
[YANG]
Fuku Ju Ko Mu Ryo!
Damn it! I ain't gonna lose!
[YANG] Rin Pyo To Sha
Kai Jin Retsu Zen!
KO!
Wha--
Let's check it out.
[YANG]
Fan! Wang!
[ground breaking]
[shocked gasp]
It can't be! Is that you, Boss?
[zombies roaring]
It was that girl...
Yang! Wang! Fan!
[TATSUMA]
That was the girl.
[KYOICHI] You mean the
girl who washed up here?
Yeah.
[KYOICHI] Old man Yang said
he'd give us the rest of
the story when we
caught up with him.
[KISARAGI]
The living dead...
There is a certain kind
of evil spirit known as
a Fuishimon, which kills
its former friends and family.
If the giant creature you
saw is controlling them,
it may be a kind of Moryo devil.
[TATSUMA]
Mor-yo, huh?
[KISARAGI] They're spirits that
live in nature, it's said that
Moryo are devils
that prey upon corpses.
[YUUYA] So they just
ended up as zombie chow.
Those guys Kyoichi knew and
that girl from Houmei High.
What the hell are you saying?
Is that why we've been at this
hunt for two weeks and we're
still ending up nowhere? Huh?
[AOI]
Komaki.
[KISARAGI] That's because
we've been unable to determine
a common link among the victims.
[KYOICHI]
Jeez.
Old man Yang was way
more helpful than you are...
[KISARAGI] Don't compare me
to that renegade Taoist hermit!
What was that?!
[KISARAGI] Were you
not the one who said
it doesn't matter
who this thing kills?
[KYOICHI]
You lookin' for a fight?
[KISARAGI] You are
such a simpleton...
[YUUYA] Cut it out you two,
give it a rest.
The point is: anyone
that devil has taken is
coming back to life
and killing more people.
So that's what we're up against.
[YUUYA]
Right, Kisaragi?
That's the jist of it.
Maybe we should
concentrate on our similarities.
[AOI] We all want to protect the
city, no matter what it takes.
Thanks, Miss Student Council.
Was that a campaign speech?
Shut your trap!
[KYOICHI]
See, the thing is...
anybody can
make a pretty speech.
What are you gonna
be doing while we're
out there, busting
our asses fighting?
What other skills
do you have? Face it,
this just isn't where
you belong, princess.
You've only got the right to
talk all important-like after
you've actually
done some real work.
[KISARAGI]
Shut your insolent mouth!
How dare you speak
to her that way!
Don't worry about it, Hisui.
But he --
[AOI] It's all right.
Please. Continue.
[KISARAGI]
Right.
Here take a look at this.
I compiled a list of
everyone reported missing
and anyone who'd been on
intimate terms with the victims.
[KOMAKI]
Oh my God...
[AOI]
There are so many of them...
[KISARAGI] The next victim will
probably be from Homei High.
[KOMAKI] Yeah,
that'd be a pretty safe bet,
but we don't have any idea
who that person might be.
Right?
Yeah! You've hit the nail right
on the head again, Sa-ku-rah-ee!
Wait a sec.
[KYOICHI] You think maybe she'd
know? She knows a lot more
than she needs to.
[YUUYA]
By "she" do you mean...?
[TONO] Huh? From Homei High?
Oh, you're asking about
Kugayama! She was
one of the best violinists
in Tokyo, you know.
She was originally
from Hokkaido.
I heard she lived on campus.
And, I believe she has a
boyfriend named Kamiyogi.
As a matter of fact, I've
got her address memorized!
[TONO]
Say...
How come you wanna
know all that stuff, anyway?
Uh, you see...
Academic curiosity.
[TONO]
What?
[TATSUMA] What I mean is
someone asked me to find out.
[TONO]
Oh? And who was that?
[TATSUMA]
Um, well...
Gotta go!
[TONO]
Uh, wait!
There's the mysterious
transfer student for you.
He's obviously
got something to hide.
Could this be a
scoop that I'm smelling?
[YUUYA] Split up? What are
you talking about, Kyoichi?
[KOMAKI] Remember the
terms of our agreement?
All five of us go.
[KYOICHI]
God, you pansies...
I don't need somebody to hold
my hand. And I never agreed
to those stupid "terms"
in the first place!
[AOI]
But...
[KYOICHI] Thanks to
our pasty-freak friend
I haven't had much
sleep the past two weeks.
Tatsuma and I are
gonna do our own thing.
[YUUYA] Well, I can't say I
don't understand how you feel...
What gives you the
right to be so selfish?
[KYOICHI] Oh,
shut yer face, she-male.
What did you call me?!
[KYOICHI] Anyhow if we
don't get our acts together and
settle this thing,
no one's ever gonna
be able to rest in peace again.
[INUGAMI] Horaiji! I haven't
received your report yet.
Inugami.
[INUGAMI] What you do at night
is your business but
I don't particularly wanna have
you in my class again next year.
[INUGAMI]
And I almost forgot...
Hiyu: it hasn't been too
safe around here lately.
I wouldn't go looking
for trouble if I were you.
[TATSUMA]
Yes, sir.
[dog barking]
[fretting in his sleep]
[glass cracks]
[YUKO]
Kamiyogi...
Huh?
[YUKO]
Come on.
Come to me, Kamiyogi.
Is that you?
[KAMIYOGI] What are you
doing here? You know...
everybody's looking for you.
I mean, they told...
they told...
they told me that you're dead.
[low growling]
[rabid screeching]
[hysterical scream]
[crash]
[explosion]
[nervous giggle]
[TONO]
Now I get it...
[glass shatters]
[concrete crumbles]
[horrified scream]
[nervous quivering]
[thud]
[whimpering]
[KOMAKI]
He's getting away! Let's go!
[YUUYA]
Uh, right!
Wha-what on earth was that
thing supposed to be anyw--
I hope that you can
forgive me for this, Kyoko.
[lightening bolt strikes]
That thing can jump.
Now we bring it down.
Hmm.
[crash]
[lightening bolt strikes]
That one?
You gotta be
joking, she's only a kid.
[cat meows]
[impact bursts]
[TATSUMA]
This place is...
[KYOICHI]
Seems more like it's luring us
to its den than
running away from us.
[TATSUMA]
Let's go.
[distant zombie groan]
[zombies growling]
[KYOICHI]
It's time...
time to follow the light.
[MONKS] No-ro-I-to-ku,
I-to-mo-re-to-ru...
Shi-ka-ku-shi-ma,
Tsu-ru-se-mi-no,
I-to-mo-re-to-ru
A-ri-shi-fu-we,
Tsu-mi-hi-to-no,
No-ro-I-to-ku!
[OLD MAN IN GLASSES]
He turned our spell on us!
[OLD MAN IN HAT]
Now what?
[OLD MAN IN GLASSES]
Try again!
No-ro-I-to-ku,
I-to-mo-re-to-ru
Shi-ka-ku-shi-ma,
A-ri-shi-fu-we...
Sha-ku-ko, Sha-ko,
Kin-ka-tsu, Kin-shin!
[MONK]
You soulless little monster!
[giggles]
[OLD MAN IN GLASSES]
Don't be foolish!
[blast]
[groans]
[TENDO]
And now for you...
Now that I've got your
attention and since all
of your friends are
gone, there's something
I wanted to ask
you, Mister Eyebrows.
[screams]
[KYOICHI]
There are so many of them!
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi, look out!
[KYOICHI] Tatsuma!
Now, quick, go for it's arms!
[pained groan]
[KYOICHI]
Goddamn renegade!
[flames roar]
[gurgling]
The Ku-ja-ku-shi...
what a pain...
[OLD MEN] No-ro-I-to-ku,
I-to-mo-re-to-ru
They asked for it.
Do your thing, Claire.
[straining]
[explosion]
[YUUYA]
Kyoichi! Hiyu!
[cars honking]
Didn't mean to blow it up.
What a friggin' mess this is.
[KYOICHI] Hey, where you
think you're going, asshole?
[bursting]
[explodes]
[TATSUMA]
You alright?
[YUUYA]
Hey! Kyoichi! Hiyu!
[AOI]
There were so many of them.
[Kyoichi]
It's like I said before.
This isn't where
you belong, princess.
[AOI] I wasn't able to protect
them...I couldn't protect them.
[Newscaster] I repeat:
according to police,
the corpses discovered in the
cave-in account for almost all
of the missing persons.
[Newscaster] ...the number of
recovered bodies alone are
thought to number more than a
hundred. Seeking to at least
confirm identities, the
relatives of those missing are
asked to be patient as the
bodies are being identified...
Huh.
Wh-What in the...
What in the world is going on?!