[AOI] Don't die! Live!
Please...
Live! Live!
[SAYO] Tatsuma.
Sorry I'm late.
[KOMAKI sighs]
Just look at all
those underclassmen,
just full of energy.
Must be nice...
[KOMAKI] God, I wanna
draw my bow again!
[KYOUICHI] Look,
it's never gonna happen!
I mean, we're all out of here
at the end of
September, remember?
[KOMAKI] How can a guy
who's never joined a club
in his life know how it feels?
You don't understand how hard it
is for me to watch and not do!
[KYOUICHI] Hey,
leggo of me, She-male!
Dude, your little lady-husband's
freaking out on me!
[YUUYA] Sakurai,
have you tried this?!
It's a brand new flavor,
mint-pineapple!
[KOMAKI] What?
Ooh, it does look good.
[YUUYA] Doesn't it?
[KOMAKI] But what is it?
[YUUYA]
It's a new kind of gum.
[KOMAKI] Gum?
I think I'll pass.
[YUUYA] Oh, come on,
try a little piece.
[KOMAKI] Ugh, no way!
It's pineapple gum--
[YUUYA] But, I went
out and bought it
--[KOMAKI] Oh. Hi, Aoi.
--[YUUYA] for you to try.
[KYOUICHI]
Are you finally done?
[AOI] Yeah. I'm sorry
I kept you all waiting.
[YUUYA] All right...
Let's get going.
[KOMAKI] Hey, Aoi. Don't you
think we stepped down
too early this year?
Huh? You mean
from club activities?
[KOMAKI]
Yeah. I mean, sheesh,
I'm so out of shape right now.
[KISARAGI] With all the recent
appearances of the demons,
I've made a chart of
where all the incidents
have been occuring.
[KOMAKI] Wow, so many.
[YUUYA] Looks like the attacks
increased all at once,
spreading out from the area
near Sakuragaoka Hospital.
Since nightmare-boy Sagaya.
[KISARAGI] Yes, that, and
last month's incident
with the blonde high school
girl, Sera Rikudo...
But the curious thing
is that since then,
the demons haven't
shown themselves once.
[KOMAKI] You don't think
they've given up on
attacking Tokyo, do you?
I mean, that'd
be pretty awesome,
don't you think, Aoi?
Yeah. That would... be nice.
Tch. I wouldn't
hold my breath.
Kozunu... Tendo Kozunu.
[KISARAGI] Yes. It does
seem fairly unlikely
that he would drop his
vendetta just like that.
I'm sure it will be
only a matter of time
before he comes up
with a new plan.
Perhaps he's... in the
process of carrying one out.
[YUUYA] So all we do now
is sit around patiently
for the enemy to
show up again, huh?
[KYOUICHI chuckles]
Well, when it finally comes,
I'm gonna be ready to go
on one hell of a rampage.
[KOMAKI] Hey, Aoi.
Earth to Aoi!
[AOI] Huh? Oh. Sorry.
[KOMAKI] What's the matter?
[AOI] Well, I've just been kind
of busy lately, that's all.
[KOMAKI] You mean with the
student council transition?
[AOI] Yeah.
[KOMAKI] Oh, man,
you're such an overachiever.
You know, you've
really got me worried!
[AOI laughs]
I appreciate
your concern, Komaki.
[KYOUICHI] Okay... so,
how's about we grab some ramen
while we're in the area?
Ooh! I'm in for that!
Sure. I was just
startin' to get hungry.
Whaddaya say, Aoi,
you comin' with us?
There's nothing like a hot,
steaming bowl of ramen
when you're feeling
down in the dumps. Right?
Heh. I guess
you're right.
[TATSUMA] Well, I think
I'll be heading home.
[ALL] Huh?
See you guys tomorrow, okay?
Hey, what's up with him?
[ANKO giggles]
Would you like the scoop?
[KYOUICHI] Oh crap... Anko.
What's that supposed to mean?!
[metal clangs]
Ha! The reason Tatsuma's
in such a hurry is this.
[ANKO] Ta-dah!
[KYOUICHI]
Hey, could that be...
[YUUYA]
Is he on a... date?!
[KOMAKI] Awww...
Look at Tatsuma and his date.
They look so sweet.
[KYOUICHI] That girl...
[ANKO laughs]
I'll bet you're surprised.
I'll bet you never suspected
that Tatsuma would have
a secret like this, did you?
[ANKO]
Her name is Sayo Hirasaka.
She's in Class 2-5 at Sakurazuka
High School in Shinagawa.
She's 5'6" and weighs 93 pounds.
And her measurements...
...are a secret.
Who gives a damn.
[ANKO] No offense.
Mmm.
[ANKO] Also, she enjoys
watching TV drama series.
And her favorite word
is... "reincarnation."
[KYOUICHI] Reincarnation?
That's, like, got something
to do with religion, right?
[YUUYA] Master Arai
told me about that.
It's the idea that souls
are reborn again and again,
and continue to wander this
world of confusion and pain.
[KOMAKI] What else?
[ANKO] Well,
this is interesting.
Both her parents died during
that whole crow-attack thing.
She somehow managed
to survive it,
but from what I hear,
she's been in the hospital
until just recently.
[KOMAKI] I see...
What's the matter with you?
You've got the
grumpiest face right now.
Uh, it's nothin'.
[ANKO] Anyway, she's got
relatives nearby in Izu
who are planning
on taking her in.
[gasps]
[ANKO] Oh, no!
I just can't sit around
eating ramen all day!
I was in the middle of
investigating a big scoop!
I'll let you
take care of the tab!
[KYOUICHI] Huh?
[ANKO] Consider it
payment for the info.
Man. I tell you what,
that girl's gonna be
[KYOUICHI]
one hell of a teleporter.
[YUUYA and KOMAKI] Reporter!
[KYOUICHI] Shut up!
I know what I'm sayin'!
[whimpers softly]
Are you all right there, miss?
[AOI sobbing]
--Hey...
Aoi?
[chuckles]
[GRANDFATHER] Hisui,
listen to me carefully.
It is about time
that you also learned
of our family's "other"
mission, which we must uphold!
It is said that
at times, one appears
who has the power to
read the Dragon Stream.
This person can discern
who are the chosen among us
and lead them
to eternal salvation.
That individual often
holds great power
in whatever era they exist,
and this is a source
of much conflict.
They're known as
the Bodhisattva Eye!
Hisui, listen to me
carefully and don't forget
that if the one who
possesses that star of fate
ever appears to you,
you must immediately...
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
[KYOUICHI] Man...
when you look at it up close,
it's pretty damn amazing.
Thanks I should be
all right from here on.
[KYOUICHI] Right.
Well, then you have
a good night, okay?
[AOI] Thanks so much for
walking me back, Kyouichi.
[KYOUICHI] Sure.
[KYOUICHI] Aoi!
[gasps]
Don't let everything
weigh you down.
[KYOUICHI] If anything happens,
then say so. Got it?
[chanting]
[gasps]
Why, good evening.
Tendo Kozunu,
what are you doing here?!
[TENDO] You don't
look happy to see me.
That bitter expression
is ruining your pretty face.
What are you doing here?
That's one good question.
[TENDO] As a matter of fact,
I'm here this time
to give my regards.
Regards?
Yes.
Mm.
This power.
You're terrified of it.
[TENDO] You've felt
something powerful
squirming inside you,
haven't you?
But you're pretending
you're not aware of it.
Stop it...
[TENDO] Your power
is bringing misfortune
to everyone around you.
It seems like wherever you go,
people are getting hurt,
and some of them
are even losing their lives.
[AOI] That's not...
That has nothing
to do with me!
[TENDO] I'm the only one
who can help you control it.
This little power of yours
needs harnessing.
So what do you say?
I just wanna protect--
I wanna protect them.
I don't want
anyone else hurt.
That's all the more reason,
don't you think?
Just come along with me
and you'll be able to...
protect everyone in the world.
All of your friends
and everyone in this city...
can be safe.
[TENDO] Well, I guess
hearing all that is enough
to make your
head spin, huh?
But it's the truth,
my little Aoi.
If you really do want to save
Tokyo, just say the word.
I can come
to you any time.
Sooner or later your fate's
going to catch up with you.
Just try to remember
that much at least,
Aoi Misato.
[AOI] Yes. Okay. I'll see
you tomorrow night, then.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[sighs]
Huh?
[INUGAMI] Take her to
Sakuragaoka Central Hospital.
I'll take full responsibility.
[KYOUICHI] Who is
that geezer anyway?
[KYOUICHI] Yo.
Hey, Kyouichi.
[KYOUICHI] It looks like you're
in quite a hurry there, man.
[TATSUMA] Yeah. Gotta take
care of some stuff.
[KYOUICHI] I see...
"Stuff," huh?
[TATSUMA] Yeah.
You, uh... you know, right?
I can't talk.
I have to get going.
Uh!
Tatsuma!
Sheesh!
[KYOUICHI]
It's not like they'll never
see each other again.
[ANKO humming]
[ANKO] I've been running
nothing but scary stories
on the front page lately.
I guess I can't forget about
my female readers,
though, can I?
Hmm...
[AOI] This is...
[TATSUMA] It's my destiny.
[TENDO] Sooner or later
your fate's going to
catch up with you.
Just try to remember
that much at least,
Aoi Misato.
[AOI] My fate?
Is it the same for Tatsuma?
[groans]
[SAYO sighs]
I guess I've gotta say goodbye
to this city, too, huh?
[TATSUMA] We can see each
other again any time.
[TATSUMA] Here,
just what you requested.
Ah! I can't believe
you remembered!
And this one tells time.
[gasps]
[SAYO] Oh, Tatsuma...!
Huh... So how does this
thing take a picture?
Oh. You should
stand back.
What?
--[SAYO] Uh...
--[camera shutter]
[SAYO]
Tatsuma, you're so funny.
[TATSUMA] I am?
[TATSUMA] Um...
[SAYO] Huh?
[TATSUMA] You know
those flowers you took
to the graveyard
yesterday...?
[SAYO] The sweet peas?
[TATSUMA] Yeah. You know
people don't usually
put those on graves, right?
[SAYO] They were my
mom's favorite flower.
[SAYO] My uncle's family
that I'll be living with,
well, he told me that they
grow sweet peas on their farm.
I've been there once,
but I was so young
I don't remember.
[SAYO] He told me the
flowers would be in bloom
all December long.
I can't wait to see them.
[TATSUMA] Sure.
That sounds beautiful.
[AOI gasps]
That's Tatsuma.
[KISARAGI chants]
Houraiji. Why are you here?
[KYOUICHI] Heh.
I got a bad feeling when I saw
you close up shop early.
So I follow you a little ways
and I catch you pulling out
that lethal weapon there.
You know, I really
hate it when people try an'
keep secrets from me.
[KYOUICHI] You're the
one who told me to
nose around
for stuff like this.
So how 'bout
you just 'fess up
and give it to me straight?
[KYOUICHI]
Say something, dammit.
[KISARAGI grunts]
[KYOUICHI huffs]
It's about Aoi, isn't it?
[KYOUICHI] Kisaragi.
What's going on
with Aoi right now?
What are you tryin' to do?
[KIARAGI] The power which
Lady Aoi possesses...
What about it?
Tell me about Aoi's power?
[KISARAGI]
The Bodhisattva Eye.
[KYOUICHI]
The Bodhisattva Eye?
What's that supposed to be?
[KISARAGI] It's an
accursed power that will
lead to the
world's destruction.
At least that's what
it's supposed to do.
[KYOUICHI]
What? Destruction?
But...
doesn't that make Aoi
part of the problem, then?
Has she been protecting
Tokyo with the rest of us
or hasn't she?!
The incidents with the demons
have been part of a plan.
[KISARAGI] I believe that
plan is to awaken Aoi's...
or rather, the Bodhisattva
Eye's long-dormant power.
In the hope of finally
awakening that power,
Kozunu sent the demons here.
[KISARAGI] He's been slowly
leading Tokyo into chaos!
[gasps]
Hisui, listen to me
carefully and don't forget
that if the one who
possesses that star of fate
ever appears to you,
you must immediately...
[KYOUICHI] So what are
you gonna do about it?
[KISARAGI] That kind of power
must never exist in this world.
...kill that person,
regardless of what their
circumstances may be!
[GRANDFATHER] This person must
be vanquished by the hand
of a Kisaragi before the
Dragon Stream is disrupted!
[KISARAGI] Naturally,
we can't allow them
to get their hands on her.
Then what you're sayin'...
is that you're
gonna kill Aoi?!
Heh. It was naïve of me
ever to have trusted you
in the first place.
Hey, Pasty. Get ready
to meet your maker.
You simpleton.
What would you
know about duty?
[BOTH grunt]
[KYOUICHI] You promised--
[KYOUICHI] Aah!
[gasps]
[KYOUICHI] You promised
you'd protect her!
[KYOUICHI] So I guess
that was all just a lie?
And instead of doing
what you said you would...
you came out here to slice
your gut open like a coward.
And you tell me about duty?!
This is it.
I'm done with your crap.
[BOTH gasp]
Everything...
Everything was my fault?
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
[KYOUICHI] Aoi!
All the demons and...
Is it... really all my...?
[KISARAGI] The fireflies...
[gasps]
--[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
--[KYOUICHI] Aoi!
[AOI sobbing]
[KYOUICHI] Aoi!
[AOI]
I wanna protect people?
I wanna save them?
More than my own life?
I had no idea
what I was saying!
I said that I wanted
to protect people,
but all along...
All along the one
behind it was...
[sobs]
[AOI] Uh...!
[SOLDIERS] It's all your
fault. It's because of you.
[whimpers]
[YOUNG TENDO]
Mother? Mother?
Mother!
[TENDO] Stop it.
Don't come any closer!
[sighs]
[KYOUICHI] Aoi!
Aoi!
[chiming]
What the hell--?
[gasps]
What on earth is... that?
[SAYO] Thanks for
keeping me company.
[TATSUMA] Well, I didn't
really do anything...
[SAYO] Tatsuma. Thank you.
[TATSUMA] Hm?
[SAYO] Well...
[beeping]
[SAYO gasps]
Goodbye.
[distant horn]
It's all right.
I'll make the trip with you.