[crowd chattering]
[AOI]
Tatsuma...?
Why you little...
Where on earth did they go?
Could that be...
[electric guitar shredding]
[RAITO]
That guitar...
[KYOICHI] Hey, man where
do you think you're goin'?
[KYOICHI]
Dammit!
Kyouichi.
[KYOICHI]
Let's get after him.
Right.
Tatsuma...
[TATSUMA] Make sure you guys
get in touch with Kisaragi.
[KYOICHI] They got
their asses kicked pretty bad
by Lightning Head.
Do what you can to fix them.
[AOI]
Right.
[electric guitar shredding]
Ryoichi...
If it isn't my enemy...
[RAITO] Ryoichi! It's me!
Don't you recognize me?
[KYOICHI]
Hold it right there!
You two again.
What's up, Lightening Boy?
Who's your little guitar friend?
[RAITO] This doesn't
concern you. So get lost.
[RYOICHI] It doesn't matter
how many of you stupid pigs
come at me. I'll
slaughter you all.
[KYOICHI] Little punk,
what did you just call us?!
I believe that I compared
the three of you to pigs.
[electric guitar shredding]
[RYOICHI] Sound is so incredibly
powerful that it can interfere
with just about anything
by using vibration alone.
And at my slightest command...
[KYOICHI]
Hey, Tatsuma, you stupid pig!
Don't just stand there with
your thumb up your--
don't look at me like
that, punk!
What the hell you
gawking at, moron?
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi's a stupid idiot!
Kyouichi's a piece of
trash! He's trash!
[battle cry]
Kyoichi!
Oh, man...
What the hell was that?
It seems you
too have the Power.
[RYOICHI]
It's magnificent, isn't it?
All things obey me and whatever
I ask for I can have.
Because I have become as
powerful as a god.
Ryouichi, did... did you...
[Ryoichi chuckles]
[RYOICHI]
The pigs wish to defy a god?
What the hell
are you doing?
[Kyoichi chocking]
It's not me,
he's controlling my body!
Stop it, man. Leave them alone.
[electric guitar shredding]
This isn't your sound.
This isn't how you're
supposed to play!
Your sound? No...
it was our sound.
It should never have
been like this.
[RYOICHI]
Raito.
[plays chord]
Ryoichi, no!
[TATSUMA]
What the hell just happened?!
You two need to get lost.
[KYOICHI]
What was all that?
Hey! Where do you
think you're goin'?
Damnit... Stupid
lightning bastard...
[ANKO] Ohran Academy, Class
3-4, Hisui Kisaragi:
President of the school's
Tea Ceremony Club,
proprietor of an antiques shop,
and well known hunk.
So how do you two
know each other, huh?
Lady Misato, I have
told you time and time again
that you must never go
act on your own.
I'm so sorry, Hisui but I
was just wanted to help out.
Hey, don't you ignore me!
[YUUYA] So the flock of crows
that attacked those people is
being controlled by the guy
with the guitar.
Isn't that right, Horaiji?
[KYOICHI] Yeah...
And he could control
our voices and our
bodies at will, too.
He had the power to control
atmospheric vibrations?
Kyoichi said some
very nasty things to me.
I'm tellin' you,
that wasn't me talkin'!
And then he
tried to strangle me.
Stop tryin' to make
me look bad! Oh, come on,
you did the same
thing to me. Oh, screw it...
So that guy with the crazy
hair is supposed to know
the guitar player,
is that right?
[ANKO] That's right! They're
from that band, Crow! You know.
I don't wanna be rude,
but nobody invited you
to this party.
Whatta you want, parasite?
[TATSUMA] Not as much
of a parasite as you are.
[KYOICHI] I told you,
it wasn't me!
[YUUYA]
So, what is this "Crow" thing?
[ANKO] They were this
crazy popular indie band.
They only released, like, 11
songs over two years, but every
one of them was a hit. They were
this huge internet sensation.
Oh, and all of the members
are Tokyo high schoolers,
just like us. So
that's pretty cool, huh?
[KOMAKI] Really? So who's
the guy with the mohawk?
That's Raito, the lead
singer. Ryoichi was the one who
was the driving force behind
the band. He played guitar and
composed all of their songs.
He was a huge
deal on the music scene,
but then...
[KOMAKI]
What?
[ANKO] Three months ago,
the band mysteriously broke up.
Word on the street was that
Ryoichi just disappeared.
[KOMAKI]
But why?
[ANKO] I dunno. From what I hear
the rumor has it he was a
real difficult person to get
along with, so the band was
always arguing and getting
into fights with each other.
They broke
up three months ago...
It was just about then, huh?
[AOI]
Yes...
[YUUYA] So there are other
people out there like us.
[KOMAKI] Which means
we're gonna have to fight
other people
with the Power.
[crying]
[TENDO] What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
[RYOICHI] I don't think I can
do this... I can't do this!
You can. You'll
find the strength because
this is what he wants.
[RYOICHI]
But...
[TENDO] You know that you're
the only person who can
grant that wish.
That's why he's
chasing you so mercilessly.
Surely you haven't forgotten?
[RYOICHI] Raito? He wants this?
Of course he does...
[KYOICHI] Well, that settles
it then. I'd sure love to teach
Lightning Head a lesson, but
I guess we're gonna have to go
after the little Crow Boy first.
[ANKO] For crying out loud!
What the heck is going on with
you guys, anyway?!
Somebody better start explaining
things to me right now
or I'm gonna get really angry!
Hey, Dungeonmaster.
[KISARAGI]
What?
You got any baskets?
Huh?
I've got a pot, will that do?
[ANKO]
Huh?
[AOI] I wonder if it was wrong
of us to do that to Tono...
[KYOICHI] It'll be fine.
With everything we're up against
we couldn't protect
her even if we wanted to.
[KYOICHI]
Don't you agree... Misato?
Well, I guess you must be right.
[electric guitar shredding]
Ryoichi!
It's me Raito.
Tell me what the
hell's gotten into you?!
[RAITO] You were always alone...
even when you were a little kid.
You didn't even try to make
any friends, except for me.
I guess both of us coming
from broken homes,
it was easy to become
like brothers.
I always think about how proud
I was of your guitar-playing.
Remember how much you loved
playing and that's why we
started the band. And I thought
the band would help you to
make friends.
[RYOICHI]
You wanna change it? Why?
[RAITO] Because if
we don't rearrange it,
then the other guys won't be
able to keep up with us.
[RYOICHI] Raito.
You promised me that we'd
never change this song.
You remember that?
[RAITO] They can't play it live.
And we've got a gig, so...
Ryoichi?
[RAITO] You just
disappeared which meant
that was the end of Crow.
I formed the band for
you... to help you.
[RAITO]
Where in the hell have you been?
[RYOICHI] Let go of me!
Get your hands off of me!
[RAITO] You're comin' back
with me, you got that?
[RYOICHI]
Like hell!
Everyone's waiting on you,
damnit! You're comin' with me!
Understand!--
[RAITO] Ever since that day,
I've been able to use the Power.
And since you disappeared,
I've been searching for you,
wondering if... maybe
you'd got this power, too.
[RYOICHI] You know I've
been waiting for you to come.
I've been waiting for you all
this time. I wanted them to hear
the music we made.
That you and I created.
I'll use this divine power
to make those ignorant
pigs understand!
Do you know this Power
doesn't make you into a god?
In fact you're acting
more like the Grim Reaper.
[Ryoichi laughs]
[RYOICHI] You can't fight
the music made by a god!
But you know that.
Don't you, Raito?
Ryouichi, you...
You've already killed--
[KYOCHI] Well, well,
lookie what we found here:
Lightning Head. And his "little
sidekick", The Crow Boy.
[RAITO] This isn't
any of your business.
So get the hell out of here!
[KYOICHI]
Put a sock in it, Bedhead!
This isn't just
your problem or ours.
It's the whole city's.
Don't be so full of yourself
to think you can fix
all this on your own.
[RAITO]
You don't understand...
[RYOICHI] Then it's settled.
I'll let everybody hear it.
The true voice of God...
that we created...
[ANKO]
I want my scoop!
[explosion]
[electric guitar shredding]
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi! Behind you!
Horaiji!
[KYOICHI]
Hey, Dumb Muscle-head!
What did you say?!
[FIREFIGHTER]
Oh my God...
[RAITO] What are you doing?
You need to fight me!
I'm the one who attacked
you remember? Ryoichi!
Hey, I got a question: how can
we be sure that mohawk guy
isn't still our enemy?
[AOI]
I'm not sure.
He's not after us.
He wasn't fighting us at his
full strength earlier.
Sure 'bout that?
All of his strikes deliberately
missed all of our vital spots.
So that means...
You did it so you could
determine whether we were your
enemies or on your side.
Your eyes tell me...
that you're not a killer.
[YUUYA] Are we really
gonna fight another human being?
[KYOICHI]
Looks like it...
Nope. It's no good.
There's just not enough
evidence to go on.
Have you looked at
anyone the crows attacked?
Yeah, I didn't find anything.
That's too bad. Well,
I guess that's what we expected.
[RAITO] You just
don't know when to quit.
I already told you:
I'll take care of Ryoichi.
[KYOICHI] Hey, you're the
one who got us involved
in this in the first place.
Weren't you lookin'
for a jamboree?
You mean, Jam session.
[KYOICHI]
Stop correcting me!
Who the hell
are you guys, anyway?
[TATSUMA] We're here to protect
the city and everyone in it.
And to protect them, we fight.
[KYOICHI]
Let's do this!
[RAITO] Ryoichi...
I wish we can go back
to the way things used to be.
But we can't turn back.
And someone has to stop you.
So I will!
[battle cry]
[screams]
[TENDO]
Hmmm...
[KYOICHI] Were you
really trying to kill him?
You can't go
through with it, can you?
[RAITO] I couldn't do it.
I just couldn't.
[AOI] There is no need to take
another person's life.
We don't know what happened
between the two of you.
But no matter how terrible the
crimes he's committed, we...
we have to try to
save his soul, and to do that,
we have to give
him another chance.
Please we must let him live!
Save his soul.
Didn't think of that...
[RYOICHI]
What happened...
You're the one
who took them from me.
It was you!
Ryoichi?
[RYOICHI] You know Raito.
You did it to us.
You ruined us!!!!
[RAITO]
Ryoichi!
[shrieks]
[people chatter]
[explosion]
[battle cry]
[multiple explosions]
[people chattering]
[KISARAGI]
Three million yen...
[ANKO] Huh? So you're telling me
that you're one of
the members of Kyoichi's gang?
Yeah, that's right.
The Boss is the one that has
shown us the right
path to follow.
[ANKO] Well, you
sure are a lifesaver!
[AZUMABASHI] Hey, I'd do
anything for one of the boss's
school friends!
Know what I'm sayin'?
Tatsuma! Damn it!
[screams]
[RAITO] Sho-Ji-Tai
San-Kan-On Myo-Ji-Rei!
[people screaming]
[gasps]
[explosion]
[AZUMABASHI]
What the hell's goin' on?!
[ANKO] Thanks for the ride. I'll
be okay on my own from here.
[AZUMABASHI]
You can't be serious! You know,
I uh think we oughta go back...
Lemme tell you a little
somethin' about journalists:
whoever gets the story wins!
[RAITO]
Ryoichi!
[KYOICHI]
Demonic Crow!
[RAITO] You were saying that I
ruined us? Well, what the hell
would you call what you're
doing now, huh? What's with this
"sound of a god" shit?!
Where's the sound we made?!
[RAITO] Were we just writing
songs to become mass murderers?
What the hell did you write 'em
for, anyway? Who did you write
'em for, Ryoichi?! Hey, are
you gonna answer me or not?!
[growls]
Ryoichi...
[KYOICHI] Tatsuma,
what the hell are you doing?
I feel sorry for her.
But we both know that for her
it's too late.
All we can do now
is try to stop him.
[TATSUMA] I can't
just leave her here.
I can't just leave her here!
[KYOICHI] Okay, then.
We'll go take care of Crow Boy.
[TATSUMA]
Thanks.
[animalistic wheezing]
[RYOICHI]
Raito?
Ryoichi, I'm here.
What's goin' on?
[shrieks]
What was that?
[growls]
[RAITO]
Ryoichi? Ryoichi?
[RYOICHI]
Raito...
[RAITO]
Stay with me.
What's going on?
Ya got me, man.
[YUUYA]
Is he... back to normal?
[RAITO]
Ryoichi...
[RYOICHI] Why did you change it?
We made that song together...
It was ours and
no one else's... Raito...
I thought at least
you would understand!
That was it? You were still
upset with me about that song?
I just wanted to protect it,
no matter what.
[AOI] Can you
tell me something?
Why did you do it?
How were you able to turn
yourself into a demon?
[RYOICHI] It was...
the Dark Arts...
[RAITO]
Oh!
[KOMAKI]
Oh my god.
[CLAIRE]
Oh, phooey.
[TENDO] We grant a favor and
give him the Power, but it looks
as if there was a trace of
humanity left in him and
the demon's power devoured
what was left of his soul.
[CLAIRE]
That's totally gross.
Who the hell are you?!
Well, we must be off.
We'll see
each other again soon.
Aw, that was boring.
[RAITO]
Ryoichi! Ryoichi!