[train horn]
Huh?
[giggles]
[KYOUICHI running breaths]
[exhales deeply]
[grunts]
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
[cell phone ringing]
[KOMAKI] Hello. She what?
Whaddaya mean
Aoi disappeared?
[KYOUICHI] I'll give you
the details later.
I've already told
Daigo about this.
Hey, listen.
Kozunu's on the move,
so watch your back, all right.
Did you say Kozunu?!
Tell me what the hell
is going on here!
Is Aoi okay?
And what about Kisaragi?
[KYOUICHI] Shut up!
Just go look for her!
[ANKO] Oh, there you are!
I've been lookin'
all over for you.
Look, I don't have time
to play your little
newspaper game right now.
What do you mean "game"?!
Focus! This is something
you need to see.
[ANKO] It was just her left
arm at first, but then...
Hey. You don't think
that it means...
[crickets chirping]
[SAYO] No?
No, it's okay. Bye.
My uncle says
something came up,
so he won't be able to
come out here and get us.
Really? Whatta ya goin' do?
There aren't any more busses.
I guess we'll
just have to walk.
[rolling sound]
[crickets chirping]
I'm sorry about this.
[gasps]
[deep exhale, inhale]
[whimpers]
[TATSUMA] Are you all right?
[SAYO] I'm fine.
Thanks. I'm okay.
♪
[TATSUMA] Are those...
sweet peas?
[SAYO] Pretty, aren't they?
[TATSUMA] Yeah.
[SAYO] There have
always been a lot of
sweet pea farms
around this area.
Everything is exactly
as how I remember it.
My best memory is how I'd
come out here with my parents.
[TATSUMA]
I know what you mean.
My parents are also...
[SAYO] Huh?
And look,
I also got the key ring.
[SAYO laughs]
Someday when I'm older,
I want to have
a farm like this one
and I'm going to grow
lots and lots of sweet peas.
Can I ask you
something, Tatsuma?
Huh?
[SAYO] When that time comes,
do you think we can...
Hm?
[train chugging]
[running footsteps]
[KOMAKI] Kisaragi!
[YUUYA] Kisaragi!
[YUUYA and KOMAKI panting]
[TATSUMA] Is this it?
[SAYO] Yes.
Uh, um. I guess...
It's all right.
Uh. Oh... I'll just...
Tatsuma?
It's pretty late,
so if you'd like...
Mm.
[gasps]
[TATSUMA quavered breathing]
[YUUYA] Have you heard
anything from Kyouichi?
[KYOUICHI] No.
Where in the hell is she?
Don't you know?
Kozunu has her already.
What did you just say?
What the hell
is going on here?!
Why would he take Aoi when
he could have any of us?
And if you know he's got her,
then what are you
doing out here?
[KOMAKI] Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Stop it, Sakurai!
Take it easy.
Kisaragi.
[grunts]
Is that you, Aoi?
Aoi, thank God!
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Take a good look at her.
Huh?
[AZUMABASHI] Yee-haw!
Hey, kick it, Azumabashi?
[AZUMABASHI] I'm just gettin'
warmed up, Boss.
[KYOUICHI] Tatsuma...
[KOMAKI] Aoi?
Lady Aoi.
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
[KISARAGI sighs]
[YUUYA grunts]
[KISARAGI, YUUYA,
and KOMAKI scream]
Kisaragi, what the hell
is going on?
Stop her. Whatever it takes,
she must be stopped!
[YUUYA]
The Demoniacal Horde?!
[CLAIRE] Hey, I can't say
that I really get it, either.
But he wanted me to get
that nasty thing for him.
[TATSUMA groans, yells]
Poor thing. Sucks to be you.
You must've thought
you were just moments away
from spooning with your
cute little girlfriend.
I'm afraid that
wasn't meant to be.
Oh, don't cry. It wouldn't
of worked out anyway.
You see, she's dead.
[beeping]
[flatline tone]
[TENDO] More specifically,
she's a corpse demon.
She's been dead
for quite some time.
--[TENDO] Mm.
--[SAYO gasps]
Take a look.
[SAYO gasps]
[fabric ripping]
[TENDO] This is what she looks
like under her uniform.
[gasps]
I gave her some extra
time back among the living.
She knew it was only
a temporary thing.
There's no blood in her veins,
and her flesh is rotting
right off her bones.
And she brought you to me
[TENDO] so she could get her
pathetic little life back.
He told me...
he he'd bring my mom
and dad back to life.
He told me that he would
bring everybody back.
That's why... That's why...
[SAYO] I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
[TATSUMA] I've known.
Huh?
[TATSUMA]
I've known all along.
Now this is why
I just don't like you.
Nothing I say fazes you.
[TENDO] That poker face of
yours makes me wanna puke.
[KISARAGI groans]
[KOMAKI grunts]
[YUUYA groans]
[TENDO] Well, let me
tell you something:
your little girlfriend
belongs to me.
And right about now,
your friends
should be mine as well...
Not Misato!
[TENDO] There you go.
Now that's the expression
I wanted to see.
My intension was to have
this girl keep tabs on you,
but she also kept you away
from the girl I wanted.
A delightful show,
my pretty thing.
Uh.
[TENDO] Now you're
the only loose end left.
[TATSUMA groans]
So why don't you just tell
me who the hell you are?
You're on my last nerves,
you little shit.
You will tell me the truth.
[groaning]
Because you'll see,
my quiet friend,
I will get the truth
with or without your help.
♪
[gasps]
[TENDO] Is that...?
[baby crying]
[TENDO groans]
Dammit, tell me--who are you?
[groans]
Manabu... How could you...?
[TENDO] You're wrong!
You're wrong...
I am Kozunu!
I am Tendo Kozunu!
I get it.
Now I understand why
I was so concerned
about you all this time.
[TENDO] Because you...
Because your people
are the ones...
[grunting]
[TENDO] Die.
Die!
[yells]
[TATSUMA yelling]
[laughs]
I am just so grateful
that we were fated
to run into each other
here and now,
aren't you, old friend?
[TATSUMA groaning]
[TATSUMA continues groaning]
[SAYO] Stop it!
Please, don't do this!
I'm begging you.
You can do whatever you want
to me, but please just...
[SAYO] leave him alone!
[TENDO chuckles]
[SAYO gasping]
[SAYO groaning]
[TENDO laughs]
If you've really gotten
to like him that much then
why don't you go to
the other side together?
[SAYO sobs]
[groaning]
Don't look.
Please don't look at me!
This is where the story ends.
Uh! You little--!
[SAYO screams]
[monsterous screams]
The balance between the sun
and moon has been altered....
What have you done,
you stupid little bitch?!
[SAYO] Uah!
Sayo, no!
Tatsuma...
[SAYO] Tatsuma...
The sweet peas...
let's... let's both...
Try to focus your minds.
[grunts]
[KISARAGI]
Don't listen to their song.
They're chanting a curse!
[gasps]
Someone doesn't
know when to die.
Kozunu...
[TATSUMA] Kozunu Tendo!
[TENDO grunts]
[TATSUMA yells]
[TENDO] You! Because
of you! You're the one!
Because of you, the Kozunu
family... my mother...!
You killed her.
You killed my mother!
[TENDO]
Give my mother back to me.
Give my mother...
[TENDO] back to me!
[yells]
[snickers]
[exhales]
[YUUYA] Sakurai, no!
Sakurai! Sakurai...!
[KISARAGI chanting]
Just hang in there!
[YUUYA and KOMAKI groaning]
[KISARAGI continues chanting]
[YUUYA groans]
[KIRASAGI] Even the
Netherworld Hymn is of no use.
Is this of the
Bodhisattva Eye's power?
[KOMAKI] Aoi!
[CLAIRE] Hmm. Come on.
Hurry up and
finish this already?
Huh?
[chanting]
[grunts]
[YUUYA] Hey.
Tell us who you are.
Is that...?
[YUUYA] It's Raito Uhmon!
I see you guys are
goofing off as usual.
How's it goin', short 'n ugly?
I'm surprised you're
out this late, kid.
It's way past your bedtime!
[CLAIRE]
Why you... Why you...
bed-head freak!
Wow. Well that wasn't
too shabby there...
short 'n ugly.
Uh! One more of you
doesn't make any diff--uh!
[BOTH coughing]
[KOMAKI] What's going on?!
I hate the smell of incense.
[HINANO] Lady Komaki!
I think you should kindly
withdraw from this place.
Hinano? What...
are you doing here?
[CLAIRE] Ew...!
It stinks! Kill them,
Bodhisattva Eye!
You're here too, Yukino?!
It'll be all right,
we'll get you out quickly!
But we--
[RAITO yells]
[grunts]
Oh... poopy pants,
they ran away.
I bet it was that
scary face you're making.
[distant engine running]
[tires screeching]
[KYOUICHI] Hey, Tatsuma!
[TENDO laughs intensely]
[KYOUICHI] What the hell?
Hey, Tatsuma?
I-I couldn't protect her...
What's that?
[TATSUMA exhales]
Huh. Hey! Tatsuma!
[KYOUICHI] Hey, Tatsuma!
Damnit... Just hang tight.
We'll get you over
that old bag's place!
[AZUMABASHI] Hm. Can the
bike carry three people?