[CHILDREN] ♪ When, oh, when
will that bird come out. ♪
♪ Out, out, out
from its little cage. ♪
♪ The crane came in
during morning light. ♪
♪ The turtle came in
♪ Now guess who's
behind you?...♪
[TATSUMA]
Toshi! Kae! Hitomi!
[BOY]
Aww, no fair, Tatsuma!
[GIRL]
This is boring...
[SMALL GIRL] Tatsuma
always gets it right!
I think he can see with
his eyes closed!
[BOY]
Creepy!
[GIRL]
I'm not playing anymore!
[SMALL GIRL]
Let's go!
[SAYO]
Um...
You're Tatsuma Hiyu, aren't you?
[TATSUMA]
Uh, yes... Who are you?
[ANKO] The seniors will be
taking the long-awaited
entrance exam and
the student council president
will soon be stepping
down from her post, so share
your thoughts on
the upcoming new officers!
Um...Yes! They are all
committed to making our school
an even better place, and...
[Komaki laughing]
Hey, no laughing!
You know what, since you're
here, I'll also do an interview
with the captain of
the archery team!
Huh?! You didn't say
anything about an interview!
Thank goodness, Sakurai's
looking like she's normal again.
[KYOICHI] Out for a little
daytime stalking?
What in the hell are you doing,
you big pervert!
[YUUYA] I... I'm sorry!
I-It's not what you think!
Looks like
Sakurai's still shook up.
She's not the only one we
should all be concerned about.
[door slides open]
[KOMAKI]
Good afternoon.
Oh, Captain Sakurai!
So we won't be able to call you
"captain" much longer.
So what do you think it will
be like after you step down?
Oh, I don't know.
Probably get out of shape,
and won't be able
to hit anything.
[SAKUYA] If I ever lost the
ability to draw my bow...
[retches]
What... What the
hell's wrong with me? Huh?
It's all right...
I'm sure it'll be okay.
This is just a temporary thing.
Just calm down, and I'm sure
you'll be back to normal soon.
[TENDO] Mother...
Mother!
[CLAIRE]
Now what's this?
[TENDO]
Get lost.
[CLAIRE]
"Mother"?
[Claire giggles]
Oh, Mother!
[TENDO]
What do you want?
[EVIL MASK WOMAN]
We have seen the sign
of one of the treasures.
Go find it. It must be here
somewhere... somewhere in Tokyo.
[GRANDFATHER] Hisui,
listen to me carefully.
It is about
time that you also
learned of our family's "other"
mission, which we must uphold!
[MODERATOR]
What do you think about that?
[COMMENTATOR]
We call them "juvenile crimes"
but this doesn't
involve only children.
We have children killing their
parents and killing other
children; we have adults who
can't seem to grow up, and a
society and a country that
fosters these kinds of people!
That's why we propose a
government that will always
be closely in tune with
the local communities.
Did you see anything?
Seems normal. How about Aoi?
Haven't seen her at all.
She might've gone that way.
Let's go.
If she found something,
she might be in trouble.
Yeah.
[mischievous laughter]
[MAN]
Come On!
[Man screaming]
Are you all right?
[KYOICHI]
Hey, you alright?!
[AOI] It was nothing, it was
just some girl getting groped.
[KYOICHI]
People sure aren't too worried,
especially with all the crazy
shit that's been happening.
[AOI] It's not their fault.
No one has any idea that
evil demons are behind
all these terrible incidents.
Watta you think?
Let's keep
looking a little longer.
[distant scream]
[GANG MEMBER]
You sonnuva bitch!
[choking]
Damn it,
these guys aren't demons.
[KYOICHI]
This doesn't look good.
[ANKO] I can't blame her.
After seeing someone
she used to know end
up like that...
Doesn't matter. We can't waste
our time babying someone who
can't fight. I guess
the one who needs to hear
this isn't here, huh?
[ANKO]
Mmm...mmm....mmm?!
[ANKO] I have a sighting! I have
a confirmed location of our
subject! He's presently
held up in the Home Ec. room.
Ooh, yummy!
[chopping]
Ugh!
[door slides open]
[YUUYA]
Sakurai?
[KOMAKI] It's no use...
Why can't I draw my bow?
[Komaki crying]
Um, Sakurai...
I... I made you some lunch.
Would you like to try it?
You're such
an insensitive moron!
[Komaki weeping]
[traffic noises]
[KYOICHI]
W-What the hell is this?!
[TATSUMA] Something doesn't
feel right about this.
[KYOICHI] There's no way
this is done by a human!
[hysterical screaming]
Is that a chick?!
Is she...?
[KYOICHI] Hey, you!
Stay right there!
[AOI]
Wait!
[KYOICHI]
Huh? Are you crazy?!
Did you just see what she did?!
We can't let her go after that!
[AOI]
But...
[KYOICHI] We can
chit-chat about it later.
Right now we've
gotta stop that bitch!
[YUUYA]
Master.
Look, you, huh...
I'm sorry.
Oh man, what are we...
[TATSUMA]
You're heavy, Kyoichi.
[KYOICHI]
Will you shut up?
[YUUYA] Master, you saved me.
But I'm not good enough.
I can't save others.
I can't even
save the girl I love.
I want to protect those who
are dear to me but...
Please tell me what I should do.
[KYOICHI] Christ, you've
gotta be kidding me!
It's not just Sakurai anymore.
Now Musclehead and the Princess
are out of action too!
[KISARAGI] So then what
do you intend to do?
Like we got options? For now
the two of us will just have
to take out the demons
on our own.
Isn't that right, huh, Tatsuma?
Well, I guess currently
that is the only choice.
[KYOICHI] By the way,
have you had any luck?
Did you found out
where that Kozunu freak
could be hiding out?
[KISARAGI] My investigation
is still on-going.
[KYOICHI] Hey, you're not
holding anything back from us,
are you?
Of course not.
You can trust me.
[KYOICHI] Hey, gotta go,
I just remembered something
I gotta go take care of.
[TATSUMA]
Oh, you, too?
No choice. I need to
do what a certain someone
didn't have the balls to.
[birds chirping]
Who's there?! Stop spying on me!
Houraiji? What do you want?
What the hell are you doing?!
[dogs growling]
You need to stop the all this
cryin' and moanin', shemale!
You can't protect the
princess all the time.
You can't be the "prince
riding in on a white horse".
What?!
What's the matter? Did you
forget to strap your balls on
this morning?
Oh, that's right, you're a girl.
Maybe I should get some
action from you.
[slap]
Stop screwing with me!
That's a pretty nice little
bitch slap you got there.
[KYOICHI] That's better.
Now relax and get back to
being your old self again.
Hi.
You know... you can talk to me.
This is...
This is where it all started.
[YUUYA]
So this is where you are?
It seems had forgotten something
very important. I'm sorry.
[YUUYA] I didn't
consider your feelings.
What your favorite foods are, or
what you really like to eat.
[giggles]
What's this?
Sakurai... What happened
to you the other day
must have been difficult.
[YUUYA] Something like that
could effect anyone, even me...
But I know that you can overcome
this. So I want you to cheer up.
So Sakurai,
I will protect you!
Please you have nothing to fear,
and protect whatever it is
you want to protect!
[KOMAKI]
Daigo...
[GIRL IN FIRE] Aoi... Help!
Aoi! Help me... Aoi!
It's unsightly, isn't it? But I
would have endured a hundred
times worse if I could have
saved my friend back then.
[AOI] This is my stigma for
not being able to help her.
I'm afraid, terribly afraid of
people suffering or dying.
I think about how terrifying
and painful it must have been
for all those people who
were killed by demons
or who even became demons.
Those thoughts consume me so
much that I feel like I'm
being crushed sometimes.
I feel like I'm being pushed
around by some sort of massive
force that I
can't do anything about.
I guess that's
what we call fate, huh?
Maybe, you're right about that.
That's...
[TATSUMA]
Here.
I've had this birthmark all my
life. It made me feel different
from all the other kids.
I hated it.
But my father told me that
it was a special symbol that
I'll need someday, and
I need to take care of it.
I think I finally understand
what he meant when I came to
Magami High. Fighting all the
demons, it feels like I'm
finally realizing
life's purpose. Even if this is
my fate,... I'm glad
that I'm able to become
friends with all of you.
So let's face our fate
together without any fear.
Even if we don't know
where it might lead us.
[insects chirping]
[downtown traffic]
[people screaming]
[YUUYA]
What the hell's that?
That girl, she has no aura.
[AOI]
Huh?
Hey, do you think, she's going
to be more trouble than
the last one?
She's being
engulfed by the energy.
[AOI]
Please stop this!
[KYOICHI] Give it a rest! You
won't get through to her now!
That energy will
swallow your will!
[shrill screaming]
[KYOICHI]
Here it comes!
[screaming]
[AOI] It's no use!
I can't hold it!
[AOI]
Komaki!
[YUUYA]
Sakurai!
Thanks for the lunch box.
It was really good.
[KYOICHI] Keep your focus!
She's on her feet.
[maniacal giggling]
[screaming]
[YUUYA]
What a disaster.
[KOMAKI] Did she
use up all her power?
[YUUYA] Is this... Is this how
everyone with the Power ends up?
If you can stay
in control of yourself,
I'm sure you'll be okay.
Stop it.
You can't save her now.
[AOI] Don't die! Live!
Please... live! Live!
[choking]
A-Aoi!
[evil laughter]
There she is! I found you,
bo-dhi-satt-va eye!
[evil laughter continues]
[KOMAKI]
It's totally awesome!
I had no idea you had
power like that!