[dog barking]
[SAGAYA]
Please stop...
Please, don't do it!
What a cute little doggie.
[SAGAYA]
Stop!
No, please don't do it...
[SAGAYA]
No, don't!
No, don't!!
[dog whimpers]
[knocking]
[MOTHER]
Reiji, open this door!
Do you hear me?
Please help us.
Evil begone, be purified now!
[PSYCHIC] Cho-co-ran cha-ka-ran
so-wa-ka!
Evil begone, be purified now!
Cho-co-ran cha-ka-ran,
un-ja-la so-wa-ka...
[ALL]
Oh!
[giggles]
[PA]
Dr. Nakamura, Code Blue. ICU.
Until recently, a viral agent
has been the suspected cause
behind a string of incidents in
which have left some high school
students in a comatose state.
[NEWS ANCHOR] But, according
to some new information
we just received,
all of the victims of this
strange affliction, apparently
all went to the same private
middle school in Tokyo.
Authorities are now questioning
the faculty and staff members of
the private middle school.
As well as, focusing their
investigation on previous
interactions the victims
might have had with one another.
[YUUYA] Is this that crazy
"spiritual healing" stuff?
Yeah. But after seeing demons
and all that other crazy shit,
we should be the last
people to doubt her powers.
It appears that your friend has
had her consciousness imprisoned
in someone else's mindscape.
Someone with considerable power.
Mindscape?
[IWAYAMA]
Very powerful mental powers.
This person seems
to have an extremely
strong hold on your friend.
[KYOICHI] That sure doesn't
sound like you're average person
off the streets, huh?
[YUUYA]
Which means...
[TATSUMA]
It's someone who has the Power.
Who the hell would do this?
[IWAYAMA] In any case, if she
remains in this comatose state,
her body will break down and
she will die.
Her life is in danger.
Come on, you can do something,
can't you?! I mean, I believe
that's why we came to this
freakshow of a hospital!
[IWAYAMA] Well! Seems you've
learned to use that mouth
of yours quite well.
I remember a certain little
brat, who used to come to
me whining and crying.
No need to bring up
stupid stuff from the past!
[IWAYAMA] Alright, settle down,
the important thing right now is
for you to find out how to save
your friend, is that right?
Unfortunately, all
we can do right now
is provide
emergency treatment.
So, what do you mean?
The only thing I can do is to
attempt to stop the other
person's thoughts from fully
imprisoning her consciousness.
[IWAYAMA] To save her,
you'll have to find whoever
is behind this and stop
that person yourselves.
And you'll want to do that
as quickly as possible.
What if this person
really does have the Power?
We have to
stop whoever this is,
even if it means
we have to kill 'em.
[KOMAKI] But at
this rate, Aoi could...
Hey, have you been able to get
ahold of Kisaragi yet?
[KOMAKI] I've
called him a dozen times!
Where the hell could
he be at a time like this?
[dog whimpers]
[dog barks]
Go ahead.
[MAIKO]
Look! A doggie...
It was just there in front of
the hospital.
[KYOICHI]
Huh? A dog?
[IWAYAMA]
Oh, don't mind her.
Maiko sees all sorts of
spirits and other things.
Do you mean,
like, ghosts and stuff?
[MAIKO]
Mmmhmm.
I sense that he really wants to
see her pretty badly.
[ANKO]
Hmmm...
In the city... a baffling string
of unexplained comas...
Students of the same
private middle school...
[screams]
[ANKO]
Here it is.
[phone ringing]
[ANKO] Hello, I'm with
the Kagura Middle School
Alumni Association.
In fact, I'm a
graduate of Kagura myself...
I was hoping to ask you a
couple of questions about our
old middle school days.
[ANKO'S MOM] Kyoko!
Where do you think you're
going at this hour
of the night?!
[ANKO] I'm going
out for a walk, Mom!
[phone ringing]
[KOMAKI] Anko?
Aoi's is still unconscious.
We're at the hospital right now.
Huh? What?
[YUUYA] So... Anko said
to meet her in Tsukimidai
as soon as possible.
[KOMAKI] She didn't tell
me any details, but she said
it's got something to do with
what's going on with Aoi.
I want to find
out what's going on.
[KYOICHI] No worries!
Princess will be fine as long
as The Old Lady
watching over her!
[IWAYAMA] We must make sure
this holds until they find
the location
of the spell caster.
[MAIKO]
Right!
This is the guy! This is
the guy who's responsible
for putting Aoi in a coma!
Uh... Who's he?
[ANKO] Reiji Sagaya. He's the
one who's behind all those
high school students
falling into comas!
[YUUYA] H-How do
you know all this?!
[condescending laugh]
[ANKO] I am the soon-to-be
journalist phenom... Kyoko Tono.
When it comes to
students in the Tokyo area,
I know all about them!
I know their test scores,
I know everything
from what's in your lunch,
right down to the
holes in your socks!
What?...Really?! Wow.
[ANKO] All of the students
who've fallen into comas
were bullies from Kagura
Middle School.
And their main target of their
bullying was Reiji Sagaya.
Rumor has it that they were
pretty mean and ruthless
with him. It's surprising that
none of this was discovered.
[groans]
[blow lands]
[muffled grunting]
[muffled screaming]
[ANKO] Sagaya hasn't set
foot outside his house
since middle school.
But, since last spring,
rumor has been going around,
among the guys who
used to bully Sagaya,
that he's going
to come after each and
every one of them and get
even... in their dreams!
His parents even treat
him like some kind of monster
or something.
[KYOICHI]
This past spring?
In their dreams, huh?
If he really is another person
with this Power we all have what
you're saying can really happen.
But why is he after Aoi?
Why is he involving Aoi
and making her go
through all this?
[ANKO] I don't know...
But, Aoi also went to
Ka-gu-ra Middle School!
There's gotta be
some kind of connection.
[KYOICHI] Okay, then we have
to find out where he lives!
[ANKO]
Hold one second!
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
Why do you think
I've called you all here?
This is where he
lives! Unit #504.
Thank you, Anko.
Alright, let's do it!
[KOMAKI]
Kyoko...
I'm sorry.
I thought you...
No need to say it, I know!
Even if it would be the scoop
of the century,
your secret's safe with me,
so don't worry, okay!
[KOMAKI]
Huh?
A secret team of
justice fighters battling
the forces of evil,
now that's hot!
Do you think I'd let
anyone else in on that?
From now on,
I'm going to devote my time
to covering your story.
Don't worry! No one will know
it's you guys! But in return,
I get exclusive rights on the
story. You see, Komaki,
I do remember how all of you
guys saved me that night.
When Aoi regains consciousness,
tell her I'm sorry, okay?
It's not that I was afraid of
you guys. I was just a little
thrown off
guard, that's all.
[ANKO]
Tell her I said sorry.
If that's how you feel,
why not tell her yourself?
We're going to
protect Aoi no matter what!
Keep an eye on her
while we're gone, okay?
Leave it to me!
There was no reason.
They simply enjoyed watching
me suffer over and over.
I was a toy to them.
[SAGAYA] But then you,
you appeared one day.
[SAGAYA]
Please stop!
[BULLY] I hear that you
and Aoi Misato have been
feeding this mutt.
Yeah, who do you think you are
hanging around girls?
[SAGAYA]
No! Don't!
[SAGAYA] It's been
three years since then
and not a single day went by
when I didn't think of them.
Then one day, I got my chance.
[strained groaning]
You were the only
one who was different.
Aoi, I will
always protect you.
Let's stay here
together in this world.
Aoi... Why won't you
please open your eyes?
I get it. There's someone
holding you to that other world,
isn't there?
[SAGAYA]
Let's go, Tiny.
Oh, come on.
It was just getting good.
[KISARAGI] Just as I thought,
all the seals have been broken.
[EVIL MALE MASK] You...
are a Kisaragi descendent?
[IWAYAMA] O-in-shi-chi-ri
kya-ra-ro
ha-u-un-ken so-wa-ka,
O-in-shi-chi-ri kya-ra-ro
--Aoi... please hang on!
--ha-u-un-ken so-wa-ka.
Breaking the barrier
and getting in the perimeter
is quite impressive.
The doggie looks a little
different from earlier.
I won't hold back on anyone who
tries to take Aoi away from me.
A vengeful spirit?
What powerful hatred.
[TATSIMA]
It's okay, he's alive.
[KOMAKI]
This woman is okay, too.
It's as if they're sleeping.
[KYOICHI] I've got
a bad feeling about this.
[YUUYA]
He might be in there?
[TATSUMA]
What's that?
[SAGAYA]
Someone's getting too nosey.
Tiny, you take care of this.
It appears that our young
friends have located the body.
[SAGAYA]
Welcome to My Dream World.
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
Let go!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[SAGAYA] I'm sorry, but Aoi is
mine. I won't hand her over
to just anyone.
You bastard!
Newsflash, asshole
she doesn't belong to you.
So get your hands
off her, freak!
You have no idea what you've
got yourselves into, do you?
[SAGAYA] If you die in this
world you die in the real world.
And the four of you will die.
[reverberating footsteps]
[KYOICHI]
Wh-What in the hell?
[all scream]
[IWAYAMA] Oinshichiri
kyararo hauunken sowaka,
Oinshichiri kyara...
[ANKO]
Aoi!
[Inwayama screams]
[ANKO] Let me tell you
something about journalists:
We'll risk our lives anytime.
and I'll never give
Aoi over to you!
Daigo, Sakurai...
you guys alright?
[YUUYA]
Yeah! We're okay!
Hey guys! This is just a dream!
Focus your minds!
N-No way! This is my dream!
[KYOICHI] Too bad for you,
we're pretty "strong minded."
So we're not gonna fall
for your little freak show.
[IWAYAMA]
Takamizawa!
[MAIKO]
Please... stop this!
You were very sad, weren't
you? And full of so much pain.
Fu-ru-be, yu-ra-yu-ra...
You're free now.
You mustn't let the hatred
within you hold you forever.
Understand?
Now return to your true self.
[MAIKO] Go and save the
people who are dear to you.
[IWAYAMA] Release this
departed soul, begone.
Release this
departed soul, begone. Now.
If they keep coming back like
this, this will take forever!
[KYOICHI]
Tatsuma!
--Tatsuma!
--Hiyuu!
[KYOICHI]
Tatsuma! Get him!
Kyoichi...
Tiny? Why did you
come back? What about Aoi?
Why didn't you
bring Aoi with you?!
[dog whining]
[AOI]
Reiji, please stop this.
Doing this won't
save you or Tiny.
Aoi!
[AOI] This isn't
really what you want.
You should know
better than anyone.
I don't want anyone, especially
a friend to go through such
sorrow ever again! I can't
forgive people who harm others
just for amusement,
or who would take the life
of an innocent, little creature.
Be strong and courageous.
Put aside your hatred!
Be better than they were.
No. I... I don't care what
happens to me! But I at least...
I wanted to protect
Tiny at the very least!
[SAGAYA] Tiny! I'm sorry
I couldn't protect you.
I'm so... sorry.
I wanted to be strong... enough
to protect the ones I care for.
I wanted to be strong!
[AOI] You can change.
I know you can.
Use this power to
protect people instead.
[KYOICHI]
Great, what now?!
[TATSUMA]
Your dream world is collapsing.
[SAGAYA]
Thank you... Aoi...
[REPORTER] A follow-up story,
the high school students who had
unexplainably fallen into
comatose states five days ago
have all made a
full recovery as of...
[IWAYAMA] They seem
to be doing just fine.
We'll take care
of him here for a bit.
[KYOICHI] Look at him with that
peaceful smile on his face...
It seems like
his soul is saved now.
[ANKO] Aoi!
Oh, thank goodness!
The "Dream Master"...
What a joke.
None of these
"people" are of any use!
Well... now getting back
to my brave little friend.
[KISARAGI]
So I was right... It is them.
[TENDO]
I'm sorry to say this concludes
our business for today.
Until next time.