[YAGYU]
Descendant of Kozunu.
Do you want power?
Kozunu descendant.
[engine accelerates]
Can you see them?
Mhm.
Demon spirits
are everywhere.
Hey Sagaya, you sure
we're going the right way?
Uh, yeah. Just keep
on going straight.
All right, guys.
Straight ahead. Step on it!
[AZUMABASHI'S GANG yells]
♪
[TENDO] That man said to me,
"To exact your revenge,
you will need a mighty power.
The power to violate
or obliterate the laws
of this world...
and change it forever."
[TENDO] He told me
I could obtain that power,
if I was prepared to sacrifice.
I would have to
abandon my human heart.
[TENDO] What heart?
I don't need any "heart."
What good is it? I abandoned
that a long time ago.
My human heart?
What is a "heart"?
[TENDO chuckles]
What a useless organ.
Much more trouble
than it's worth.
What did the "human
heart" ever do for me?
What did the "human heart"
ever do for my mother?
[TENDO] Those people...
those miserable pigs
don't deserve to live.
So why don't you... kill them?
There's nothing stopping you.
[TENDO] I have been chosen.
I don't have to worry
about those swine anymore.
Destroy them!
Do them in!
End their lives!
Murder every last one!
And then...
become a demon.
[TENDO] I'll show you
once and for all
why we call it the Dark Arts.
[MIKURIYA'S PARTNER]
Hey, what's going on here?!
[MEN talking over eachother]
Hey, the line
just went dead.
[growls]
[RYUZAN] Don't be frightened.
Her barrier is
too strong to be
breached by
creatures of this ilk.
[ANKO]
You--you really think so?
[RYUZAN] Godspeed, you who
bear the stars of fate!
[groaning]
[TEITSU]
What's going on here?
[YAHIRO]
My head kinda hurts...
[OSHIGAMI] I can't see
the fire god anymore.
You okay, Sakurai?
Mm.
[KOMAKI] Aoi...
I'm coming to save you.
So, uh... now what?
Don't ask me, I dunno.
We're screwed whether
we stay here or go back.
Hey. You guys head
back to the hospital.
Go protect gramps, the old bag,
and the parapazzi chick.
[KYOUICHI] I'm countin' on you,
four kings of Sumida.
Okay, you stay safe, Boss!
Take it slow. Using telepathic
powers can be draining.
I'm okay. I can
sense her. She's close.
You rest here. We'll take
care of everything else.
No way. I'm going with you!
[KYOUICHI]
You'd only get in our way.
[ALL] Huh?
[KYOUICHI]
You've done your job.
But we'll take it from here.
[SAGAYA] But I--
Heh. We're pros at this.
Don't worry, we're going
to save Aoi, I promise you.
[AOI screaming]
[TENDO laughs]
Oh, Mother... I hope
you're able to see this
wherever you may be. This
world that made you suffer,
[TENDO] this world that tried
to destroy the Kozunu clan,
forced us to
hide away like mice.
With this hand
I will make it ours!
Ew! What's that?
[CLAIRE] That is so gross!
[IWAYAMA gasps]
[ANKO]
What's going on now?
[IWAYAMA]
It seems he has come.
[RYUZAN]
He has been awakened?
The Head of...
The Demoniacal Art.
This is our begining...
the Kozunu Horde!
[roaring]
[KYOUICHI] Kozunu!
[TENDO] Hm.
Oh, it's them.
[TENDO laughs]
My goodness,
you sure are persistent.
It can't be!
They've manifested
themselves?
Forget about
the other freaks,
we're here for Aoi.
[RAITO] It's him. He's right
in front of me, Ryouichi!
Hey, lightening head!
[bellows]
Ignorant fool.
[grunts]
[RAITO yells]
Aw, come on! Try
keepin' your cool! Crap!
Kill them.
[HINANO] Lord Hiyu,
please leave this to us.
[YUKINO]
Please go and save Misato!
Just do what you want.
Outta my way!
[KYOUICHI yells]
[grunts]
Yukino!
[gasps]
[YUUYA] Crap, what now?
[BOTH yell]
[chuckles]
[KISARAGI screams]
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
[TATSUMA] Aoi?
[TENDO chuckles]
[gasps]
[TATSUMA yells]
[growling]
Aoi. No...
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Shut up. I can
take care of myself!
[gasps]
[RAITO] Ah!
[RAITO] Not with that.
That's for...
Stop playing around and
get your head in the game!
[YUKINO] A wall of wind!
We're sealed in.
Sister...
[MONSTER bellows]
[YUUYA and KOMAKI grunting]
[grunts]
[TENDO laughs]
[TATSUMA] Kozunu!
[TENDO] Don't worry,
I'm just borrowing her
for a little while, until
her soul becomes more stable.
But for now I think...
I'll have a little fun
with you first, Tatsuma Hiyu.
[gasps]
[TENDO laughs]
Here.
Go on.
[KYOUICHI] Tatsuma?
Tatsuma!
[squelch]
[coughs]
Aoi...
Kisaragi!
[KISARAGI] Lady Aoi...
Uh?!
I already told you, I'm not
going to let you kill her.
[TATSUMA] Aoi.
Aoi, can you hear me?
I want to say...
sorry. I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to do
anything for you...
even though anyone could
see you were suffering.
[TATSUMA]
I didn't tell you...
I was glad to have
met you all, right?
I've never... never had
a group of friends
like you before.
[TATSUMA] I was so happy,
and I said I wanted
to protect you all.
That's what I wanted...
but then...
[TATSUMA]
Aoi, you were so worried
you couldn't protect us...
but you know, you were
wrong about that, Aoi.
You may not realize this,
but you protected all of us
more times than I could count.
Time and time again...
you came through for all of us.
[TATSUMA] You may not have
realized it, but believe me
Kyouichi, Sakurai, Daigo,
all the others, we all have.
We were only able to
make it this far
because you were there for us,
because you put yourself
in harm's way to protect us.
Listen to me. We all need you.
I don't care what kind
of power you have.
I'm going to do whatever
I can to protect you.
We're all going to try.
We're going to do our
best to keep you safe.
I promise.
[TATSUMA]
Please, come back to us...
Aoi...
[gasps]
[growling]
Could it be?!
[yells]
[sobs softly]
He couldn't have
broken my spell!
Aoi is--Aoi is mine,
do you hear me?!
[TENDO] Aoi!
You won't hurt them.
[gasps]
[AOI] I won't let you.
I'll protect them.
I'll protect the whole world!
[YUUYA yells]
[BOTH breathing heavily]
[MONSTER groans]
Movin' kinda slow...
huh, dungeon master?
Shut up and fight, simpleton.
Ha! Well, well.
Kisaragi, looks like still
got a little fight left in ya.
[KYOUICHI] So have you made up
your mind on your duty yet?
Stop talking.
[RAITO] To protect...
Fight to protect...
K-Kill her! I have no
further use for that girl!
Kill the Bodhisattva Eye and
every last one of her friends!
[KYOUICHI] Let's finish this!
[grunts]
Daigo!
Haven't I already said,
I'm never gonna let
anything happen to you.
[MONSTER yells]
[KISARAGI screams]
Hisui, no!
Huh?
Even if it... costs my life.
You're so predictable,
ya furry hairball.
Get... outta my face!
[grunting]
This looks like a
good time to leave.
[CLAIRE] Everything's got
this out of control
because you refused
to listen to his orders.
Betcha you sure
feel dumb now, huh?
[quavers]
[yells]
[MONSTER yells]
[screams]
[gasps]
[RAITO yells]
[yells]
Oh, Mother...
Recognize your toy?
I wanted to make sure
you got it back,
you fuckin' asshole!
[screams]
Ah!
Do you think that means...?
It seems...
like they did it.
[ANKO giggles]
Is it over?
Hey you haven't seen
the other two, have you?
[AZUMABASHI]
What?! We lost 'em?!
We screwed up
pretty good this time.
Now we're not gonna
be able to get anywhere!
How'm I gonna face the boss?
[TENDO whimpers]
[KYOUICHI] Hey.
Pretty sweet jamboree. Hmm?
[laughs]
"Jam session."
Hello!
[TATSUMA] Ah!
Miss Takamizawa.
[MAIKO chuckles]
We had to join you.
[AOI] Reiji! You must
be feeling better.
[SAGAYA] Yeah. I could
say the same to you.
[KOMAKI] What are the
two of you doing here?
We know that you think
we'll just get in your way.
And we might not
be able to help much...
but still...
[BOTH chuckle softly]
[TENDO groans]
You filthy insects...
Please stop! I felt
your painful sorrow.
I felt it when you put me
in contact with your heart.
I know that's why
you're doing all of this;
to end your sadness... But--
Shut up!
[TENDO] Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up, shut up!
You scum... You bastards!
[AOI] Tatsuma.
[TATSUMA] Tendo. Kozunu.
I want... to save you, too.
Don't give me that shit!
[gasps]
[TENDO grunting]
Hiyu! Huh?
Kyouichi?
[grunting]
[TENDO] Why do you despise
the Kozunu line so much?!
You're the one who gave
birth to me! This world...
[exhales heavily]
The whole world!
You stupid people!
You all--you all made me!
This world can--
it can--it can just--
[gasps]
[TATSUMA] Even so...
I still want to... save you.
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[breathing heavily]
[TENDO groaning]
It's not--it's not over.
No.
Not so soon...
[TENDO] Mother,
make sure you watch, okay?
I can still do it. I can.
I can...!
[ALL gasp]
[KYUICHI] What now?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[TENDO] How...?
What's going on?
[DEMONS moaning]
No. Let go!
Let go of me!
--Kozunu!
--What are you doin'?
Get back!
But he--
[CLAIRE screams]
What did I do? Lord Yagyu!
Lord Yagyu, please don't!
This does not
look good, you guys.
Let's get out of here.
Tatsuma!
Give it up already!
He's toast!
[KYOUICHI] We gotta go!
[running footsteps]
[YAGYU] And so
one star has fallen.
The foolish...
young Tendo Kozunu.