[electric guitar shredding]
[RYOICHI]
Shit! It's shit!
[hysterical scream]
[RYOICHI]
Who the hell are you two?!
[TENDO] How about if
I give you some power?
Doing this isn't gonna
accomplish anything, man.
You hate them, right?
You want to get back at them,
don't you? Those guys
who made an ass of you...
Then why don't you do just that?
There's nothing that can stop
you! 'Cause you, lucky boy,
have been chosen!
You don't have to worry about
those idiots anymore!
Just kill them!
Do them in!
You hear what I'm saying?
End all of their lives!
It's so easy!
Just become a demon.
[TENDO] I'll show you what's
known as...the Dark Arts.
[screams]
[GIRL] Help me, Aoi!
Please! Help me! Aoi!
[heavy breathing]
[engine purrs]
[MARIA]
Good morning!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[KYOICHI] Gotta love
those summer uniforms, huh?
I think girls should
have to wear short skirts
whether it's hot
or cold out, don't you?
Or better yet, make
'em all wear swimsuits!
You know what that
would be? Sexual harassment.
Oh, come on,
lighten up, would ya?
[KYOICHI]
Hey.
Whaddaya say we, uh, head
down to the beach and pick up
some honeys this summer, huh?
Hmm.
What?
[TATSUMA] You're not
being serious are you?
[KYOUCHI]
Man, Tatsuma.
Why can't you just
let a guy dream, huh?
[GIRL] Do you
know what this is?!
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
Is that a Crow CD?!
[EXCITED GIRL]
Whoa!
Is that the unfinished one that
they've been talking about?
[KOMAKI] So, what are you
gonna do over the summer, Aoi?
Huh?
There's a tournament
that's gonna keep me pretty busy
the first couple of
weeks of the break.
But I wanna make
sure that we can still--
I know!
Maybe we can go on vacation!
I mean, this is gonna be
our last summer together
as high-schoolers, so we
should make it fun, right?
I'm sorry, but I
can't go anywhere.
Why not? 'Cause
student council? Oh!
The college entrance exams...
No, that isn't it.
Aoi! Listen: you've
got to let it go!
[clock tower strikes]
[door opens]
[STUDENT]
Teacher in the room.
Aoi, we'll
talk about this later.
Right.
[STUDENT]
Bow.
Return to your seats.
[TEACHER] So, this will be my
third time lecturing at this
school, and as you know today's
lecture will cover questions
that came up during
my previous visits...
[KISARAGI] It was a demon
that attacked you the other day.
[YUUYA]
A...what, now?
[KOMAKI]
A demon? You mean, like...
[KISARAGI] Demons do exist.
They've made themselves known
numerous times
throughout history.
But in recent years
they've tended to remain
hidden in the shadows.
Are you telling us that demons
are behind all those murders?
[AOI] But how...how can
you be so sure, Hisui?
[KISARAGI] For generations it
has been my family's "duty"
to fight these creatures of
darkness, no matter the cost.
Lady Misato, I
never would've imagined
that you'd become involved.
I can't believe this.
This is just total crap!
Oh, come on!
You were there, you saw
it with your own two eyes.
I still don't know...
All right!
[KYOICHI]
So, like, this uh...
power thing... that we used.
What is that exactly?
[KISARAI]
I'm not sure.
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
[KISARAGI] But still, even if I
could explain it in full,
I doubt you could comprehend it.
[KYOICHI]
Huh, what did you just say?!
Hisui, please.
There is something known
as the "Dragon Stream."
Dragon Stream?
[KISARAGI] It's a current of chi
that flows throughout the earth.
Oh!
I know about chi!
It's that, y'know Feng
Shui hocus-pocus, isn't it?
It tells you if you put
your couch by the front door
or across the room determines
whether you're gonna be
happy or rich, right?
So, you gonna be an
interior decorator now?
Knock it off.
Knock what off?
[KISARAGI] There's been a
disturbance in the current
of the Dragon Stream.
I think that could be the reason
the demons seem to be making
a resurgence of late.
Add to that your
powers, as well as...
In any event,
I'll take care of this.
Until then, I'm asking
you to please try to stay
out of harms way.
I trust that that's
understood, Lady Misato?
Aoi... where could you
have disappeared to?
Uh hey, Sakurai? You know I
brought some meat and potato
stew today, but I made a little
bit too much just for me, so
if you wanna, uh.. y'know,
maybe have lunch with me, then--
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[YUUYA]
Wait! Hold on!
It took me three days
to learn how to make it...
[COOK]
Here you go, nice and hot.
I'll bring the bowl
back after school.
I sure would
appreciate it, Kyoach.
I told you, don't call me that!
[COOK]
Aloha, Kyoach.
What?
I just wanted to thank
you for the other day.
What?
When the Mor-yo
demon attacked us.
Oh...
If the two of you hadn't
been on lookout someplace else,
that thing might have
claimed even more victims.
So I wanted to
thank you in person,
for all the quick thinking.
So, thank you, from
the bottom of my heart.
I imagine that was your plan,
to split away from the rest of
the group to save more lives?
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
[AOI] If we'd all stayed
together in one spot...
well, the demon
may have gotten away.
But you anticipated that and--
[KYOICHI] Let's not read too
much into this, all right?
It makes me sick how you guys
pretend to be best buddies
with each other all the time.
[AOI]
But, Kyoichi...
And you can quit
hovering around me,
'cause I ain't
buying into your crap!
I'm not lookin' to join forces
with you losers or anyone else.
To be honest with you,
I don't give a rat's ass
if anyone dies over this!
I just want the
chance to test my strength
against somebody
who's worth my time!
Got that?
[AOI] But... Even so... none of
us really understand anything
about our powers in the first
place, so... don't you think it
would be better if... well,
Hisui thinks it would be better
if we all joined forces and--
And have you get in
my way? Forget it!
[KYOUICHI] You'd just
be dead weight in a fight
and you know it.
If I had nine lives to
spare then maybe, maybe
I'd consider
teaming up with you.
[KYOUICHI] If you don't like
hearing that maybe you should go
do something useful on your own.
I'm sorry.
Aw, shit.
Now my food's all cold.
[TATSUMA] You might've gone
a little overboard.
But I understand how you feel.
[KYOICHI]
How I feel?
[MARIA] Mr Inugami!
I figured I'd find you here.
What?
Don't you "what" me!
You and I've got a problem
if you don't attend
that meeting.
What meeting?
About guidance counseling
over summer vacation!
Oh.
That's right.
A lot of disturbing stuff has
been going on lately,
and we never know
what's gonna happen
once those kids are
away from us on break.
And they're having
enough trouble as it is
with entrance exams
coming up, you know.
I'm telling you all
this assuming that you care
about your students'
emotional states and how they--
Oh!
[MARIA]
What is it?
You've been hurt very
badly in the past, haven't you?
Tell me, what happened?
Ugh!
Why did I even bother?!
I've had about enough of you.
[INUGAMI] Worried about
my students, are you?
Well, aren't you
the model teacher...
[INUGAMI] These are
from central Japan...
[KOMAKI] You're really
serious about this, huh?
You know, that
Kisaragi guy said
that we should
stay out of trouble.
I think maybe we
should listen to him.
Who the heck is this guy?
He's the son of an antiques
dealer who worked with my father
and grandfather
for number of years.
He recently inherited
the family business.
So he'll come by
the house with old pots
or other weird artifacts
that my father's asked him
to find for us, but he...
[terrified scream]
[panting]
[low growl]
[roar]
[snarls]
Tha...that's Kyouichi?
[low growl]
[YUUYA]
What are you two doing here?!
[AOI]
Yuuya?
[KYOUICHI] Meathead?
What the hell are you...
What do you people
think you're doing?!
[KISARAGI] This creature
is not the sort of thing that
you can defeat on your own.
[REPORTER]
It's utter chaos here!
I-I've never witnessed
anything like the panic that's
going on behind me right now!
It's because of the crows!
A huge flock of
crows is attacking--
[REPORTER]
Watch out!
[ANCHORMAN]
Ms. Amano, are you still there?!
[pandemonium]
[MAN IN CAR]
Oh my God!
[crash]
[television static]
[KISARAGI]
A call about Lady Misato?!
[KOMAKI]
That's right!
I got a call from one
of her housekeepers.
[YUUYA] She wasn't
at school either.
I thought maybe
she'd be over here, but...
[KOMAKI]
What's going on?
Why did you let her
go out there alone?
I told the five of you that
you'd have to stick together
to fight these demons. From the
start I told you that I'd only
assist if you all stuck
together, but now look at you!
It's really easy for you
to stand there and make
accusations, but we
don't know what she does
after she goes home!
[KISARAGI] Quickly!
You've got to go find her
before it's too late.
[KOMAKI]
Daigo, let's go!
[YUUYA]
Right!
[door slams shut]
[KISARAGI]
Lady Misato...
[pandemonium]
[AOI]
I'm so sorry...
[AOI] Someone else is
killed almost every night now...
It seems like the
demons must be behind it.
It makes me feel so restless;
I don't want to just sit back
and let it happen again.
But that doesn't
mean that you have to--
[YUUYA]
I feel the same way.
[KYOICHI] Yeah, and I
just want to know how far
my powers can take me
once it comes down to a fight!
Right, Tatsuma?
[TATSUMA]
Huh?
I think we
should take action.
Please, Hisui,
let me do something!
[KISARAGI]
But, Lady Misato...
[AOI] I can't just do nothing!
If there's any way at all that
I'd be able to
protect somebody...
Or not just one person--
if I could protect the people!
of this city...! Please, Hisui!
I'm begging you!
It seems that the crowd
disturbance is over for now.
However, no one can predict when
the next attack might occur.
The experts are
divided on this matter,
but it seems safe to say that it
will likely be some time before
people here feel at ease again.
[siren]
[AOI]
I'm so sorry...
[siren]
Picking through the trash is
one thing,
but I've never actually
seen a crow attack anyone.
[ANKO] That's because crows
hardly ever attack humans.
It's not in
their nature, you know?
[KYOICHI]
Anko?!
[ANKO] Crows only usually attack
during their breeding season.
Y'know, when someone comes too
close to a nest full of chicks.
But even in those cases
it's just individual birds
that attack,
not an entire flock.
[KYOUICHI]
So...
you wanna tell us what
the hell you're doing here?
You know I could ask
you the same exact thing.
What could possibly motivate
two juvenile delinquents
to investigate this incident?
Oh. Is that what we're doing?
We're not "investigating",
we're just out doing
a little shopping.
For what?
Uh, well it's...
It's for underwear.
Ugh.
Man, this guy
can't lie for shit!
Damn!
Stubborn idiot...
[AOI] Let go of me!
Kyouichi, please!
I told you to
stay out of the way!
I'm gonna do anything I can to
help. I know that I might seem
helpless compared to the
rest of you guys and maybe
a little bit weaker, but I--
Glad to hear you understand.
Now get your ass home,
princess.
I won't!
Wha'd you say?
I won't go home.
I'm staying here!
[KYOICHI]
You little...
[KOMAKI]
Horaiji!
Aoi, are you okay?
[KYOUICHI]
Shit, they're all here.
Horaiji! I certainly hope
that you weren't being
a total jerk to Aoi again.
Ha! I was giving your
girlfriend a reality check.
She needs to get her
useless little ass home.
Say that again!
Stop!
It's okay.
You know, why don't you
go home with her, too? I mean,
it looks to me like you just
wanna have some fun with
Miss Student Council, right?
So why don't you two
run along to her
little mansion and play house?
Asshole!
Sakurai, don't.
Hey, Daigo, don't you
ever get tired of that
"daddy will protect you"
song and dance? I do.
Horaiji! You sonnuva...
Just stop it, everyone!
[ANKO]
What's going on?
Got me...
A demon.
[battle cry]
[AOI]
But he's...
It's a guy.
Not a demon.
[YUUYA] You're telling
me that he has the Power?
You mean...That guy?
Things got very interesting.
So, do you think
that we should tell him...
That his enemies are here?
[KYOUICHI]
Son of a bitch!
[RAITO] Guess I was
right that you weren't just an
ordinary buncha onlookers.
Horaiji!
Not you.
Komaki!
Don't argue with me.
You're not strong enough to
fight this guy and you know it.
Please, just
stay out of the way.
Where is Ryoichi?
Ryoichi?
What are you talking about?
Tell me! You've all got
the Power, so there's no way
you don't know!
[RAITO] Are you and Ryoichi in
this together? Did he have
something to do with those
crows attacking everyone?
[KYOICHI] I have no idea
what you're talking about
You're talkin' crazy.
[RAITO] Yeah, like
hell you don't know.
I'll beat it outta you!
Daigo, get outta the way!
You can't do this on your own.
Sakurai...what the hell?
Sakurai.
[KYOUICHI]
Didn't I tell you to go home?!
[KOMAKI] Shut up!
Don't tell me what to do!
[YUUYA] Stop it, you
guys! Horaiji's right,
you should get outta here.
[RAITO] The three of
you together and this is all
you've got? This is
one hell of a jam session.
Let's rock!
[ANKO]
He's glowing! No.
He's flying! No.
He's glowing again!
Wha-What's going on...?
[explosion]
Man, that was close.
[pained screaming]
[light chuckle]
[TATSUMA]
Aoi, no!
Aoi.
Get out of here.
You idiot.
Get the hell out of here
before you get yourself killed.
Go on!
Go home!
I'm protecting you!
It's what I do.
[chuckles]
[RAITO] You sure about that?
'Cause you don't seem to have
very much power...
[AOI] I think that you're
making a huge mistake here.
We're not your enemies.
I have a feeling
we're after the same thing.
I think you're looking
for whoever's behind these
crow attacks, and that's exactly
what we're doing here, too.
We should be working
together instead of trying to
destroy each other.
And what if I said I don't
believe you.
If I have to, I'll fight
you with every ounce of
strength I have!
I'm going to protect my friends
and the people of this city,
no matter what it takes!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi...
Sounds like fun.
Let's see if you can
protect your weak little
friends from this.
[battle cry]