[YUKINO] The five Buddhist
shrines that sealed the demons
have been destroyed.
[HINANO] Along with the seals
under Kisaragi's protection
were also broken...
[YUKINO] The Eight-Hands-Breadth
Sword was found and
stolen by the
Demoniacal Horde.
And the vessel
of the Golden Dragon?
[HINANO] He was there
and was in contact.
[RYUZAN]
I see.
It appears the stars
of fate are on the move.
[gentle breezze]
This isn't it...
this won't do.
[SAKUYA]
This arm...
[screaming]
[maniacal laughter]
[choking]
[screaming]
You stay back.
Hiiyah!
[KYOICHI]
Not too bad...
But!
You're gonna need more than
technique if you wanna win.
Come on!
One more time!
[KYOICHI] Why don't
you just give it up?!
Please, once more!
You're not gonna get any better
if you let your emotions
get control of you.
[ANKO] There were
more attacks last night.
[YUUYA] There're been
a lot of incidents lately.
[KOMAKI] I have a strange
feeling it's not all demons.
You're exactly right.
[ANKO] There've been more
and more copycat incidents
to look like demons.
At this point, it's hard
to tell which ones are real
and which ones are fake.
People are dying around here.
There's nothing fake about that.
I'm sorry.
But why so many?
Guess all this means is that
there's no difference between
people and demons.
So, what is it
that you do know?
This one that's been going after
members of athletic clubs...
It kinda feels like the work of
demons to me. What do you think?
The news reports that "part of
the body" has been dismembered,
but it's the arms they're going
for, the right arm to be exact.
Why would anyone...?
[KYOICHI]
What does Kisaragi say?
Nothing, really.
It's impressive to see how hard
you guys have been working, even
doing this special
training and all...
And Aoi even dusted
off her old na-gi-na-ta!
I had no idea!
Without strength in my
moves with the naginata,
I don't know if
I can help to fight.
Aoi will be okay.
We all decided to do this.
That's right,
we'll all do it together!
This will have to do.
[MIKURIYA's PARTNER] Get the sea
lice to the lab for analysis.
[DETECTIVE] It's possible
the same culprit's behind both
the I-ha-ra parasite incident
and the No-za-wa incident.
Ko-zu-ka's barnacle incident
seems to resemble the I-wa-ta
murder from the other day.
The man killed in Miya Park
appears to be a copycat murder
after the unusual
string of incidents.
We've got the suspect in
custody back at the station.
[phone ringing]
[RYUTA]
Hey, it's me.
About that high school student
from the other day...
[MIKURIYA]
The one with the holes?
Yeah. They're not holes.
They're honeycomb cells...
like that of a beehive. And
just like the other incidents,
the right arm
was completely severed.
[ambulance siren]
Hey, I said I'm sorry! I didn't
think I'd actually hit you!
[KYOICHI]
Oh, man.
Hey, Tatsuma, what's that?
Long underwear!
Underwear? You mean that
time from the other day?
[KYOICHI] You weren't making
that shit up to fool her?
[TATSUMA] Yeah. You do realize
it will be getting cold soon.
[KYOICHI]
And how old are you?
[ANKO]
This shatters the image of the
mysterious transfer student!
[TATSUMA] They're not for me.
I was planning to send them
to my dad.
[KYIOCHI]
Okay, I certainly hope so.
[YUUYA] "Send" it to him? So,
he lives away from your family?
No, I do.
I live in Tokyo on my own.
Really?
A new detail uncovered!
The mysterious transfer student
is living "on his own"?!
Lucky him, it seems like it
must be fun living all alone.
[YUUYA] Your parents couldn't
come to Tokyo with you?
Well, at their age it
would be too difficult.
Really, how old are they?
And so... you live apart from
your parents? Not simply apart,
but as a high school student
living alone in Tokyo!
[ANKO] Wow! Why is that? What's
the reason for your situation?
Alright already. Let's go get
some ramen. I'm starvin'.
[KOMAKI]
Well, I have archery practice,
so I'll see you guys later.
Oh, right. You've got that
tournament coming up, right?
Yeah, this will be my last
archery tournament at the
high school level.
I got to do my best.
You will come to watch,
right, Aoi?
Uh, yeah, sure!
Um... Hey, I'll come to
cheer you on, too, Sakurai.
Thanks, guys!
[CLAIRE] Why don't
you stop fussing over this
Kisaragi guy or whoever, and
go for something bigger?
[TENDO] You do know it's your
fault my plan went awry.
[CLAIRE]
Oh, shut up...
[TENDO] The seeds have
been sown, haven't they?
[CLAIRE] We haven't done very
much and I know that "he"
won't be happy about it.
[cat meows]
[Tendo laughs]
What's so funny?!
Oh, nothing. I couldn't
care less about your "him".
I will do whatever I please.
Understand?
[TENDO] Where the hell are they?
The Dragon Stream should have
activated their powers. They
should have appeared by now.
And that one's
getting on my nerves.
[NEWS ANCHOR] This is supposedly
an effect of gelidium jelly.
[NEWS ANCHOR]
Our other top story...
Police have identified the body
that was found on the roadside
of Na-ka-mu-ra in the Ne-ri-ma
ward in the early morning
of the 20th. The victim is
20-year-old E-i-ta I-ke-da.
[YUUYA] So where do
you guys want to go?
[KYOICHI]
The usual spot, of course.
[TATSUMA] Say, Kyoichi, do
they have strawberry ramen?
--What?
--You...You there!
I sense a very powerful light
emanating from you...
This light is mighty and
illuminates all.
Master Arai!
It has been some time, Daigo.
It's so good to see you.
When did you get back?
I returned just the other day.
What can this old geezer
possibly be a "master" of?
Watch your mouth, Kyoichi!
It's quite all right.
My name is Ryuzan Arai and
you two are Daigo's friends
from school, I take it?
--What?
--Did he say "friend"?
[YUUYA] We all go to the same
school, his name's Houraiji.
And that's Hiyu.
[RYUZAN]
You have a nice face, young man.
[light laugh]
Daigo, has it begun? Has
time begun to flow inside you?
[MIKURIYA]
A nasty affair...
They say the bodies were
completely dried up. If you
think about it, it's pretty
disturbing 'cause it seems like
this is happening
more often around here.
I wonder what the police are
doing about this? But even if
they do catch whoever's
behind these incidences,
that's not going to bring
back the dead, you know?
Christ. You have to
feel really bad for all
the victims' families.
I'm sorry, Excuse me.
[SAKUYA] Not it... This isn't
it! This isn't the arm either.
[SAKUYA] Komaki... Sakurai?
Komaki Sakurai!
[maniacal laugh]
[KISARAGI] The Kozunu clan...
they summon demons, disturb the
Dragon Stream...
And beyond that,
the Eight-Hands-Breadth Sword...
With that and the disturbances
in the Dragon Stream...
It couldn't be...
the Bo-dhi-satt-va Eye?!
Um, so...
You made all this yourself?
Yeah, I got up early and
spent nine hours preparing it.
Sweet!
Hey! Get your
damn hands off the food!
Hey, you too Tatsuma.
[KYOICHI]
Hey, spread the love!
[YUUYA] The most important thing
is that Sakurai will like it.
Mmm...
It's better than I expected!
Hey hubby, lunches made by the
wives are always best.
What the hell's
that supposed to mean?!
[ANKO]
Well, now that looks good!
Hey, Komaki,
nice to see you again!
How've you been, Komaki?
Oh, hi guys. It's really
nice to see you! I was hoping
to get to see you guys here!
Good luck in the tournament,
Komaki.
Hey, who are they, Anko?
They're on the Yukimigahara
High School archery team.
Hinano Oribe and her
older sister, Yukino, who
specializes in the naginata.
[ANKO] Hinano and Komaki
are long-time rivals,
and their duels are always
the main attraction
to these tournaments. Plus,
the Oribe sisters are as smart
as they are pretty,
and they're quite popular
even at our school!
It'd be a total waste not
to do an article on them!
Who cares?
Hey, do you guys
want some of this?
No thanks, I've got other
stories that I need to cover
today, so I've gotta run but
you guys have a good time.
[KYOICHI]
Your loss.
Hey, you two want some of this!
This shit's good!
What did I do?
Don't scare my little sister!
Let's go.
Komaki, Number 2.
[SAKUYA]
Komaki...
No... No... No... No...
No, no, no, no!
No... No...
Komaki... Sakurai!
[clapping]
[MIKURIYA] Christ, you have
to feel really bad for all
the victims' families.
[OFFICIAL]
Who's that?
Huh? Looks like trouble...
[OFFICIAL] Hey,
there's a sign over there.
No one can be admitted
unless they're involved
with the tournament.
[sharp inhale]
[shrill screaming]
[all screaming]
It's the demons!
They just come
out whenever they want!
I will protect them!
[screaming]
[evil laughter]
You'll give it to
me, right, Sakurai?
You're a nice person...
You'll give it to me, won't you?
Gimme your arm!
[buzzing]
[AOI]
Komaki!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
Komaki!
--My arm's broken...
--Let go!
--Give me this one!
--Damn it, let go!
[AOI] Komaki! Stop it!
Let go of her!
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
[KOMAKI] Aoi! Aoi!
You're bleeding...
Don't worry about me. Help her!
I told you don't let
emotions dictate your actions!
But...!
Just keep your
ass there for now!
--Aoi!
--Kyoichi!
Take it easy! Aoi!
I got this!
[screams]
Hmm.
Tatsuma!
Go ahead! I'm okay.
[TENDO]
Who are you?!
It doesn't matter.
You'll still die!
Please let go,
Komaki!
--What's wrong?!
--I want to...
I want to... protect them!
I don't want anyone else to...
[KYOICHI] C'mon, let go!
You are one pushy bitch!
[KOMAKI]
Daigo!
I got it...
[bellows]
W-Whoa, not good!
[KYOICHI]
Aww, can't fly away?
Get ready to die, Bug Girl.
Don't do it!
[TENDO] Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Thank goodness...
Again... I've been made a
fool of by Komaki Sakurai.
She's so innocent with The
Power. She crushes me again.
Nothing has changed since then.
[KOMAKI] What in the hell are
you talking about? You act as if
you know me or something.
[SAKUYA]
What? You don't remember?
[Sakuya chuckles]
[KOMAKI]
What?!
[SAKUYA] She says
she doesn't remember!
[laughing]
[KOMAKI]
Watch out, Aoi.
[AOI]
It's all right.
I don't know what horrible
things you've been through,
but what
you're doing won't help.
All this, won't help
make things right.
Please stop all this killing.
You don't have to do this!
Why can't you just become
friends with Komaki? I'll do
whatever I can to help you get
through this! So please stop,
all this killing.
Please! Please.
Give it back.
[SAKUYA] Give me my arm back.
Give it back... Give it back...
If I ever lost
the ability to draw my bow...
No!
[car alarm goes off]
Sakuya...
[YUUYA]
Sakurai!
I can't protect them...
I couldn't protect her...
I couldn't...
We've practiced
really hard for this.
So let's go out
and try our best!
Sure.
So that we
don't have any regrets.
If I ever lost the
ability to draw my bow...
...then I might as well die!
You know how I feel!
I'm gonna do my
best and not lose!