[insects chirping]
[ANSWERING MACHINE] We are
not available to take your call.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
[machine beeps]
[AOI ON MACHINE] Hisui?
This is Aoi. Where are you?
Are you all right?
[AOI'S MOTHER] Thank you
very much, Mr. Kisaragi.
Oh, my, and who is this?
This is my grandson, Hisui.
I brought him along
to introduce him to you.
[AOI]
Mom?
[AOI'S MOM] Ah, you're just in
time. Introduce yourself, Aoi.
[AOI]
Sure, mom.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Aoi Misato.
[giggles]
[KOMAKI]
Aoi!
Good morning, Aoi!
Good morning.
Huh... How are you doing?
Is everything okay?
You seem a little down...
Oh, no... I'm alright.
[KOMAKI] It's nice to know that
even you get a little depressed
at the beginning of a new term.
I'm really disappointed
that we didn't get to hang
out at all
over the summer break.
But we get to spend time
together here at school.
[NAGINATA INSTRUCTOR]
Lady Aoi!
Yes, ma'am!
[fight noises]
[NAGINATA INSTRUCTOR]
Excellent job, Lady Aoi.
My...
[GRANDFATHER] Mrs. Misato,
please accept my apologies.
You clumsy child!
[AOI'S MOTHER] Please,
Mr. Kisaragi, it's all right!
Everyone makes mistakes.
I believe you, yourself
have said that we grow
through our mistakes.
[GRANDFATHER]
Of course... Hisui,
apologize again to Mrs. Misato!
[KISARAGI] I'm really sorry...
Mrs. Misato.
[MARIA] All right, Miss Misato,
read this section. Miss Misato?
Y-Yes?
[MARIA] Starting from the sixth
line on page 25, please.
Come on. Let's go, Hisui!
[KYOICHI] What's the matter,
Miss Honor Student?
What's up with the
staring off into space
and not taking any notes?
[TATSUMA] You're no where
near as bad as Kyoichi.
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
Will you look at this,
well now, here's something
you don't see every day.
Mr. Horaiji and Miss Misato
chatting during school hours?
Did something happen
over summer vacation?
Hah! With "Snooty-Little-Miss
Student-Council"?
[KYOICHI] Actually,
I prefer more mature women.
So whaddya say, Maria, Sweetie?
Wanna hang out
with me some time?
[MARIA] Well, you haven't handed
in your summer homework yet,
have you?
So how about we "hang" out for
some remedial work after school?
[KYOICHI] W-What?
Sorry, I can't hear you!
[MARIA]
Remedial work.
[KYOICHI] Glasses,
where're my glasses...
Fireflies...
This is my secret place.
[AOI] One time I got
in trouble for tearing
one of my father's scrolls.
[KISARAGI]
Huh?
[AOI] I know
exactly how you feel.
Here.
[GRANDFATHER] Hisui, as
members of the Kisaragi family,
we have a very
important obligation.
Our family has served the
Misato family through the ages,
and have also served to protect
this city of Tokyo,
since as far back
as the Edo period.
I have told you this many times
and you must always remember.
[KISARAGI]
Yes, sir.
Hisui, listen to me carefully.
It is about time that you also
learned of our family's "other"
mission, which we must uphold!
Hisui, I heard...
about your grandfather.
You're worried, too, huh?
Oh, that's right. My mom told me
that we just got some really
good fruit from the market.
I'll go get some for you.
[KISARAGI]
You needn't trouble yourself.
[AOI]
Just wait right there.
[KISARAGI]
Lady Misato...
To think that those creatures
had been revived...
[TENDO] God of Kotoshiro, god of
Naohi, god of Furumita...
Come now to those who serve and
venerate you in this shrine;
we implore you, hasten,
heal our ills...
Mirror of the Deep,
Mirror of the Shore,
Eight-Hands-Breadth Sword,
Jewel of Life,
Jewel of Perfection...
[CLAIRE]
It's cold...
[TENDO] ...Jewel of
Resurrection, Jewel of Warding,
Serpent-Repelling Scarf,
Wasp-Repelling Scarf,
Scarf of Multifarious
Protection...
There we go!
[gunshots]
[screaming]
[cat meowing]
I have now taken it on...
I've taken on
all your resentment!
[KOMAKI]
What? Kisaragi?
[AOI] Yeah... And the
shop has had its shutters
closed the whole time.
[KYOICHI] Shit...
what the hell is he up to?
The clouds...
[KYOICHI]
Huh?
[TATSUMA]
We're in for a storm.
[ANKO] Are you sensing
something troubling?
[KYOICHI]
That voice...
Well, you needn't worry, now
that the Kyoko Tono is here!
Look, the latest digital camera!
With this, I can...
Who asked you to come?
Simply awful!
Is this any way to
treat the newest member
of the Demonbuster Club?!
Demonbuster Club?
[KYOICHI]
This ain't no damn school club!
[GIRL]
Hey, who's that?
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
Huh? Where?
[STUDENT] Wow, he looks
like a model or something!
[GIRL'S FRIEND]
He's totally yummy!
Who's that?...
[ANKO]
The antique guy!
It's Hisui!
How does he keep going?
These are from Hokkaido.
[car idling]
[AOI] Oh my god, Hisui,
what happened to you?
[YUUYA] Hey!
How about saying something?
[TATSUMA]
Kisaragi, you're wounded.
[YUUYA AND KOMAKI]
Huh?
[KYOICHI] Wake up.
Stay with us, Tatsuma.
Uh, Hisui...
[KYOICHI] Please don't
tell us that you fell down
a flight of stairs.
[KISARAGI] I thought the chain
of all the strange incidents
that have occurred had
been due to some disturbance
in the Dragon Stream...
But I was wrong.
Someone has been deliberately
causing these events
by practicing the Dark Arts.
[KOMAKI]
The Dark Arts...
[YUUYA] That's right. "Crow Boy"
said something about that?
[KISARAGI] "Dark Arts" is a
general term to denote sorcery,
which lies in opposition
of all that is righteous:
religion, heaven, humanity,
and the Earth itself.
There is something
known as the Demoniacal Art,
the path of the demonic, which
is one of the Dark Arts.
The Demoniacal Art is a
dreadful form of sorcery,
which is used to awaken
the souls of the dead
and summon demons.
There was a certain clan who
used the Demoniacal Art to
incite a rebellion
against the Tokugawa
in the last days
of the shogunate.
[KYOICHI] "Shogunate"?
What era was that again?
The Kurama Tengu era, right?
...Tengu? Those aren't demons!
[KOMAKI] You're thinking
about the TV show, you idiot!
[KISARAGI] I don't know
their reason for revolting,
but it is said that
this clan augmented their power
through the Demoniacal Arts,
summoning demons using the
souls of those who died with a
grudge against the Tokugawa.
They called themselves...
the Demoniacal Horde.
What?
It appears as if something
fun is about to start.
[YUUYA]
What does this mean?
The Demoniacal Horde
has been revived.
[TENDO] Now all we need
is the bodhisattva eye.
[CLAIRE]
Bo-dhi-satt-va eye?
[KISARAGI] If the Demoniacal
Horde has been revived,
then it's most likely
that their head family,
the Kozunu clan
too has revived.
[KYOICHI]
They're like the head of a gang?
[KISARAGI]
Correct.
They're trying to wreak havoc
upon this world once again.
By using the darkness in
people's hearts...
What? They're still pissed over
the end of the shogunate?
Talk about a fuckin' grudge!
[AOI]
Hisui?
[KISARAGI] I... I will
fight the Demoniacal Horde!
This obligation is
my soul duty as a member
of the Kisaragi family.
Even if I am alone,
I must fight...
...even if it means my death.
But you do not have to do this.
You have no reason to fight.
If you feel a need to withdraw
from this, I will not hold it
against you.
It is not too late.
Now that we know we're up
against the Demoniacal Horde,
I cannot guarantee
you're safety.
Is that acceptable to you?
Are you prepared to lay down
your life for all this?
[AOI]
I'll fight too.
I will fight.
[KOMAKI]
Me, too.
Komaki!
[KYOICHI] What, you're
still all worried about that?
Hey, Dungeon Master-
[KISARAGI]
What?
[KYOICHI] So basically
if we take out all these
Kozunu assholes, that be it?
Then there won't be anymore
people turning into demons
and monsters, right?
[KISARAGI]
Yes, that's right.
Hey there, Captain,
get all that?
[KISARAGI]
Lady Masato?
Is something wrong?
[AOI] Oh, I'm sorry,
my mind was just wandering...
I was thinking about
something from long ago.
That time you and I snuck away
to see the fireflies?
They're such nice memories...
Lady Masato. Please forgive me.
I shall protect
you without fail.
Oh, Hisui...
[YUUYA]
Whoa. This place is...
[KOMAKI]
Amazing.
[KYOICHI]
It's a bit dreary.
[KISARAGI] These are the sacred
grounds of the Kisaragi family.
Those who would trespass
upon it shall be cursed.
[KOMAKI]
Huh...
[KISARAGI]
Just a silly legend.
We had reason to make sure
people kept their distance
from this place.
[KISARAGI]
Just a silly legend.
[TATSUMA]
You don't sound like him.
[KISARAGI]
I knew it.
[AOI]
Hisui!
[KYOICHI] So, is that
the shogunate bastards.
[YUUYA] I knew it.
It's the ones from before.
[KOMAKI]
It's those two again.
[TATSUMA]
The Demoniacal Horde...
[TENDO] So, you've finally come.
I've been waiting for you.
The Demoniac Verses.
It is a collection of dark
spells used to summon demons.
My clan had sealed it away,
it appears as if...
[YUUYA]
You guys no longer have it?
[KOMAKI] And you came
here to be double check.
[KYOICHI] For cryin' out loud...
keep your valuables in a safe
or something!
Y'know?
[TENDO] A simple barrier
like this can't keep me out.
I have thus been able
to revive the Demoniacal Horde
without trouble.
Thank you so very much,
Kisaragi descendant.
[KISARAGI] You bastard...
Tell me your name?!
Kozunu...
Tendo Kozunu.
Tendo...
Kozunu...
[TENDO]
Kill them.
[screaming]
[KYOICHI]
Shut the hell up!
[KISARAGI]
No... This is...
Ah!!
Aoi!
[KOMAKI] What...
What is this?!
Stop it!
[KYOICHI]
Damn it.
Are you my enemies?!
[KISARAGI] I, Hisui Kisaragi,
shall not make the same
mistake twice!
[all screaming]
[KYOICHI]
Shit!
[TATSUMA]
Kyoichi!
[TENDO]
Not bad!
So tell me, where is it?
I found the Demoniac Verses
easy enough...
but I haven't had the same luck
with the "other" thing.
Come, tell me.
That's the only reason
I let you live before.
You know what they say,
what goes around comes around.
[TENDO] Now then,
what to do, what to do...
I've grown weary of you.
Guess I'll have to kill you all,
and look for it at my own pace.
[KISARAGI]
Lady Misato...
What are you...
looking at?
I don't care for
the look in your eyes.
What was that?!
[CLAIRE]
Boooring...
You all get out of here!
[TENDO] Sealed in a tube? That
explains why I couldn't find it!
In any case,
that is what I need.
The Eight-Hands-Breadth Sword...
What do you plan to do
with the ten sacred treasures?
[yawns]
Not again...
[CLAIRE] This dress was a gift
from a very special person!
You shall all die!
[people screaming]
[YUUYA] You knew they'd come.
Didn't you, Kisaragi?
[KISARAGI]
Yes.
[KOMAKI] Huh?! Then you knew we
could have been killed?!
[KYOICHI]
Get a grip, Sakurai!
[KOMAKI]
But...
If we couldn't handle what just
happened, then we'd be no match
for the Demoniacal Horde, right?
So then this
was all a test, huh?
I had to make sure.
Pft, that's nice.
Komaki?
Hmm.
[KISARAGI] The five of you
did a good job tonight.
So I'll treat
you guys to dinner.
I recall you mentioning your
favorite ramen establishment
was around here somewhere?
[KYOICHI] Hey, now you're
speaking my language,
Dungeon Master!
Okay, I'll have a
large miso battered kimchi
roasted pork ramen!
[KISARAGI]
I'm not paying for yours.
[KYOICHI]
What?! But you...
[KISARAGI]
Not paying.
[KYOICHI]
You just said...!
[KISARAGI]
Not for you!
[RYUZAN]
The time has come.