[girl] Some fish
can never be caught
because they belong to the sky.
IN THE NORTHERN OCEAN
THERE IS A FISH
THAT GOES BY THE NAME OF KUN.
ITS SIZE IS TOO LARGE
TO MEASURE.
[woman] Who we are?
Where do we come from?
And where are we going?
No one thinks about
these questions.
We go to work.
Day in and day out,
we laugh, we complain,
we buy things,
we eat, and we sleep.
Somehow a century has
already gone by.
I am 117 years old now.
As I often tell people,
the legend says that mankind
came from the ocean,
and that when our life’s
journey
as human beings on this
earth is done,
our souls return to the sea
as beautiful fish.
No one believes me when
I tell this story.
They call me an old fool.
But I know it’s true.
I can see them in my dreams,
giant fish swimming down
from the sky.
I can hear them calling
out to me
and their lovely voices
awaken my memories.
Long, long ago, when
the Earth was young,
all that existed was
a vast ocean
and the great primordial fish
that lived in it.
These ancients were
the first incarnations
of the human soul.
That’s why,
from the moment we’re born,
the ocean calls to us
and eventually we return to it.
My name is Chun.
I come from a world beneath
the ocean.
The sky of our world
is connected
to the oceans of
the human world.
Once freed by death,
human souls drift down
from their world to ours
and it is our task to
look after them
and keep them safe.
We are the ones who
control time,
the tides, and the changing
of the seasons.
We are not human beings
but neither are we gods.
We are The Others.
[chittering]
Look! Sister Leizu’s woven a
new sky for the humans.
Hurry, Chun. The Rite of Passage
is about to begin.
We’ll hurry, Chisongzi!
Sister Leizu!
I need to join
the Rite of Passage.
Can we borrow two horses?
I don’t mind if
the horses don’t.
I’ll take this one.
Of course!
You like ’em big and strong,
don’t you?
That’s why you like‐‐
[groans]
[both laugh]
Wait for me!
Wait up, Chun!
No way!
Oh, yeah?
Qiu, tell me about
the human world!
I loved it there.
I almost didn’t
want to come back.
Maybe you shouldn’t have!
Then who would keep
you out of trouble?
You’re the one
who’s in trouble, slow‐poke!
The Rite of Passage is starting!
Hurry!
Let’s go, come on!
[chattering]
I can’t believe
it’s finally here.
It’s so loud!
Why is everybody being so noisy?
‐Be careful in the human world.
‐I will.
[woman] Chun! Over here!
Coming, Mother!
[all laughing]
Hey!
Yeah! Looking good, Grandma!
The seasons pass before us all,
Earth and Heaven, Moon and Sun,
tied by the elements,
we are one!
You’ll be all on your own up
there in the human world.
Here. You need to eat more.
‐Mother, I’m full.
‐I don’t want you to go, Tingmu.
Are you gonna come back?
I’ll be back.
Don’t you worry, OK?
The sun above shines on
the earth below,
and the friendly gods,
their blessings bestow.
For seven days
you will roam the human world
and observe the natural laws
that we govern.
But remember this,
you must not have any contact
with humankind.
Dragon of the sea and sky,
awake!
[Grandmother]
Let the gateway be opened!
You heard him.
Keep away from the humans.
‐The farther away the better.
‐I know.
You hear?
‐Chun won’t get into trouble.
‐Please.
‐She’s a clever girl.
‐Tell that to Ah King.
Her girl never came back!
What are you waiting for?
I can’t hold this up forever!
[horns blare]
Remember, you must get back to
the gateway in seven days.
‐You can’t be late...
‐Mother‐‐
Or you’ll be left behind.
[child] Here comes the soup!
The soup. Out of the way.
My little girl has grown up.
I should go.
Chun...
Be careful.
I will.
Keep track of the time.
You run along now, Chun. Go on.
Don’t worry. Goodbye.
[woman] Please be careful!
[man] Stay safe!
[mother] Chun! Wait!
The human world is beautiful,
but dangerous.
Remember, your world is here.
[sobbing]
So long, Chun!
Try not to miss me too much!
Behave yourself up there!
[Chun] Every child who
has turned 16 in the past year
is sent to the human world
in a Rite of Passage...
to see for ourselves
how we control the rain,
the wind,
the sun, and the stars.
We have been taught how
dangerous their world is
but seeing it for ourselves, it
didn’t seem dangerous at all.
It was magical and so
beautiful.
I had never been happier.
Look!
The red dolphins came
back again.
I knew that they would,
just like last year at
the same time!
Come on. Let’s say hello.
Hey!
Up here!
Good to see you again!
[Chun] For six days,
I explored the human world.
I saw great wooden
sailing ships,
and lights that flickered
and danced
across the heavens.
I saw the candles that
the humans lit
to accompany the souls of
the departed
on their journey down the
rivers to the sea.
I followed them,
and on the seventh
and final day,
I too, returned to the ocean.
It was time to go home.
[flute plays]
[chittering]
Watch this!
[girl gasps]
‐[laughs]
‐You like that?
Well, just you wait.
What are you doing?
Dolphin bait.
Get my back, will you?
OK.
Come here, you.
‐Wait right there.
‐I will.
Look at all the fish!
What were you doing down
there so long?
Chasing a red dolphin.
Do you see it?
There’s something different
about her.
I can feel it.
[Chun] I’d lost track of the
time.
The seventh and last day
was nearly over.
I had to get back.
[crying]
I was running out of time.
The gateway wouldn’t stay open
much longer.
[yelping]
‐Where?
‐Out there. By the whirlpool.
‐It’s a dolphin.
‐Yeah.
The red one from before.
She’s caught in the net.
I’m gonna try and cut her free.
Go fetch my knife.
‐What about the whirlpool?
‐I’ll be fine. Don’t worry.
Go get it.
Thanks.
Brother, be careful!
[yelping]
OK, all right.
Brother!
I’m trying to save you.
Come back! No!
[squeaks]
[panting]
[sobbing] Where is he?
Where’s my brother?
I want my brother back.
I want him back
and everything to be all right.
Please, Brother. Don’t go away!
Come back!
[girl screams]
Chun! You’re back!
Thank heavens!
What’s the matter?
‐Chun, are you all right?
‐I’m fine.
Come on. Let’s talk at home.
Thank goodness you’re safe.
I’ve made your favorite dinner.
[thunderclap]
Good morning, Grandmother.
Is Grandfather up?
Grandfather, where do humans go
when they die?
Their body is turned back
into the dust
from which they were made.
And their souls?
They go to Ascendance Palace
where they
are transformed
into tiny fishes.
and watched over by Ling Po,
the Lady of Souls.
‐Will we die too, Grandfather?
‐Of course we will.
[chuckles] Death is part of
the natural order of things.
In fact, your grandfather’s time
is almost over.
‐No! I don’t want you to die.
‐Now, now, sweet child.
Death is not an end just as
birth is not a beginning.
They’re just stops
on the path to eternity.
[Chun] I knew grandfather was
right, of course.
Because I knew I was destined
to inherit his powers,
and how could I do that if he
did not die?
But knowing of things true
is not the same as wanting it
so.
[ominous voice] What’s that
you’re playing, child?
Who’s there?
Your flute sounds like
something from another world.
It’s not mine.
The sound is very pleasing.
Where did it come from?
The human world, a boy...
He’s dead now...
because of me.
So that’s why you’re here.
A human boy.
Perhaps the Lady of Souls
can help you.
Come back here
at midnight tonight
and bring that bell with you.
Ring it and someone
will come for you.
I will be here waiting.
[animal cries]
[bell rings]
FLOWER
WATER
CHEN
Did I do that? Sorry.
Where you going?
Kinda late, isn’t it?
[ominous voice] The bell.
That’s it.
Now get ready.
[Chun] I had made my choice.
There was no turning back.
The moment I stepped aboard
that boat,
I knew my destiny
had changed forever.
HOUSE OF RUSHENG
LIFE
[snorts, snores]
FISH
You came alone?
Follow me.
Sit.
Thanks. I’d rather stand.
What brings you to
the Island of Souls?
There’s a soul I’m looking for.
The soul of a human boy.
What time was it he died?
It was two days before
the Wheat Harvest.
You need to be sure of the date,
otherwise you’re searching
for a needle in a haystack,
so many die every day.
I’m sure.
It was my birthday.
I know what you’re
trying to do, girl,
and it goes against
the laws of nature.
I don’t care.
I’ve got to save him.
The punishment is harsh
for those who defy nature
no matter who you are
so you should care!
But I owe him...
for saving my life.
How very touching.
I’ve been stuck here
for 800 years,
and I’m still not done paying
penance for my sins.
‐But you didn’t‐‐
‐Don’t interrupt!
Let me tell you what
real tragedy is.
Meeting someone you care about
so much you forget yourself
and make a mistake.
So then you go back and you try
to fix it and make things
right again.
And then you learn
that fixing it is impossible.
We could never undo the wrongs
we’ve done, this I know.
You’re saying you won’t
help me?
I’m saying I pity you.
Besides, resurrecting someone
from the dead doesn’t
come cheap.
What would it cost?
No less than a lovely girl’s
loveliest features.
Your eyes.
[laughs]
Now she’s scared.
Don’t want to give up
your pretty eyes?
All right. I’ll take half of
your life instead.
If that’ll save him,
take it.
BINGYIN YEAR
No, no, no! How many times do
I have to tell you?
Not on the carpet!
Why do you have so many cats?
Who else would spend
half of eternity
with an old bore like me?
[Chun] Humankind came
from the ocean.
That’s why people’s tears
and blood
are salty like the sea.
From the moment they are born,
their lives are journey
homeward
though they are
unaware of this.
They think they follow a path
of their own choosing.
They meet, they part.
Some grow old, some do not.
LIFE ‐ DEATH
But when they die,
the voice of the sea speaks
to the soul
calling all of them back
and each swims off
to their own separate destiny.
[Ling Po]
This is the Hall of Souls,
where all human souls
are kept after death.
So many souls.
Will you be able to find him?
He won’t look the same
as he was.
I’ll know him when I see him.
[Chun] I didn’t even
know his name,
but I remembered everything
about him...
the scar on his forehead,
the way he looked at me.
I searched in there for hours
and hours,
all night long.
And then...
Well, you see?
It requires a piece of your soul
to wake him.
Now your lives are
bound together.
It’s up to you to protect him
and guide him through all the
difficulties ahead...
until he’s grown enough
to return to his world
and be restored to life.
Now there’s no turning back.
Do not fail him...
or his soul will vanish into
the void...
Forever.
Lazy rascal.
Where were you all night?
And where did you get that?
No.
I’m Chun. Remember me?
I’m the red dolphin you saw.
I suppose you don’t remember
your name.
I’ll just give you a new one.
My name means begonia.
One day I’ll look after
all the begonia trees like Mom.
Don’t worry.
You won’t always be small.
You’ll get bigger,
bigger than this fish bowl,
and the mirror, and the table.
and the bed even!
Bigger than this whole room!
And this building!
[man] What’s with all the
racket? Keep it down!
Anyway, I’ll give you
a good name.
You cannot keep a fish here.
Who asked you? Go away.
Wait! I can keep a secret.
You can trust me.
Hey! I know a good name for him.
What?
Open the window.
There’s a fish in
the Northern Ocean.
His name’s Kun and
he’s enormous.
I mean so big
that he can’t even be measured.
That’s what
the ancient books say.
So anyway, this Kun is gigantic,
and get this. He can fly. Yeah!
He’s got wings
that are the size of clouds!
Are you finished?
‐Goodbye.
‐Hey!
From now on,
Your name...
is Kun.
Kun?
Rain this time of year.
That’s unusual.
It’s salty.
[chittering]
You’re growing.
You wanna play, don’t you?
Remember when a red dolphin
played in the sea with you?
Remember that?
[plays tune]
You do remember!
Come here.
I wanna try something.
You can fly!
It’s true.
Just like your namesake.
Amazing!
[dolphin cries]
Your family’s calling you.
They want you to come home.
Kun, you keep growing, OK?
I’ll get you home again.
Promise.
Kun?
Mother, were you in my room?
Yes. What’s wrong with that?
What did you do with him?
I threw it out.
Time you stopped playing
with that thing.
Mother, that thing
is a human life!
What? Come back here!
What did you say?
‐Chun.
‐Stop following me.
Where you going?
You all right?
My mother threw Kun away.
Don’t worry.
I know where to find him.
Here! Over here.
Nasty. But I bet he’s there.
Kun?
It’s him.
Grab my feet. I’m gonna look.
What? You can’t go in.
You sit tight.
I’ve got it covered.
Besides, your mother would have
a fit if you got lost too.
Qiu! Be careful!
I knew it’d be nasty
but not this nasty.
Qiu,
thanks for doing this.
Kun? Kun?
Rats! Lots of ’em!
Won’t these rats
try and eat Kun?
You can be sure of it.
They’ll strip him to the bone,
they will.
What an enchanting scent.
That provocative perfume.
Smells like... love.
How can I help you, handsome?
What brings you to
my neck of the woods?
‐I’m looking for a fish.
‐A fish?
Well, as it happens,
I’ve seen a fish.
Really? You know where
Kun is then?
That’s no ordinary fish, is it?
You got it from the
Lady of Souls, didn’t you?
Ling Po gets all the good people
who turn into fish when
they die.
I get all the bad ones
who turn into rats.
I think my rats are much cuter
than her slimy fish, don’t you?
So you’ll help me find him?
No, sorry.
Unless...
You let me borrow your
sweetheart for a dance!
Relax. Go with it. Music!
Ready, baby cakes?
Just follow my lead.
‐[music plays]
‐Chun!
TREASURE
There are two things
that boys need to learn...
how to dance,
and how to control
their own little rats.
[laughs]
It’s a wonderful place,
isn’t it, the human world?
You’ve been to the human world?
Look. They caught one.
Kun!
In you go.
That’s it.
Is he all right?
He’s not waking up.
‐[plays tune]
‐Look, he’s alive!
Such a pure soul.
Yes, he’s sure to grow into
a big fish indeed.
I found ya!
There you are.
Now where’d they go?
There you‐‐
[chittering]
[screams]
Grandpa Houtu! Grandpa Houtu!
There’s a fish. I saw a fish.
A big fish.
Here. Down in this well.
But it was there before.
I saw a fish. I swear!
The unseasonal weather,
the salty rain,
these are bad omens.
We must stay vigilant,
every one of us.
Good thing I saw them coming.
If they’d found him...
This is your new home, Kun.
OK?
Hey, I think there’s something
hiding in there.
Come on out!
Chun! Watch out!
‐Qiu!
‐Stay back!
Watch out! It has two heads!
Now you tell me?
Get off of me!
Take this, snake! And that!
And that!
Qui! That’s enough!
You OK?
[groans]
Qiu!
Chun...
I feel so tired.
I just wanna go to sleep.
No, don’t fall asleep.
You’ve got to stay awake.
How about a song?
I’ll sing you a song.
♪ The moon and stars hanging
above the sea ♪
♪ The moon shines‐‐ ♪
You’re not very good, are you?
If it was pretty,
it would put you to sleep.
Where are we?
We’re almost there.
Don’t you dare go to sleep.
Grandfather!
Help!
He has been bitten
by a two‐headed serpent.
There is no known antidote
to its venom.
Grandfather, save him! Please!
Chun...
This is for you.
There is perhaps one way.
Chun, wait outside.
I will do what I can.
Thank you.
‐[makes noise]
‐[gasps]
Hey! You’re getting me all wet.
You’ve got fish breath.
Qiu! Thank goodness you’re OK!
Alive and kicking thanks
to your grandpa.
He’s pretty good.
Pretty good? He’s the master
of all herbs and plants.
He’s awesome!
Dearest old friend,
can you still remember the day
when we first met?
[Chun] Soon I was to find out
what it had cost my grandfather
to save Qiu.
‐Grandfather.
‐Chun...
come here.
It’s time for me to go.
It’s ’cause of what I’ve done,
isn’t it?
No. No, child.
Don’t blame yourself.
It is the natural
order of things.
Life and death are one thread.
I must tell you something, Chun.
The course you have chosen
is not an easy one.
Everyone will be against you.
But if your conscience
is clear,
then it doesn’t matter
what others think.
Simply follow your heart.
I will become a begonia tree
and reunite with
your grandmother,
but I will always be here
to support you.
[Chun] Grandmother had been
the master of birds.
When she died, she turned
into a phoenix
and kept Grandfather company.
Two days after we talked,
Grandfather was gone.
All the birds came to visit
that day.
It felt like Grandmother
had come back as well.
Snow in mid‐summer.
The seasons have fallen
into chaos.
Something is coming.
Isn’t this crazy weather?
It’s great!
I love the snow!
‐[Qiu] Do you believe God
exists?
‐[Chun] No.
[Qiu] I do.
[Chun] No one’s ever seen him.
[Qiu] Humans have never seen us,
but we exist.
I won’t be here when my parents
get as old as Grandfather.
Just when they need me
to look after them...
I’ll be gone.
What are you talking about?
I traded half my life away.
You did what?
‐I traded it for Kun.
‐[mother] Chun!
There you are! Get down here
at once!
‐I gotta go.
‐Chun!
‐Coming!
[mother] You can’t really
believe my daughter is
responsible!
[father] She’s connected to it
somehow.
[Rat matron] The Elders are
beginning to suspect Chun.
She and Kun are both in danger.
[Qiu] Who are you?
Don’t you recognize me,
handsome?
If they find Kun,
your sweetie will be punished.
You must hide him in the river
inside the mountain cave.
Go on. Go on, hurry!
Chun’s in big trouble...
and it’s all ’cause of you.
Come on.
As long as you’re here
she’s in danger.
If you care about her
you’ll leave.
Now.
Where’s Kun?
He’s gone.
‐Gone? Gone where?
‐I set him free.
He’s in the river.
Chun, wait!
I was trying to help you!
[gasps]
A token. Just what I needed.
You’re my ticket to
the human world.
Kun...
I thought I’d never
see you again.
Let’s follow them. They’ll know
the way out of here.
[groans]
[panting]
Chun...
IMMORTAL QUEEN MOTHER
I didn’t have parents growing up
like you did.
Just my grandmother.
She does her best
and I love her,
but the only thing
I’ve ever really cared about
is you.
Now I realize
how much you care about him.
I was scared.
I don’t wanna see you hurt.
Please let her wake up.
Kun!
Kun, it was you who woke me,
wasn’t it?
I don’t ever wanna
lose you again.
She’s OK! Yeah!
Isn’t that great?
Chun’s OK!
[screams]
Your turn.
What a terrible hand!
Well, since you’re here,
you might as well come in.
‐I’m sorry to bother you‐‐
‐Triple.
‐I have a question.
‐What?
Why did you give that
human soul to Chun?
It was a trade, not a gift!
If you’re willing to pay
the price...
There’s not a thing in this
world that can’t be traded.
Even half a lifetime?
Well, aren’t you
the clever fellow?
So, I can give half my lifetime
and trade for hers.
Of course.
However, the price just went up.
You’d have to trade your
whole life.
Fine.
I should warn you, however‐‐
Even that’s not gonna save her!
That little girl’s life is tied
to that great big fish of hers.
When it dies, she dies.
What if the fish returned home?
If the fish goes back...
On the very day it leaves...
She’ll die too.
There must be a way to save her.
Mahjong! I win!
Come play a round.
You might even win.
The table’s full.
There.
Now it isn’t.
Wow. That’s lucky. I win.
I don’t believe‐‐
[laughs] What’s luck anyway?
Good luck, bad luck.
It’s just fate, really.
It’s all up to you now.
What?
I said it’s all up to you now.
All in your hands.
[whispers indistinctly]
Goodbye. Thank you.
You young kids live life
like a worthless rock you found
by the side of the road,
while old hags like me
have to rack our brains
figuring out how to
live another day.
Without joy,
what’s the point of a long life?
[Chun] What would we give up?
What sacrifices would we make
for those we love?
What are we willing
to risk losing?
Half our lives,
our family and friends,
and the world we know?
By the time we ask ourselves
these things,
if we ask them,
it’s usually too late to
matter.
We already know the answer.
What have you got
to help me forget something?
You sure you want to?
Real forgetting
is not that difficult.
But it hurts.
Feeling pain
can be a good thing.
Do you have anything
that’ll make it go away?
There is something.
It will make you forget
all your sorrows,
but all your pleasures as well.
Mengpo potion.
Well, maybe just some wine.
Got something for a hangover?
It’s my first drink.
[shouts] Do you even know
who’s in love with you?
And the things he’s done
for you?
He’s forsaking everything,
betraying everyone...
for your happiness!
The sea is flowing backwards.
The heavens are angry with us.
Only by destroying that creature
will we set things right.
[Rat matron] I can tell you
where the big fish is,
but first, you will have to
break the seal
and allow me to see
the sunlight.
Things are getting
awfully messy.
I think it’s time
to clean it up.
Well, baby? Are you ready?
♪ The great fish comes
and we must go ♪
♪ To get to higher ground ♪
♪ We shall all go up to
the mountain top ♪
♪ While the waters
gather round ♪
♪ The rains come down,
the rains come down ♪
♪ Till the land becomes
the sea ♪
♪ Old home gone,
get your new home on ♪
♪ Where will my new home be ♪
[laughs]
Pei, terrible news.
Someone has taken
the Dragon mask!
Chun! Listen to me.
Get away from it right now.
Leave that monster to us.
Don’t hurt him.
He’s not a monster.
Ungrateful child!
Mother, forgive me.
Feng, why do you stop?
Go. Destroy it!
‐No, I’ll do it.
‐You had your chance.
Kun. Go. Fly!
Don’t let it get away!
Fly, Kun. Fly!
Go, Chun! Now’s your chance!
Get Kun back home! Go on!
Heavens, no.
Hurry, Chun!
Get him out of here
while you can!
‐Qiu!
‐Qiu, stop!
You’re not strong enough
to control the gateway.
Just watch!
We need Pei.
Go find his grandmother. Hurry!
I can’t hold on much longer!
Chun! Get going!
Go, Kun!
I’m finally going back to
the human world!
Thanks for the help, handsome!
I’ll think of you from up there.
What have we done?
Sorry, sweetie, but without a
token from the human world,
you can’t pass through
the gateway.
[groans]
Grandfather saved us.
Kun, be strong.
Our fate’s have been connected
since the day we met...
and I don’t regret it.
Brother Songzi, what will we do
if we don’t find everyone?
‐We’ll find them.
‐OK.
Grandma.
Down there!
There’s people in the water!
Help! Help!
Over here!
It’s Tingmu and his sister!
Take her first!
Little sister!
‐Has anyone seen Qiu?
‐No, not yet.
Tingmu is still out there.
We have to go back.
I’ll come with you.
‐Tingmu!
Tingmu!
Kun, don’t give up now.
You have to fly
and get through the gateway.
Go on. I’ll be all right.
Don’t worry.
Grandfather will protect me.
Now go while you can!
Go on!
Down there. It’s that creature.
Quick. We mustn’t let it
get away.
But first, let’s find Tingmu.
If that monster escapes,
our whole world will
be destroyed.
We can’t wait.
Go, Kun!
Go!
Kun!
Fly! Fly, Kun!
Grandfather.
Please help.
What should I do? Tell me.
What can I do?
Please save him.
Please, Grandfather.
Grandmother! Here!
He’s done nothing wrong.
Why are you protecting him?
He died saving me,
now I need to save him!
His little sister is waiting.
Tingmu has been swept away
in the flood.
What about his sister?
Run. Everyone, run!
Get to higher ground. Go.
To the mountaintop. Hurry!
Over here.
Help me make a bridge.
The others need us.
We have to go help them.
I’ve got to help my family.
I can’t go with you.
‐My brother!
‐Chi Songzi!
‐Where’s Tingmu?
‐Did you find Tingmu?
I’m afraid not.
‐What?
‐I’m sorry.
Mother!
Mother, I’m here to help!
No! We don’t need any help
from you!
Please, child. Go.
Give me my Tingmu back.
[sobs]
I want Tingmu to come back.
Hurry, everyone. We must hurry.
[mother] Stay calm.
Hold the water back!
Let’s go.
Hey.
Feng!
[Chun] It’s all my fault.
Everything bad that’s happened
is because of what I’ve done.
The one good will be if
you make it back
and live your life again...
as it was before we met.
Fly, Kun.
Go home and live your life...
a beautiful life.
I’m coming, Grandfather.
Ma!
‐Tingmu?
‐It’s me! Up here!
Tingmu!
‐Mama! It’s me!
‐Tingmu!
‐Look, it’s me!
‐Oh, Chun!
Chun!
Finally, the moment’s here.
Why haven’t you left?
Here. Sister Leizu
wove this for you.
Try it on. It should fit.
Thank you.
Why am I here?
Am I dead?
No, child.
But you’ve lost all your powers.
You can’t stay here.
What about the others?
Don’t worry.
Your sacrifice saved them...
and now the balance is restored.
Go south till you come
to the Southern Sky Pools.
You can accompany him
on his journey home.
But know that when he returns
to the human world,
he won’t remember you
or any of this.
All right.
You’ll tell my mother I’m
still alive, won’t you?
[Ling Po grunts]
Go now.
Thank you.
No need for that.
A deal is a deal.
You should thank the one
who traded away his life
for yours.
[Qiu] Chun! Chun! Hey!
Over here!
Wait up! I’m coming with you!
I can’t swim!
What you thinking?
There’s so many...
So many stars.
Whenever I look up at the sky,
it’s like I hear someone
calling to me.
What do you think?
There’s something
I’ve been wondering.
Does love last forever?
Like the stars?
Yeah.
Once Kun is safe,
we’ll go home, right?
My powers are gone.
I can’t go home.
The human world is nice.
Is that where you want to live?
With Kun?
Impossible.
I don’t belong to his world.
I wasn’t asking if
it’s possible.
I asked if it’s what you want.
Here.
You know, you look cute when
you’re eating.
I know you pretty well by now.
I’ve seen all of you.
When you’re tired,
when you’re angry,
when you’re sad,
even embarrassed.
It’s all beautiful.
You’re like a brother to me.
Right.
‐You awake?
‐Uh‐huh.
‐You cold?
‐No.
You should sleep.
Qiu?
Thank you for always
being there.
You treat me better than
anyone else ever did.
[Chun] Will we ever see
each other again?
Would you recognize me?
We will meet again.
And despite what Ling Po said,
I know we will recognize
each another,
no matter how much we’d
changed.
Kun!
Leave now.
It’s time to go home.
Qiu!
Quick! Take hold of my hand!
Come on, hurry!
We don’t have much time!
What’s happening to you?
I fixed it so you can live...
in Kun’s world.
But aren’t we going
home together?
I got your life back for you
so you can go with him
if you want.
‐No.
‐Wait!
‐No!
‐Stop it!
Chun, listen...
Listen to me.
Listen.
It’s OK.
‐Qiu.
‐You know this is right, Chun.
You have to go.
Trust me on this
and I know we’ll meet again.
I wish I’d...
I wish I’d held you closer
when I could have.
Just one time...
Come on.
When I count to three,
we jump, OK?
Trust me!
One,
two,
three!
When you see the wind and rain,
think of me and
I’ll be with you...
‐Always.
‐Qui...
Goodbye, Chun.
No!
[Chun] Do you believe
in miracles?
We each spend countless
cycles waiting...
waiting for the chance to enjoy
this adventure called life.
It’s so easy to forget how
precious life is, how short.
It’s lost in a thousand little
moments of not caring.
It doesn’t hurt to be braver,
to be more grateful,
more loving.
There are many things
I don’t understand,
and many questions
I can never answer.
But one thing I do believe,
that the heavens gave us life
so that each of us can
create miracles.
It’s time, my friend.
From now on,
you’ll be taking over for me.
In ancient history
there was a tree called Ta‐khun,
whose spring (Chun)
was 8000 years,
and its autumn (Qiu) the same.