[NARRATOR] The dismal concrete
jungle of the Furutama Projects.
An underworld
industrial district
built by Omura Industries.
Amid these identical towers
of brick and steel,
hope cannot be found.
[engine revs]
[beeping]
[NANCY] Jose-san,
this is Nancy calling.
The mission is proceeding
as planned. Over.
[JOSE] Listen. You gotta
quit playing around
with all the cloak
and dagger crap.
This is serious, ya know?
And if you blow
this one you're screwed.
You're a real charmer.
I appreciate it.
[tires screech]
[NANCY]
Building fourteen, right?
[JOSE] Yes, sixth floor.
That's the story, at least.
But something seems
fishy about it to me.
[footsteps]
[NANCY]
Room 606?
Jose-san?
[door creaks]
[NANCY]
It's open.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Jose-san.
Bad news! It's Taragi!
[MAN]
Bite!
[yells]
[NANCY gasps, groans]
[MAN] Now squeeze
the little rat!
[NANCY whimpers]
[MAN chuckles]
[MAN]
Having trouble moving?
[NANCY gasps]
Feel the venom pulsing
through your veins!
Now, come back, my pretty!
[SNAKE hisses]
Domo. Nancy Lee-san.
I am the one
they call Cockatrice.
[NANCY] How does
he know my name?
The man in your ear.
Jose-san has been working with
the Soukaiya for a while.
Now be a good
little girl,
and tell me why
a hot chick like you
is snooping around
this place. Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Cockatrice-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Domo. Ninja Slayer-san.
I am the one
they call Cockatrice.
Why are you snooping
around this place?
No reason.
But now I am here
to kill you!
[COCKATRICE]
Bite!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
So all the rumors
about you are true.
You're a hard rat
to kill. Until now!
I'm gonna fill you
so full of poison
that your head'll explode.
[NARRATOR]
I can't believe my eyes!
This man is some sort of
human animal hybrid!
Instead of arms, he has
twin cobras! Scary!
Only the most badass
ninjas can survive
Dr. Lee's reptile
augmentation surgery,
and master the
Daija Bite attack!
That's why I'm
the only one around!
Does the Soukaiya
train all their ninjas
to deliver these
long-winded introductions?
Come on!
Let's get to the action!
[COCKATRICE] Sink your fangs
into his flesh, my pets!
Psyche!
Constrictor attack!
My twin serpents will
keep on squeezing you
until you're nice and tender!
And then I'm gonna
swallow you whole!
Blaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[COCKATRICE]
Aaaargh!
Aaaargh! Aaaargh!
[panting]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Who will feed you now that
your precious "pets"
are gone?
[COCKATRICE groans]
Maybe this Dr. Lee
can get you in
for another surgery. I hear
he has a waiting room.
Down in Hell! Yeeart!
[COCKATRICE]
Sayonara!
This has gotta be some
kinda crazy nightmare!
[gulps]
[NANCY] I don't normally accept
drugs from strange men.
It hasn't been very long
since you were bitten.
That pill should counteract
the venom very soon.
What's going on here?
Who killed Taragi Wei?
Who are--
Domo, I am
called Ninja Slayer.
Nancy-san, you should
stop playing detective
and flee to Kyoto right away!
The syndicate is heartless.
They will murder you!
Answer my question!
Damn it!
[mellow electronic music plays]
[NANCY] Tanuki. I have a
hunch that that's the key
to finding the truth about
this mess once and for all.
[NANCY] And maybe even
the truth about him.
[engine revs]
[long beep]
[BIRDS cawing]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
[cawing continues]
[CROW caws]
[MAN 2]
Domo.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Yeeart!
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
That is quite
an impressive title.
Pleasure to meet you.
Domo Ninja Slayer-san.
I am just a simple man.
My name is
Sugawarano Tomihide.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Sugawarano-san, I have a favor
I must ask you.
Please sir. I ask that
you forget we ever met.
Buddha sees all, but
these crows and I do not.
[NINJA SLAYER]
But you did, in fact,
spot me perching overhead.
[SUGAWARANO]
Yes, but I didn't notice you
out of pure suspicion;
it was something else.
I sensed "good."
This world
has many who only
concern themselves with
their own discomforts,
but few who would stop
to aid an injured bird.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo.
So I don't frighten you?
I am a ninja, after all.
I've lived many years.
And full ones, at that.
Not much frightens
me these days.
Besides, I told you
that I could sense
the goodness in you
earlier, remember?
Ah. Let me
show you something.
A picture of my family.
The happiest
point in my life.
My wife passed away soon after.
And my son left home to follow
his dreams without me.
Is that so?
Have you not heard from
your son since that day?
Well, you see,
he always wanted
to go off to university.
But for some reason he
failed his entrance exams.
So he set off for
the Kyoto republic.
Many years passed.
Then one day,
I received a
message saying he was
working for Murasaki
Shikibu Cosmetics.
I have heard
about this corporation.
A titan in the
cosmetics industry.
They do have
quite the reputation.
From that day on,
every now and then,
some money is deposited
into my bank account.
That is most honorable.
I suppose it is.
But truthfully, I believe
spending time together
would be far more valuable.
But I wouldn't
want to interfere with
his work or the life he's
created, so here we are.
You've suffered
many hardships,
yet I can't sense a hint
of murderous rage.
How is that? Do you
practice the tea ceremony?
[SUGAWARANO laughs]
I'm afraid I don't practice
any intricate rituals
like that, my friend.
To be honest, I don't
even drink much tea.
It doesn't matter.
You just struck me
as one who does.
Well, I should
be taking my leave.
Sayonara, Sugawarano-san.
Ninja Slayer-san.
When tomorrow comes,
will I be able to find you
perched on the tower again?
[NINJA SLAYER] No.
Take care of yourself.
[SUGAWARANO]
You do the same.