[NARAKU]
Domo, Laomoto-san.
I am Naraku Ninja.
[LAOMOTO]
Domo, Naraku Ninja-san.
I am Laomoto Khan,
Demolition Ninja.
[LAOMOTO yells]
Impossible!
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[NARAKU]
Carnage!
[LAOMOTO yells]
[LAOMOTO]
[HELLKITE]
Abbah!
[LAOMOTO] I've never
seen a ninja soul burn
with such ferocity.
He's lost all control of it.
[LAOMOTO yells]
[NARAKU yells]
[NARAKU]
You miserable whelp!
[LAOMOTO]
This is absurd!
Where is this power coming from?
Who the hell are you?!
[NARAKU]
Absurdity kills reason!
My power flows from vengeance!
I am your karma!
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO]
Impossible!
[NARAKU yells]
This cannot be!
[LAOMOTO gagging]
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[LAOMOTO coughs]
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[LAOMOTO coughs]
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[LAOMOTO cries]
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[NARAKU] He should be steaming
pile of guts right now!
I knew it; Fujikido's
body is too weak!
It won't let me unleash
all of my ninja power
on this gold-plated skid mark!
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO groaning]
[NARAKU]
Allow me to behead you!
[NARRATOR] Naraku Ninja
continues to lay the smack down
on the kingpin, Laomoto Khan.
But what has happened to
Fujikido Kenji-slash-Ninja
Slayer-san?
Is he still in there somewhere?
Ninja! Ninja!
Tochinoki sure is fascinated
by ninjas, huh?
He absolutely loves them.
That's good to know
for this Christmas.
Well, maybe,
you could get him
some throwing stars.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Stop! Please, stop!
I'm a ninja!
Ninjas aren't real, sweetpea.
Well, maybe,
you could get him
some throwing stars.
I'm a ninja!
[NINJA SLAYER]
I can't take this anymore!
Ninjas aren't real, sweetpea.
Aren't real.
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
[NARAKU] You've got some
brass balls, Fujikido!
But did you really believe
you had the strength
to burn through my
power like that?
You will never contain me!
Your body is mine,
now and forever!
--[NARAKU yells]
--[LAOMOTO groans]
[LAOMOTO]
Hellkite!
You worthless, flying
sack of excrement!
Do something!
[NARAKU]
I will exact vengeance
for your wife and
child, Fujikido!
You just lie there.
Writhing on the futon
in your mind.
Agonizing over your
impotence, for all eternity!
[NINJA SLAYER inahles, exhales]
[NARAKU grunts]
[NARAKU]
Huh?
[NARAKU groans]
[NARAKU]
Has this pathetic human body
given me all that it has?
[LAOMOTO grunts, yells]
[NARAKU]
Damn you, Fujikido.
I know you're up to something.
Stop it!
[NINJA SLAYER inahles, exhales]
[FUYUKO]
Sweetie.
[TOCHINOKI]
Daddy.
[NARAKU]
Come on, Fujikido!
Let your rage burn!
That's how this works!
Fury is my gasoline!
We will never take
revenge for your family
unless your brain is
boiling with hatred!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Furinkazan.
Chado.
Don't stop.
Furinkazan.
[NARAKU] Are you trying
to get killed, you ninny?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Naraku Ninja,
you may be the housemate
of my neurons,
but you can't evict
me from my mind!
I realized something.
I, Fujikido Kenji, summoned
you that fateful day.
I hungered for blood,
and you fed me well!
But by summoning you,
I invited you in.
Two souls, living in one body.
And now I need your
strength, Naraku!
[NARAKU]
Such insolence!
You summon me, use me,
fight me tooth and nail,
and now you ask me for help?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Nay!
It was my rage, my burning
scream for vengeance
that summoned you from the
very depths of my soul.
I cannot deny you or
hide you anymore!
Naraku, I accept you!
You are the ninja inside
me that I cannot slay!
[NARRATOR] Fujikido had
discovered a zen-like truth
at the far end of his Chado.
Fujikido could not disavow
the raging bloodlust
deep within him.
Yet he could not
fall into its grip.
Fujikido had to accept it.
As he accepted the loss of
his beloved wife and son.
[LAOMOTO yells]
[glass shattering]
[LAOMOTO]
Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[LAOMOTO]
Wha...?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Laomoto-san! Come at me!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer's
very appearance has changed.
A sure sign that he and
Naraku Ninja have indeed
become one in mind and body!
[LAOMOTO]
You don't know when to die!
[LAOMOTO grunting]
[NARAKU] This enemy soul is
from the Big Ninja Clan.
Power like a freight train,
but slow and clumsy.
I was hoping you'd say that!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[LAOMOTO yells]
[LAOMOTO groans]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NARAKU]
Stop, Fujikido!
That's the classic strike
absorption stance
of the Itami Ninja Clan!
But those Itami fools have a
glaring hole in their defense.
Do you know what it is?
Damn straight!
[LAOMOTO]
Huh?
Ah! Impossible!
You may recognize my
seven ninja souls,
but you will never defeat me!
[NARAKU]
Now, Fujikido!
Finish him off with one shot!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[LAOMOTO]
Taste my foot!
Nnnnng!
[NARAKU] A move from
the Shrike Ninja Clan!
[LAOMOTO]
Nnnnng!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[LAOMOTO yells]
[NARAKU]
No! Fujikido, don't look at him!
[LAOMOTO yells]
[LAOMOTO]
Throw yourself at me head on!
Why run from the inevitable
when you can die
before your life
is completely ruled by pain?
[LAOMOTO]
Impossible!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NARAKU]
Fujikido!
Hand over your body!
Take it! Now!
[NARAKU yells]
[LAOMOTO]
Mmmm!
[NARAKU]
Carnage!
[HELLKITE yells]
[NARAKU groans]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[HELLKITE]
Aieee!
[NARAKU]
Look down!
Right beneath your feet!
He's losing his
situational awareness!
[LAOMOTO exhales]
[NINJA SLAYER]
What?
[HELLKITE] Prepare for
Laomoto-san's judgment!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Let go!
[NARAKU]
Damnit, Fujikido!
If he hits you with those
massive karate missiles,
your body has no chance
of surviving the trauma.
Our only hope is for me
to use all of my power
to defend us from the onslaught!
[LAOMOTO]
And now, I'll seal the deal!
[LAOMOTO yells]
[NARAKU]
We're out of time!
What are you doing? Naraku?
[HELLKITE]
Abbah! Sorry boss!
Banzai!
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[LAOMOTO yells]
[LAOMOTO laughs]
[LAOMOTO]
Victory!
But of course, I am
Demolition Ninja.
True Leader of the
Soukai Six Gates!
You never had a chance
of beating me.
Death is... the only way out.
[BOTH grunting]
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
[LAOMOTO]
Aaaargh!
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[LAOMOTO groans]
Death is the only way out!
You win.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
I am beaten.
Anything you want,
I will give you.
You want to buy your
way out of death?
Listen, if you let me live,
I'll give you whatever you want.
The only thing that I want...
[NINJA SLAYER]
...is for you to die!
Wasshoi!
Death is the only way
out for ninjas! [yells]
[LAOMOTO screams]
[LAOMOTO]
Damn you, Ninja Slayer-san,
I offered you anything,
and you took everything!
It's bad business!
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
You're finally awake.
Where am I?
And how did I get here?
I bet you ask those questions
more than most people.
All you need to know right
now is that you're safe.
You can rest.
Laomoto.
[AGATA] Whatever you've
been going through...
it's over.
How do you know?
I just know, okay?
It's all over.
The nightmare is over?
[AGATA] It's the morning
of a brand new day.
You can leave all that pain
and suffering in your past.
Focus on building
your life again.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Rebuild my life.
[AGATA]
Yes. The pain is over.
It's time to heal.
Of course, you'll have more
than your fair share of scars.
But those will only serve
as proof of your healing.
I have to rebuild my life.
Fuyuko.
Tochino--
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
Nancy-san?
[NANCY]
Rise and shine.
[NINJA SLAYER] This is what's
left of the castle keep, right?
[NINJA SLAYER]
I'm still here.
I guess I was dreaming.
[NANCY] I gave you a
shot of ZBR adrenaline.
Sorry if you're a naturalist or
whatever, but it's all I had.
[NINJA SLAYER]
No.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
What time is it?
[NANCY]
It's getting close to daybreak.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Is it all over now?
Is Laomoto-san dead?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?
I see.
You truly do reap what you sow.
[NANCY]
Yep.
But we really don't have to
time to wax philosophical.
Time to GTFO.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[NANCY]
What?!
I don't know what's happening.
It definitely wasn't
part of the plan.
[NARRATOR]
Neo-Saitama in Flames.