[NINJA SLAYER]
My answer is no.
[gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER] I won't
be lured by your schemes
and empty promises anymore.
I don't understand
what you mean.
After everything,
we're still no closer
to the antidote
for the Takeuchi virus.
I'm beginning to
suspect you're just
using me to satisfy your
journalistic curiosity.
No way! I want
to help you find it.
We've just run into
some bad luck is all.
But I know
the answers are hidden
somewhere in that
Yoroshisan factory.
[NINJA SLAYER]
I can't read her.
Is she telling
the truth or lying?
Tanuki is the key to
unlocking this mystery,
and with my hacking skills,
I know I can do it.
But, I have to
get inside that factory,
and I can't do that
without your help.
[distant sirens wailing]
[horns honking]
[keyboard clicking]
[beeping]
[NINJA SLAYER] My strength
is in slaying ninjas,
not cyber espionage.
It's unfortunate,
but I suppose I'll have to
continue working with her.
[NARRATOR] Nancy had
a back alley surgeon
perform an illegal
cybernetic augmentation.
She can wire straight into any
computer with an ethernet port.
And the pharmaceutical cocktails
she's just downed,
allow her to project
her consciousness
into IRC chat rooms. Trippy!
[beeping]
[NARRATOR] She maybe drooling,
but her typing speed
is beyond human comprehension!
Domo. I am Daedalus.
And you are a sight
for my sore eye.
[chuckles]
Abandon all hope, ye--
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
You told me this
chat room was secure!
Impossible to break into!
This creep must be
a better hacker than I am.
We've spent way too much
time in here anyway.
Domo.
Abandon all hope ye--
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
Domo. Your puny little
firewall has
more holes in it than an
eighty-column punch card.
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
[DAEDALUSES]
Domo. I am Daedalus.
He's using multiple logins!
[ding]
[NARRATOR] The yakuza clones
march in lockstep
down this squalid hallway
until they reach a door.
They were given their orders by
that one-eyed monster, Daedalus.
Who after breaking
into the chat room,
scanned Ninja Slayer's
IP address
and pinpointed
his physical location.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[YAKUZA CLONE 09A] Aaaargh!
--[YAKUZA CLONES] Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] At the center of
Neo-Saitama is Ayase Junction.
A sprawling and pollution filled
industrial waterfront
bisected by a large canal,
which leads into the bay.
All of Japan's most mega
mega-corps have a presence here.
[distant sirens wailing]
[MERCENARY 09A chuckles]
Now what
do we have here?
[chuckles]
Well, according to
the records,
this order is legit.
Gaigake-san is getting one of
these fancy whores delivered.
[MERCENARY 09A] Oh, it's
definitely legit!
C'mon man, don't bogart
that piece of ass!
[MERCENARY 09A chuckles]
Sorry brother.
But our work here is done.
[alarm beeping]
[footsteps]
[NINJA SLAYER] So you think
Yoroshisan Pharmaceuticals
are hiding their secrets
in this filthy place?
"To deceive an enemy,
one must first
deceive one's allies."
That's straight from
Miyamoto Mushashi,
if I'm not mistaken.
This is it.
I'm just sayin'
you coulda let me do
a double-check
on that whore, ya know?
All right, all right,
woulda ya quit
yer bitchin' already?
I know what'll
fix your problem, man.
Oh yeah, what?
Fuck and
sayonara, broham.
Little honey
on the stinger.
Just what I need!
--[NOTORIOUS] Yeeart!
--[MERCENARY 09A] Aaaargh!
Holy shit, a ninja?
What the fuck?
--[NOTORIOUS] Yeeart!
--[MERCENARY 09B] Aaaargh!
[NOTORIOUS]
Booyah! There it is!
My Bio-Iaido is freakin' badass!
[FOREST] I told you
to stand down, damnit!
If this was 'Nam
we'd be up to our asses
in VC and supremely FUBAR!
Yeah, uh my bad, Cap'n.
But did ya clock the speed
on that brutal takedown?
C'mon, admit it.
My Bio-Iaido totally slays!
[FOREST]
Stop runnin' your mouth.
Don't forget,
we're on a mission.
And it looks like some
cunning little bastards
have already been through here.
Hey Cap'n. I don't
get why someone else
would wanna come here.
D'ya think that maybe they're
after the Bio-Ingot too?
[FOREST] Yeah,
I seriously doubt that.
Hardly anybody even knows
about the thing's existence.
They'd think it's just a
green bar of adzuki paste.
[NOTORIOUS] Yep, someone's
definitely been here.
[FOREST] I told you
to put a sock in it!
[NOTORIOUS]
Abbah!
Spontaneous bleeding.
That's the first symptom of
severe ingot deficiency.
Then comes the vomiting.
[NOTORIOUS]
Abbah!
[NOTORIOUS] Uh, I can
still hack it, Cap'n.
It'll take more than that
to stop my Bio-Iaido!
Aaahhh! Abbah!
[FOREST] Just hang
in there, Notorious.
Iroquois Helicopter Evac
is gonna fly in
and get us out of this
godforsaken jungle!
[NARRATOR] Once again,
Forest-san's mind is clouded
by the Vietnam war flashbacks
that plague his ninja soul.
My intel says
the Viet Cong have
a Bio-Ingot maker
in their possession.
If we can sneak past
the DMZ and grab it,
our platoon can
keep on fighting
till we send Charlie back down
the Ho Chi Minh trail to hell.
On your feet! Let's move!
Move! Move! Move!
[YAKUZA CLONE 09A]
Hm?
[YAKUZA CLONES]
Die you bastard!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[YAKUZA CLONES]
Aaaargh!
[modem dialup static, beeping]
[gasps]
[alarm buzzes]
There's a tiger
at the front gate
and a buffalo at
the rear one, huh?
Yeeart!
Hurry and disable
the booby trap!
Nancy-san!
Ugh, talk about
outdated design.
Hate to do this,
but I kinda need that.
Even disabling the
password turns my stomach.
[alarm buzzing]
[NINJA SLAYER] Nancy-san,
are you okay?
I'm kinda woozy,
but I'll be fine.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Them again.
The Survivor Dojo!
My sweet and
sexy electronic bride.
I'm gonna get you this time.
I just hope your port can
handle the size of my LAN.