[NARRATOR] Looking into the
sordid dealings of Yoroshisan
and a cure for
the anti-ninja virus,
Ninja Slayer and Nancy Lee
have infiltrated
a hot water bottle factory.
Do you actually have any
idea where we're going?
No, but if we
don't stop moving
they're bound to catch up
with us any second now!
Yaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
What is this?
[NANCY] Looks like the
back door to the mainframe.
[NINJA SLAYER] They're about to
burst through the curtain,
so I hope you have a plan.
Don't worry. A girl
like me always has a plan.
I betcha I could
hit her with a suriken.
Ya want me to?
Why the hell
would I want that?
Blondie is gonna be
my future wife,
so don't damage the goods.
Keep your eyes peeled.
The enemy could be anywhere.
No doubt we're walkin'
right into a honey trap.
I know Ninja Slayer-san
is hidin' somewhere
out in that
bamboo jungle.
Waiting to terminate with
extreme prejudice.
I dunno, he prolly
got spooked
by my Bio-Iaido
and decided GTFO.
[FOREST] Do not let
your guard down, soldier!
I can't see the bastard,
but I can feel him.
Only two ways outta
here are death or victory.
All I'm sayin'
is that with my Bio-Iaido,
we ain't gotta worry
about anyone--
Would you please shut
your mouth for one second?
[NOTORIOUS growls]
[FOREST] You're a sly fox,
Ninja Slayer-san.
Very sly indeed.
[FOREST] Just behind
that wall scroll there.
That's where we'll find
the Bio-Ingot maker.
Mmm.
[FOREST] She's dangerous, but
those're some crazy ass titties.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Aaaargh!
Cap'n!
[FOREST yells]
[NINJA SLAYER] Domo.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Domo. They call
me Notorious.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NOTORIOUS] Double Iaido!
Whatcha gonna do,
Ninja Slayer-san?
You can't touch my Bio-Iaido!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NOTORIOUS]
Double Iaido!
Uh. Where'd he go?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Aaaargh!
Yeah, that hurts.
But there's still no way
you can put the brakes
on my Bio-Iaido!
[NARRATOR] The suriken begins
a chemical reaction,
and once again, Notorious-san
feels the pains
of severe Bio-Ingot
Deficiency Syndrome!
[NOTORIOUS]
Abbah!
--[NOTORIOUS] Aaaargh!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Carnage!
--[NOTORIOUS] Aaaargh!
[NOTORIOUS]
Sayonara!
[gasps]
Geronimo!
[FOREST groans]
[NANCY]
Aieee!
[FOREST]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] He could dodge it
with ease, but Nancy-san's face
won't be so pretty
if it's cut in half!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Saigon! Saigon!
[FOREST grunts]
Aargh!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Aaaargh! Yeaart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Yeaart!
--[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[grunts]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Aargh!
[NARRATOR] Whether due to
innate animal instinct,
or the situational assessment of
a seasoned platoon leader,
Forest-san becomes
increasingly aware
of the danger
that is Ninja Slayer.
He does as anybody who wants
to live would do. GTFO!
[NINJA SLAYER] Nancy-san,
are you okay?
Aieee!
Buddha. What's happening
in computer space?
Exactly like before.
The system developer is
definitely with them.
In that case...
[NANCY] Okay, the cybernetic
flux seems out of whack.
Is someone else hacking in?
Well, Domo. Nancy-san.
Don't deny my service.
Come and get cozy with me.
Share words and fluids
in IRC kotodama space.
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
[NANCY] Why the hell
is this creep here?
What's he looking for
in Yoroshisan's server?
[DAEDALUSES] Hope you've been
working your fingers.
You'll need to type faster
to outmaneuver me.
--[NANCY] Take this! Take this!
--[DAEDALUSES] Aaaargh!
[DAEDALUS] Resistance
is futile, m'lady--
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
The sheer speed
of my connection--
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
[DAEDALUS] I'd like to
give you an upvote!
--[NANCY] Take this!
--[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
[DAEDALUSES] Yeeart!
[NANCY]
Yeeart! Eat this!
[NARRATOR]
Nancy explodes into a
spinning ball
of death by karate!
Even Ninja Slayer
would have a hard time
pulling off this move!
[NANCY]
Tough luck, noob.
I don't waste time with
butthurt basement dwellers
who don't know
how to treat women.
[DAEDALUS]
Ponder this.
What is kotodama space,
and kotodama imaging?
It isn't something
that anyone programmed.
It's a spiritual experience.
We can share this
and all the sensations it
provides as a single user.
It's reality with benefits!
Doesn't that
sound amaze-balls?
Sounds like
cult garbage to me.
[DAEDALUS]
Open your mind.
Consider the radiant,
golden cube
that floats in the sky
above our heads.
Don't you want to unravel
all the mysteries inside?
Let me direct connect my LAN
and we'll go to digital heaven.
[NANCY] It's a trap. Just sweet
talk to try to crack my code.
I need to give him another kick!
We'll do it
the hard way, then.
I always have a tough time with
girls that are still conscious.
[DAEDALUSES]
Oh my Buddha!
Yeeart! Take this! Take
this! Take this! Take this!
[DAEDALUS] Oh baby, let me
interface with you!
[NANCY]
Take this! Take this!
Aieee!
Ugh! Scumbag!
[grunts]
[DAEDALUS]
No fap, just fucking.
[NANCY groans]
Aieee!
[DAEDALUSES] Aaaargh!
Aaaargh! Aaaargh!
Aaaargh! Aaaargh! Aaaargh!
What the hell?
Am I getting hacked?
[gasps]
Take this!
[DAEDALUS] Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer
spoofed his login!
This is a secured profile!
How in the hell
can a total white-hat
wannabe noob
hack into it like that?
--Take this!
--[yelling]
[DAEDALUS] No don't.
Are you banning my IP?
I'll die IRL!
[NANCY]
Sayonara, Daedalus-san.
[gunshot]
[alarms ringing]
[NANCY] Now. Once more
unto the breach.
[modem dialup static, beeping]
Nng, damn this thing.
A non-hacker like me has
no idea what to do with it.
I throw my hands up!
It's all up
to you, Nancy-san!
[beeing]
[NINJA SLAYER]
What the--?
This is bad!
[NANCY] I'm almost certain the
password is "tanuki," right?
[NANCY] Almost,
but not quite sure.
What the hell does this
calligraphy mean?
Nancy-san.
Time is running out!
[NANCY] All I have to do
is write "tanuki."
But for some reason,
I just can't do it!
[NANCY] It's like
my hand's frozen!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
30 seconds remaining.
[gasps]
[bells chime]
[NANCY]
Jose-san? Is that you?
"Speak naught of the past."
Arigato. My doubts
have been cleared away.
[gasps]
That's right, cleared away!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Excellent work, Nancy-san.
[NANCY]
I didn't do it by myself.
Taragi-san helped me.
And you. And him.
Jose-san.
Jose-san?
Never mind that.
It must've been a hallucination
or something I had.
All those drugs and electricity.
[NINJA SLAYER] To think she has
the drive to go further
than her body can take her.
She can't be the only
person in my life like this.
This world is
rotten and hellish.
But could there be more to
seek in it than vengeance?
At this moment,
my goals are pure.
Help Nancy-san and
Dragon-sensei. That's all.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!