[NARRATOR] After learning
of a plan to pack
the police force
with violent clone cops,
Nancy enlists
Ninja Slayer's aid.
If he'll help her infiltrate
the secret location where
they're being manufactured,
she'll share info on
the antidote for Takeuchi,
the anti-ninja virus.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Let me look at the map.
[gasps]
Don't scare me like that!
There it is.
The rice cracker factory.
[NANCY]
The intel checks out.
[NINJA SLAYER] I just
hope you're right.
[NINJA SLAYER] NN445s.
The same fearsome weapons
used by the Coast Guard.
Look at those ugly,
scowling faces.
[NANCY] They're clone
yakuza, right?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Correct.
Is the rice cracker
industry so cutthroat
they need that kind
of security?
Or are those mindless meat
robots guarding other secrets?
Let's find out.
I'll destroy them.
You wait here!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[YAKUZA CLONE 08A] Aaaargh!
--[YAKUZA CLONE 08B] Aaaargh!
[YAKUZA CLONE 08A, 08B]
Aaaargh!
I heard something over here.
What was it?
I don't know.
I'll investigate.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SNIPER YAKUZA CLONE 08B]
Aaaargh!
--Yeeart!
--Aaaargh!
[NANCY]
They out of our way?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart! We can sneak in
through the back door.
[NINJA SLAYER]
This is it.
[NARRATOR] The door is locked,
but steel's as good as paper
when faced with the
powerful grip of a ninja.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[door creaks]
[footsteps]
Let's see if your source
was right about this.
[NANCY]
Four to the right.
Then six to the left.
Four to the right again.
Once you're there, go back
left to number three.
[beeping]
[NANCY gasps]
[NARRATOR]
They're in an elevator!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE 08A]
Be prepared!
The door is about to open.
[NINJA SLAYER]
You heard the thing.
[ELECTRONIC VOICE 08A]
Here we are! Door opening!
[NANCY grunts]
[NARRATOR] Upon this discovery,
one has to wonder what
a rice cracker factory
could be doing
with this level
of industrial technology.
Something shady is cooking!
The hell?
What is all this?
[NINJA SLAYER]
I don't know.
But they're not making
crackers down here.
[NARRATOR] Oh my Buddha!
How taboo!
Scores and scores of those
ill-mannered yakuza
incubating in vats
of green, gooey liquid!
[NANCY]
If my intel is correct,
the clone cop experimental
division is straight ahead.
All we have to do is find
the main computer terminal.
Take this...
...nifty little memory card
and the virus program will
install itself. Like magic.
While that's happening it'll
also steal the info on "Tanuki."
[NARRATOR] A simple plan.
But one crafted to delve deep
into one of the greatest
mysteries man has ever known.
A conspiracy that may
never cease unraveling.
What is "Tanuki?"
[keypad beeping]
[long beep]
[NARRATOR] Anyone familiar
with a Japanese number pad
would be shocked
by this password.
Yoroshisan Yakuza? Come on!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE 08A]
The door is opening! Now!
[alarm buzzes]
[thud]
[gasps]
Are these all clone cops?
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
If the Neo-Saitama police
force gets a shipment
of these bio-mechanical brutes
as their new wave of rookies,
excessive force
will be the norm.
There it is. Let's go in.
--[MAN] Yeeart!
--[NANCY] Ngaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Domo, very
pleased to meet you.
My name is Forest Sawatari.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Forest-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Now I understand.
I'd assumed their security force
hadn't been hatched yet.
But it turns out there's
a ninja standing guard.
However, this will be
your final day on the job!
Death is the only
way out for ninjas!
[FOREST] "Ninja Slayer"
is a pretty ballsy thing
to call yourself.
[NANCY groans]
[NARRATOR] That's not the latest
fashion trend Nancy's sporting!
She's been bound and gagged
with shiny metal rope!
And in record time!
[NANCY groans]
[FOREST] Listen. You're right
about this being
my last day to work here.
I just resigned my post as
Yoroshisan security today.
I'm movin' on
to greener rice paddies.
[NINJA SLAYER]
And why should I care?
All I was doing
was collecting my things
and cleaning up as a
courtesy for the next guy.
[NINJA SLAYER] Hmm.
So that's why we were able
to get this far
without any problems.
But you're in our way.
[FOREST] You can go as far
inside as you want to.
But you'll have to
do it alone,
because I'm taking
the hottie with me.
I'm gonna love her
long time. Now step aside!
I refuse!
[FOREST]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[FOREST]
You wanna test me?
My Bio-Bamboo is four
times stronger than steel!
Bring it on!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi! Yeeart!
[gasps]
[FOREST]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[NARRATOR] Forest-san's arrows
are laced with deadly poison!
--[FOREST] Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
Aren't you a ninja?
Act like it.
Show me what you're made of.
You wanna know what
I'm made of, do ya? Hah!
You're never gonna
know that, man.
Because you weren't there
when all the shit
was going down back in 'Nam!
[NARRATOR] The ninja soul
possessing Forest-san
shows himself!
And when that happens,
things can get pretty hairy!
[FOREST]
Yeeart!
Hi-yah!
--[FOREST gasps]
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
[FOREST]
Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer
delivers a devastating blow
of dark karate
right to the face!
The "Somersault Kick"!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[FOREST] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[FOREST]
Aaaargh!
[FOREST groans]
[NINJA SLAYER] He's
neutralized for the moment,
but you've got to
get out of here, now!
[NANCY]
See ya!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Allow me to behead you.
--[MAN 2] Yaaa!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Huh?
Come on, Cap'n,
you can do
a hell of a lot
better than that!
Domo. What's up?
My name's Frogman.
Domo. How's it hangin'?
I am Disturbed.
Domo. What's goin' on?
They call me Notorious.
Domo.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Ninja Slayer.
I'll call you once
they're all dead. Hear?
[NOTORIOUS] Nobody really gives
a crap about your girlfriend.
In fact, I'm single
and loving it!
All I wanna do is show
off my sweet ass Bio-Iaido!
[DISTURBED moans]
You guys
hang back, will ya?
I'm stoked to show
this clown my Bio-Iaido!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NOTORIOUS grunts]
[DISTURBED]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DISTURBED] Aaaargh!
[NOTORIOUS] Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NOTORIOUS] Aargh!
[DISTURBED]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[NOTORIOUS] Let's rock!
I'll cut ya right in half!
[NOTORIOUS]
Aaaargh!
[NANCY] Sorry boys, but two
against one just isn't fair.
[DISTURBED]
You little...
[NARRATOR]
She's open!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DISTURBED] Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer
unloads with another brutal
dark karate move!
The "Body Check!"
[NOTORIOUS]
Iaido! Yeeart!
Booyah!
Notorious-san,
look above you!
[NOTORIOUS]
Uh! Huh?
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NOTORIOUS] Aaaargh!
Allow me to behead you.
I gotta say,
that was a sweet ass move!
[FROGMAN]
Yaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Nng! Not again!
We have learned
a painful lesson
from your dark karate.
So let's put a hold on this
battle for a little while.
Tell me this!
Do you ninjas
work for Yoroshisan?
Yeah, we used to work for
those cheap drug pushers,
but not anymore!
We're on our own now!
You can call us
the Survivor Dojo!
[FROGMAN] We were all
Bio-Ninja test subjects.
But then we
started thinking,
"should we be taking
orders from these
pencil-necked geeks?"
Hell no!
That's why
we're outta here!
So we can be free!
We are free at last!
[FROGMAN] But we're not greedy.
We gotta share our freedom!
So we're gonna go grab
all the other poor bastards
that they're keeping down
in the basement!
You didn't come out here
lookin' for us anyway, did ya?
So if you and
your lady friend wanna
snoop around, screw it.
Okay, I'm just gonna take
your silence as a yes.
Totally works for me.
We'll see ya later!
[sighs] Well, I guess
our work here is done.
The virus program
is doing its job.
The clones' genetic schematics
are being rewritten as we speak.
It's gonna take a pretty long
time for Yoroshisan to fix it.
That's very good to hear.
Now about the data
you promised me.
Hand it over.
[NANCY]
I still need to process it,
so you'll have to wait.
I'll get it to you soon.
You trust me, don't you?
[NANCY]
Mmm.