[NARRATOR]
Polluted heavy metal rain
falls on pier three
in Neo-Saitama.
The scene of a negotiation
over the going rate
of the drug Men-tai.
But it, and a few heads,
were cut off, by a ninja!
Is this how you pledge
allegiance to the Soukaiya?
[MAN]
Yes! Please forgive us!
[groans]
[ARSON] I suppose
everyone makes mistakes.
Especially those who have
not been taught their place.
Soukai ninjas are not
to be trifled with,
but I suppose you know that now.
[MAN]
Yes! Please forgive us!
[ARSON] Then you will
cooperate, Smith-san?
[SMITH]
Yes! Please forgive us!
[NARRATOR]
The ninja known as Arson
and the Yakuza clones
climb into the family taxi.
[ARSON]
Tokorozawa Pillar.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm. Yes, sir.
[ARSON] Hmm.
You're not the same driver
I had last time, are you?
[NINJA SLAYER] No. Kameji-san
has retired, sir.
[ARSON]
Good for him.
[tires squeal]
[ARSON]
You idiot! Don't you realize
you're going the wrong way?
[NINJA SLAYER] Oh, this'll
get you where you're going.
[ARSON]
What do you mean?
[NINJA SLAYER]
You're going to hell!
[gasps]
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
[ARSON] What is this? What do
you think you're doing?
[NARRATOR] This is
a very pertinent question.
What is the driver of
the Yakuza family taxi doing?
[NINJA SLAYER]
You're roadkill now! Yeeart!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS, ARSON]
Aaaargh!
All right you bastard!
You'd better tell me
who sent you!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Hey, screw you!
A ninja?
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
[ARSON] So you're the
"ninja-slayer," are you?
Domo. Ninja Slayer-san.
I am called Arson.
I thought surely
you were just a legend.
A lie told by
weaklings and losers!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Don't worry.
Soon you will no longer have
to care about such lies.
I'll break your karate
and send you to hell!
No you won't!
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR]
Arson's karate was a form
of the Inferno-style,
Kajon-Jitsu!
This involves using pyrokinesis
to cause your opponent
to spontaneously combust!
[ARSON]
Yeeart! What the--?
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[ARSON] Aaaargh!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Die! You bastard!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Aaaargh!
[ARSON] Ah! Impossible!
This cannot be happening!
[NINJA SLAYER] You should
know that death
is the only way out for ninjas!
[ARSON] This aggression
will not stand, Ninja Slayer!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Death is the only way out!
[ARSON]
Yeeart!
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Uh-oh. Arson realizes
he's missed his opportunity!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[ARSON]
Abbah!
More ninjas
from the syndicate
are coming here now
to avenge me!
[NINJA SLAYER]
That sounds perfect!
[ARSON] You can't escape!
They're coming!
Darkninja-san will be with them!
And he'll kill you himself!
Aarrgh!
Then I will just
have to kill him myself!
[ARSON]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[FEMALE VOICE 02A]
It's cheap! It's cheap!
Ridiculously cheap!
Do not be alarmed!
This blimp is for
advertising purposes only!
There's absolutely
nothing fishy about it!
This is only
a demonstration of how
targeted marketing
solutions can help you
grow your business.
And knock out the competition.
Please do not be alarmed.
[FEMALE VOICE 02A]
Consider using explosions
to maximize your
advertising's effectiveness.
[NARRATOR] The Omura Industries
blimp is not just fishy,
but a counter-ninja Airship
dispatched by the Soukaiya!
[NARRATOR] The Soukaiya's
headquarters looms over the city
atop the Tokorozawa Pillar.
Laomoto's Penthouse!
The rogue ninja
has been located
and we're locked on target!
Very good.
Omura Industries' battle
demon gargoyle airship,
the Bubujima--
Fool!
[KINJIMA]
Aieee!
[LAOMOTO]
Such insolence!
We will only
talk about business
when I want to talk about
business! Understood?
[KINJIMA] A thousand
pardons, please sir!
[LAOMOTO]
Now let me see.
Show me how your toy works!
[NARRATOR] The Otoro Maguro
sushi overflowed
with fatty goodness!
He devoured two pieces at once!
[NARRATOR] With lightning-
fast ninja reflexes
and kinetic visual acuity,
taking out homing missiles
is as easy
as swatting mosquitoes!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[KINJIMA]
Aieee?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] The deadly surikens
wielded by Ninja Slayer
are like no other known to man.
Other ninjas might as well
throw pocket lint!
[KINJIMA] Aieee!
What the hell is going on?
[LAOMOTO] Why are you
letting this happen?
Don't tell me that
your technological arsenal
of lasers and missiles can't
even kill a single ninja?
[KINJIMA]
No! No sir!
I mean, this is
just a prototype,
the real one will surely be--
[LAOMOTO] I am beginning to
lose patience with both you
and your pitiful
spectacle, Omura-san.
Finish the job!
[KINJIMA] Aieee! Laomoto-san,
if you want this ninja to die,
we can send our
company ninja after him.
[LAOMOTO] All I want, is for you
to kill this damned ninja,
and don't waste another
second of mine doing it!
[KINJIMA]
Go get him!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Yes sir! With Pleasure!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
The only thing
worse than a ninja,
is a ninja wearing a jetpack!
Domo! I am called
Cloud Buster.
Domo! I am Ninja Slayer.
Whatever you try,
will end with your demise!
[CLOUD BUSTER] Pride goeth
before a fall! Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Behold! This is science!
Yeeart!
[grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Industry!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[CLOUD BUSTER] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER gasps, grunts]
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Industry!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
[CLOUD BUSTER grunts]
[LAOMOTO]
Mwa-ha-ha-ha!
That proved to be quite
entertaining indeed, Omura-san!
Ooh! I appreciate that sir,
and I am so sorry
for that little "inconvenience"
we had earlier!
Recover his body
and bring it to me at once.
This insect must be dissected
and studied closely
by the syndicate.
Of course, sir!
[NARRATOR] No! Has Ninja Slayer
himself been slain by a ninja?
This cannot be!
[NARAKU]
How pathetic.
I had such high aspirations
for you, Fujikido.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Silence!
[NARAKU laughs]
If you possessed my true karate,
you would have never fallen
victim to that lowly ninja.
That crane fly!
[NINJA SLAYER] Silence.
You are just a ghost!
I swear I will do it!
[NARAKU]
Do what, exactly? Tell me!
[NINJA SLAYER]
I will kill the ninja!
[NARAKU] But there's only
one way that can happen!
[NARAKU, NINJA SLAYER]
Death is the only way out
for ninjas!
[NARAKU] I will have to
kill the ninja myself!
Let me show you how it is done!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Huh? No! That's impossible!
I killed him with my own hands!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[CLOUD BUSTER] Aaaargh!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Uuh? Industry!
What the--? Your body
should be convulsing
from the shock of
a billion volts right now!
You're just a toy robot!
[NARRATOR] His eyes
burn like sparklers,
leaving an afterimage in the
darkness of the witching hour.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[CLOUD BUSTER] Augh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Aaaargh!
[KINJIMA]
Huh? Aieee!
[CLOUD BUSTER]
Aaaargh! Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
You're nothing but a tiny man
with a flying piece of garbage!
Your meager, pitiful karate
cannot help you now!
[KINJIMA]
Aieee!
[COURTESANS scream]
[LAOMOTO]
Yeeart!
Damn you. Ninja Slayer!
[SMITH] Hmm. Thought I
smelled some money.
But this dude's busted.
He's got somethin'
on him though.
Aieee!
Where am I?
Tell me where I am!
Just calm down, man.
You're in Old Tokyo Bay!
I want you to take me to a
back-alley doctor right away!
Right!
You guys take care
of things for a while.
I'll explain everything later!
[MAN 02A, 02B gasp]
[SMITH] That's it!
I'm outta the game!
I knew karma would bite me
in the ass sooner or later!
No more dealin' Men-tai!
I'll drop this dude off
at the doctor,
give all my money
to a drug rehab,
and take my ass to Kyoto!
I'll become a Buddhist monk
and pray every day
I never come across
another ninja in my life!
I'm gonna be a new man,
I promise!
[NARRATOR] Smith has a severe
case of Ninja Reality Shock,
which creates a feedback loop
of fear and repentance.
He guns his jet-ski,
carrying the Grim Reaper
of ninjas back to the city.
[SMITH]
Ain't karma a bitch!