[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer
and Nancy formulated a plan
to assassinate Laomoto Khan,
the Soukaiya kingpin!
But the plan was leaked and
ninjas were sent to capture
Nancy and slay the
Ninja Slayer himself!
Our hero fought them off,
but Nancy is still in the
clutches of ruthless ninjas.
How could this have happened?
To find out, let's travel
back in time one day!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe Miyamoto
Musashi once said:
"Poke at affections
with a man-catcher,
and be swept up
in the maelstrom."
Or, something like that.
Yeah, uh, domo. This is
Trufflehog calling. Hey.
False alarm here.
Looks like this lucky fellah
won the stray bullet lottery
while he was surfing the net.
I don't think it's
syndicate related.
Yep. Just a victim of physics.
Hm? Wait. That's weird.
[snorts]
[NARRATOR] This ninja is an
expert at reconnaissance!
He can glean volumes
of information
from just a few sniffs!
Ah. Scent of ninja soul.
It's still close.
I'll just have to
follow my nose!
[TRUFFLEHOG]
Yeeart!
[WARLOCK] There are no Soukai
ninjas in that part of town.
In fact there have
not been for some time.
I think you may have rooted
out the elusive Ninja Slayer.
[TRUFFLEHOG] Yeah, domo.
I'm inside the apartment.
No one's here but me right now,
the Ninja Soul has
left the building.
Whoever lives here, doesn't
give a crap about decorating.
[WARLOCK]
Excellent work, Trufflehog.
[TRUFFLEHOG]
Thanks.
[WARLOCK laughs] But I shall
take over from here.
[TRUFFLEHOG]
Huh?
[WARLOCK shouts]
[NARRATOR]
And with that brief warning,
Warlock thrusts his
consciousness into Trufflehog!
It's the motionless
possession jitsu!
[laughs]
Well then, how about you
and I begin our dance,
Ninja Slayer-san?
[NARRATOR] This series of
events was set into motion
by the valiant
defense of Agata-san
by the chivalrous Ninja Slayer.
As the saying goes,
"no good deed goes unpunished,"
tossing out that no good bum
would indeed come back to haunt
our masked defender of justice.
[WARLOCK chuckles]
[NANCY grunts]
[gasps]
I'm here to pay
my respects, Nancy-san.
Domo, I am the one
known as Baba Yaga.
[gasps]
[BABA YAGA]
Actually, I have a task
I need you to
accomplish for me.
So try to stay alive
at least a bit longer.
[BABA YAGA laughs]
[NANCY gasps, grunts]
Damn it. This is impossible!
How can this be happening?
The transportation's ready.
Are you?
I simply just can't
comprehend it!
He makes no mistakes!
He's some kind of superhuman!
Let's take the girl and go!
Did you get all the
recording devices?
I may be flummoxed, but I have
not lost my presence of mind!
Let's make haste!
[WARLOCK]
We're plotting a straight course
directly to the wharf!
I do still have faith
in you! Trust me.
We are very far from
being checkmated!
[NANCY] My hideout at the
abandoned movie theater
was a secret to everyone,
including Ninja Slayer-san.
He won't know this pig has me!
This is an emergency,
yes, but a minor one.
We get through this,
Ninja Slayer will have
no idea where to find us.
Absurd!
He found us, Warlock-san!
Oh Buddha. How can this be?
See ya!
[BASILISK]
Hold on! Let me handle him!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Basilisk-san,
pleased to meet you.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[BASILISK]
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Basilisk. How the
devil did you find us?!
[NINJA SLAYER]
I'll show you how!
[shouts]
[BASILISK]
Huh?
[gasps]
[BASILISK]
Go on, Warlock-san!
I'll crush this fly!
[WARLOCK growls]
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart! Yeeart!
Taste my tire tracks!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
It was my mistake.
I should have killed you
from the beginning myself.
Instead of leaving
you to my underlings!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[BASILISK] Yeeart!
Like you, I've tasted slaughter
and hunger for more!
It's a true warrior's feast!
And in this city I am
the apex predator!
[NARRATOR] Gouranga!
Am I seeing things?
I've heard of someone
being driven up the wall,
but this is ridiculous!
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
Now, Ninja Slayer-san.
Cough up your guts like
the road-kill you are!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[BASILISK]
What the-?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Yeeart! Yeeart!
[BASILISK]
Argh!
[BASILISK grunts]
[BASILISK] Very impressive,
Ninja Slayer-san.
Kwah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] Basilisk throws a
fierce stare with his evil eye!
Without his lightning
fast Ninja sixth sense,
Ninja Slayer would have been
vaporized by this fatal Jitsu!
[BASILISK] Hmph,
awfully quick on you feet.
My Evil Eye kills whether or not
it matches my opponent's gaze.
One hard look and it's all over.
Your demise will be
mine alone to witness!
Unfortunately, it is not an
attack I can use too often.
Kiyah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Argh!
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[NARRATOR] A forbidden
move in aikido circles,
it's the catapult throw!
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
This will be your final moment.
Once you're dead, I will be
free to slay Laomoto Khan!
I'm sure you'll have a view
of the action. In hell!
[BASILISK] Seems that
you're feeling the poison
from my suriken! Ha!
You might as well
be dead already!
[BASILISK]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[BASILISK screams]
[BASILISK screaming]
[BASILISK groans] What kind
of monster are you,
Ninja Slayer-san?
[grunts]
You slayed four of my assassins,
and as for the
Shadow Guild-- Bleh!
Your death haiku. Recite it now.
I will not! Your pity is false.
Used only to mask your pride.
It will be your end! Kwah!
[BASILISK screaming]
[NARRATOR] Using the mirror
torn from the motorcycle,
he reflects Basilisk's
Evil Eye right back at him!
[BASILISK screams, groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Domo, Laomoto-san.
I am the ninja
known as Trufflehog.
[LAOMOTO]
Domo, Trufflehog-san.
Is this bedraggled woman
some sort of offering?
If that's what you wish.
But she is the one who summoned
you and DarkNinja-san
to this location.
She was plotting to
take both of your lives.
With a little help from
Ninja Slayer-san, that is.
Ho-ho. So she's in cahoots
with Ninja Slayer-san.
She is. And if we
torture her long enough,
we could get all
kinds of information
on this mysterious Ninja Slayer.
Yes, perhaps that's true.
Without further ado--
Gwah!
[NANCY gasps]
His true body will
be dealt with.
It will be dealt with.
[phone rings, clicks]
[GATEKEEPER]
Domo, this is Gatekeeper.
The body's been dealt with.
[DARKNINJA]
It has been dealt with, sir.
You know how much I
appreciate efficiency.
[LAOMOTO, DARKNINJA]
Huh?
Neenja Slayer-san!
Ho-ho.
[NANCY grunts]
Then I shall take my leave.
Toy with him a bit.
[DARKNINJA]
Consider it done.
[NINJA SLAYER] Domo.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Gwagh!
[DARKNINJA grunts]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
Damn! Yeeart!
[LAOMOTO]
That's enough.
I can't sit idly by and watch
you have all the fun, now can I?
Mwah-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Laomoto Khan.
I must tell you I admire your
bravery, in taking me on.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
You work quickly, but I'm
the one in charge here!
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Argh!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[LAOMOTO] If you don't
broaden your focus,
you will never see the
forest for the trees,
or the natural order of things,
Ninja Slayer-san.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Huh?
[DARKNINJA] On your feet,
Ninja Slayer-san!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Argh!
[DARKNINJA]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Argh!
--[DARKNINJA] Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Aargh!
[NARRATOR]
The fatigue of endless battle
and the poison
inflicted by Basilisk
have taken their toll
on Ninja Slayer!
He is getting tore
up by Darkninja!
[LAOMOTO]
Return, Darkninja!
[DARKNINJA]
Yeeart!
[LAOMOTO]
Mwah-ha-ha-ha!
That was quite an
entertaining show!
But the mongrel's
had enough.
I think it's time we
put him to sleep.
[gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Laomoto.
Laomoto. Laomoto!
Laomoto!
[AGATA gasps]
Morita-san?
Domo Agata-san.
Good to see you.
[NARRATOR "Poke at affections
with a man-catcher,
and be swept up
in the maelstrom."
If whoever originally coined
that phrase were to witness
these two now, what bizarre
saying would they offer?
Morita-san! Let me help you!
Take me home. I have a
first aid kit. Back there.
Of course!
[NARRATOR]
That altruistic yet savage act
our hero performed yesterday.
Would that ricochet and cause
his untimely but imminent death?
I'm still not done.
One more battle.
[NARRATOR] Or was that shining
good deed in a weary world,
a harbinger of the
golden light of humanity?
A light that Ninja Slayer will
surely summon from
Pandora's Box.