[AGONY screaming]
I think the fire could
use more fuel!
Yeeart!
[AGONY screaming]
[screaming continues]
[AGONY]
Gwaaaaggh!
[AGONY panting]
[AGONY groaning]
[AGONY screams]
[screaming continues]
[GINICHI whimpers]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
Run while you can!
Go, now!
[GINICHI grunts]
[AGONY]
Sayonara!
[GAUNTLET] You're gonna die,
Ninja Slayer-san!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[GAUNTLET]
Aieee!
[CENTIPEDE]
No! This is the end!
[GAUNTLET, CENTIPEDE]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Death is the only
way out for Ninjas!
[YAMAHIRO]
Aieee!
Yakuza Tengu-san's comin'!
He's gonna murder our asses!
Like a plague of justice,
Yakuza Tengu
descends from above!
[GREEN ELEPHANT]
Domo, Yakuza Tengu-san.
I am Green Elephant!
[YAKUZA TENGU]
Hey, screw you!
The Ninja smote the
waters of the Nile,
until they ran red
and deep with blood.
[YAKUZA TENGU] I'm sorry
that it's come to this.
I really am.
But still.
I've got to send you back
into the burning pits of hell
where you belong.
I should never have done it.
I should never have turned you
loose on that godforsaken day.
Pay up!
There was a bounty
on that ninja's head!
So you gotta pay up!
Cause if you stiff me,
I'm taking you to
the land of goblins,
and we'll eat you alive!
[MINUTEMAN grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[MINUTEMAN]
Sayonara!
[INTERRUPTER]
I guess...
I should've seen this coming.
Right, Morita-san?
[INTERRUPTER groaning]
I chose this life.
It was bound to happen
sooner or later.
I have one last wish.
Ninja Slayer-san,
please behead me.
[INTERRUPTER]
Listen.
There's a bar... called "Chab."
Find Mainichi-san.
He can tell you where Yuk--
I mean Amnesia-san....
Where she can be found.
[INTERRUPTER]
Sayonara.
[NANCY grunts, gasps]
[NANCY yells]
[NANCY gasps]
[SABOTEUR]
Kchertu!
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[QUICKSILVER gagging]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo.
Darkninja-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[DARKNINJA]
Domo.
Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Darkninja.
I'm a little busy, so...
[QUICKSILVER groans]
[DARKNINJA] I'll have to
tag in Quicksilver-san.
[QUICKSILVER screaming]
[DARKNINJA]
See ya!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
Huh?
[beeping]
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[QUICKSILVER]
Hail Laomoto-san!
Banzai!
You have my loyalty.
Until my dying breath.
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
Fuyuko.
Tochinoki.
[yells]
Back then.
Back then...
Why didn't I...?
Fuyuko.
Tochinoki.
Back then...
Why didn't I...?!
Fuyuko. Tochinoki.
Why didn't I...?
Back then!
Fuyuko.
Tochinoki.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[glass shatters]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?!
[SUICIDE groans]
[SUICIDE]
I think I broke my spine.
I'm dead.
Domo Sonic Boom-san.
I am Yamoto Koki.
[SONIC BOOM] So you're
a psychic Ninja as well.
Very surprising for
someone to harness
the gift at such a young age.
[footsteps]
[FYLGJA]
Well...
It would seem this is the
end of the line, friend.
[SUICIDE groaning]
[FYLGJA laughs]
[MATADOR]
Olé!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hmmm.
Hmmm...
Hm... Mm. Mm.
Hmmm.
Hmmm...
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[MATADOR yelps]
I will not play shogi
with the likes of you!
[SUGAWARANO]
Abbah.
Ninja Slayer-san.
Please.
Listen to me.
I told you my son, Hitori,
left for Kyoto to work for
a cosmetics company.
[DEADMOON]
It's been a long time, Pop.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[SUGAWARANO]
Abbah.
Hitori.
Is that really you?
That used to be me,
but because of you,
I have a completely
new life now.
I should thank you.
One more thing.
I have a new name these days.
You can call me Deadmoon.
The two of us are a
lot alike, aren't we?
Ninja Slayer-san.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
No way in hell I'm getting
captured this time.
[YAKUZA CLONES]
Hey, screw you!
[NANCY]
Take this!
[YAKUZA CLONES groaning]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Chupacabra-san.
Or should I say,
Chief Chaveta-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Moo.
[CHUPACABRA]
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Chupacabra.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[CHUPACABRA yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[NINJA SLAYER] To me, you are
neither human, nor Chupacabra.
You are a ninja!
And death is the only
way out for ninjas!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[CHUPACABRA]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo.
I am the one called
Ninja Slayer.
Why did you kill them?!
[DARKNINJA]
Domo, I am Darkninja.
The syndicate has a powerful,
methodical system
of dark control.
I can't waste my time
trying to explain it
to a renegade like you.
[NINJA SLAYER] Then explain
it with your Karate!
[DARKNINJA] I already told
you, I don't have the time!
[DARKNINJA grunts]
[DARKNINJA]
Uh?
[NINJA SLAYER] You're not
getting away that easily!
[DARKNINJA]
You mad dog!
[NARRATOR] So, what did you
think of Ninja Slayer's battles?
Slaying ninja after ninja!
Ninja Slayer will not stop
until he has slain all the evil
ninjas that plague this world!
Carnage!