[NARRATOR] High above the
rotting heart of Neo-Saitama
stands the Nekosogi fund's
Tokorozawa Pillar.
Headquarters of
the Soukai Syndicate.
Release the
man-eating lions!
[LIONS roar]
[BOTH] Muah-ha-ha-
ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
That kind of discipline can
only be found in clones.
They're killing machines
that can't be stopped!
If they're that strong,
then release Hugeshuriken.
[YOROSHISAN]
Huge what?
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Aaaargh!
Hiee!
Muah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
"Can't be stopped,"
you say?
[YOROSHISAN]
Um. Laomoto-san!
I am terribly sorry, sir!
If those clones
could kill my ninjas,
I would have to ask myself if
they were loyal to me or to you.
Yoroshisan. Once again,
you've provided me
with exactly what I wanted.
[YOROSHISAN]
Mmm.
[LAOMOTO] Still, I can't let you
live after fouling my floor.
I have a reputation.
You understand.
Aieee!
I have more tasks
for you, Hugeshuriken.
Two forces stand in defiance
of the syndicate.
First, there is Niinja Slayer.
Second is the Dragon Dojo.
I want you to
go with Earthquake
and burn that dojo
to the ground.
[HUGESHURIKEN]
I'll be glad to, sir.
[NARRATOR]
Neo-Saitama's north side.
The Chugoku District.
[HUGESHURIKEN] Excuse me sir;
I seem to be lost.
Where might I find
the Dragon Dojo?
I'm in a rush, so talk
before I get bored
and break your pinky.
Please don't do that!
I don't know anything!
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Yeeart!
--[KANBAGI] Aieee!
[HUGESHURIKEN]
You'd better talk or else
I'll break
your ring finger.
[KANBAGI] Please don't do that!
I don't know anything!
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Yeeart!
--[KANBAGI] Aieee!
[HUGESHURIKEN]
You'd better talk or else
I'll break
your middle finger.
[KANBAGI] Please don't do that!
I don't know anything!
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Yeeart!
--[KANBAGI] Aieee!
[HUGESHURIKEN]
You'd better talk or else
I'll break
your index finger.
[KANBAGI] For the love of
Buddha, I really don't know!
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Yeeart!
--[KANBAGI] Aieee!
[beep, beep]
[HUGESHURIKEN] Huh?
[EARTHQUAKE] Huge. You can
cut your "interview" short.
We've got some
new surveillance intel
from Hellkite-san.
It seems he's found
the Dragon Dojo for us.
Wow, the bat did
something right for once.
I'm sure he'll take more than
his share of the credit too. Ah!
I was just about to
take that piss-bag's
little piggies to the market!
[EARTHQUAKE] This traffic
is intolerable.
Are they obstructing me
deliberately?
I don't have time for this.
There's no room in the plan
for such a lengthy commute!
[engine revs]
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Aaaargh!
--[EARTHQUAKE groans]
[panting]
Who's responsible for this?
That bastard Ninja Slayer;
he's on his way now!
Ninja Slayer? There's no way
he could have found us!
Does he know
about our plan?
[engine revs]
[tires screech]
[HUGESHURIKEN] He attacked
me like a mad-man!
No, like a rabid wolf
with blood red eyes!
Earthquake-san,
we have to move faster!
He'll catch up with us in a
matter of seconds at this rate!
[EARTHQUAKE] A formidable
opponent he may be,
but I doubt he has what it takes
to defeat the both of us.
What confounds me
is the fact that
he's showing up here and now.
Is it merely a coincidence,
or is he interfering
with our attack?
Does this mean he
and the Dragon Dojo
are somehow connected?
[alarm buzzing]
[EARTHQUAKE] Huh?
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Danger! Danger!
[HUGESHURIKEN]
No, It's him!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. Hugeshuriken-san.
Earthquake-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Tell me. For what purpose
do you seek the Dragon Dojo?
[HUGESHURIKEN]
D'ya really expect us
to answer that, ya idiot?
[NINJA SLAYER]
I suppose not. Yeeart!
Damnit! Yeeart!
Aaaargh!
Hellkite-san!
You've finally arrived.
[HUGESHURIKEN] Not that
anyone asked you to.
[beeping]
[EARTHQUAKE grunts, chuckles]
[NARRATOR] They did not
need to use words.
Instead, they communicated
through a secure,
high-performance
IRC terminal wired into
Earthquake-san's Harley by
the Soukai Syndicate's
partners at Omura industries.
[NARRATOR] This man is the
master of the Dragon Dojo.
His name is Dragon Gendoso.
The last true ninja in Japan.
[NARRATOR] This graceful young
girl is Dragon Gendoso's
only known grandchild.
Her name is Yukano.
Amongst other traits,
she boasts an ample bust.
[GENDOSO] It seems Ninja Slayer
won't be showing up after all.
Perhaps it's better
this way. Time will tell.
[distant motorcyle rumbles]
Go men.
Seek out the intruders
and leave none alive!
[NINJAS]
Sensei!
Domo. Dragon
Gendoso-san, is it?
We are the Soukai's
Six Gates ninjas.
We've come here tonight
to burn your dojo
to the ground.
Domo. Soukai-Six-
Gates-Niinja-san.
Indeed I am Dragon Gendoso.
So you are the
lap-dogs of Laomoto--
[HUGESHURIKEN]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] Oh my Buddha!
What a dastardly surprise!
Aaah!
[gasps]
[NINJAS]
Yeeart!
No, fall back!
[NARRATOR] The arrowhead ninja
formation, as described in
the record of ancient matters,
is "a nigh unstoppable
attack formation capable
of breaking stone walls."
[NINJAS]
Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] However,
Hugeshuriken observed that
these ninjas were
all the same height.
An excellent toss, Huge.
[HUGESHURIKEN]
Huh?
--[YUKANO] Kieee!
--[HUGESHURIKEN] Aaaargh!
Uh! Unhand me!
[coughs]
Huh?
Gendoso-san.
Aknowledge your defeat
and come quietly.
Or else her blood will be
on both of our hands.
Ngaaah!
[gasps]
[ALL]
It's Niinja Slayer-san!
Stop right there,
Ninja Slayer-san!
Or else this
busty lass will die!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Carnage!
[NARRATOR] Fujikido's ego
has been subjugated
by the soul of Naraku
Ninja, who wants to
kill all ninjas,
good or bad.
What happened after
his defeat on the highway?
What could have
pushed him so far?
To solve the
blood-soaked puzzle of
Ninja Slayer's psyche,
we must turn back the clock.
[YAK grunts]
[NARAKU]
That was disgraceful!
I'm embarrassed
to be haunting you!
Let me take things from here.
Using my dark karate,
we can wash away your shame
in a jacuzzi of
Soukai ninja blood!"
[NARRATOR] Oh my Buddha!
What a tragic turn of events!
Desperate to create
a safe world for the pair
to whom he felt indebted,
Fujikido acquiesced to
Naraku Ninja's seductively
phrased demands.
[YAKS grunt]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARAKU]
Well done, my boy!
Now that you've admitted
you're a pantywaist,
Daddy's gonna slit
some ninja spleens!
Not just the Six Gates ninja,
I'll make ribbons outta
every last one of em!
[EARTHQUAKE]
Hm?
--[YUKANO] Ngaaah!
--[EARTHQUAKE grunts]
Ngaaah!
[EARTHQUAKE]
Aaaargh!
Yukano! Run away!
[YUKANO gasps]
[grunts]
--[YUKANO] Kiee!
--[EARTHQUAKE grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[EARTHQUAKE] Yeeart!
[NARRATOR]
The red light of madness
has vanished from his eyes.
Now they run with
manly tears of blood.
Yukano and Gendoso's cries have
re-awakened Fujikido's ego!
[NINJA SLAYER] I'd pay
any price for a chance
at revenge, but those lives
aren't mine to barter.
[EARTHQUAKE]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
I tried to slay the people
I set out to protect.
There's no virtue
in the fact that I failed.
I'm as bad as the ninja scum
that slayed my family.
[NARRATOR]
Are we about to witness
the downfall of our hero?
[NINJA SLAYER] I need
rest and there's no futon,
so I'll just die.
I'd commit sepuku
if I had a sword.
[GENDOSO] On your feet,
Ninja Slayer-san! Now!
Gendoso-san!
You're just
an ancient relic.
The age of true ninjas
is over! Yeeart!
Remember this well,
Ninja Slayer-san!
A true ninja doesn't fight
power with power alone!
Consider this
your first lesson!
Study my movements
and do as I do!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh? Yeeart!
Now, Ninja Slayer-san,
use your shuriken! Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[EARTHQUAKE]
Nng! Aaaargh!
Listen up! The first truth
I wish to teach you
is illustrated by the giant
standing before us.
Remember, if you
cannot slay your foe
with one hundred shurikens,
that doesn't mean that
you attack with only one.
It means you throw
one thousand shurikens!
Hellkite-san,
you tardy bastard,
why haven't you come
with the reinforcements?
You've left us for dead!
Huge! Wake up, please!
[BOTH]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR]
Dragon Flying Kick!
[EARTHQUAKE]
Aaaargh!
Sayonara!
Congratulations.
You've passed the first
section of your training.
You've saved
my life twice now,
but I don't understand why.
Inside your soul,
I see a battle between
a pitch-black shadow
and a warm golden light.
That light
is of your spirit,
and should it
banish the shadow,
I can guide your soul to the
heights of Kinkaku Temple.
A path I've walked before.
Sensei!
[chuckles]
--[squelch]
--Aaaargh!
--[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
[NARRATOR]
A dart in the back!
Fired by none other
than Hugeshuriken!
He's still alive!
The dart was coated in
Takeuchi, an anti-ninja
virus developed by
Yoroshisan Pharmaceuticals.
It works its way through the
body of Japan's last true ninja,
leaving devastation in its wake.
[NINJA SLAYER]
You poisoned him? Really?
What kind of pansy ninja
fights with poison?
Damn you and your hopping.
Now I'm fresh out of darts.
Ya see, Earthquake
used me as a decoy.
Least he got what he deserved.
We'll meet again in hell.
Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER, GENDOSO]
[ALL]
Aaaargh!
[GENDOSO] Looks like
we'll have to run for it,
Ninja Slayer-san!
This way! Come!
[HUGESHURIKEN]
Aaaargh!
I know a safe place;
follow me!
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
The dojo!
[NARRATOR]
Talk about overkill!
The Soukai have dropped
twenty-five megatons
of Banzai ba-boom onto the dojo!
Run, Ninja Slayer!
You've come too far!
Dozens of back-to-back
death-matches
have taken their toll
on Ninja Slayer's body.
He's nearing his limit.