[HELLKITE groans]
[LAOMOTO]
Damn you, Hellkite-san!
Why didn't you report
this to me sooner?
How dare you embarrass me
with your incompetence!
Unacceptable!
Huh?
[LAOMOTO] He's moved through
the gates this quickly?
[yelping]
It looks like even
Gatekeeper-san has fallen!
[HELLKITE grunts]
Politics can wait.
Ninja Slayer-san is a
plague on the syndicate.
He must be eradicated at once.
Cover me on my way
out of the castle keep.
Fail me this time and it
will be your last mistake.
[HELLKITE]
Yes, sir! I understand!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Attention! Attention!
Ninja Slayer-san has seized
70% of the castle keep.
Where is Nancy-san?
[ELECTRONIC VOICE] Currently,
she is in an offline domain.
I'm sorry, but this is
as far as I can take you.
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Go right ahead.
You have arrived.
Oh, look.
Hey, big boy.
[GREEN OIRAN]
You wanna play with us?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Laomoto-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[LAOMOTO laughing]
[LAOMOTO]
Domo to you, Ninja Slayer-san.
I must say that the
amount of disruption
you've left in your wake
is very impressive.
You are quite an ambitious
little rat, aren't you?
[NINJA SLAYER]
But if that little rat
bites a lion just once, the
king of the jungle can die
from anaphylactic shock.
[NARRATOR]
Wow! What a poet!
Can you believe how Ninja
Slayer expertly fused
metaphor with modern
medical science?
So you crawled out of the sewer
and into the lion's den.
Such a foolish endeavor.
What drove you
to take this risk?
[NINJA SLAYER]
You murdered my wife and child.
You stepped on my family
like we were insignificant
worms, weak and helpless.
What you failed to realize
is you didn't step on a worm,
you stepped on a cobra
with deadly fangs!
That so?
It won't matter in the least
if you can't get within
striking distance.
[BLUE OIRAN]
Oh my.
[BLUE OIRAN cuckles]
[GREEN OIRAN]
He is so worked up.
[PURPLE OIRAN] I think he's
just about ready to explode.
[RED OIRAN]
What a bad boy.
[NARRATOR]
Oh, Buddha! A honey trap?
Who saw that one coming?
[OIRANS]
Eat this!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[OIRANS]
Oh my!
[OIRANS yelling]
[OIRANS]
Oh my!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?
[yelling]
[SPIDER screaming]
[SPIDER]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Tell me,
am I in "striking distance"
now, Laomoto-san?
[LAOMOTO] I suppose you
are, Ninja Slayer-san.
But first, let me tell you
something about myself.
There are seven ninja souls
dwelling inside of me.
Seven of them.
That makes me the most powerful
ninja the world has ever known.
No man, living or
dead could beat me.
You may wonder,
"If that's the case,
then why does Laomoto-san
have so many traps
and ninjas surrounding him?"
Do you want to know why?
Because you waste my time!
Do you understand what each
second of my day is worth?
Instead of playing
silly games with you,
I could be making billions.
My time is the most precious
commodity on the planet
and you've made me squander it!
The Six Gates were
put in place to ensure
that I don't have to deal
with this kind of headache.
[NINJA SLAYER]
But now, your precious Six Gates
have been torn wide open.
This so-called "headache" should
be the least of your worries.
What you should be
more concerned about
is keeping your head
attached to your body.
But once I remove it, you won't
have a care in the world.
Because you'll be dead!
[LAOMOTO laughing]
[LAOMOTO] This conversation
is going nowhere.
But I suppose a rat like
you could never dream
of understanding the
thoughts of an eagle.
Did you not hear me before?
I'm an unstoppable
force of nature.
The most powerful ninja
the world has ever known.
I will have to show
you what I mean
as I end your pathetic life.
[NARRATOR]
Gouranga!
What an incredibly frightening
display of psychokinesis!
[laughs]
[laughing]
[LAOMOTO]
Now strike, Ninja Slayer-san.
I can end your suffering.
You can see your wife and child.
I'll send you across the Sonzu
River to be with them in Hell!
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[LAOMOTO growls]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?
[BOTH yelling]
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
[LAOMOTO laughing]
[LAOMOTO] How boring. Has
the cobra lost its fangs?
[laughing]
[LAOMOTO]
Arrogance beget by ignorance!
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
[LAOMOTO yells]
This is the fate that
befalls all of those
who are foolish
enough to defy me.
Now recite your death haiku,
Ninja Slayer-san.
[NINJA SLAYER]
I refuse. I refuse!
[LAOMOTO laughing]
You're a joke that's
run its course.
You call yourself Ninja Slayer,
yet you squirm under my boot.
Ha!
[NINJA SLAYER]
I will slay you. Ah!
I am the one true ninja.
The one who's
mastered the jeetsu
to control seven ninja souls.
I have no equal in this world.
In time, I will be worshipped.
I am more than a ninja.
I am a god!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Death is the only way out...
...for ninjas.
Perhaps I should start by
dismembering you alive.
Stop, Fujikido. I won't have it.
Fujikido, stop now!
[LAOMOTO]
Huh?
Is this a runaway ninja soul?
Death is the only
way out for ninjas.
way out for ninjas!
So die!
[yells]
[yelling]
You may have murdered
my wife and child,
but you will not
murder me today.
Today, you will be
murdered, Laomoto-san!
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[laughing]
It seems the room cannot
contain my power.
Come up here if you
dare, Ninja Slayer-san.
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[NARRATOR]
These foul, evil, black flames
were a telltale sign
of Naraku's presence.
But since Fujikido still
had control of his own body,
how was this possible?
The answer was
simple, yet elegant.
Ninja Slayer was
consuming the ninja soul,
using it like fuel to feed
his appetite for vengeance!
Huh? Such ferocity.
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[HELLKITE yells]
[LAOMOTO]
It's still not enough.
Out of steam so soon?
[LAOMOTO, HELLKITE laughing]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[LAOMOTO]
You may think this is unfair,
but combat and business
are one and the same.
You either take the advantage,
or you suffer the loss.
Now die, Ninja Slayer-san!
The only way out...
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] The secret
Iaido technique, maki-age!
[laughing]
It's all over now.
Sayonara, Ninja Slayer-san.
Now explode and scream it out.
[laughing]
[LAOMOTO]
Huh? What the--?
Is this body-double jitsu?
Huh?
[NARAKU]
Domo, Laomoto-san.
I am Naraku Ninja.