[NARRATOR]
The story of how Ninja Slayer
arrived in the secret hideout
of the revolutionary movement,
Ikki Uchikowashi is a
ascinating one indeed.
And at its center is Yukano,
the granddaughter of
his sensei, Dragon Gendoso.
[ANSWERER]
Hajime!
[GIANT yells]
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[NARRATOR] After Darkninja's
devastating attack
on Gendoso's bamboo grove,
Yukano fled and somehow
lost her memories.
She is now an agent
working for the
leftist rebel ninja group,
and goes by the name Amnesia.
A fitting title.
[GIANT shouts]
[groans]
With that. I hereby welcome
Ninja Slayer-san into our ranks
and to fight alongside us in the
name of progress and revolution.
[PARTY MEMBERS] We approve!
Revolution! Revolution!
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am the one they call Answerer.
You are now part of
Ikki Uchikowashi.
Domo.
[NARRATOR] Before moving on
to the next plane of existence,
Dragon Gendoso's spirit charged
Fujikido to watch over Yukano.
Now he must investigate
this group she's joined.
[NINJA SLAYER] What can
you tell me about Yuk--
I mean, Amnesia-san?
[ANSWERER] She is an
outstanding warrior.
[NINJA SLAYER] What can you
tell me about your leader,
this Buster Tetsuo?
[ANSWERER]
He is an outstanding leader.
[NINJA SLAYER] Is this
"Buster" a ninja as well?
[ANSWERER]
All your questions will be
answered in due time, comrade.
And allow me to remark on your
astonishing combat skills.
It may seem like hyperbole,
but just adding your
strength to ours has
doubled our potential for
radical progressive revolution.
Your previous exploits
have been...
Somewhat "lacking in direction,"
to put it politely.
[clears throat]
Please forgive me,
but I truly believe
that joining our cause
will provide you with
the opportunity to harness
your ninja skills and let
them be a driving force
for meaningful progressive
change in our society.
Perhaps that will be the case.
We have a common enemy.
Defeating Laomoto Khan is
paramount to overthrowing
the bourgeois ruling
class once and for all.
[PARTY MEMBER A]
Incoming signal!
Comrade Flickshot-san
has returned!
[PARTY MEMBERS] Recognized!
Revolution! Progress!
The ruling class has
long had its boot
on the neck of the proletariat,
but you will provide
the downtrodden
with a katana sharp
enough to sever the heads
of their oppressors
once and for all.
Domo, comrades.
Answerer-san and
Ninja Slayer-san.
I am comrade Flickshot.
[NARRATOR] Like a bullet shot
from the barrel of a gun,
a small transport
pierces the almost
artificial natural scenery
with amazing speed.
It is the two-car bullet train,
dubbed The Galaxy.
Despite the immense
connotation of its name,
it is the smallest
in existence,
and carries quite a
rather unique cargo.
A cargo so unique,
it has caught the eye
of the militant
progressive revolutionaries
known as Ikki Uchikowashi.
[MEN scream]
[warhorn bellows]
[PARTY MEMBERS shout]
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Throw!
[FLICKSHOT]
Second wave... strike!
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Strike! Violence! Revolution!
[PASSENGERS scream]
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Assertion! Revolution! Progress!
[screaming continues]
[PROMINENCE yells]
[PARTY MEMBERS shouting]
There he is.
[PROMINENCE yells]
[PROMINENCE]
Domo. Behold my glory,
you commie crumb snatchers.
I am Prominence.
[FLICKSHOT]
Domo, Prominence-san.
I am a warrior for revolution.
And I fight in the name
of Ikki Uchikowashi.
I am Comrade Flickshot.
Our mission here is to confirm
this bourgeois bullet train
is nothing more than a
transport for the Soukaiya.
The true enemy of the people.
Prominence-san,
you are a member of that
corrupt gang's elite Six Gates.
The ninja dagger in the
back of the proletariat.
Our aim is to purge
society of your evil.
[PROMINENCE laughs] So that's
how you substantiate your sins?
Flickshot-san,
your reputation precedes you.
My association is well
aware of your actions.
Your pitiful idea
of parceling out
possessions is sending
your pathetic party members
to plunder pachinko parlors,
and partition up the property
amongst your principals!
[yells]
[PROMINENCE yells]
Are these flaccid fragments of
flotsam flung to foment fear?
[FLICKSHOT grunts]
[PARTY MEMBER G]
Comrade Flickshot-san!
[FLICKSHOT]
Huh?
All of our comrades
that were ejected
from the transport are dead!
They've been turned into ashes!
[laughs]
Please allow me to
show you personally
how my Katone-jitsu is
the superior ninja weapon,
as I parlay your puny
pellets into smoke.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[PROMINENCE groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Prominence-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[PROMINENCE]
Domo.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance,
Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Prominence.
Has your one-man war
against the syndicate
now turned into a crusade under
the colophon of communism?
How completely comical!
The reason I fight is
none of your business.
--[NINJA SLAYER yells
--[PROMINENCE groans]
[PROMINENCE]
Blarg!
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[PROMINENCE grunts]
[NARRATOR] Gouranga! This is
how a true ninja fights!
Although one may
possess specialized jitsu
or fearsome ninja weaponry,
If they don't have the
karate to back it up,
they will always
get their ass beat
by the incredible
ninja slayer!
Oh, drat. What a
disastrous denouement.
Will your death haiku
be as alliterative?
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Take the spoils of war!
Take them from the bourgeoisie!
Commandeer their stuff!
Just as I thought!
The transport was hauling
decadent bourgeois goods!
The Soukaiya are foot soldiers.
Preying on the working
class of Neo-Saitama.
Ninja Slayer-san. You must kill
that patrician puppet at once.
Cut off his head!
[PARTY MEMBERS] Compulsion!
Assertion! Evolution!
[PASSENGERS whimper]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh? Children?
[GIRL A]
Mama!
[GIRL B]
I'm scared!
[FLICKSHOT]
There stands the next generation
of feckless aristocrats.
Swathed in their silken robes.
[PARTY MEMBER H]
Compulsion!
[FLICKSHOT] You're in
charge of the indoctrination
of these depraved and
selfish offspring?
Aiee. Don't hurt them.
Do whatever you will to me,
But for the love of Buddha,
please spare the children.
Vice Principal-san!
Please sir, have mercy on him.
Mercy is useless, when dealing
with filthy capitalist pigs.
Please forgive us sir. A-Aiee.
Forgive? Bourgeois scum.
We're here to purge you all.
[growls]
[yelps]
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[FLICKSHOT grunts]
What do you think you're doing,
Ninja Slayer-san?
Now I realize the true
nature of the Ikki Uchikowashi
is not what you and your
"comrades" claim it to be.
Death is the only
way out for ninjas!
You dare go against the
will of the movement?
If you expect me to
believe a killer like you
has a problem purging
scum from our society,
Then we'll have to
purge you first!
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Assertion! Revolution! Progress!
This is a dangerous game you're
playing, Ninja Slayer-san.
You should realize that death
is also the only way
out for those infidels
who criticize Ikki Uchikowashi!
[PARTY MEMBERS]
Purge! Purge! Purge!
[FLICKSHOT]
Criticize yourself!
[yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[FLICKSHOT] I warned you
this is a dangerous game,
Ninja Slayer-san.
[FLICKSHOT]
One individual cannot overcome
the power of
collective ideology.
Their shields will ricochet!
[FLICKSHOT]
Don't you see?
My pachinko-jitsu and
the tools of my comrades
work in perfect harmony.
Feel our collective power!
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Oh, my Buddha!
Their combined efforts result
in an omnidirectional attack!
[TRAIN CREW]
Hurry! Get inside now!
[TEACHER] While they're fighting
each other, we can escape!
[FLICKSHOT]
The poisonous ways
of the bourgeoisie
are trickling down
to the proletariats,
who are now content to
live in slothful idleness.
And you've taken
it upon yourself
to challenge the saviors
of the common man?
As an Ikki Uchikowashi
party member,
I declare you, Ninja Slayer-san,
to be a danger to society
and hereby submit
an ex-post-facto
resolution to purge you,
on which I now act!
[yelling]
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[PARTY MEMBER screams]
Impossible!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[shouts]
[PARTY MEMBERS scream]
[NINJA SLAYER shouting]
[FLICKSHOT yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[PARTY MEMBERS scream]
No! Inconceivable!
We are the people's hammer!
The mighty blunt force
of the working class!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[FLICKSHOT groans]
Now die, Ninja Slayer-san!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[PROMINENCE groans]
[PROMINENCE]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
--[FLICKSHOT groans]
Earlier you said that I
was a danger to society,
challenging the saviors
of the common man!
But the true danger
is an organization
that believes power grows
from the barrel of a gun
and uses that philosophy
to slaughter the innocent.
You think mercy is worthless?
And compassion?
These concepts may not be in
your organization's vocabulary,
but they're what make us human!
[FLICKHOTS groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
You and I are similar.
We're like two raccoons
from the same hole.
We're killers, plain and simple.
After all the blood
that we've spilled,
our humanity is the one
thing we can't lose.
We'd be monsters!
[FLICKSHOT]
Sayonara.
Hmph. I must say,
he is quite fascinating.
But who is he?
Someone you used to know,
Amnesia-san. Very long ago.
In your former life.
[AMNESIA] I've forgotten
that life completely.
The organization is my life now.
And Ninja Slayer is threatening
it, so he must be dealt with.
I'd thought you'd
say that, and I agree.
To some extent.