[NARAKU] Do you see
what happens, Fujikido?
If you'd let me take over
you could be raising
the severed head of
your enemy in triumph
and showering
yourself with his blood.
Then give me strength.
[NARAKU]
Listen to me!
Allow me to control your body,
And you will have more strength
than you ever dreamed possible!
[NINJA SLAYER] No, I refuse.
This is my vengeance.
I just need more
strength to carry it out.
[NARAKU]
You're like a child, Fujikido.
Petulant and selfish!
You make demands of me?
I won't stand for this outrage!
[NINJA SLAYER]
You think this is outrage?
I'll show you outrage!
[NARAKU]
How dare you?
[yells]
[gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER]
I see. So it worked.
Forgive me for
bothering you, but--
[gasps]
[AGATA whimpers]
[AGATA]
Aieee.
How much time have
I wasted sleeping?
I found you last night.
Around the witching hour.
You've been asleep ever since.
[NINJA SLAYER]
A full day gone.
[TV ANNOUNCER] With one day
remaining before the deadline
for candidates to declare.
Laomoto Khan throws
his massive hat--
[NINJA SLAYER]
The governor's race?
Well, of course, I've invested
billions upon billions
into this city. It's just
a matter of common sense
that I'd want to personally
protect my investment
by making Neo-Saitama
great again.
The people need someone
with my financial knowledge
and negotiating power.
So it would be wrong of me to
not share my gifts with them.
You're leaving,
right now. Aren't you?
I'm afraid I must.
Sorry. Thank you.
It's the least that I could do.
You saved my life.
I had to repay your kindness.
I don't know exactly
what you're doing.
But can I imagine that it
will be extremely dangerous.
So please be careful.
[tires squealing]
[NINJA SLAYER]Yeeart!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
First floor.
[CLONES]
Die, you bastard!
[LAOMOTO' VOICE]
Muah-ha-ha-ha-ha!
That you have the
nerve enter this place
thrills me to no end,
Ninja Slayer-san.
It seems you are
quite infatuated
with this Caucasoid woman.
And with a body like that,
who could blame you?
[clapping]
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE]
Domo. The Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Laomoto's Voice and it's
quite an honor to meet you.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE]
My boss and I
are extremely happy you've
joined us here today.
The only thing that could
make this moment better
is if you kneel down and swear
your loyalty to the Soukaiya.
Laomoto-san is magnanimous.
Do this and I'm absolutely
certain he would immediately
appoint you top ninja
of the elite Six Gates.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE]
Aieee! How rude!
[CLONE]
Argh!
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE] So it's true,
what they say about you.
You're nothing but a mad dog,
ready to bite the nearest hand.
I bet you ravaged that
blonde slut every night
with that kind of intensity!
Buried yourself inside
her like a wild animal!
Muah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
She's being taken care of
by the big man himself.
He's probably with
her right now.
Licking that tight little
body up and down.
As she moans and shudders with
unimaginable pleasure. Oh yes!
He's going to love finding out
all her dirty little secrets!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE]
Aieee!
[CLONE]
Aaaargh!
You'll end up on your knees by
showing your devotion
to the syndicate,
or begging for your life.
Kill him!
[CLONES repeating]
Die, you bastard!
[CLONES]
Aaaargh! Aaaargh!
Die, you bastard!
[CLONES]
Argh! Argh!
--[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
--[CLONES] Argh!
There he is!
Shoot him out of the sky!
[CLONES]
Die, you bastard!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[CLONES]
Hey, screw you!
[CLONES scream]
Aieee!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[LAOMOTO'S VOICE] Argh!
Listen. I have one question.
Tell me, sir.
What is your floor?
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Training ground.
[ELECTRONIC VOICE] Where
there's a will, there's a way.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[LAOMOTO'S VOICE]
Sayonara!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Athletic floor.
[SAWATARI]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
You didn't offer me a greeting!
Have you forgotten
your etiquette?
Well, it wouldn't be much
of an ambush if I stopped
to ask you how your day was
going beforehand, now would it?
What business do you
have in this den of thieves?
Are you one of the
Soukaiya dogs now?
What I'm doing
here is surviving.
I've been combing my way
through here for the past week.
Stay away from my treasure!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
But I can't let you
stand in my way!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SAWATARI]
But now, you're in my way!
[NINJA SLAYER, SAWATARI]
Yeeart!
[SAWATARI] The Soukaiya has
been completely FUBAR lately,
and I bet it's because of you.
They want you as a POW, right?
Wait. The only POW they're
keeping is that blonde POA,
and you came to rescue her!
Just imagine how
grateful she'll be.
Well, that settles it then.
To make my time in this
hellhole worthwhile, I'll snatch
the treasure and the booty!
She seems more than
a handful, so wish me luck!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?
Yeeart!
[SAWATARI] The early worm gets
the bird, Ninja Slayer-san!
Yeeart!
See ya!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[SAWATARI yells]
[BOTH YELLING]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Battlefield level.
[yelling continues]
[SAWATARI]
Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[SAWATARI] Gwar!
[SAWATARI]
Hate to break it to ya,
But making money and making
love are way more important
to me then wasting my
time messing with you.
[SAWATARI]
Argh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm?
I tried to shake you off, but ya
couldn't resist, could ya?
[MOTOR DOKURO]
Enemy spotted!
New tactical
opponent discovered.
Greeting mode. Engaged.
Domo. I am Motor Dokuro.
I refuse to offer
greetings to a machine.
[MOTOR DOKURO]
Ninja soul detected.
Opponent meets the criteria for
positive ninja identification.
Exterminate! Exterminate!
Exterminate! Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SAWATARI] Our battle will
have to wait, Ninja Slayer-san.
Looks like the
VC're gettin' backup
from the latest
Soviet technology.
War is hell, ain't it?
For them!
[MOTOR DOKURO] Exterminate!
Exterminate! Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[MOTOR DOKURO] Pigaah!
[SAWATARI]
Yeeart!
[MOTOR DOKURO]
Pigaah!
Exterminate! Exterminate!
[SAWATARI]
Saigon!
[MOTOR DOKURO] Piga-ga-gaah!
Pi-ga-ga-gaah! Piga-ga-gaah!
Pi-ga-ga-gaah!
[crashing]
[SAWATARI] I guess we can
get back to our battle.
So step up and get some!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wait!
Yeeart!
[SAWATARI]
What the--? Yeeart!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Domo. I am Motor Dokuro.
Ninja soul detected.
[RED MOTOR DOKURO]
Exterminate! Exterminate!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[RED MOTOR DOKURO]
Pigaah!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Exterminate!
Saigon!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Pigaah!
Yeeart!
[RED MOTOR DOKURO]
Pigaah!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Piga-ga-gaah! Exterminate!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[RED MOTOR DOKURO]
Pigaah!
Yeeart!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Piga-ga-gaah!
Yeeart!
[YELLOW MOTOR DOKURO]
Piga-ga-gaah, gaah!
So now that Brezhnev's
robotic commie
goons are out of the picture.
Huh?
It's time for you and me to
settle the score, Ninja--
[groans]
[SAWATARI]
Slayer-san.
No...
[coughs]
Your heart is on the
opposite side, is it not?
Then I suppose you'll suffer
much more than a normal man.
[SAWATARI]
The hell?
All this time I've been
chasing down Charlie,
and he's standing right
behind me. Damnit.
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
[SAWATARI groans]
[SAWATARI grunts]
I can't fail the Survivor Dojo.
I still have to find
Ho Chi Minh's
secret treasure and
bring it back to them.
[SAWATARI]
Abbah!
[crashing]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, Darkninja-san.
I've been waiting for the
time we'd meet again.
[DARKNINJA]
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
Please excuse the delay.