You can't hide
from me, little pig!
You're the last one gettin'
slaughtered today!
So stand up!
[FUJIKIDO groans]
But before I
send you to hell,
how about I peel off your face?
You won't be needing it
now will you?
Mwahahahaha!
Why is this one still alive?
[OFFENDER]
Huh?
Just get to the
entertaining part already!
Let's see what he looks
like under his skin!
Mwahahahaha!
Let's scare him so bad
he pisses his pants first,
Scatter-san.
Come on, he is the
last one left, isn't he?
The scouters
are only picking up
three life signs at the moment.
And we all know that
that's one too many.
I was hopin'
there'd be more,
so we gotta make this one count!
Yeah, well Darkninja-san
killed almost everybody
worth killing in the feud.
So why does he
get to hog all the fun?
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee
Let's play a game!
The more you scream
the faster you die!
Must die.
Huh?
Death is the only way out.
You actually
want me to kill you?
Death is the only way out.
Uh-huh.
[FUJIKIDO]
Yeeart!
[OFFENDER]
Aaaargh!
No! Offender-san!
Death is the only
way out for ninjas!
What's going on here?
Who in the hell are you?
[FUJIKIDO]
Yeeart!
[SCATTER]
Aaaargh!
[FUJIKIDO]
Yeeart!
Augh! But I'm a ninja.
How can this be happening?
--[FUJIKIDO] Yeeart!
--[SCATTER] Aaaargh!
But I'm a ninja!
--[FUJIKIDO] Yeeart!
--[SCATTER] Aaaargh!
[SCATTER groans]
--[FUJIKIDO] Yeeart!
--[SCATTER] Aaaargh!
Impossible! I'm a ninja.
Death is the only
way out for ninjas!
[FUJIKIDO]
Yeeart!
Augh! Sayonara!
What the hell
kind of demon are you?
The boss told us
that this was gonna be
a walk in the park!
[FUJIKIDO grunts]
[yells]
[bellows]
[grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[NARRATOR] Before a ninja
engages in a bloody,
merciless battle,
it is imperative
he offer his rival a greeting.
And according to the Record
of Ancient Matters,
this greeting must be returned.
Hey. Uh.
Domo Ninja Slayer-San.
I am called Offender!
What in the hell
do you want from me?
To die!
But why?
Because you are a ninja!
Then I'll have to
kill you first!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[OFFENDER]
Aaaargh!
Recite your death haiku,
Offender-San.
Before it's too late.
I don't want to die.
I'd do almost anything
--to go on living! Aaaargh!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
[OFFENDER]
Sayonara!
[SALARYMAN 01A] Man, get this
crap outta the way!
I gotta get through!
[MALE COP 01A] Sir! This area
is closed to the public!
You gotta go around!
[SALARYMAN 01A] What's the
big deal? Is there a fire?
Towering inferno, cop?
I don't care what
you're playing around with,
'cause I got go to
work in the morning!
What's your badge number?
[COP 01A] Oh! You think
I'm playin' around, huh?
--[COP 01A] Yeeart!
--[SALARYMAN 01A] Aaaargh!
Lousy drunk! You need to
check that attitude right now!
--[COP 01A] Yeeart!
--[SALARYMAN 01A] Aaaargh!
[COP 01A] Hey boys,
we got a live one here!
--[COPS] Yeeart!
--[SALARYMAN 01A] Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
[somber music plays]
[FUJIKIDO]
Fuyoko, Tochinoki.
Ugh! I am Fujikido Kenji.
I am Fujikido Kenji.
[MALE VOICE]
Yes, that is you!
Domo, Fujikido Kenji-san.
I am Naraku Ninja.
Domo, Naraku Ninja-san.
I don't understand this at all.
You are a ninja?
[NARAKU]
Yes. That is I!
A ninja that kills other ninjas!
Join me in my quest
for vengeance!
Death is the only
way out for ninjas!
[FUJIKIDO] My family
was killed. By ninjas!
[NARAKU] Yes, your beautiful
wife and son
lost their lives
at the hands of ninjas!
And you would have
joined them in death.
But I saved your life.
I saved you,
so that you could
take out your vengeance!
[FUJIKIDO] Vengeance. Yes.
Vengeance will be mine!
[NARAKU laughs intensely]
Yes, it will! Join me!
We will kill all ninjas!
[NARRATOR] The cross katana is
the mark of the Soukaiya.
The murderous syndicate
that killed his family.
They put no value
on human lives.
They believe the strong
can trample on the weak.
Fujikido-san thought
about how he could
make them pay for what they did.
All the ways he could
make them suffer.
It sounded like
a great time to him.
At this time,
Fujikido-san saw the ninja
reflected in the glass and
realized he was that ninja.
He was now the ninja
that kills ninjas!
Ninja Slayer!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[alarm rings]
[DELIVERYMAN 01A] Aieee!
Oh my Buddha, it's a ninja!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[DELIVERYMAN 01A]
Aieee.
Aieee!
[rock music plays]
[beeping]
[rapid beeping]
Ha ha! It looks
like he's been injured!
That means he won't
get away from me! Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[MYRMIDON]
Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER] Domo!
Let me introduce myself!
I am Ninja Slayer.
Domo Ninja Slayer-san!
I will now introduce myself!
I am Myrmidon!
[NARRATOR] The witching hour.
When even the plants sleep,
and when Ninja Slayer
launches into battle
from the stately Torii gate.
You are the lowest
piece of garbage there is!
A rat that feeds on blood!
[MYRMIDON]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
This is a mistake
that you won't even
live long enough to regret!
No one defies the Soukaiya!
So that is what the cross
Katana emblem means, does it?
It marks you as a Soukaiya.
That's good to know.
Now that you know,
what are you gonna do?
I will slay ninjas. And you
are the next one to die.
I will slay all of
the Soukaiya ninjas!
Then, I will slay all ninjas!
These sound like
the ravings of a lunatic!
[NINJA SLAYER]
You think this is just talk?
[MYRMIDON]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
[MYRMIDON]
Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR] Though the villain
is covered head to toe
in heavy ninja armor, he is
still light on his feet!
But, the ninja soul that
dwells deep inside of him,
his fighting spirit, wants
nothing more in the world
than to turn and run
from the terror before him!
The terrifying might
of the Ninja Slayer!
[MYRMIDON]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[MYRMIDON] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[MYRMIDON]
Aaaargh!
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER laughs intensely]
[NARRATOR] And with these
three ninjas dead and gone,
Ninja Slayer begins his
bloody quest for vengeance.
The road he was
just beginning to travel
will be a long one indeed.
And it will most certainly
be littered with the dead
and dying bodies of countless
ninjas along the way.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[cell phone static]
[beep]
[ALL]
Here you go big daddy.
Kill him!
Consider it done.