[MAN breathing heavily]
Society is a hole, man!
The system is jacked!
I gotta shoot somethin'
to feel better!
[metal clangs]
[MAN] Oooh!
[OLD WOMAN]
Aieee!
[panting]
Abbah!
That was awesome!
Die, ya old bitch!
[chuckles]
Ah!
Aw, man I missed!
Damnit!
[SILVER KARASU] I'd assume
not hitting your mark
would be something
you're used to.
Gimme a do-over!
I'm gonna fill ya
full of holes!
[SILVER KARASU] It's one
strike, punk. Sorry.
[MAN]
Abbah!
[SILVER KARASU]
Namu Amida Butsu.
[GEISHA 13A] Aieee!
I didn't see anything!
I swear. Please don't kill me!
[SILVER KARASU]
Oh, yeah?
[trigger clicks]
[MALE GUN VOICE]
Power level: low.
[SILVER KARASU]
Goddamn technology.
[SMILING OLD MAN] Good job,
Silver Karasu-san.
You always give me
exactly what I want!
Now let's make tracks,
Smiling Old Man.
Of course! We don't
even need roads!
[MALE AD BALLOON]
Yoisho! Yoisho!
Come to our resort and
enjoy sweet rice cakes
and sweet deals on our
vacation points system.
Never mind the maintenance fees,
bring on the fuggitaboutit!
A vacation?
[KAGI] Mm. Just something to
pass the time till I die.
Which won't be very long.
[WOMAN]
Oh yeah?
[BOTH laugh]
[NARRATOR] The unscrupulous and
depraved can find many ways
to make money in Neo-saitama's
grimy underbelly.
Cyber-tsujigiri,
or techno-tsujigiri
is one such way. It is
a kind of "on the street"
human experimentation,
where random passersby
are attacked with
new weapons, poisons,
or sometimes malignant
strains of bacteria.
Of course, even in this
urban jungle it is still
considered highly illegal and
punishable by death.
[YAKUZA 13A grunts]
I'm gonna murder
your ass, you bastard!
[NARRATOR] This is how Silver
Karasu made his living.
[HEROINE 13A] Oh no!
This is terrible!
We're completely out of power!
No one has the strength
to fight anymore!
[MALE VILLAIN laughs]
That's right!
Say your prayers!
[BARIKI BOY] Don't worry,
here comes Bariki Boy!
I can soar like a crow in the
sky, 'cause I'm Bariki Boy!
I've got plenty of power
to kick some tail!
Domo. Uh. My name's
Kagi Tanaka.
Domo to you.
I'm Yamoto Koki.
So uh.
Can I take one?
Go ahead.
[KAGI]
Hmmm.
[BARIKI BOY] I've got
the power of Bariki Drink!
Taste my karate! Apow! Apow!
[MALE VILLAIN] Aah!
Curse you, Bariki Boy!
You just watch out next time!
The galactic empire's
technological might
will make you
taste our science!
[beeping]
[FEMALE DRYER VOICES]
Drying is now complete.
[BOTH gasp]
[chuckles]
I'm out. It was...
nice meeting you.
This is a rough part of town,
so be careful out there.
[YAMOTO]
Thanks.
[footsteps]
[door thuds open]
[door thuds close]
Domo. I am the one
they call Nutcracker.
Domo. I am Yamoto Koki.
So you're the brat
who's been taking on
the Soukaiya? It's a
miracle you've been able
to survive this long,
but your luck just ran out.
[YAMOTO]
Yeeart!
--[NUTCRACKER] Yeeart!
--[YAMOTO] Ngaaah!
[NUTCRACKER]
Your karate is pitiful,
just as I expected
from a stupid ass kid.
And I'm supposed believe
you killed Sonic Boom-san
and Bicorn-san all by yourself?
That's bullshit!
Who's your daddy?
--[NUTCRACKER] Yeeart!
--[YAMOTO groans]
[yells]
I read the report
on your jitsu.
You fight by throwing stupid
little paper cranes?
Origami's not
a weapon, girlie.
And it ain't gonna
do ya any good
in this tiny-ass room!
[NARRATOR] Oh my Buddha!
He's read his Sun Tsu.
Using a Furinkazan approach and
controlling the elements.
[NUTCRACKER] I wanna hear
you beg for your life
and the name of every swingin'
dick you're working with.
I have ways
to get what I want.
A little thing like you, no
tits, is really not my type,
but you gotta make do
with what you got.
You know what
I mean? Gwaaagh!
[KAGI]
No. What do you mean?
Are you trying to
tell her that there are
some people out there who
like to attack from the rear?
You bastard. Abbah.
[KAGI] Soukai ninjas are
always so thick headed.
I'll push extra hard.
[NUTCRACKER]
Abbah!
S-Sayonara!
[KAGI]
Oh yeah, sayonara.
[YAMOTO]
You. You're a ninja?
[KAGI] Why the hell're you
meeting up with creeps like him?
Start talkin'.
[DOCTOR] You see all these
little black circles here?
They look like
shadows, don't they?
We get these kinda
scans off someone,
we start prepping them
for the inevitable.
So I'm done.
Ninja or not,
there's not a man alive
that can outrun the grim reaper
when he finally
comes calling for you.
We talkin' six months?
Sorry. That would
be a miracle.
You've got money, right?
I'd stop being a ninja,
and do whatever
makes you happy with
the time you've got left.
And get your affairs in order.
[WOMAN] I'm thinking
of quitting my job.
[KAGI]
Oh, yeah?
[WOMAN] I've got money
saved, and I wanna live
somewhere where
there's more sunshine.
[KAGI] Sounds nice.
Not really what
the future's got
in store for me, though.
[WOMAN] Not while there are
little girls to save, right?
She's not some trophy from
a one-night stand, is she?
I mean, because you've
been acting a little weird.
Well, I am dying, babe.
Of course I'm weird.
[WOMAN] Come on, don't start
with all that again.
[KAGI] I guess if
I wanna see you again
I'll look someplace sunny.
[WOMAN]
You'll find me.
[KAGI]
Sure.
If I'm still alive.
So why in the hell am I
even doing this, again?
[YAMOTO]
Huh?
Ah. Don't worry about it.
Tell me somethin'.
That Nutcracker.
He said you killed
Sonic Boom. Is that true?
Yeah, course not.
That guy had
quite the reputation.
And you beat him with your
training-wheels jitsu?
You got no karate.
That's why those Soukaiya
clowns look down on ya,
besides your height.
The fact is, you'd be dead
if I didn't come back
to the laundromat that night.
That was
on the house, dig?
And don't go feeling
sorry for yourself.
Hey. No waterworks,
neither.
[YAMOTO gasps]
The karate
I use is iaido.
It's with a sword. But all
styles pretty much originate
from the same basic movements.
Let's start out
with tile-breaking.
From above, downward.
[KAGI]
Yup.
That's about it.
From above, downward.
Damn straight.
From above and then
move it downward.
You got it.
[BOTH]
From above, downward.
--[YAMOTO] From above,
--[KAGI] From above...
...downward.
[sirens wailing]
[SALARYMAN 01A mumbling]
[SALARYMAN 01A]
Abbah!
[SILVER KARASU]
Namu Amida Butsu.
[SMILING OLD MAN] All righty!
Now, if you will go to
the body and get
a few pictures for me,
I'd so appreciate it.
[SILVER KARASU]
You serious?
This place is about to be
crawling with cops.
[SMILING OLD MAN]
I need pictures.
[SILVER KARASU]
Send a commando--
[grunts]
Okay, fine.
But I would
appreciate a bonus.
Kagi-san!
Oh hey.
What're you doing up?
It's gotta be
way past your bedtime.
You don't look so good.
[KAGI] Thanks.
Hazard of the trade.
You got a smoke?
Naw, that's a dumb question.
Forget me,
worry about yourself.
[KAGI coughs, retches]
[groans]
What a mess.
But it's got nothin' to do with
what happened tonight.
So it's fine.
Everything's cool.
You expect me to believe
"everything's cool"?
I mean, the blood's not from
any combat-related injury.
In fact, these injuries
are nothin' next to
what is causing the blood,
so it equals out somehow.
You gotta go
to the hospital!
If I go there
I'm not comin' out!
[sobbing]
[KAGI]
Damnit. I didn't mean to
bite your head off.
I'm sorry.
That's not why
I'm crying, Kagi-san.
[continues sobbing]
[KAGI] I'm gettin'
in the shower.
And it is past your bedtime.
[KAGI] So this is how
the story ends for me, huh?
Hunched over a sink
full of blood
wondering about "my affairs."
--[KAGI] This pleases Buddha?
--[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[KAGI]
To hell with that.
Man.