[grunts]
[NANCY] I guess that's
all I can do for now.
[NANCY]
Huh?
Hold on. Who is that?
How'd they get past
the booby traps?
Domo, Y-C-N-A-N-san.
[NANCY grunts]
I'm afraid I
must inform you
that your little
scheme's been busted.
[NANCY]
A ninja? But how?
[BASILISK]
Domo.
My victims call me Basilisk.
Word on the street is
that you're Ninja Slayer's
Achilles' heel.
Let me. Let me go.
[BASILISK]
Why would I?
You still haven't
introduced yourself.
Don't you know how rude that is?
[chuckles] You're a
feisty one, aren't you?
I wonder what your
screams sound like.
I think I'd like to spend
all day finding out.
[NANCY grunting]
[gasps, grunts]
Make haste, Basilisk-san,
we are on a schedule.
[BASILISK]
Huh? Ugh.
You look like a gang
of walrus bikers
made love to
a slab of bacon.
I can see the humor,
but this is the best I could
do given the time constraint.
Guy had scabies,
rat bites, you name it.
But his fists work,
so hakuna matata!
[laughs]
[BASILISK] How do you think we
should begin the interrogation?
There's nothing else to be
learned from this woman.
[BASILISK]
So we kill her?
Not yet. She may
have other uses.
Just put her down, for now.
[BASILISK]
Fair enough.
Gaze into my eyes,
and despair!
[gasps]
[NANCY]
My body. What's happening?
[NANCY grunts]
We found Ninja Slayer's IRC.
Guessed his password
on the first try.
"Death is the only
way out for ninjas."
[NANCY gasps]
Suffice it to say,
we know about your plan.
No need to worry,
we're basically gonna keep it.
With several minor modifications
of our own, of course.
[NANCY]
What the hell is he getting at?
But the part of your little
plot we're definitely keeping,
is the bit where our bosses
say their sayonaras.
But I think we'll let your
friend say his as well.
[NANCY]
Does this mean that these guys
aren't with the Soukaiya?
Now, we're still
with the Soukaiya.
It's just due for a change.
Admittedly our bosses are
strong and clever leaders.
But mucking around a few
days ago, I had this idea.
My ninja soul is
very ambitious.
So I figured life would
much be more palatable
if I took control of
the whole syndicate.
Think you meant to say "we."
You and I will take control.
Well of course
that's what I meant.
The mortality rate for a Six
Gates Ninja is higher than ever.
Without them, this syndicate
lacks stability.
I need your help to control
my other underlings.
[BASILISK]
Our allies are here.
[laughs]
Get excited my lovely.
You're about to witness
the greatest coup de' tat
of the 21st century.
We're gonna kill your
little boyfriend.
Then kill the boss
and Darkninja-san.
We'll fill their
corpses with punch
and serve it at our
New World Order soirée!
[laughs]
[NANCY]
Ninja Slayer...san.
[knocking]
[DAIGO]
Lemme in, Maria!
--[door clatters]
--[AGATA] Aieee!
[DAIGO]
Hey, screw you!
--[AGATA] Aieee! Aieee...!
--[DAIGO] Hey, screw you...!
--[doorbell rings]
--[DAIGO] Huh?
Who the hell is it?
Uh. Sushi Deliveryman.
[DAIGO] Huh? Okay,
be right th--
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yah!
--[DAIGO grunts]
--[AGATA gasps]
[footsteps]
[AGATA] You're the man
from Room 808, aren't you?
Morita-san?
Domo.
Son of a--.
We're working on some
relationship issues here,
so mind your own business!
If I acted out of turn,
Agata-san. Tell me now.
No you haven't.
I'm very grateful.
Do you want him gone?
[gasps]
--[DAIGO] Maria! You stu--
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yah!
[DAIGO grunting]
There is one thin wall
between this room and mine.
I hear you come back,
you'll leave on a stretcher.
Please don't kill me!
--[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
--[DAIGO] Argh!
Are you coming back?
No! I promise! Just let
me live, I'll never--
--[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
--[DAIGO] Aieee!
Aieee! A-Aieee! Aieee!
I'll impress our pact upon
you with a little trauma!
[DAIGO]
Aieee!
[DAIGO grunting]
Aieee. A-Aieee...
I'll reimburse you
for the window.
[gasps]
Please wait!
I apologize for
the intrusion, ma'am.
Sayonara.
[gasps]
I know I sound pathetic, but...
Stay a while longer, please.
I'm still so afraid.
[NARRATOR] 1000 health
benefits of powdered tuna?
Or a coded message from Nancy?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Goaisatsusama Life Insurance.
5th floor, past the
centaurs. Eight A.M.
[NARRATOR] Tomorrow,
Ninja Slayer will finally enact
his long-laid plan to
assassinate Laomoto Khan,
kingpin of the Soukai Syndicate.
[chuckles]
Based on what you've told me,
I expect we'll have to rough
it for another quarter or so
before we can put an
end to Ninja Slayer-san.
[DARKNINJA]
Yes, sir.
Time is money, Darkninja-san,
so let's not let this
little coup d'etat
cost us more than it must.
[DARKNINJA]
Yes, sir. Hmm.
You seem rather
distractible today.
Is something vexing you?
[DARKNINJA]
Yes, sir.
The winds have shifted.
[LAOMOTO]
Such poetry! Mua-ha-ha-ha.
Still, if I trust anybody's
poetic sentiment, it's yours.
I will be cautious.
[NARRATOR] This
is the main office of
Goaisatsusama Life Insurance.
And this is its lobby!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer has
donned a clever disguise!
[TOPKNOT] Domo. We've been
told to expect you.
Right this way, please.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hiyup!
Fuyuko, Tochinoki.
Your vengeance is at hand.
[LAOMOTO laughing]
--[gasps]
--[laughing continues]
[NINJA SLAYER]
He's alone?
[laughing continues]
[NARRATOR] This Laomoto
was a robotic dummy
and a booby trap to boot!
He's rigged to explode!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
Domo. Ninja Slayer-san.
My name is Wired.
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
My name is Ten-Count.
[BEEHIVE] Domo,
Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Beehive.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo, I--
[BEEHIVE]
Psyche!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Argh!
[NARRATOR]
Beehive fired up the Gatling gun
on his back even as he bowed!
For such wanton incivility,
there are no words.
My ambush will crush you
like a can of spoilt tuna!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Huh?
[ALBATROSS]
Yeeart!
Domo Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Albatross.
[ALBATROSS, NINJA SLAYER yell]
[NARRATOR] A one-sided
greeting is also pretty rude!
[BEEHIVE]
I'm not out of bullets yet!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart! Yeeart!
[TEN COUNT]
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
[NINJA SLAYER] shouts]
[TEN COUNT yells]
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[ALBATROSS]
Yeeart! Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[BEEHIVE shouts]
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
What the--?
[WIRED] Metal is useless
against my Magne-jitsu!
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
[ALBATROSS, BEEHIVE laugh]
[WIRED, TEN COUNT laugh]
[TEN COUNT] HUH?
[ALBATROSS] HUH?
--[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
--[ALL] Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
He's getting away!
Hunt him down, men!
Let's get him!
[ALBATROSS yells]
[BEEHIVE]
We'll tear him apart!
[WIRED, TEN COUNT]
Yeah!
Where are you? Where'd you go?
Come on out! Let's do this!
[NINJA SLAYER] How did they
find out about my plan
to assassinate Laomoto?
Did Nancy-san betray me?
Out you rat! Come face me!
Come on out you coward!
No. She'd never give me up.
Never let me down. Or hurt me.
Show yourself!
You can't hide forever!
So it seems if
I'm to find out,
I must show these thugs
how a true ninja fights.
[BEEHIVE] Aieee!
It's Ninja Slayer-san!
Help! Gwah!
[ALBATROSS]
Wonder if things went as bad
for the four we sent
after Darkninja-san
as they did for us.
I couldn't see anything,
but I heard the screams.
Chances are I'm the last
ninja left, aside from--
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
[ALBATROSS shouts]
[ALBATROSS]
Domo. I am Albatross.
How did you find me?!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Situational awareness.
I can't beat him. He'll slay me.
But I'll be damned if I
can't get a shot off first!
[ALBATROSS yells]
[yells]
[ALBATROSS]
Aieee!
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[ALBATROSS screams, grunts]
[ALBATROSS whimpers]
Aieee...
I have some questions for you.
[ALBATROSS screams]