[distant owl hooting]
[NARRATOR] The skin of
Neo-Saitama is comprised
of grime ridden concrete.
Still, it does harbor
a few places of beauty,
such as this bamboo grove.
Ninja Slayer
swiftly circumvents
a scattered web of wire traps.
He knows this place.
Clappers,
a traditional booby trap
among the ninja.
Useful tools indeed.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[WOMAN]
Kieee!
[NARRATOR]
It's an ambush!
I nearly made you
flinch that time.
You should give me
bonus points. Hm.
No, Yukano.
We'll leave that to Sensei.
[FUJIKIDO] How is
the master's condition?
[YUKANO]
Worse every day.
[FUJIKIDO]
I see.
[NARRATOR] This proud
warrior was the master
of the Dragon Dojo.
Still he bears the name of
"Roshi Ninja." Dragon Gendoso.
[FUJIKIDO]
Sensei.
[GENDOSO]
That you, Fujikido?
[NARRATOR] Huge-Shuriken
poisoned the master
with the anti-ninja
virus, Takeuchi.
Since then, he has been
a shadow of his former self.
A shadow on the brink of death.
[FUJIKIDO]
Yukano.
Huh?
[FUJIKIDO]
For him.
This vial is from
Yoroshisan Pharmaceuticals.
I believe it's the cure
to this virus.
How'd you get it?
[NARRATOR] There was no way to
describe the trials he'd endured
in pursuit of that
holy grail of antidotes
without letting go
of his modesty.
So he kept his silence.
That was rash. You
shouldn't have done it.
It was a simple task.
All I needed was my iron will,
and the ninja soul within me.
That is precisely
why it was rash.
[FUJIKIDO] At times,
I find Naraku's thirst
for blood repugnant,
but I do owe him.
Without his soul, I'd just
be another casualty.
I no longer live
to seek revenge.
But to leave evil ninja alive
when I have the strength
to stop them would be
a crime worse than theirs.
They prey on the weak,
so I must slay them.
I mixed the
antidote into your tea.
Please drink it all.
I'm sure it'll help.
I thank you both.
This is a foolish thing
you've done for me.
Foolish and kind.
[rumbling]
[FUJIKIDO] Yukano!
Stay with Sensei! Yeart!
[NARRATOR] An explosion set
the bamboo grove ablaze.
Who did this? Why?
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[NINJA SLAYER]
How was I followed?
Huh?
[beeping]
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Domo. Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Darkninja.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. Darkninja-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
Uh-oh. Aaaargh!
My iaido is
beyond the reach
of your pathetic karate.
You've slayed
your last ninja, Slayer.
You've stepped on the tail of
the tiger that is Soukaiya.
And now you shall
meet your bloody end
between its jaws.
The boss is sick of
hearing about you.
So he sent me.
You call yourself
a true ninja.
Let me to show you
what that means.
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
[groans]
This lusty sword
is named Beppin.
Mark my words,
she shall drink her fill
of your blood before
this night is out.
You think you're
skilled because you've
slaughtered men even worse at
playing ninja than you are?
Filthy poser.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi! Yeeart!
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
Pathetic. Huh?
How did you--?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] If there are any
amongst our viewers who have
schooled themselves
in 19th century
North American Ninja History,
you will be all too familiar
with this brutal
karate technique,
called the "Alabama Drop."
This attack was developed
by the evil ninja assassins
of Santa Ana,
the Mexican Sun Tzu,
during the Texas War
of Independence.
The Abundantly Dark
Side of History says,
"They repeatedly
lift and slam their
victims' melons into the earth,
as if determined to plant their
bloodied skulls within it."
[NINJA SLAYER]
Aaaargh!
[NARRATOR]
The tables turn again!
Should any of our viewers
possess the hawk-like vision
of a ninja, they'll have seen
exactly what occurred.
But for the wretched
majority: a recap.
Darkninja found
the weakest point
in Ninja Slayer's hold,
bashed it,
took control of their fall
and flung Ninja Slayer
into a world of hurt!
Any physicists amongst
our viewers would say
these ninja moves
make Newton's
laws of motion seem
like far-out theories!
I've turned your ultimate
move against you, yield.
Death is the only
way out for ninjas.
Kirisute.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
Gomen!
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
Aaaargh!
[DARKNINJA] That one's
called my "Death Kiri."
[DARKNINJA] Now, allow me
to behead you.
[NARRATOR] No! Ninja Slayer lies
bleeding and defenseless.
Can such a man
find peace in death?
[GENDOSO]
Take my head instead,
if you have the skill.
[DARKNINJA]
Huh?
Domo.
Darkninja-san, is it?
I am known as Roshi Ninja.
Domo. Roshi Ninja-san.
I am Darkninja.
So you survived
the poison and the bomb.
What divine providence.
I'll claim two fine
trophies on this night.
Trophies are
useless to the dead.
Only Ninja Slayer
will survive this night.
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
No Sensei. Fight,
but fight to survive!
[DARKNINJA]
Yeeart!
--[GENDOSO] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Gwaaa!
[DARKNINJA]
Yeeart!
[GENDOSO] Yeeart! Can't a true
ninja best a sick old man?
[DARKNINJA] You dare
taunt me? Kirisute gomen!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Sensei!
[GENDOSO]
Yeeart! Aaah!
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
Your precious Sensei
is no more.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
[DARKNINJA]
You're finished.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Fuyuko, Tochinoki.
[TOCHINOKI sobbing]
It was you there.
At the Marunouchi
Sugoitakai building!
My wife, my child, you killed
them both you bastard!
[DARKNINJA] Ooh. Could've sworn
I killed everyone in there.
Were you gone, or merely hiding?
[NINJA SLAYER] I'll kill you.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
[NARAKU] That's right,
Fujikido. You're a killer!
Now then, turn your body
over to me and take a rest.
I will see to it that you
get your sweet revenge.
[GENDOSO] Nonsense!
Pay his words no heed.
[FUJIKIDO]
Sensei, you're here?
I always will be.
But not like this, so here is
your final assignment.
Never allow your ninja soul
to consume you again.
Harness its power,
but don't forget your body
is a ship and
you're the captain.
--[GENDOSO] Yeeart!
--[NARAKU] Aaaargh!
Sensei!
Draw from the power
of your ninja soul,
but never lose sight
of the man you truly are.
This is farewell, Fujikido.
Between saving your butt
and honing your skills,
I've wasted a lot of time.
Make it count.
Oh, and look after
Yukano for me.
[FUJIKIDO]
Sensei!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Impossible!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
Aaaargh!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer's stance
may seem reminiscent of jujutsu,
but it's part of a far more
ancient martial art.
Chado of the Assassin!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA] Aaaargh!
Aaaargh! Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
Yeeart! Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] I.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Am.
--[DARKNINJA] Beat-en!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Sensei.
[helocopter blades whirl]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[NARRATOR] Though Ninja Slayer
managed to harness
his ninja soul's full strength
without yielding to its will,
his thoughts are burning
like his master's corpse.
Could he have
saved Sensei?
Did Yukano find a way out?
Forget such things,
Ninja Slayer! Run!