I just can't catch a break.
[explosion]
[PURPLE HAT]
What the hell?
Damned rioters.
I've got somewhere to be!
What's up their butts?
Omura Industries is building
a new dam, and these people
are whining that it'll flood
their homes or something.
So these activists are blocking
the whole damn highway
as some sort of protest.
Why don't they just move?
This thing's a real CF.
But it's gonna be over soon.
You know something?
[RED SCARF] I heard Omura
is gonna send some kinda
crowd control weapon. So we'll
be sitting here a bit longer,
but at least we'll get one
hell of a fireworks show.
[PURPLE HAT] Yeah, I don't know
if I like the sound of that.
Omura doesn't play around,
that's for sure.
I know I wouldn't want
to get in their way.
[RED SCARF yells]
[PURPLE HAT yells]
[PURPLE HAT gasps]
[MOTORYAB] Please excuse
the inconvenience.
Landing site coordinates
have been revised.
Have a pleasant evening.
[whimpering]
[NARRATOR] A barricade set up
by the Tottoriville Resistance
movement has
inconvenienced commuters
and incurred the wrath
of Omura Industries.
It's turned into urban warfare!
[ALL yell]
[MOTORYAB] Domo.
It's nice to meet you.
I am Motoryab.
I've been sent here on
behalf of Omura Industries.
We politely request your
immediate surrender.
Okay, I surrender!
Please don't kill me!
[MOTORYAB]
Thank you sir.
Your surrender
has been accepted.
I hope you have a
pleasant evening.
[gasps, yells]
[MOTORYAB]
Now accepting surrenders.
[YAMAKITA]
Headquarters needs to know Omura
is sending in the big guns!
Go tell them and I'll
hold these things off!
[stomping]
[YAMAKITA yells]
[yelling, explosions]
[RESISTANCE B] The situation
is out of our control!
They sent in these huge
robots to take us out!
We're screwed!
Our weapons are no match
for their gatling cannons!
What are we gonna do?
Heartless bastards finally
sent in the Motoryabs.
What are you talking about?
Omura's new robo-ninjas.
They're killing machines.
What do you
suggest that we do?
[RAPTURE]
The technology is new,
and rumored to
be indestructible.
Tonight, we begin the
toughest fight of our lives.
[EXPLOSIVE laughs]
What do you say we get this
party started off with a bang?
[YAMAKITA yelling]
Yes. Fly... and then go boom!
[YAMAKITA yelps]
Here they are!
[ALL yell]
[ALL yelling]
[EXPLOSIVE laughs]
[EXPLOSIVE grunts]
No! Oh, Buddha!
They sent a ninja!
[RESISTANCE yelps]
Where did Rapture-san go?
[RESISTANCE LEADER yells]
[groans]
[NARRATOR] The robo-ninja
possesses the grace
and lightning fast reflexes
of an actual ninja!
[RESISTANCE LEADER yells]
[RAPTURE yells]
I didn't realize that
you were a true ninja.
That is correct.
Domo, Leader-san.
I am Rapture.
[gasps, yells]
[EXPLOSIVE] Seems we've
got a ninja on our hands!
[EXPLOSIVE laughs]
[EXPLOSIVE] Allow me
to introduce myself.
Domo. I am known as Explosive.
Well. Domo to you,
Explosive-san.
I am known as Rapture.
[shouts]
[yells]
My, that is a
sassy little jitsu,
how can I counter it?
[RAPTURE, RESISTANCE LEADER]
Argh!
That's a tough one, kid.
Ya blink your eyes, and ka-boom!
Your guts get blown to
bits all over the place.
Like a bunch of confetti
made outta meat.
A true ninja can take your life
before you realize
he's even there.
But seeing you
helpless like this
makes me wonder
if you even are one.
Big, bad Rapture-san.
--[AMNESIA yells]
--[EXPLOSIVE grunts]
[EXPLOSIVE]
Another ninja joins the party!
No. Just a stupid little girl.
To be a real ninja, you gotta
have a ninja soul inside you!
That's something ya
can't fake, sweetheart.
[yells]
[gasps]
Tag. You're it!
[EXPLOSIVE laughs]
[gasps]
[AMNESIA grunts, shouts]
And now to watch
the fireworks.
This is gonna be
one hell of a show!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yes!
Explosive entertainment
sounds like just the thing.
Someone's there!
[EXPLOSIVE]
Hm? Who?
[gasps, shouts]
Go on! Someone like you
deserves to go out with a bang!
No. It can't be.
You're Ninja Slayer-san!
Domo, Explosive-san,
I am Ninja Slayer.
Rapture-san. And, uh...
Domo, Yukano-san.
Yukano? I don't know that name.
[NARRATOR] And with this
tidbit of information we learn
that Dragon Yukano's ninja
nom-de-guerre, Amnesia,
is a very fitting one indeed.
She doesn't remember a thing!
I've heard you don't
remember a thing,
so I've come to find you,
and tell you who you truly are.
[yells]
[BOTH shout]
You've just met.
But you and Rapture-san are
gonna light up the sky together.
He's covered head to
toe with explosives!
Huh?
Go...
[RAPTURE]
This is it for me.
I wish I could've
done something useful.
At least my death
will be kind of cool.
Boom-boom.
Rapture-san, no!
Now!
[RAPTURE]
Sayonara!
[EXPLOSIVE laughs]
We finally get to see
some fireworks tonight!
Go on Yukano, and take
the leader with you.
The resistance needs him
to continue fighting.
[gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER] Death is the
only way out for ninjas!
Death is the only way out
for everybody isn't it?
But you'll be making your final
exit right here and right now!
Me and my robo-buddy are
gonna make sure of that.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[yells]
[MOTORYAB]
Surrender accepted. Thank you.
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[EXPLOSIVE]
Heh!
That's impossible!
No way! Why in the hell
aren't you blowing up?!
[NARRATOR] To find out the
answer, we'll have to switch to
slo-motion to see Ninja Slayer
deftly pulling out every single
fuse one after another,
and rendering the
explosive device unusable to
his rival ninja in less
than half a second!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[EXPLOSIVE yells]
No! This is
unbelievably embarrassing!
I didn't even get a real
chance to attack him yet!
[NINJA SLAYER] I told you death
was the only way out for Ninjas.
But seeing you now makes me
doubt if you truly are one.
Hey. You don't
have to rub it in!
[EXPLOSIVE] Those are mine!
What in the hell do
you think you're doing?
These will detonate whether
you press the button or not,
won't they?
Recite your death haiku,
if you have one.
[EXPLOSIVE] It's too ironic!
Blown up by my own fireworks!
Spare me and I'll talk!
I've heard enough yammering,
so sayonara.
[EXPLOSIVE]
I'm not ready to die!
[NINJA SLAYER]
That's too bad.
[EXPLOSIVE]
Sayonara!
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I owe you my life.
Yes, I know. You're welcome.
But, where is Yuk--
I mean Amnesia-san?
[MALE RESISTANCE LEADER] She
told me to give this to you.
[AMNESIA]
"Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
Earlier you called me Yukano,
but that name belongs to a girl
whose life I don't remember.
I have a new life now,
here with the Ikki Uchikowashi.
They treat me as one of
their own, like family.
In fact, Rapture-san
and I were planning
on becoming husband and wife.
We were deeply in love.
But after losing him tonight,
I must wait here for more
reinforcements to join us.
I must also take some
time to mourn his death.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but the person you came
looking for is gone forever.
So, I'm afraid I won't
be able to help you.
Although, both the
resistance and I
will be forever in your debt
for what you did tonight.
And for avenging...
[NINJA SLAYER] Give this to
Yuk-- I mean, Amnesia-san.
[RESISTANCE LEADER]
The sun is rising again.