[SHIGAKI]
Tamago.
[NARRATOR]
Meet Shigaki.
Once he was an ink-wash painter,
who lived for the creation
of beautiful art.
Until his arm was
hacked off by a tofu press.
When Shigaki received
his settlement money,
he decided to purchase
a cybernetic arm.
[SHIGAKI]
Tamago.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
he could only afford
an old battle gauntlet:
cracked and worn
from decades of use.
Shigaki's unlicensed
prosthetist quipped that
it would cost an arm
if not a leg
to keep the gauntlet
in working order.
The joke bombed.
Maguro. No--Tamago.
[SHIGAKI] I'm rotting away here.
Gotta find more work soon.
[KOKESHI 05A]
Word is they're givin' out
those horsepower drinks.
[KOKESHI 05B] What, for free?
They bringin' on anyone, or?
[SHIGAKI]
'Scuse me, fellas.
[KOKESHI 05A, 05B]
Huh?
[SHIGAKI] I'd like to get a
piece of that action, if I can.
What's a guy gotta do?
[NINJA SLAYER]
This ends now, Bandit-san.
You have nowhere to run.
How'd you get my name?
Wait, you must be...
Ninja Slayer-san!
[NINJA SLAYER] Domo. Indeed.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[BANDIT]
Domo, I am called Bandit.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[BANDIT] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER] Now then.
Tell me what you know.
[BANDIT]
Sayonara!
[NARRATOR]
He self-destructed!
The secrets of
the Soukai Syndicate have
shriveled away like the
skin on Bandit-san's corpse.
Or have they?
[KATAGI]
Laomoto-san!
You have my company's undying
gratitude and admiration.
[LAOMOTO]
Mwah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
But of course.
Yoroshisan Pharmaceuticals
has provided me with an
unspeakable amount of drugs.
Now, about this
tofu maker: Sakaiesan.
My sources tell me they refuse
to purchase our yakuza clones.
Is this true?
It is true! What's more,
they continuously
refuse to join our
Keiretsu conglomerate!
How are guys like us
supposed to conduct business
if we have to compete
in a free market?
[LAOMOTO]
One simply does not provide
fairly priced tofu
to the working class.
Not on our watch.
My men will attack
their factory tonight.
And your company
will provide them
with the required materials.
Is that correct?
[KATAGI]
Yes, absolutely sir!
Five hundred twelve packs of
special horsepower drinks,
and by "special" I mean
they're laced with enough
ZBR Adrenaline to
resurrect a dead elephant!
[LAOMOTO]
Five hundred?
[KATAGI] Aieee!
I'm extremely sorry, sir,
I meant a thousand
twelve packs!
Made a little typo
with my mouth.
[LAOMOTO]
Mwah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Excellent!
Eh? Why have you
returned, Darkninja?
Bandit-san has gone missing.
I don't care
if he self-immolated.
There can be
no delay in the plan.
If Bandit is gone, then
deliver the secret document
to Beholder yourself.
Sir.
[SHIGAKI] If folks are gatherin'
to take down a tofu plant
then the whole world's
gone to hell.
[KOKESHI 05A] They wanna
stick it to the man,
but I guess the vegetarians
are the next best thing.
[KOKESHI 05B] Strange.
Of all places, they chose
to attack the
Sakaiesan Tofu plant.
How many of these bums
are only able to eke out
a living because of the
hundred yen tofu quartets
that they're about to destroy?
[KOKESHI 05A]
Ah, I love these things!
Shigaki-san. Ya gonna
drink that or what?
Uuh.
Huh?
[WORKERS chattering]
Domo! Pleased to be here.
I am Beholder,
and this is my riot.
Lemme tell ya why you're here,
aside from the drinks.
The time has come
for us to take revenge
against that despicable
company Sakaiesan Tofu!
Thanks to their deplorable
"safety" standards,
I got shoved
into their generator.
Their carelessness left me
paralyzed for life.
They paid their lame
excuse for blood money
and then sent me packing!
Since that day I have
heard tale after tale.
Good men used up,
then thrown away!
[heartbeat]
[SHIGAKI]
What is this?
[NARRATOR] Oh, my Buddha!
Poor guy has no idea.
But the sensation he feels
coursing through his veins?
It's a reaction to
the ZBR Adrenaline
with which his drink is laced.
[BEHOLDER] Sakaiesan Tofu is
the darkest mega-corporation
known to man!
Their tofu may be cheap,
but it's filled to
the brim with carcinogens
and crap they've designed
to shrink our brains!
[NARRATOR] Beholder's
audience is in the throes
of an extraordinary
neurochemical reaction.
They're tweaking out hard, man.
[SHIGAKI grunts]
My ink-wash art
was worthless.
Utterly devoid
of individuality!
I must harden
my painter's heart
and strike down
this tofu company.
My inspiration will be their
shareholders' blood!
[alarm blaring]
[WORKERS shouting]
[SANADA] Ooh, haven't heard
the riot alarms in a while.
[HYOROKU] I know. Must be
that time of year again.
[SANADA]
Let's play a game!
We can shoot them all
and whoever gets
the highest body count wins!
You are so on!
[SANADA] Now this
is crowd control!
[WORKER 05A]
Abbah!
[SHIGAKI] A ninja?
No, it's Beholder-san.
But he scoots with
such incredible speed.
Did he fit his wheelchair
with a turbo-engine?
[beeping]
[BEHOLDER]
Rekufuyu no kia.
[beep]
[YAKUZA MEMBERS yell]
Hey, screw you!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Aieee!
[NARRATOR] Beholder is a master
of the kanashibari-jitsu:
a psychic art which
places the unfortunates
who meet his gaze
into a vegetative state.
[WORKERS yelling]
Has anyone seen
Beholder-san?!
We must protect him!
[SHIGAKI gasps]
--[SUPERIOR] Yeeart!
--[SHIGAKI] Yeeart!
[SUPERIOR]
Aaaargh!
[SHIGAKI panting]
[YAKUZA MEMBERS]
Die, you bastard!
[SHIGAKI] Yeeart! Yeeart!
[YAKUZA MEMBERS groan]
This is Marvelous! Hm-hm.
[SHIGAKI]
Now I see.
My talents were wasted
as an ink-wash painter.
I was destined for karate!
The security locks
have been released.
If I take the elevator,
I can find the men
inside that tower.
[BOTH]
Aieee.
[SHIGAKI]
Yeeart!
[BOTH yell]
[rumbling]
[panting]
[SHIGAKI] You the scumbags
in charge here?
[SANADA, HYOROKU]
Yeah. I guess so!
[SHIGAKI] Stay still,
and I'll let you fellas
leave with one good punch.
[SANADA, HYOROKU] Aieee!
Uh, that's a strangely
reasonable offer.
We'll take it!
[SHIGAKI]
Yeeart!
[SANADA, HYOROKU]
Aieee!
[SHIGAKI]
I kept my word, fellas.
But my gauntlet
is an old model.
The power controls are busted.
[SHIGAKI] We did
what we set out to do.
Now I can use this wad of bills
to buy myself a better arm.
And kiss this world
of violence goodbye.
[BEHOLDER] Marvelous!
And incredibly ruthless.
A man of your talent would fit
right in with the Soukaiya.
[SHIGAKI]
Beholder-san lied.
He isn't a former
factory worker
burning with rage against tofu.
[SHIGAKI] He's a
Soukai Yakuza? A yakuza!
Please spare me, sir!
I'm just a humble laborer
who aspires to be
an ink-wash painter!
[BEHOLDER]
Let me see your face.
[SHIGAKI]
Huh? Aieee!
On your feet! If you're
too scared to join us,
die like a man!
[SHIGAKI]
Aieee! Please spare me!
--[BEHOLDER laughing]
--[SHIGAKI screaming]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[BEHOLDER]
Who the hell are you?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
[BEHOLDER] Domo.
I am called Beholder.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[SHIGAKI] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
Let's see what's
under that mask.
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
[BEHOLDER] But why
should I do the work?
Be a good slave and take
that faceplate off yourself.
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[BEHOLDER] What the--?
--[NINJA SLAYER] Aaaargh!
--[SHIGAKI] Yeeart!
You broke my
kanashibari-jitsu?
I was planning
to take you alive,
but that was
clearly a mistake.
[NINJA SLAYER gasps, groans]
[NARAKU] That was
quite foolish, Fujikido.
[NINJA SLAYER]
What do you mean?
[NARAKU] His kanashibari-jiitsu
is very powerful.
Meet it with your naked eyes,
and it will kill you instantly.
Let me take over
and I'll paint the walls
with his blood!
[NINJA SLAYER]
No! Never!
[NARAKU] Have you forsaken
the path of revenge?
Go on! Crush him
like a can of spoilt tuna!
[SHIGAKI]
Aieee!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[SHIGAKI]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[SHIGAKI] Aieee!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Prepare yourself.
The Cobra Ninja Clan's
about to be short one member.
There is no place for you
in the world of true ninjas!
Nor is there mercy.
Yeeart!
[groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer didn't
turn his back to throw shade.
He's countered the
kanashibari-jitsu!
[NINJA SLAYER] Behold,
the way of the true ninja!
[BEHOLDER]
Aieee!
[quavers]
--[NINJA SLAYER yells]
--[BEHOLDER groans]
[NINJA SLAYER] Where are
the Soukai Six Gates?
Well no one's seen
Bandit-san for a while.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Because I killed him.
[BEHOLDER] Aieee!
Hugeshuriken-san
and Earthquake-san
were told to burn down
the Dragon Dojo, but they
can't until they find it!
Hellkite-san was flying
somewhere around here,
but we finished the mission,
so he's probably gone!
Buddha only knows what
Daedalus-san and his gang
are getting into
and there's no one else!
I swear!
[NINJA SLAYER] Now then.
There's a Soukai ninja
who killed a salary-man
named Fujikido Kenji,
and his wife and child
several months ago.
In the Marunouchi
Sugoitakai Building.
Tell me his name!
I don't know; we don't
count civilian kills,
but if this was in
the Marunouchi Feud
it was most likely Darkninja!
[groans]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SHIGAKI gasps]
[clanging]