[bell clinks]
[SHOP OWNER]
Welcome! Come on in.
[gasps]
It's good to see you, Naraki.
Aieee. Uh, domo, Maname-san.
Glorious. Sounds like you
truly believe in the cause.
Yeah, so I wanna be
as useful as I can,
but I'm kinda new to this.
Like I've never marched before.
Do you think I
should bring a jitte,
or a bo staff, just in case?
[giggles] You could,
but I don't suggest it.
We want peaceful reforms,
not revolution.
Plus, if we did take up arms,
we'd give the cops
an excuse to arrest us,
the news to condemn us.
And the people to do nothing.
[NEWSCASTER] Now for more on the
so-called "Occupy Sugoitakai"
protest in the
Marunouchi district.
Its leaders describe the
movement as a grassroots
effort to end a number
of "unfair subsidies
and tax breaks" for
the Sugoitakai group,
amongst other Kyre tsu
Conglomerate companies.
So uh, how long have
you been marching there?
Two weeks. Our marches in
Marunouchi are getting bigger
thanks to people like you.
So what changed?
I thought that you
weren't "into politics."
You know, I... just had
a change of heart.
With some help from you.
Oh, really? I'm flattered!
[gasps]
I wish I could stay, but I
have some things to do
before the march.
Oh, sure.
I'll see you there.
Sounds good. I'll look for you.
[chuckles]
Draw from the power
of your ninja soul,
but never lose sight of
the man you truly are.
Between saving your butt
and honing your skills,
I've wasted a lot of time.
Make it count.
Oh, and look after
Yukano for me.
Now I realize the true nature
of the Ikki Uchikowashi
is not what you and your
"comrades" claim it to be.
You dare go against the
will of the movement?
Then we'll have
to purge you first!
[GENDOSO echos] Oh, and look
after Yukano for me...
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yuk-- I mean Amnesia-san's
amnesia changes nothing.
This "Buster-san" is
taking advantage of her.
And I must honor
Sensei's final request.
First I shall find Yuk--
I mean, Amnesia-san,
and then I'll make her remember.
[NARRATOR]
A throng of protestors bound
for the Sugoitakai group's
Marunouchi headquarters.
They will march
through Neo-Saitama's
wealthiest district, chanting
to make their presence known
to the salarymen in
the skyscrapers above.
What a massive crowd.
How'll I find Maname-san?
You seem lost.
[NARAKI]
Aieee?
Domo. What's your name, bro?
You in school?
Domo. I'm Naraki.
University of Neo-Saitama.
[BUSTER TETSUO]
Whaddaya know?
That's my Alma Mater.
Good luck finding a
job when you're done.
So what brings you out here?
Doesn't seem to be your
passion for activism.
It's cause of a girl, right?
I don't not care about
this kinda stuff,
but yeah, there is a girl.
[laughs]
Oh, you dirty dog.
Gimme a break. I wasn't totally
devoted to the cause at first.
But marching it out
like this? I dunno.
It's like I'm part of
something real. I like it.
[BUSTER TETSUO]
Mm-hmm.
I'm dead serious! It's like...
[BUSTER TETSUO] Relax bro.
I'll take your word for it.
But ya gotta wonder.
Can we really change the
world by just marching?
Huh?
[gasps]
Ya ever watch one of those
really old zombie movies?
The ones with real zombies.
Back before they
started runnin' around
and pukin' everywhere.
Uh. Well yeah, of course.
[BUSTER TETSUO] Each individual
zombie is stupid, slow, weak.
So we're not that surprised at
how well the survivors get on,
once things've settled down.
They hole up in a shopping mall,
hoard supplies, and live
in sheltered luxury.
I'm not sure if I follow ya.
[BUSTER TETSUO]
Just feel out this metaphor.
So when they get the smallest
chance: a half-closed door,
a rotting wall, these weak,
starving, stupid creatures
break through every barricade
in a sea of tattered flesh.
And one by one,
the survivors go down.
Who are you? What are
you planning to do here?
What am I planning?
Funny you should ask.
[SHOPKEEPER A]
Go home, will ya?
[gasps]
Week after week,
you pull this crap.
You're killin' my business!
You wanna be bums, go for it!
But do it at home!
Screw you, old man!
Some people don't have homes!
Open your eyes,
we're marching for you!
Flint on the left and
steel on the right.
The spark of conflict
is ready to fly.
All it needs is friction.
[NARAKI] I'm gonna
get arrested, aren't I?
[BUSTER TETSUO]
Maybe.
[NARAKI]
But why?
That is the question.
[NARAKI]
Aw, crap
[gasps]
[NARAKI]
Maname-san!
[MARCHER C]
Hey, screw you man!
[NARAKI]
Look. I'm sorry about this.
But could you just...
deal with it!
I gotta get through!
[NARAKI grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[gurgles]
[MARCHERS gasp]
[MARCHER G]
They killed him!
The cops killed a student!
[gasps]
[NARAKI]
Maname-san? But why?
This is it.
Our half-closed door.
[NARAKI]
Were you planning to kill him?
Who are you?
[BUSTER TETSUO]
I am him.
I'm you as well.
Hell, I'm every hapless
zombie in this horde,
and we are all soldiers
of Ikki Uchikowashi.
Ikki... Uchikowashi?
[BUSTER TETSUO]
Yes.
What's your name, though?
[BUSTER TETSUO laughs]
It's Buster.
Catch ya later, if ya live.
[NARAKI gasps]
[NARRATOR] Naraki realizes
Buster Tetsuo's men
are scattered throughout the
ranks of the protestors,
attacking at random.
This is madness!
Arrest them all!
Please sir, I didn't
do anything!
Stop resisting!
[yells]
[grunts]
Was that Maname-san?
[shouting]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[NARRATOR]
From the heights of empyrean,
a hellish voice descends!
That's a ninja!
Why's a ninja here?
Your festival's
been canceled. Now go!
[MARCHERS murmuring]
Do I stutter?
Wha--? No sir!
Fall back! Withdraw!
--[JÖTUNN] Out of my way!
--[NARAKI] Argh!
[JÖTUNN]
Domo. Nice to meet you.
My name is Jötunn.
You're Ninja Slayer-san?
Domo, Jötunn-san,
the pleasure is mine.
Yes, I am Ninja Slayer.
Then it was you who cut
down Comrade Flickshot
before he could fulfill
his life's ambition.
I mourn my comrade as I
celebrate his martyrdom
in the name of
glorious revolution!
Only in death can
we find immortality!
Down with the bourgeoisie!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yah!
Yeeart!
Chop away, Ninja Slayer!
You have no chance against
my Furinkazan hazy jitsu!
Soon you'll be surrounded
by fog and I'll kill you!
Damn it! Where is she?
Death and ninjas. Endless fog.
Why is this happening?
[sobbing]
[gasps]
[NARAKI]
Maname-san!
Do you remember me?
I came here to see you.
Why'd you shoot that student?
You turned the protest
into a slaughter!
His sacrifice was needed
for the cause to advance.
That's insane. No!
You can't mean that.
You said this wasn't
about violence!
Reform, not revolution.
That's what you said you wanted.
Why? Why'd you convince
me to come here?
Was it--? No...
It was more than just me.
You tricked others.
Conned yourself an army.
Told them nothing.
Put our lives in danger!
Everything you say is true.
We made you soldiers in a war
you weren't prepared to fight.
[sobs]
[YUKANO]
But complacency's not an option.
You can be a lone fugitive,
or you can be my comrade.
You'll need to stop
calling me Maname.
My true name is Amnesia.
[gasps]
[sobs]
[yells]
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[grunts]
Let me go!
Yukano!
[YUKANO]
Don't call me that!
My name is Amnesia! The girl
you think I am is gone.
You have some nerve
showing your face
to an Ikki Uchikowashi soldier
after what you've done, traitor.
I should kill you now!
I am charged to look after
you by Dragon-Gendoso Sensei,
your grandfather!
Don't say that name!
It means nothing!
[NINJA SLAYER]
You manufacture violence,
lead innocent people
to their deaths,
and force the
survivors to join you.
Is that the life you want?
[YUKANO] Those people
should feel, honored!
Their corpses will build the
stairs to a truly equal world!
You really must have amnesia.
It seems you've forgotten
the smell of bullcrap!
How dare you say that?
Buster Tetsuo's the hero
inside every single soldier!
[NINJA SLAYER sighs]
Yukano, is this truly
who you want to be?
[YUKANO]
For the last time.
My name is Amnesia.
[JÖTUNN]
Release my comrade!
The lady isn't interested,
Ninja Slayer-san!
Your unsightly fixation
on her is begining--
Quiet, you!
[NINJA SLAYER shouts]
[JÖTUNN]
Gwar! Sayonara!
Damn you, Ninja Slayer-san!
Stop murdering my comrades!
Put that down. Your arrows
are useless against me.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Ikki Uchikowashi is my foe.
Now so are you, Amnesia-san.
Leave. And may we
never meet again.
[NARAKI grunts]
[YUKANO shouts]
[NARRATOR]
Ninja Slayer's thoughts reeled
as he scoured his
mind for a better way.
Could the right words
have convinced her?
Was he wrong to let her go?
His sensei had
given him one job,
and it seems he'd
failed spectacularly.
[SHOP OWNER]
Welcome. Come on in.
Ah! Hey, Senpai! I wanted
you to meet my friend.
[NARAKI]
I'm glad you came.
[KOHAI'S FRIEND] Okay, so do
ya think I should bring a jitte,
or a bo staff, just in case?
[KOHAI]
Don't be stupid.
Fair question, but the answer
is no. We don't do weapons.
Now lemme tell you why.
The problem with violent action,
is it doesn't really work.
Peaceful reforms are
the only kind that last.
That help people.
It's harder this way, but it'll
be well worth it in the end.
Yeah, I think you're right.
--Atta' boy.
--[watch beeps]
Sorry. Gotta run.
Thank you for showing
me the way, Amnesia.
[bell clinks]