[YAMOTO gasps]
[ASARI screams]
[PUNKS chuckle]
[YAMOTO]
She needs my help.
[YAMOTO] I have to
save her. But how?
[PUNK 03B chuckles]
[YAMOTO]
First I have to save myself.
If they kill me,
it's over for both of us.
But there's nothing I can do.
[SHI NINJA]
Have some faith, child.
You can save yourself
and your friend.
You can do anything you want.
[YAMOTO]
How?
[SHI NINJA] I, Shi-Ninja,
will lend you my power.
It's yours for
the taking. Use it!
[YAMOTO]
This is my power now.
[SHI NINJA]
Yes! Use it to the fullest.
Just turn off your mind
and let it happen.
Bid them all sayonara!
[YAMOTO]
Now, we are one!
[SHI NINJA]
Yes! We are one!
[YAMOTO]
Sayonara! Yeeart!
[PUNK 03B]
Abbah!
--[YAMOTO] Yeeart!
--[PUNK 03B] Abbah!
[thud]
[YAMOTO]
What's happening to me?
[ALL quaver, gasp]
[YAMOTO gasps]
Who have I become?
Where are these feelings
of rage coming from?
What matters now,
is that they are mine.
I feel this rage.
You saved my life.
[sobbing]
They were gonna kill us!
[continues sobbing]
[YAMOTO] But they didn't.
It's gonna be okay.
Let's go home.
[car horns honking]
[ASARI] Hey, Yamoto-san.
It's so good to see you.
Today's my first day back.
Domo, Asari-san.
It's mine too.
That guy sitting
in the back over there.
Do you know who he is?
I've no idea. But he
looks like trouble to me.
I think he's new here.
Probably a transfer student
or something.
[birds chirp]
[distant banging, clacking]
[GANG MEMBER 03A]
Screw you, man!
[GANG MEMBER 03B]
You think you tough?
[YAMOTO]
Hm? Huh?
[GANG MEMBERS laughing]
Hey look! That's the
guy from this morning!
You're dead, bitch!
Let's get this thing
started already.
I don't wanna miss lunch.
You're gonna be
eatin' though a straw!
[NARRATOR] Oh my Buddha,
what a surprise!
Instead of getting his head
squashed like a tomato,
he actually grabs the bat!
Big mistake.
'Cause now, you're dead.
No way.
What's wrong?
[NARRATOR] Yamoto is filled with
a growing sense of dread.
She knows this boy
with the afro is like her.
A chosen one.
There is no doubt in her mind.
And there shouldn't be.
What she senses is the ninja
soul dwelling within him.
[GANG BOSS] Oh, you screwed up
now! We're gonna kill ya!
[gasps]
[GANG BOSS, MEMBERS]
Abbah!
Heh.
[distant sirens wail]
Back off, man.
Don't you know
I'm the victim here?
I just got in and you're
already lettin' me out?
Mm?
Well, Domo, Shogo-san.
I am Fumatoni.
It's a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
What do you want from me?
I came here to release you
from your iron cage.
Don't you want to fly again?
I will post your bond,
and even claim responsibility
for the incident
that got you here.
[SHOGO] I think I'm gonna
take the rap for that one.
[FUMATONI] Now slow down.
This is a delicate matter.
You should be extremely careful
about what you say here.
I ain't sayin nothin'.
[GUARD 03A]
Abba-ba-ba-ba-bah!
Ugh. You're like
a rabid animal.
--[FUMATONI] Yeeart!
--[SHOGO] Aaaargh!
Do you honestly believe
your paltry ninja soul
gives you license to do
whatever the hell you want?
Arrogance beget by ignorance.
You don't know enough
to fully grasp
how insignificant you are.
Allow me to
introduce myself again.
Domo, Shogo-san.
I am called Sonic Boom.
A ninja of the
elite Soukai Six Gates.
Ninja are ya?
It would seem you find
yourself at a crossroads.
Join our syndicate and live,
or refuse and die.
What is your decision?
[PUNK NINJA]
Domo, Shogo-san.
You know death
will be the end, right?
[SHOGO]
Who are you?
[PUNK NINJA]
Right, I'm Punk Ninja.
Grew up in London,
but I went tits up
and shuffled off
the coil in 1979.
[PUNK NINJA] My death
was complete bollocks.
Ol' grimmy's a real arsehole.
So don't be a wanker,
and get back on your feet.
[SHOGO] You don't get it!
I wanna die!
[PUNK NINJA] Sorry, mate.
Not really up to you, is it?
Besides, as of now,
you're a ninja.
[SHOGO]
Please stop!
[SHOGO gasps,
quavered breathing]
[distant sirens wail]
[JOCKS gasp]
Do we need to continue
this conversation?
Or are we done?
[JOCK 03A] No we're done!
And we're very sorry!
But please, don't tell
anybody about this!
[YAMOTO] I won't,
but only if you promise
to never try it again.
[JOCKS]
Yes! We promise!
[YAMOTO]
That boy is just like me.
[YAMOTO] We're exactly
the same. Our fates.
[ASARI] Yamoto-san!
Are you okay?
The girls said they saw
some jocks bothering you.
And I was so afraid that--
There's nothing to
worry about. Everything's fine.
[ASARI sighs]
[YAMOTO] You should be
more worried for them.
--[ASARI sobbing]
--[YAMOTO] Don't cry.
[YAMOTO] Why were they talking
about me in the first place?
Well, uh. The word got out
that you were
in the origami club.
At your old school, I mean.
Yeah, I was.
I also heard that
you placed in the
All Inter-High
School Tournament.
So is it true?
Uh, yeah.
It's true. First place!
That's awesome!
[YAMOTO] Now, just blow some
air into this notch here,
and it's done.
[YAMOTO exhales]
[ALL]
Whoa! So cool!
[giggles]
[SHOGO] Screw this.
I could take down
this whole damn syndicate
if I wanted to.
That sounds like fun.
Domo, Shogo-san.
It would appear you've
passed your final exam, eh?
Of course,
if you had failed,
I would make sure
your death came swiftly.
Tch! Thanks, dick!
Maybe I should
go ahead and kill you too.
Ha! You're quite
welcome to try.
From now on, this is
what you'll be known as.
It's my gift to you,
as the godfather.
Don't say I never
gave you anything.
But now your life
is not yours to take.
It belongs to the syndicate.
You can only take lives
for the Soukaiya.
[SUICIDE]
I get it. And I'm not
the man I used to be.
I'll be the
goddamn grim reaper,
but with a badass afro.
What a bold statement!
So then. Here's your
first mission.
Your target is this ninja.
She's a ninja? That chick?
I assure you
the syndicate investigated
the details of your pathetic
suicide attempt thoroughly.
Ninja soul possessions
require very extensive
research on our part.
When you gracelessly
fell from the sky,
you landed on this girl.
She was critically injured, but
was revived by a ninja soul.
What amazing providence!
You both escape death,
become possessed,
and transfer to
the same high school.
That kind of fate
cannot be ignored!
[SUICIDE grunts]