[NARRATOR] Kagi Tanaka and
Yamoto Koki met by chance.
The man, AKA ninja
Silver Karasu,
is getting out of
the killing business
to spend his final days teaching
karate to the young ninja.
However, what fate
has bought together,
the Soukaiya threatens
to tear apart.
Silver Karasu has just received
orders to assassinate his pupil.
Let's be clear.
This isn't about you.
I'm selfish. So I'm
teaching you because
that's what I wanna do, got it?
[YAMOTO]
Mm-hmm.
[KAGI]
I don't have a lot of time,
so this is gonna be kinda
"crash course" style.
You'll have to learn
more on your own.
[YAMOTO] Mm-hmm.
[KAGI] Iaido is ultimate
control of the katana.
Focus all your energy,
all your karate into your blade.
It can't be separate from you.
To "be the blade,"
is the true goal of Iaido.
[YAMOTO]
Mm-hmm.
[KAGI] If the So-kaiya
is on your tail,
they've already got their
next goon on the hunt.
They'll find you. And it's
gonna be sooner than later.
Trust me on this one.
They will not be alone.
So I wanna skip ahead
to the final skill.
It's more of a Zen method.
I've only used it
a few times myself.
You're gonna be
fighting your battles alone,
so pay attention and remember
everything about this technique.
How it feels.
C'mon, enough cryin' okay?
[MALE TV VOICE A] You're on top
of the world and then boom!
--Life hands ya a turd sandwich!
--[MALE TV VOICE 14B] Ew, gross!
[AUDIENCE, YAMOTO laugh]
So. Ya thought about
your next move?
Running off to
Kyoto or someplace
with more sunshine
might be good for ya.
And if you leave Neo-Saitama,
the Soukaiya might
just forget about ya.
I don't have
anywhere else to go.
[KAGI]
I bet if you looked, you--
[KAGI coughs]
Kagi-san!
[KAGI]
Ah.
Buddha. Damn it.
[phone rings]
[whimpers]
[KAGI] You should
probably bail, ya hear?
You can find a place?
[YAMOTO]
Mm-hmm.
[KAGI]
Take care.
[YAMOTO]
Thank you.
[KAGI]
I'm counting on you.
[KAGI] Well, better get
ready for company.
[NARRATOR]
The Soukaiya Ninja, Third Eye,
is a skilled tracker who can
see the traces of ninja souls.
Whereas the bounty
hunter Sword Dancer
is a ninja proficient in
a deadly two-sword style.
From this point
it seems as though
the target ninja soul's
tracks split into two.
[Can you tell which
set of tracks is newer?
Sorry. But that's impossible,
even for me.
[NARRATOR] Nuh-uh. He's lying
through his fearsome ninja mask.
[THIRD EYE] So that means
you and I need to split up.
I'll look around
in this direction,
and you go and look in that one.
[SWORD DANCER]
All right then.
Do you know where we're supposed
to meet up with Silver Karasu?
[THIRD EYE] He never responded
to the message, so no.
I bet he's planning on taking
the prize all for himself1
What a complete moron!
I mean, we're just
looking for a little girl.
Honestly, I'd be more than
happy to cut him out of it.
Now let's go!
[SWORD DANCER]
Hmph.
[THIRD EYE]
All right, you dog.
You can go chasing your
tail all over town.
The ninja soul left
the run-down dojo
and continued on this street.
Then it looks like she
and her partner
went to their secret hideout.
Whoever that is, is there now.
It's probably Ninja Slayer,
the maniac that
killed the six gates.
Definitely do not want
to run into that guy!
I'll let Sword Dancer find out
what's behind door number one.
The little ninja
bitch is all mine!
[YAMOTO]
Domo.
I am Yamoto Koki.
Domo, Yamoto Koki-san.
I am Third Eye.
[SWORD DANCER]
Shh...
Argh!
[SWORD DANCER]
The hell?
[SILVER KARASU yells]
Domo, Sword Dancer-san.
[SWORD DANCER]
Domo, Silver Karasu-san.
Have you gone insane?!
[SILVER KARASU]
Batshit.
You don't have a
smoke on ya, do ya?
A "Somewhat Bright Sea" brand?
It's a long shot.
Cause ya don't
seem like the type.
I'll still check
your corpse, though.
Sword Dancer calling
Third Eye-san!
We've been set up!
IRC won't work. Sorry pal.
I mixed in some chaff
with the dynamite earlier.
[SWORD DANCER] Why are you
doing this, Silver Karasu?
I found out I'm dying.
So I went a little crazy.
[SWORD DANCER]
Oh, you're gonna die, freak.
Right now!
[BOTH yell]
[SWORD DANCER yells]
[grunts]
[SWORD DANCER yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Oh my buddha!
That has got to be the wildest
two-sword style
karate I've ever seen!
Silver Karasu's Katana
is called 'Ubaste'
referring to the
practice of leaving
a poor old person
somewhere to die.
Sword Dancer isn't
that old, but he'll do!
[BOTH yell]
Sword Dancer-san.
Let me hear your death haiku.
No. I won't. I... Hate poetry.
I was positive. My two-sword
style would beat you.
Let's rematch in hell1
[SWORD DANCER]
Sayonara!
Namu Amida--
[SILVER KARASU coughs]
[grunts]
[THIRD EYE grunts]
[THIRD EYE]
Didn't expect that?
You still have to obey
the laws of physics.
My ninja soul is
perfectly matched
with industrial technology.
It's made my karate
infinitely more awesome!
[THIRD EYE]
You look so smug.
But not for long.
I'll rearrange your face!
[YAMOTO]
Bring it on!
[THIRD EYE]
I'll break your weak jitsu!
[KAGI] Watch the
angle of their katana,
their eye line, and the
direction of their feet.
Nature does not lie.
[BOTH yell]
[KAGI] The strike of
iai is always clean.
But you can't sit back
and wait for it to happen.
You have to make it happen.
[BOTH yell]
[NARRATOR] Yamoto's world
has dramatically changed.
Thanks to the crystal
clear instruction
she received from her
new sensei, Kagi-san,
She deeply understands
the way of karate.
She is now, a badass fighter.
[KAGI]
Mastery is not the end-game.
It is a gateway
to more learning.
To understanding the
spiritual side, the 'do.'
But if ya get too cocky,
that'll be the end of ya.
[THIRD EYE yells]
[YAMOTO]
This is it! I've found my iai!
And this is when I use it!
[YAMOTO yells]
[THIRD EYE screams]
[stutters]
The kid beat me?
No! Silver Karasu!
Where are you?
[yelps]
[gasps]
[THIRD EYE]
Sayonara!
[SILVER KARASU] Shouldn't
rush a sick man, ya know?
Domo. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yamoto Koki.
Domo, Yamoto Koki-san.
I'm Silver Karasu.
[sighs]
Show me what you know.
I'd love to see it.
[SILVER KARASU] Not that I
really deserve to, mind you.
I mean, I've pretty much
just used my ninja skills
to kill poor dumb bastards
for a little coin.
I have no real honor or worth.
[SILVER KARASU]
Come on.
You know that was pointless.
Yeah, that's more like it.
Show me what you can
do with that blade.
[YAMOTO yells]
[YAMOTO gasps, yells]
[grunts]
--[SILVER KARASU yells]
--[YAMOTO grunts]
[yells]
[sobs]
[SILVER KARASU]
Buddha.
I've never fought someone
who cried so much.
[yells]
[YAMOTO yelling, sobbing]
You're gonna break it.
[yells]
[SILVER KARASU]
Please.
Would ya just...
...stop the waterworks and
close the deal already?
This is my moment here.
[SILVER KARASU]
My last fight.
[YAMOTO sobs]
I'm trying to teach
ya something here,
but it doesn't work
if ya know it's me.
Ya gotta learn how to kill.
But I could never kill you!
I'm not an idiot Kagi-san.
I knew it was you
from the start!
I can't do it!
[SILVER KARASU]
Are you sure?
[YAMOTO sobs]
Yes.
[SILVER KARASU]
Okay.
I should've known this
wouldn't tie up so neatly.
You're still a kid after all.
[SILVER KARASU] I can't even
bum my last smoke from you.
[SILVER KARASU] Like they
say... karma's a bitch.
Ha. Ha. I guess that's
my only true regret.
[SILVER KARASU]
Now all that's left...
...is to slip into the long
sleep, and go to hell in peace.
[ELECTRONIC GEISHA VOICE]
Attention. Attention.
Please be aware that the
train is coming through.
We must make abundantly
clear that being hit by it
will be extremely inconvenient,
to say the least.
[train honks]