[NARRATOR]
Making his way towards the keep
in which Laomoto
has ensconced himself,
Ninja Slayer battles
through the Six Gates,
with plenty of
backup from Nancy.
[NANCY] The first ninja
was Devilfish-san.
The multiple mechanical
arms were a problem,
but once his head was
gone, it was game over.
Ninja Slayer fought
long and hard.
The next ninja
was Razoredge-san.
He had ceramic katanas
attached all over his body.
I mean, everywhere.
But even the katanas hidden
in his ears couldn't help him.
Once he was nailed to
the wall, it was game over.
Ninja Slayer fought
long and hard.
The next ninja
was Waterboard-san,
master of scuba jitsu.
He filled the room with water,
and attacked him with his
underwater combat skills.
But, once his air
supply was cut off,
it was game over.
Ninja Slayer fought
long and hard.
I was able to drain the
room and help him escape.
But then his head was filled
with some kind of noise.
Even still, he moved
on to the fourth room.
The next ninja
was Armadillo-san.
He was covered in armor
stronger than steel,
but once his spine was snapped,
it was game over.
Ninja Slayer fought
long and hard.
The noise inside his head
came back even stronger.
It was the voices of all
the ninjas he'd slain.
All those tormented souls,
screaming in anguish.
And what's worse, the
voices of his family.
But Ninja Slayer stood firm.
He forced his way
through the exit
and headed towards
the fifth room.
[HELLKITE]
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san!
I'm the one called Hellkite!
Domo, Hellkite-san.
I'm the one called Ninja Slayer.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
It's game over,
Ninja Slayer-san!
This room was
custom built for me
to perform my
hellish kite-jitsu.
[NARRATOR]
The giant fans everywhere
were operated by Hellkite-san's
remote IRC! Oh my Buddha!
[HELLKITE yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
You will never
escape this place!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER screams]
[HELLKITE yells]
Hurts doesn't it?
That is what the power of a
true Six Gates Ninja feels like!
I told you this was game
over, Ninja Slayer-san!
[HELLKITE yells]
Aw, no way!
[HELLKITE] You got me that time,
but that's all you're gonna get!
From now on, I'm going to have
to keep hitting you
from a safe distance!
[HELLKITE yells]
[HELLKITE]
What's wrong, Ninja Slayer-san?
Are you sad because your
sensei isn't here to help you?
Better watch your step!
[NINJA SLAYER screams]
[HELLKITE] Allow me to
behead you, Ninja Slayer-san!
What in the hell?
[HELLKITE]
Hey! I didn't turn on that fan!
[yelling]
[growling]
[HELLKITE]
I almost have you!
All hail Laomoto-san, banzai!
[NINJA SLAYER]
You can not win, Hellkite-san!
Recite your death haiku!
I told you! As long
as I'm in this room--
What?
[NARRATOR]
Nancy-san hacked into
Tokorozawa Pillar's
computer space.
She owns this room!
[HELLKITE]
She hacked in?
[HELLKITE groaning]
I've gotta hurry up and
report this to Laomoto-san.
He's almost to the top floor.
[GATEKEEPER]
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am the one they
call Gatekeeper.
Domo, Gatekeeper-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
You may guard the sixth gate,
but death is the only
way out for ninjas.
[GATEKEEPER]
It's a shame.
I never dreamed I would have to
dirty my hands with this mess.
[GATEKEEPER] You have struck
down gate after gate.
Each one has been
a blow to my heart.
Don't worry, I'm sure
you'll be seeing them again
when all of you
regroup down in hell.
[GATEKEEPER] The grief
I feel is truly profound.
And the fact that it's
been caused by some fool
on a pointless
quest for vengeance
makes matters far worse.
It pains me to think
that I'm involved--
[NINJA SLAYER] It seems to
me you're suffering from
emotional diarrhea of
the mouth, Gatekeeper-san.
[GATEKEEPER] I thought
I'd gotten past having
to participate in this
kind of mindless violence
for the most part.
Do you even realize
what you're saying?
You've aligned yourself
with cold-blooded murderers.
They've murdered my wife,
my child, and my sensei,
so please spare me all your
ridiculous crocodile tears.
Enemy ninja, death
is the only way out!
[GATEKEEPER]
The ravings of a lunatic.
I believe Miyamoto Musashi said,
"Dead men tell no tales."
But if you insist,
I suppose I must engage.
[yells]
[GATEKEEPER]
Come on!
Show me what you can
do with your Karate!
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[GATEKEEPER] Although you've
sustained a great deal of damage
to your body, your skills
are still respectable.
But how long can you keep it up?
[GATEKEEPER] It seems
you're becoming desperate.
Is it because I'm
still unharmed?
[BOTH yelling]
[GATEKEEPER] Your suriken
will not penetrate my Tonfa!
[NARRATOR]
Look at that timing!
The aptly named Gatekeeper
is a true master
of the spin and
thrust Tonfa method!
[yells]
[GATEKEEPER]
There's no use!
[NINJA SLAYER]
There is use!
[GATEKEEPER sreaming]
[GATEKEEPER]
I underestimated your karate.
I thought it would be good,
but not this good.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Hm.
[GATEKEEPER]
I know what you're thinking.
You intend to finish me
with your next strike.
That's not a bad idea.
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
Ninja Slayer falls
headlong into the abyss!
[yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Recite your death haiku.
Before it's too late.
[GATEKEEPER]
Abbah. You're quite skilled.
But you don't have a chance
of defeating Laomoto-san.
You'll die on your knees
begging for your life. Like a--
That's not a haiku.
[GATEKEEPER]
Oh, Laomoto-san.
You will reap what you
have sown, a bloody harvest
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[GATEKEEPER]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
This rubbish again?
Bring it on. I will not
yield to this trickery.
[MORBID]
It's not trickery.
This is what you've sown.
The deaths you've caused.
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
You did this to me.
It's your fault, daddy.
You killed me. Now you
should perform seppuku.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Stay calm.
None of this is real.
They're just toying with me.
[MORBID] Behold your works,
Ninja Slayer-san.
You're a true artist of death.
[GENDOSO]
Your vengeance is meaningless.
No matter what you do, you'll
never bring back the dead.
You're just a murderer!
I'm dead because of you.
Now I'm never gonna grow up.
[MORBID]
So, tell me.
Who am I?
I doubt you can answer that.
After all, you and I
have never met until now.
I went against the boss
and paid dearly for it.
He doesn't take assassination
attempts lightly.
I brought it upon myself.
But who am I?
[MORBID laughing]
[NINJA SLAYER]
I can't stray from my plan.
Furinkazan, chado,
and then, Furinkazan.
I never imagined you'd
fail me so completely.
Silence! You're not real!
I'm doing everything exactly
as my real sensei instructed.
You have no power here!
[screaming]
[FUYUKO]
It's all your fault, dear.
[TOCHINOKI]
Daddy.
[FUYUKO]
Sweetie.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Fuyuko. Tochinoki.
[MORBID screaming]
[ding]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
You have arrived.