[YAMOTO] I'm so tired. But I
know they'll be coming after me.
Can't sleep. Have to
be ready for them.
I have to stay awake.
Have to stay--
[door clatters, slams]
[grunts]
[footsteps]
[YAMOTO]
Huh?
[gasps]
[YAMATO shouts]
[GENOCIDE]
Ah, you're a ninja. Interesting.
Domo. I am Yamoto Koki.
[GENOCIDE]
Domo. I am Genocide.
Start talkin', small fry.
What are you doing here?
Did the Soukaiya send you?
Give me a little credit, kid.
I'm not some kind of monster.
Did 'ya come here to fight me?
Your karate against mine?
Winner buries the loser?
Sounds like fun.
Wait...
Shi? Shi Ninja?
[YAMOTO]
Huh?
Forget about it.
[GENOCIDE] My brains are
like pudding these days.
I don't know what
I'm talkin' about.
[gasps]
So, uh. What are you doing?
[GENOCIDE]
Burying her.
Don't want her to get
all rotten, and nasty like me.
Nobody wants that.
Who is she?
When she was alive, she was
the lady that lived here.
Kicked her oxygen habit, though.
Old age'll do that.
Found her in there.
All by her lonesome.
And it's too late for company,
so here we are.
[sighs]
Why can't I catch
that dead, green oaf?
Genocide was my creation!
A fearsome,
mindless zombie ninja!
But he just had to become
self-aware and go on a rampage.
Destroying my lab and running
away like a rabid dog!
I must capture him soon,
no matter what the cost may be!
All this worry and stress
is keeping me awake
at night and if it stays like
this for very much longer,
I'm afraid it's going to
drive me completely insane!
Oh no, doctor,
we can't risk anything
bad happening to your big,
throbbing, brain!
However, there is one bright
spot in all of this, Fubuki-kun!
He is a truly amazing ninja!
My creation, my Genocide,
cannot be stopped!
I'm so unbelievably
proud of him!
I made him! He's my son!
My baby boy!
Be careful doctor!
You need to get those
emotions under control!
That's why I created
a sweet little ninja
of my very own to capture him!
Huh?
[beeping]
[LEE] Hmm? You did
this all without me?
Manticore, eh?
Okay! I'll take it!
I have also pinpointed the
exact location where Genocide
has been hiding recently.
That's amazing! You clever fox!
[FUBUKI giggles]
Ah, just a moment.
It seems a Soukaiya ninja
has also been deployed
to the same area.
[shower hisses]
[gasps]
[alarm buzzes]
Hey, your name.
It's uh, Yamoto, right?
So what's your story?
Just the Soukaiya is looking
to kill ya, and that's it?
[YAMOTO]
Mm-hmm.
I've got enemies, too.
Imagine they'll find
me sooner or later.
[sighs]
You want a slug, kid?
[YAMOTO]
Mm-mm.
I'll share it with you.
[GENOCIDE]
Naw, I'm good.
[YAMOTO]
So. Were you a priest?
I mean, when you...
[GENOCIDE] Ha! Do I look
like a priest to you?
Oh, the outfit. Came with
the place. Seems to fit okay.
Don't really remember
what I was before.
Told ya my brain's a pile
of mush. I forget stuff.
[YAMOTO] I wonder what happened
to the priest. Did he leave?
[GENOCIDE]
No idea.
[gasps]
[GENOCIDE]
You look like you need a nap.
When's the last time ya slept?
[YAMOTO]
I'll be fine.
Get some sleep.
I don't need it, myself.
I'll keep watch, okay?
--[YAMOTO] Mm-hmm.
--[rustling]
[GENOCIDE]
Hm?
Hey, there's a bed
in the room upstairs.
Probably be more comfortable.
[YAMOTO]
Mm-hmm.
[alarm buzzes]
[gasps]
[GENOCIDE] Get up!
We've got company!
Go to the tower and
see what's going on!
They're coming.
Lots of them!
[GENOCIDE]
Exterminate! Exterminate!
Exterminate! Exterm... Exter..
Exterminate... Eterminate...
--[YAMOTO shouts]
--[GENOCIDE] Die you bastards.
[CLONES scream]
[NARRATOR]
Gouranga!
Like a swarm of
abandoned space probes,
plunging into an asteroid belt,
the hapless Yakuza clones can
do nothing but move forward!
Headlong into extermination!
[CLONES scream]
[gasps]
[CLONE A]
Die, you bastard!
[CLONE B]
Hey, screw you!
[GRENADIER] Domo.
Pleasure to meet you.
I am Grenadier.
[GENOCIDE] Domo,
Grenadier-san.
I am called Genocide.
[GRENADIER]
Shoot 'em all to hell!
--[GRENADIER shouts]
--[GENOCIDE yells]
You're outnumbered
and over-powered!
[GRENADIER laughs]
[GRENADIER]
Give up and go to hell already!
[YAMOTO shouts]
[CLONES scream]
Hey! What are you
doin' half-pint?
[YAMOTO] Another ninja!
He's here! And he's big!
[MANTICORE]Ga-ta-ta-
ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
[MANTICORE yells]
Domo. Me go by Manticore.
[GRENADIER] Say what? Manticore?
Just what in the hell are you?
[MANTICORE yells]
[GRENADIER yelps]
[CLONES scream]
[YAMOTO shouts]
[GENOCIDE]
Exterminate!
[GRENADIER yelps]
[CLONES scream]
[yells]
[GRENADIER, CLONES scream]
What the hell?
[YAMOTO]
Domo, Grenadier-san.
I'm Yamoto Koki.
[GRENADIER] Domo.
Yamoto Koki-san.
I am Grenadier.
Your little adventure's over.
The Soukaiya Clan
will always find you
when you least expect it.
What the--?
--[GRENADIER screams]
--[GENOCIDE] Exterminate!
[GRENADIER]
A-Abbah! Sayonara!
[MANTICORE, GENOCIDE yell]
I'm gonna take a stab
and say you're Dr. Lee's
new pet, aren't ya?
Me come here to kill you.
Then take body.
Then go back home!
Ha. Well good luck killing me.
[shouts]
[yells]
Now me gonna kill
little girl, too!
[gasps]
[YAMOTO]
Genocide-san!
[GENOCIDE]
No problem, I'm a Zombie.
But can you hack it?
Yes I can. Let's go!
Alright then. Come on!
[YAMOTO shouts]
[MANTICORE]
Huh?
[YAMOTO yells]
[MANTICORE]
Gwah!
Ga-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta! Huh?!
[GENOCIDE yells]
You zombie! You weak!
Me test muscle power. No way
me can lose to weak zombie!
Me kill you, take body,
then go back home!
Never gonna happen.
[chains clinking]
Huh?
[MANTICORE]
What this?
Gwaagh!
[GENOCIDE] You can't
kill me! Because, I am...
...Genocide!
[MANTICORE]
Abbah! Sayonara!
Huh? Aah!
Not even Manticore
could capture him?
I'm a bad girl, doctor!
I should've communicated
with the Sokaiya beforehand!
I'm not mad at you!
Just look at all this
beautiful combat data
we were able to accumulate
from my Genocide!
What I wouldn't give to have
him back! It makes me crazy!
[FUBUKI, LEE grunting]
[LEE] Genocide will
exterminate everything!
I must have him! I need him!
I can't take it!
Oh, I'm gonna go crazy!
I need him! I need him, dammit!
I can't take it! Agrh!
--[LEE] I'm gonna lose it!
--[FUBUKI] Oh, Doctor!
There's gonna be more of them.
So you should bail while
you still have the chance.
[sighs]
If I see you...
Did I tell ya my brains
are like pudding?
If we do happen to
see each other again
and I don't recognize ya,
don't be mad.
[YAMOTO]
Okay.
Bye.
[YAMOTO chuckles]
[GENOCIDE chuckles]