[LAOMOTO] Mua, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
--[DARKNINJA yells]
--[NINJA SLAYER groans]
[LAOMOTO]
Finish him!
[NARAKU]
You need me, Fujikido.
You've got the body,
I've got the power.
[NINJA SLAYER
Silence, Naraku!
[NARAKU] You can't win this.
If you weren't so weak,
he'd be a red smudge
in the dirt by now!
[NINJA SLAYER] For the last
time, this is my vengeance.
I will slay this
ninja. On my own!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[DARKNINJA]
Tch!
[DARKNINJA yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yelling]
[DARKNINJA yelling]
[NINJA SLAYER groaning]
[DARKNINJA]
Say sayonara! Ninja Slayer-san!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[DARKNINJA, NINJA SLAYER
yelling]
[NARRATOR] Their karates
are symmetrically opposed.
One strikes with great force.
The other, with great speed.
Neither has a clear advantage.
[LAOMOTO growling]
This is boring!
[YAKUZA CLONE]
Laomoto-san.
You have another televised
press conference to attend.
[LAOMOTO growls]
End this Dark-ninja-san!
I have constituents to deceive!
[LAOMOTO]
Make him bleed from his eyes!
From his-- where-ever!
[DARKNINJA]
Having performance issues,
Ninja Slayer-san?
You aren't using the
power of your ninja soul.
Too weak to get it up
without your sensei?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Tell me this.
Is my ninja soul unable
to rise to this occasion?
Or are you too weak
to stimulate it?
[NARRATOR] Between blows,
our combatants trade barbs
with provocative Zen dialogue.
[NINJA SLAYER] Perhaps you
should draw your katana,
Darkninja-san.
Although faint, I can still
sense the ninja soul within it.
It's not still broken, is it?
[DARKNINJA] I'll not use
Beppin on the likes of you.
Your feeble blood
might make her limp.
[DARKNINJA, NINJA SLAYER
yelling, groaning]
[DARKNINJA yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[DARKNINJA grunts]
[DARKNINJA groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Carnage!
[DARKNINJA]
You misjudge me.
[NINJA SLAYER, DARKNINJA
yelling]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[DARKNINJA]
A truly desperate technique.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NARRATOR] Though Ninja
Slayer charges faster
than a speeding
bullet train, for him,
his movements seem slow.
As does the world around him.
It's the neuron
acceleration jitsu!
[DARKNINJA yells]
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[DARKNINJA]
He's forced my hand.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[DARKNINJA]
Kirisute gomen!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Not this time.
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
[DARKNINJA] That was too much
to ask, even of Beppin.
Yet I have no choice but to use
her if I'm to settle this feud.
[TORTOISE]
Darkninja-san.
Consider the wants and
needs of your Beppin.
[CRANE]
Darkninja-san.
It's time for you to pledge
your fealty to a new master.
[TORTOISE]
Domo. I am Master Tortoise.
I can look into the future,
but not very far, mind you.
[CRANE]
Domo, I am Master Crane.
I can see into the past,
but not that far back, either.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Are they Soukai ninjas as well?
[NARRATOR] Darkninja was
strong enough alone.
Ninja Slayer did not look
forward to fighting him
and two more.
[NINJA SLAYER]
But still.
[NARRATOR]
The firewood of fury
fuels the furnace of his soul!
Power floods Fujikido
Kenji's entire body!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[TORTOISE] Stand back.
This is not your fight!
[CRANE]
We will dispatch this pest!
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
They're coated in poison!
[CRANE, TORTOISE]
Now then,
[TORTOISE]
Darkninja-san.
[CRANE]
Thunder Forge-san is in Kyoto.
It perplexes us that
you've not sought
his assistance as instructed.
[DARKNINJA]
Kyoto is currently controlled by
the Zaibatsu Shadow Guild.
Moreover, I'm on a mission.
A mission entrusted
to me by Laomoto-san.
[TORTOISE]
Compared to the task destiny
has set before you,
your mission...
[NINJA SLAYER]
Death is...
[CRANE]
You must locate...
[NINJA SLAYER]
...the only way out.
[DARKNINJA]
The Imperial Regalia.
I need a sword,
a jewel, and a mirror?
[TORTOISE]
No.
Those things are
obviously make-believe.
[DARKNINJA]
Then what treasures do I seek?
[CRANE] The mask, the
nunchaku, and the bracer.
[GENDOSO]
Ninja Slayer-san.
I know you miss me,
but stop almost dying!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Roshi Dragon-sensei-san.
I was such a fool. So arrogant.
I squandered all of your
training and counsel.
[GENDOSO]
Well, don't screw this one up.
Furin-Kazan. Chado.
Keep going. Furin-Kazan.
[NINJA SLAYER breathing deeply]
[NARRATOR] Ninja Slayer's
found the sweet spot!
His Chado breathing is perfect!
[DARKNINJA]
Kyoto. Zaibatsu.
[TORTOISE]
Shogun. Overlord.
[CRANE]
Gion. Kinkaku.
[TORTOISE]
Katsu Wanso. Nunja.
[NINJA SLAYER] Dragon-sensei.
You've saved my life again.
Thank you for watching over me.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
What is this?
Found another pathetic excuse
for running away, have you?
This score is anything
but settled, Darkninja-san.
[DARKNINJA]
You survived? How shocking.
Stand aside.
My "destiny" will have to wait.
This fight has needed
to end for a long time.
[DARKNINJA] Ninja Slayer's life
is mine, and mine alone.
[TORTOISE]
You're mistaken, Darkninja-san.
Destiny doesn't wait!
[CRANE] Also, if you
slay an unhallowed man,
he'll taint your hand
with unworthy blood.
[CRANE, TORTOISE]
And your hand is precious.
[NINJA SLAYER]
You will not escape!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NARRATOR]
My Buddha!
What kind of mystery
jitsu was that?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Huh?
[NINJA SLAYER] Fuyuko.
Tochinoki. Please forgive me.
[NINJA SLAYER breathes deeply]
[NINJA SLAYER]
This does not mean failure.
I will corner him
again before long.
In preparation for that day,
I must slay Laomoto Khan.
And find Nancy-san.
[NINJA SLAYER]
My ninja senses tingle.
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Just as I thought!
[NINJA SLAYER yells]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Nancy-san! Are you okay?
[NANCY]
I guess. Well, I'm in a cage.
Other than that,
I'm pretty much fine.
I'm so sorry. If I
hadn't screwed up.
--None of this would've--
--[NINJA SLAYER] Shh.
Thanks a lot.
[NINJA SLAYER grunts]
Everything'll be fine.
I have some organic sushi.
[NARRATOR] Chado assassination
techniques consume
a fair number of calories.
The corresponding acceleration
of one's metabolic
processes creates a need
for high quality,
nutritional replenishment.
--[door scrapes]
--[NINJA SLAYER, NANCY] Hm?
What're you doing in here?
You've got some nerve,
breaking into my room.
Do you know who I am?
What I can do to you?
[NINJA SLAYER]
Let's go.
[laughs] Good idea,
and you'd better run fast.
Because sooner or later,
I'll get you for this.
Hey! You can't take her,
she's mine! Mine!
I'll call Fujio!
I'll make him kill you! I swear!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Who was that boy?
[NANCY] Laomoto-san's son.
Or one of them at least.
There were way more
than I could count.
[NINJA SLAYER]
I see.
Can you make it
out of here alone?
[NANCY] There's a computer
room pretty close to here.
If you can get me that
far, I should be fine.
And if the mission's still on,
then I'll stay and support you.
Once I'm hacked in,
I'll do my best
to get you into the keep.
I owe you at least that much.
[NANCY]
Also...
If I hacked into that,
I could make the race
for governor a lot
more interesting.
After all, I have
proof of nearly
every crime his
syndicate's committed.
Locked in to my own
neural hard-drive.
If I can plug it in, well...