[ASARI]
This is gonna be great!
And I'm so glad you
came with us, Yamoto-san!
Meeting you was
luckier than I thought!
[BUNAKO]
The more the merrier!
[OKAYO]
Totally!
[MACHI]
Yay!
[squeaking]
I think that's gonna be
just a little too much.
They'll have to send
everything in the kitchen.
I couldn't really tell
if it was doing anything.
Well it looks like fun!
[squeaking]
[MALE MACHINE VOICE 04A]
Yo!
[MACHI]
Ooh, my turn!
There're barely any songs
in here I actually like.
Yeah, no kidding.
[gasps] Hold on,
I'll be right back.
[SHOGO]
Domo. My name is Shogo.
Domo. I am Yamoto.
You came here looking
for me, didn't you?
I did. You know why.
I mean, you can tell,
can't you?
[YAMOTO]
What do you mean?
[SHOGO] It was crazy
to see you again.
But finding out you'd become
a ninja totally blew my mind.
[FEMALE ELEVATOR VOICE 04A]
Bong! Fifth floor!
[SHOGO] Buddha fuck!
That's them.
We're out of time!
You gotta listen to me.
This is some life or death shit!
I'm a ninja, just like you.
After that big brawl,
I got recruited by
the Soukai Syndicate.
I had no choice. It was
either join them, or die.
They're gonna try and do
the exact same thing to you.
They'll be here any second!
[SONIC BOOM]
Suicide!
You should get the hell
outta here right now!
Run away!
[SONIC BOOM] Suicide-san!
It's getting late,
and I need to
get my beauty rest.
[SHOGO exhales deeply]
[SONIC BOOM]
Oh, there you are.
Having a nice chat?
Discussing our family?
Domo, Yamoto Koki-san.
I am known as Sonic Boom.
A Soukai Six Gates Ninja.
I see you've met
my fluffy headed associate,
Suicide-san.
We've come here
tonight to offer you
the once-in-a-lifetime
chance to be
a full-fledged Soukai Ninja.
[SONIC BOOM] Think of it as an
achievement, a badge of honor.
Even Suicide here
puts some value on his life
now that he's one of us.
[SONIC BOOM]
The syndicate can show you
your true purpose.
You can redeem yourself!
You understand me,
don't you? There's hope.
Even for a despicable
parent-killer.
[YAMOTO gasps]
[SONIC BOOM] I can't
imagine you'd refuse
this generous offer. Unless
you want me to kill you.
And if that's the case,
I'll oblige after
I have a little fun.
[SHOGO] Yamoto-san, I
apologize for all this crap.
I take full responsibility.
Please forgive me.
--[SHOGO] Yeeart!
--[SONIC BOOM] You fool!
You'll get your death wish!
Run while you still can!
--[SHOGO] Yeeart!
--[SONIC BOOM] Aaaargh!
You're finally beginning to
accept your power, aren't you?
--[SHOGO] Yeeart!
--[SONIC BOOM] Aaaargh!
[SHOGO] I don't know how
much longer I can hold him!
Move your ass!
[alarm ringing]
[GIRLS panting]
[SHOGO]
Aaaargh!
[SHOGO] You're not totally
like me. You have friends.
People who care about you.
No Soukai has that.
These guys
are a bunch of dicks.
Shogo-san, get up.
[distant rumbling]
[BUNAKO, OKAYO,
MACHI, ASARI gasp]
You need to run. Right now!
We can't just
leave 'im here!
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
But how?
I've got it. See you soon.
[ASARI gasps]
[running footsteps]
You've decided
to stand your ground.
I do admire your tenacity.
Now let's test
your pain threshold.
[grunts]
Domo. Sonic Boom-san.
I am Yamoto Koki.
[SONIC BOOM] So you're
a psychic ninja as well.
Very surprising for someone
to harness the gift
at such a young age.
But, as throughout history,
the one who possesses stronger
karate is the one who rises.
Let me beat that lesson
into your tiny skull.
You won't touch me!
[SONIC BOOM]
They're like mosquitoes!
Go! Yeeart!
[SONIC BOOM]
You little bitch!
This girl is a denominated
archninja class,
just like that suicidal loser?
How the hell can that be?
[SONIC BOOM] You need
to respect your elders!
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
[CLONE YAKUZA]
Hey, screw you!
[NARRATOR] Sonic Boom gave
the signal for a mass attack,
and the Yakuza clones
swarm like locusts.
[CLONE YAKUZA]
Hey, screw you!
[YAMOTO]
Yeeart!
[CLONE YAKUZA]
Aaaargh!
[SONIC BOOM]
Yeeart!
[YAMOTO]
Aaaargh!
[thud]
[rumbling]
[SONIC BOOM]
I warned you earlier,
but history repeats itself.
"I killed Mommy and Daddy,
but I still want friends."
Oh my Buddha,
what a frikkin' joke!
The only path in life for a
little piece of shit like you
is joining the Soukaiya and
killing who we tell you to.
Ha ha!
You'll never repay your
debt to society or family,
so you might as well
just give in.
No. Never!
[SONIC BOOM grunts]
[thud]
[clatter]
[footsteps]
[YAMOTO gasps]
[SONIC BOOM] I could crush
your head like a melon.
--[distant slurping]
--But I don't think you deserve
a quick death without suffering.
[slurping continues]
[SONIC BOOM]
Ugh. Do you mind?
We're having a moment here!
Who are you?
Domo. Very pleased to
meet you, Sonic Boom-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
[NINJA SLAYER] And all your
talking is disrupting my meal.
Oh yeah?
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
Now, tell me how in the hell
do you know who I am?
Because I've been
keeping an eagle eye
on all of you Soukai
Syndicate scumbags.
And if you think for
one moment there won't be
consequences to your
heinous actions,
you're a bigger fool
than you look.
"Sonic Boom."
You draw too much
attention to yourself
with those ridiculous,
garish outfits.
But the Soukai headhunter
and Master of
Six Gates Sonic Karate
would be arrogant.
You've got some nerve!
I have made it my goal to
slay all the Soukaiya ninjas.
And you are at
the top of my list!
You've just signed
your own death warrant
by threatening me. My Sonic
Karate will break your face,
shatter your spine,
and make you soil yourself.
Give me your best shot.
[SONIC BOOM]
Yeeart!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart! Yeeart!
[SONIC BOOM]
Stand still and die!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart! Yeeart!
--[SONIC BOOM] Yeeart!
I'll kill you!
[NARRATOR]
Oh my Buddha!
It's the Sonic Karate
anti-air pom-pom punch!
[SONIC BOOM]
Hey, screw you!
[NARRATOR] The beautiful
choreography of battle.
A thousand minimalist
masterpieces of precision!
A pointillist piece of art
using skin and blood
in lieu of canvas and oils.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SONIC BOOM]
Aaaargh! Now, you die!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SONIC BOOM]
Aaaargh!
Yeeart!
[NARRATOR]
In the ancient Edo period,
and in the American South,
it is said that
even if a poor gun
shoots a lot of bullets,
it will eventually hit.
But that may be
wishful thinking.
I don't get it! You should
be full of holes by now!
Aaaargh!
The fact that I am not
means this fight is over.
Recite your death haiku.
Before it's too late.
You cocky bastard.
You're not callin'
the shots here,
so prepare to die!
[SONIC BOOM]
Huh?
What the hell?
What the hell is that thing?
That is not origami!
[SONIC BOOM]
I'm gonna shred it!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[SONIC BOOM]
Aaaargh!
[SONIC BOOM grunting]
[YAMOTO]
Go!
[SONIC BOOM]
Sayonara!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
Thanks. Domo to you,
Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Yamoto Koki.
All of this destruction
was your handiwork?
I caused all this, yes,
because they provoked me.
But now,
I think I'm done here.
It would seem that way.
[NARAKU]
Kill her, Fujikido!
This girl is possessed
by that minx, Shi Ninja!
But she's completely
exhausted herself.
It would be easy,
like scratching an itch!
Carry out your vengeance!
[NINJA SLAYER] Silence!
This is my road!
My vengeance that must be
paid in the blood of ninjas!
Not yours!
[NARAKU] We agreed that you
would kill every last ninja!
Failure is not an option!
[YAMOTO gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER groans]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Leave! Now!
[knock, knock]
[gasps]
Aieee!
I don't believe it!
You're alive!
[YAMOTO] I should've
come sooner. I'm sorry.
[ASARI sobbing]
Truth is,
I'm a bad luck charm.
Trouble follows me around.
All we did was
go do some karaoke,
and we almost get killed.
Because I was there.
[ASARI sobbing]
Is this sayonara, forever?
Please don't
think of it like that.
If you need me,
I'll come running.
Sayonara...
...dear friend.
Best friend.
[YAMOTO]
Yeeart!