[YARUKI]
Aieee!
You'd better talk
before my finger slips.
Please don't
kill me, man.
I'll tell you everything
you wanna know!
I was hired by Yoros--
Aieee!
[grunts]
Who the hell are you?
[LOBSTER]
Domo. I am Lobster.
Hey, screw you man!
Well this took
a turn for the worse.
Ah! Ah!
Ngaaah!
[LOBSTER]
Yeeart!
[AZAWA]
Aieee! So hot!
Aieee! Who the hell
are you working with?
Aieee! I'll make
you pay, you bastard!
[gasps]
Ah! Ah!
[NANCY]
Ngaaah!
[LOBSTER] You idiot. You've been
killing people left and right.
That lack of discretion
has landed you
on your sponsor's shit list.
I was sent to deal
with you by Yoroshisan--
[LOBSTER]
Aaaargh!
[gasps]
Ah! Ah!
Ngaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. Lobster-san.
I am Ninja Slayer.
Domo. Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Lobster.
[NINJA SLAYER] Do you have
a death haiku prepared?
Why would I do that?
I'm not gonna die tonight.
I'll pinch your brains out!
[LOBSTER]
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[LOBSTER] Aaaargh!
Defeated so easily.
Aaaargh! Sayonara!
[alarms buzzing]
[NANCY] You saved me,
again, Ninja Slayer-san.
I'm sorry that you had to.
This place was all be--
[distant sirens wailing]
[monitor beeping]
[DARKNINJA]
You're finished.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Fuyuko, Tochinoki.
Yeeart!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[DARKNINJA] Aaaargh!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[DARKNINJA]
I. Am. Beat-en!
[monitor beeping]
[distant sirens wailing]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Raging Salmon.
The first hair gel
to also treat ED.
[sirens wailing]
[footsteps]
Domo Darkninja-san...
I am called Master Tortoise.
Domo. Master Tortoise-san.
I am Darkninja.
[TORTOISE]
I am pleased to see you
doing so well, Darkninja-san.
I feared that I'd
wasted my time on you.
[DARKNINJA]
Huh?
The shards of Beppin.
I recovered both the hilt
and broken blade
from the place of your defeat.
You really should take better
care of your things.
[DARKNINJA]
Could this be the end?
[TORTOISE] You have time
to live yet, Darkninja.
Destiny has
a purpose for you.
Thus you've been preserved.
[DARKNINJA] Uh. It was you
who told me I would live.
You'll want to search
for Thunder Forge-san.
For he can mend your sword.
In fact, no man aside from
him could possibly do it.
Thunder Forge-san is the finest
smith that hasn't croaked yet.
Anyone but him would fail you.
You say he's called
Thunder Forge?
I've never heard of a
sword-smith by that name.
Well It's not like
you've been looking.
I'll see you soon.
Take care of yourself!
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Fuegan is not for everyone.
Side effects include brain
damage, projectile tooth loss,
cancer, and rectal bleeding.
Ask your doctor if
Fuegan is right for you,
and tell him if you develop
suicidal thoughts
after taking it. Fuegan.
Tear your migraine
out by the root.
[NAKATA]
Aaah...
The culmination of decades
of bio-tech research, lost!
Aaah!
[gasps]
Even now, it moves.
Could this mean that some of the
bio-tissue can be salvaged?
Damn you to hell
Ninja Slayer-san...
Thus I swear on
this severed pincer
that I will create another
Lobster-san, and then--
Hmmm.
That I'll create
another lobster-san and then--
Hmmm.
I swear by this pincer
to create another Lobster-san!
Both swift and strong!
And when he is finished
I shall exact a most
brutal revenge!
[NANCY]
Nng! Ngaaah!
[LOBSTER] You have such a lovely
screaming voice, my dear.
I do hope that
Ninja Slayer-san
gets here soon for your sake.
It'd be a shame for such a
voluptuous and tech-savvy woman
to be tossed into the pot.
[laughs intensely]
[NANCY]
Nng! Nng! Ngaaah!
A scream like that
could make a lobster blush!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
Domo, Ninja Slayer-san.
I am Lobster.
[NINJA SLAYER]
Domo. I am Ninja Slayer.
Am I to believe that you've
managed to regenerate?
Ooh. Work that out
all by yourself?
You're almost as slow-witted
as my clone Yakuza!
Hyah!
[CLONE YAKUZA]
Hey, screw you!
[LOBSTER] Either surrender,
or I'll cut this chain!
[gasps]
Nng! Nng!
Ngaaah!
[CLONE YAKUZA]
Die, you bastard!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[CLONE YAKUZA] Aaaargh!
[LOBSTER]
How foolish of you.
You might as well have killed
this saucy wench yourself.
[gasps]
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NANCY]
Nng! Nng!
Ngaaah!
What the hell?
You have the reaction time
of a damned... viperfish!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart! Yeeart!
Are these surikens
made of steel or origami paper?
Taste my science!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
He dodged it?
That's impossible!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Yeeart!
[NAKATA]
Aaaargh!
What is this?
Why would you
do such a thing?
You tore my life's work
asunder and boiled it.
I can't let you get away
with that crime!
I craved revenge,
but my options were limited
as this claw was the only
thing you left me with!
[NAKATA]
Yeeart!
Aaaargh!
The closest thing
to a son I'll have.
Lobster-san, now lends me the
strength of his body and soul!
Thanks to him,
I have become a ninja.
Now! I'll kill you with
your latest victim's hand!
--[NINJA SLAYER] Yeeart!
--[NAKATA] Aaaargh!
Aaaargh! Yeeart!
[NANCY]
Nng! Nng!
Ngaaah!
[NINJA SLAYER]
Wasshoi!
[NANCY] And once
again you saved me.
But in the future,
I'll be more--
This time was simply
the result of
my carelessness from last time.
I promise you,
it won't happen again.
[NANCY] Strange. A little adage
just popped into my head.
Should you destroy
what a man loves most,
he'll cling tighter
to the pieces
than he ever did
the thing itself.
[NINJA SLAYER] That is
truer than you know.
[gasps]