[MITSUHA] Some mornings, I wake
up crying without knowing why.
That sort of thing
happens now and again.
[TAKI] Whatever the dream was
I had, I can never remember it.
But...
[MITSUHA] But the only thing
that does last when I wake up
is a sense of loss which lingers
for a long time afterwards.
[ringing]
[TAKI] I'm always searching
for something, or someone.
[MITSUHA] I've been
consumed by this feeling
ever since that day.
[TAKI]
The day a star fell.
It was almost like...
[MITSUHA] ...like seeing
something out of a dream.
Nothing more or less...
[MITSUHA, TAKI]
...than a breathtaking view.
[phone ringing]
[MITSUHA]
Taki.
Taki!
Don't you remember?
[gasps]
[MITSUHA gasps]
My name is...
...Mitsuha!
[gasps]
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Hm?
[door opens]
[YOTSUHA]
Sis, what are you doing?
Whoa. They're so
realistic feeling.
Hm?
"Sis"? Me?
Are you still asleep?
Breakfast time!
Hurry up!
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Wha--?
[gasps]
What?!
Do you wanna have any a
last night's fish, Grandma?
[HITOHA]
You can eat it.
[MITSUHA]
Mornin'.
[HITOHA]
Lazy butt! You're so slow!
[MITSUHA]
I'll fix breakfast tomorrow.
[HITOHA]
Hm?
Oh, that's a lot.
Oh, well!
You're back to normal today.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
You were so crazy yesterday.
What do you mean "crazy"?
[ringing]
[ANNOUNCER A]
Attention citizens of Itomori.
Good morning.
This is an offical announcement
from Itomori Town Hall.
It is in regards to
the mayoral election.
The election will be held
on the 20th of next month.
The election committee would
like to remind everyone that--
A comet that comes only
once every 1,200 years
will finally be headed
our way in a month.
The comet will be visible to
the naked eye for several days
once it approaches the Earth...
Just make up with
him already, okay?
It's an adult matter.
[NEWS ANCHOR A] According
to JAXA's spokesperson,
they're preparing for the
celestia show of the millennium.
[MITSUHA, YOTSUHA]
We're leaving!
[YOTSUHA]
I can't wait till the festival!
It's gonna be so much fun!
[YOTSUHA]
Study hard, Sis!
Oh!
Mitsuha!
Good mornin', Saya.
Mornin', Teshi.
Mornin'.
Come on! Would you
get off already?
What for, meanie?
'Cause you're heavy.
Hey, that's rude.
You know, I've gotta say,
you two make a great couple.
[SAYAKA, TESHIGAWARA]
No we don't!
[MITSUHA chuckles]
[SAYAKA] Oh, I see you actually
bothered to do your hair today.
Wait, what?
Oh, yeah, what happened?
Did your grandma exorcise
all your demons?
Exorcise?
Somethin' totally
possessed your body.
[SAYAKA]
Wouldja just give it a rest
with all this occult nonsense?
Mitsuha's gotta be feelin'
stressed enough as it is, right?
[MITSUHA]
What're you guys talkin' about?
Are you feelin' okay?
Hm?
[TOSHIKI]
And above all,
restoring the town's
fiscal health
so we can continue our
revitalization project!
It's only when all these
things are achieved
that we can create a safe
and secure community!
As the incumbent,
my administration has...
Miyamizu's gonna get
another term anyway.
I hear he's been dolin' out
the pork, just between us.
Hey, Miyamizu.
[MITSUHA]
Mornin'.
Looks like the mayor and
the contractors' kid
are pretty cozy too.
[SAKURA]
Ew.
[TOSHIKI] ...and improve
the quality of life
of each and every resident.
Hm?
Mitsuha!
[gasps]
Stand up straight
when you're walking!
[OLD RESIDENT C]
Oh, he's tough on his family.
Well, that's the mayor for ya.
Awkward.
Sucks to be her.
Mitsuha.
In front of everyone...
[MITSUHA]
Hm?
Two-light.
That's the origin of
the word "twilight."
I'm sure everyone
here knows that word.
It's dusk. A time when it's
neither day nor night.
When the border
between worlds blur,
and one might encounter
something not human.
Another older term
for it is "dusklight."
Some people also call
it "golden hour."
[SCHOOLBOY A]
What about magic hour?
It's somethin' my grandma says.
[MISS YUKI]
Well, golden hour and magic hour
are techincally the same.
But it's a term that
mostly photographers use.
[SCHOOLBOY A] Well, she does
take a lot of pictures.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[MITSUHA]
Hm...
[MISS YUKI]
Okay, next, Miyamizu!
Uh! Yes!
[MISS YUKI] Well, I can
see that you remember
your own name today.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[MITSUHA]
Hm?
[SAYAKA]
You don't remember?
[MITSUHA]
Uh-uh.
[SAYAKA]
Well, believe it or not,
you forgot where your own desk
and locker were yesterday.
Plus you had the worst
case of bed head,
and you didn't have
your ribbon on either.
[MITSUHA chuckling]
What? No way!
Yeah, it was like you had
amnesia or somethin'.
[MITSUHA]
Now that you mention it,
I do feel like I've been
havin' weird dreams lately.
Like a dream about
someone else's life?
Ugh... It's all so fuzzy.
Wait a sec.
I've got it! It's memories
from a previous life!
Or maybe your
subconscious linked
to the Everett interpretation
of the multiverse!
Keep your fool mouth shut!
Wait a minute, Teshi!
Don't tell me you're the one
who wrote in my notebook!
Huh?
[MITSUHA]
Forget it.
But you really were actin'
just a little funny
yesterday, Mitsuha.
You been feelin' okay?
That's what's weird.
I feel fine.
Maybe it's from stress.
Y'know, you've got that ritual
comin' soon, don'tcha?
[MITSUHA]
Aww! Don't remind me!
I can't stand this
place anymore.
It's too small and town-y.
I wanna graduate already and
go to Tokyo as soon as I can!
[SAYAKA]
Can't say I blame you.
There really is nothin'
at all in this town.
There's only one train that
stops here every two hours.
[MITSUHA] And all the store
closes at nine o'clock.
[SAYAKA]
No bookstores, no dentists.
[MITSUHA] But two cocktail
lounges for whatever reason.
No jobs in town.
No one dateable.
[SAYAKA]
Even the days are too short!
[grumbles]
[TESHIGAWARA]
You know what?!
[SAYAKA, MITSUHA]
No, what?
Uh.
Forget that stuff.
Why don't we go to a café?
--[SAYAKA] A café?
--[MITSUHA] Really?
[SAYAKA, MITSUHA]
Where?
[GRANNY A]
Hello, kids.
--Evening, ma'm!
--Hi there!
How is this a café?
[TESHIGAWARA]
Like this town's got a café'.
Mitsuha just went
straight home.
Things have gotta be really
rough for her right now.
[TESHIGAWARA]
She's on center stage and all.
--[SAYAKA] Yeah.
--[DOG whines]
[TESHIGAWARA]
Hm?
Hey, Teshi.
[TESHIGAWARA]
Hm?
What're you gonna do after
you graduate high school?
Where'd that come from?
You talkin' about the future?
[SAYAKA]
Mh-hm.
I don't know.
I think I'll probably
just end up
livin' in this town, you know?
Same as ever.
[sighs]
I wanna do what you're doin'.
It's still too soon
for you to try, Yotsuha.
Listen to the thread's voice.
When you twine it round
and round like this,
feelings will start flowin'
between you and the thread.
It's not like threads talk.
[MITSUHA]
She's tellin' you to focus.
Etched within our braided cords
is a thousand years' worth
of Itomori's history.
Listen, somethin'
happened 200 years ago.
Here she goes.
[HITOHA] The bathroom of
sandal maker Mayugoro Yamazaki
caught on fire, and
this whole area burned down.
The shrine and old
documents were destroyed.
This is known as--
Mayugoro's Great Fire.
They named the fire after him?
I feel bad for Mayugoro.
The meanin' behind our festivals
was lost because of that.
Only the surface was left.
But even if those
words are gone,
the tradition shouldn't fade.
That's the Miyamizu Shrine's
duty, our important task.
[sighs]
Despite all that,
that son-in-law of mine--
Abandoning the Shinto priesthood
and leavin' this house were
bad enough, but politics?
Oh! He's hopeless.
[TOSHIKI]
Have another, Mr. Foreman.
[EMPLOYEE A] The site
we've got is a tricky one,
that's for sure.
I'll be counting on your
help again for this election.
[TESHIGAWARA'S DAD]
Leave it to me.
You'll get the votes from the
Kadoiri and Sakagami districts,
guaranteed.
How's the datin' scene?
It ain't easy, that's for sure!
[TESHIGAWARA'S DAD,
EMPLOYEES laughing]
Smells like corruption in there.
[TESHIGAWARA'S MOM]
What're you talkin' about?
We're gonna need two
or three more bottles
Yes, dear.
Katsuhiko, you're gonna help
out at the site this weekend.
We'll be usin' explosives,
so you better study up.
[groans]
What was that?
Got it!
[TESHIGAWARA] Guess we both
can't stand things here.
[SPECTATOR A] Is that Yotsuha?
She's all grown up.
[SPECTATOR B]
They're lookers all right,
just like their mother.
[TESHIGAWARA]
Hey-a.
Hey.
[TESHIGAWARA]
World's oldest kind of saké.
By chewin' on rice,
spittin' it out,
and then lettin' it ferment
naturally, it becomes alcohol.
Kuchikamizake . Do the gods
really appreciate that?
--The way it's made--
--Yeah! Of course they do!
[SAYAKA groans]
[MATSUMOTO] Hey, check
it out. It's Miyamizu.
Uh! I'd never do that!
[SAKURA]
And in front of everybody.
[HANA]
Embarrasing, right?
[YOTSUHA]
You should try to cheer up, Sis.
Who cares if a few of the kids
from your school saw all that?
It must be nice for you,
not being a teenager.
[YOTSUHA] Hey, you should
just sell kuchikamizake
and move to Tokyo.
I bet you could sell it
with all sorts of stuff,
like photos and
making-of videos.
Oh!
And then you could call it
"Shrine Maiden Saké."
You'll make butt-loads!
[MITSUHA]
Hmm...
I can't! There are liquor laws!
Huh?
That's what you have
a problem with?
I hate this town!
I hate this life too!
Please make me a handsome
Tokyo boy in my next life!
[sighs]
[YOTSUHA]
What a jackass.
[TAKI]
Ow!
Ouch.
[TAKI]
Where?
[grunts]
[TAKI]
Hm?
Somethin's... there.
[screams]
[NEWS ANCHOR B] A spokesperson
confirmed the story today
in a press conference
and stressed that the company
will do everything...
[TAKI'S DAD]
Taki! You up?
It was your turn to cook
breakfast, wasn't it?
Did you sleep in?
Uh. I'm sorry.
[TAKI'S DAD]
Hm?
Uh, I'm heading out.
Finish the miso.
[TAKI]
O-Okay.
[TAKI'S DAD]
Make sure that you go to school
even if you're late.
See ya.
Have a nice day!
What a strange dream.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
Huh? It's from... Tsukasa?
Who's that?
[groans]
I gotta go pee.
[toilet flushes]
[whines]
Way too real.
[chuckles]
[TAKI]
I'm in Tokyo!
[SCHOOLGIRL A]
Where did you get this?
[SCHOOLGIRL B]
Daikanyama.
Guess who's opening
our next gig?
[JINGU SCHOOLBOY C]
What?
[SCHOOLGIRL C] Hey,
let's skip club stuff today
and catch a movie.
[TAKI]
Uh...
Taki!
[TSUKASA chuckles]
[TSUKASA] Can't believe
you got in at noon.
Come on, let's grab lunch!
You ignored my text too.
Uh, Mister Tsukasa?
[TSUKASA] "Mister"?
You don't have to go that far.
--[TAKI] Uh.
--[TAKAGI] You got lost?
[TAKI]
Yeah.
[TAKAGI]
Wait a second,
how'd you wind up getting
lost on the way to school?
[TAKI]
Uh, well, a girl--
A girl?
Uh, a gal.
[BOTH]
Hm?
I mean--
[BOTH]
Huh?
A guy!
[sighs]
You know, guys just
wanna have fun!
Every day's a festival when
you're livin' in Tokyo.
As a guy.
[TAKAGI]
Hey, you sound funny.
[TSUKASA]
And where's your lunch?
Uh!
Seriously?
What is up with you?
We can share somethin'.
Let's make a
croquette-egg sandwich.
[BASKETBALL PLAYER B]
Yes! Ha, ha!
[TAKI]
Uh.
Thank you.
[TAKAGI chuckles]
[TAKAGI]
Wanna hit the café later?
[TSUKASA] Oh, that one?
Sure. You in, Taki?
[TAKI]
What?
What?!
A café?!
They've got nice
timberwork in here.
[TSUKASA]
Yeah, it's pretty intricate.
Taki, all set?
[TAKI]
Uh! Uhh...
[gasps]
[TAKI]
I could live for a whole month
on what these pancakes cost!
[TSUKASA]
Uh, maybe a decade ago.
[TAKI]
Hmm.
Oh, well! It's only a dream!
[TAKAGI, TSUKASA]
Hm?
[TAKI sighs]
Dreams are great.
[TAKAGI, TSUKASA]
Huh?
[phone rings]
[TAKI]
Huh?
[gasps] What? Oh, no!
I think that I'm late for work!
You've got a shift today?
Guess you'd better get going.
[TAKI]
Uh, Right.
Uh, sorry, but uh--
[TAKAGI, TSUKASA]
Huh?
[TAKI]
Where exactly do I work?
[TAKAGI, TSUKASA]
Wha...?
[PEOPLE shouting]
[CUSTOMERS chattering]
[CHIBA] Tables six, seven,
and ten are waiting!
[TANAKA]
Three new diners!
Table 12! Taki!
Got it!
Here you go.
So the zucchini and
tomato salad with a side...
--We didn't order that.
--Wha--?
Taki! I told you that
we were out of truffles!
Taki, you've gotta talk louder!
Taki!
[TAKI yells]
When is this nightmare
gonna be over?
Waiter.
Hey, you!
Uh, yes?
See this? Does it look right?
A toothpick's in it.
Uh...
[YAMAMOTO] What would've
happened if we ate it?
It's really lucky I
noticed when I did.
Do something.
[TAKI]
Uh, it's just that--
Well, I don't even think we
have toothpicks at this--
What?!
[MADAM B]
Huh?
[OKUDERA]
Excuse me.
Is everything
all right over here?
[YAMAMOTO]
Well...
I'll take care of this.
What's wrong with you today?
[TAKI]
Huh?
[OKUDERA]
We truly apologize.
Your meal tonight
is on the house.
Why, thank you.
[OKUDERA]
You weren't hurt, were you?
Uh, Okudera.
That's "Miss" to you.
[TAKI]
Miss Okudera, about before--
We just had some
bad luck is all.
[TAKI]
No, I--
Those guys were
definitely scamming us.
I handled it according
to the manual, but still...
[CHIBA]
Miss Okudera, your skirt!
Are you all right?
Did something happen?
[CHIBA]
Looks like someone cut it.
That guy.
[CHIBA] What now? Do you
remember what he looked like?
[NAKAMURA]
No.
[TAKI]
Come with me.
[OKUDERA]
Huh?
[NAKAMURA]
Hey, Taki!
[TAKI]
Okay, take off your skirt!
What?!
[TAKI]
I'll-I'll look the other way!
Yeah?
Hold on. This won't take long.
[TAKI]
All done! Ta-da!
You're really good, Taki!
It's way cuter now!
[BOTH chuckle]
By the way, I wanted to
thank you for all your help
with that customer earlier.
To be honest, well,
I was worried about you.
You aren't that strong, but
you're quick to pick a fight.
Heh. I like you better today.
You've got a feminine side.
Who would'a guessed?
[TAKI] I gotta say, this
dream sure does seem real.
Ah, looks like he
keeps a journal.
[TAKI]
Hm.
So organized.
I wish I lived in Tokyo.
One of her!
[TAKI]
Unrequited love?
[gasps]
[TAKI]
What is this?
Wha--?
What?!
What is going on?
[TAKAGI]
So café today?
[TAKI]
Thanks, but I gotta go to work.
Ha! Do you remember where to go?
Huh?
Wait a second, was
that you, Tsukasa?
Are you the one that's been
messin' with my phone?
[TSUKASA]
Huh?
[TAKI]
Uh. Never mind. Later.
Well, he's back to normal.
I think he was kinda...
cute yesterday.
Uh...
[gasps]
[TAKI]
What's up?
Don't play dumb!
What about bro code, huh?
You walked home with
her yesterday, right?
[TAKI]
Uh.
What're you talking about?
Me and Miss Okudera?
[OTHERS]
So what did you guys do?
Uh, well, I don't
remember actually.
Quit messin' around and tell us!
[OKUDERA]
Okudera, reporting for duty!
Don't slack off today, you guys.
[BOYS]
Yeah.
[OKUDERA] We're gona
have a good day today.
Aren't we, Taki?
[TAKI yelps]
[MITSUHA]
Hmm?
[door opens]
[YOTSUHA] I see you're not
touching your boobies today.
Breakfast time! Hurry up!
My boobs?
[MITSUHA]
Mornin'.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[STUDENTS whispering]
I feel like everyone's
starin' at me for some reason.
Well, ya did kinda
make a scene yesterday.
Uhh?
[HANA] Didja see all
the election posters?
[MATSUMOTO] Doesn't matter
who wins, nothin'll change.
Except for who gets
the gift bag.
[SAKURA] Shh! Somebody's
daddy's depending on it.
[HANA, MATSUMOTO,
SAKURA chuckle]
[MITSUHA]
They're talking about me, right?
Wait! Mitsuha?
[chuckles]
[MITSUHA]
I-- I...
I did what?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Mitsuha?
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Huh?!
[MITSUHA]
Could this--? Could this mean--?
[TAKI]
No, no, no, no!
Could this mean...
that we're really--?
That we're...? In our dreams,
that guy and I...
That we're--? In our dreams,
that girl and I...
[MITSUHA, TAKI gasp]
[BOTH]
We're switching places?!
[MITSUHA] I'm slowly beginning
to get what's goin' on.
Taki's in high school
and living in Tokyo.
[TAKI]
Two or three times a week,
I'll suddenly and randomly
switch with Mitsuha,
who's somewhere
out in the boonies.
The trigger is sleep.
The cause is unknown.
[MITSUHA] Any memories
I have of the switch
get more and more hazy
after I wake up.
[TAKI] But there's no doubt
that we're switching places.
The reactions of everyone
around us prove it.
That's why--
[MITSUHA] That's why we decided
to lay out some rules
so we could protect each
other's way of life.
Things to watch out for
during the switches,
and a list of stuff
we should never do.
[TAKI] We also agreed to leave
each other reports on our phones
on the days we switch places.
[MITSUHA]
So that we can work together
to get through this weird
thing that's happening.
[MITSUHA]
And yet--
[TAKI]
--I cannot believe this guy!
--I cannot believe this girl!
[groans]
[whines]
[SCHOOLBOYS gasp]
[MITSUHA]
Guys'll stare.
Watch the skirt!
These are basics for a girl!
[TAKI]
Stop wasting my money on sweets!
[MITSUHA]
It's goin' in your body!
Plus I also work for that money.
[TAKI]
Braiding cords is impossible!
[MITSUHA]
You work way too many shifts!
[TAKI]
'Cause you keep wasting money!
[MITSUHA] Had tea with Miss
Okudera on the way home.
You two have a good thing goin'.
[TAKI] Quit messing with
my relationships, Mitsuha!
[MITSUHA] Hey, Taki, why's a
girl confessin' her love to me?
[TAKI] Maybe you're just more
popular when I'm you.
[MITSUHA]
You're so full of yourself!
Like you have a girlfriend.
[TAKI] It's not like you
have anyone either!
[MITSUHA]
I don't...
[TAKI]
[BOTH] ...because I don't
want a relationship!
[phone ringing]
I shouldn't for her sake.
[YOTSUHA] You sure do
like your own boobies.
Time to go! Get ready!
[HOST A] Over the course
of the last few days,
the Tiamat comet
has been visible.
But when and where
can people see it?
The Tiamat comet will be moving
in the same direction
the sun does,
from east to west from
our point of view.
So right after sunset.
As for where...
Why're you wearing your uniform?
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
[YOTSUHA]
Grandma?
Why does our shrine god's relic
have to be kept so far away?
[HITOHA] 'Cause of Mayugoro;
I don't really know.
Who's Mayugoro?
What? He's famous!
[MITSUHA]
Hop on, Grandma.
--[HITOHA] Oh!
--[YOTSUHA] Watch out! Careful!
Mitsuha, Yotsuha, do
you know about Musubi?
Musubi?
It's what we used to call the
local guardian deity long ago,
and it means "union."
This word has profound meanin'.
Tyin' strings together
is a union.
Connectin' to people is a union.
And the flow of time is a union.
These are all part
of the god's power.
The braided cords that
we make are tied to that.
A skill from the god,
they represent the
flow of time itself.
They assemble and take shape.
They twist, tangle,
unravel now and then,
break and reconnect.
That's what a union is.
What time is.
[HITOHA]
Have a drink.
[MITSUHA]
Thanks.
I want some too!
[HITOHA]
That's also a union.
[HITOHA chuckles]
[HITOHA] Whether it's
water, rice, or saké,
when somethin' becomes
a part of a person,
it's a union, it
joins their soul.
Which is why the offerin'
we're making today
is such an important custom.
It connects the
god with people.
[YOTSUHA gasps]
Hey, I can see it!
This is where it is.
The sacred relic of
Miyamizu Shrine.
What lies ahead
is the hereafter.
[YOTSUHA]
Huh?
It's the netherworld.
[YOTSUHA giggles]
[YOTSUHA]
The netherworld!
In order to return
to this world,
you have to leave behind what
is most important to you.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
[HITOHA chuckles]
Like the kuchikamizake .
[MITSUHA]
Kuchikamizake ?
[HITOHA] You'll offer it at the
foot of the shrine god's relic.
After all, it is half of you.
[MITSUHA]
Half... of Mitsuha.
[BOTH laugh]
Wow! It's already magic hour!
Hm? Magic hour?
[MITSUHA gasps]
[YOTSUHA]
Oh, yeah!
Maybe I can see the comet.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
The comet?
Oh.
Mitsuha, you're dreaming
right now, aren't you?
I'm crying? But why?
[phone rings]
Miss Okudera?
She's almost where?
Uh!
Oh, Mitsuha, what did you do?
Date?!
[MITSUHA] Tomorrow's your
Tokyo date with Miss Okudera!
Meet up at the station at 10:30!
[MITSUHA] Well, that's what
I had planned, but--
Hi, Taki!
[OKUDERA giggles]
Wait long?
Yeah. Uh, no.
Uh...
[chuckles]
I just got here.
Thank goodness. Let's go.
[MITSUHA]
Must be nice.
They've probably
met up about now.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Why am I...?
Why?
[MITSUHA] It was a date
I wanted to go on,
but if it so happens
you end up goin',
you'd better be
grateful and enjoy it!
[OKUDERA] This is a nice.
It's my first time here.
So is this one of your
usual go-to spots, Taki?
[MITSUHA]
At any rate,
I bet you've never even
been on a single date.
It's too expensive!
[OKUDERA]
Uh.
[chuckles]
[TAKI]
I don't know what to say to her.
[MITSUHA] That's why I've
hand-picked some links below
to help you out,
you wall flower.
For real?
[TAKI]
Hm?
Hm...
[TAKI growls]
She's making fun of me.
[gasps]
You know something, Taki?
Today you're... you're
like a different person.
[TAKI] Um, Miss Okudera,
you getting hungry?
We could get dinner.
[OKUDERA]
Uh. Let's call it a day.
All right.
I could be wrong,
and I'm sorry if I am.
About?
[OKUDERA] But you used to have a
little crush on me, am I right?
[TAKI]
Uh!
But right now, there's
someone else you like, huh?
[TAKI]
Wha--?
No. No, it's not that.
[OKUDERA]
Really?
There's no one.
It's not like that.
[OKUDERA]
Are you sure about that?
Well, thanks for today!
See you at work.
[TAKI]
By the time the date's over...
[TAKI, MITSUHA] ...you should
be able to see the comet
in the sky.
[TAKI]
What does she mean? Weirdo.
[phone ringing]
[MITSUHA]
Oh, it's you, Teshi.
No. I just didn't feel
like goin', that's all.
I'm fine.
What? The festival? Oh...
Oh, yeah, the comet.
It'll be at its brightest
today, right?
Okay, got it. See ya later.
[SAYAKA] You're just lookin'
forward to seein' Mitsuha
in a yukata, aren'tcha?
I-I am not!
I mean, it didn't
even cross my mind.
[SAYAKA]
Mm...
Y'know, she sounded kinda
down when I talked to her.
Maybe she just didn't
want a call from ya.
It's not funny!
[MITSUHA]
Sorry to keep ya.
--Oh, she's here!
--You're late.
[BOTH gasp]
Mitsuha, what happened to--?
[TESHIGAWARA]
Your hair!
I guess... it's weird.
[TESHIGAWARA] You think it's
gotta do with some guy?
Like... he broke her heart?
Guys always just assume
that it has to do with a boy.
She said she felt
like cuttin' it.
[TESHIGAWARA]
Ya sure about that?
You really think she felt like
cuttin' off that much of it?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Hey, guys! I can see it!
[TESHIGAWARA]
Whoa.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
[VOICE MESSAGE A] The number
you are trying to reach
is currently outside
the cellular network
or has been turned off due--
[TAKI] I'll just have to tell
her how lousy the date ended up
the next time we switch.
That's what I thought.
But--
For some reason, the
switches Mitsuha and I'd
been going through until now...
they never happened again.
[TAKI]
Wha--?
What're--?
What're you doing here?
[OKUDERA giggles]
[OKUDERA]
Tsukasa told me, so here I am.
[CONDUCTER A] We thank you for
riding the Shinkansen line...
[TAKI]
I asked for two things.
To cover my shift, and to back
up my alibi if my dad asked.
Relax, Takagi's gonna
take your shift.
Gotcha covered!
But you owe me dinner!
So you're all in on it.
You've got everyone
worried about you.
Huh?
We can't ignore this.
What if somebody's trying
to pull one over on you?
Like catfish?
[OKUDERA] I mean you met this
person online, didn't you?
No, not exactly!
It's kinda complicated.
Could be from a dating site.
She's not!
It's because you've been
acting awfully fishy lately.
So we're keeping
an eye on you.
I don't need a
baby sitter, okay?
[TAKI]
The switches stopped.
My calls never connected and
texts never went through.
That's why I decided to
go see Mitsuha in person.
I wanted to see her.
But--
[OKUDERA]
What?
You don't know where
she is exactly?
The town's landscape
is your only clue?
Yeah.
[OKUDERA]
And you can't contact her?
What's that about?
[TSUKASA] Where are we?
You're a terrible tour guide.
[TAKI]
'Cause I'm not one!
Oh, well.
Guess we'll help you search.
Ah! It's so cute! Look, Taki!
[TAKI grumbles]
Seriously, guys?
[OKUDERA]
It moved! Aw!
[TAKI]
This is a lost cause.
[OKUDERA, TSUKASA]
What?
After everything that
we've done for you today?
[TSUKASA]
Um-hm.
[TAKI sighs]
You haven't done anything.
[OKUDERA]
One Takayama ramen.
[TSUKASA]
[TAKI]
I guess I'll have the same.
Sure. Three orders of ramen.
[HUSBAND A]
Got it.
Think we can make it
back to Tokyo tonight?
Well, I think we'll
be cuttin' it close,
Let me take a look.
'K, thanks.
Wait, Taki, you sure about that?
[TAKI]
Yeah.
I kinda feel like maybe I've
been barking up the wrong tree
this whole time.
Hey. That's a sketch
of Itomori, isn't it?
[WIFE A]
It's drawn really well.
Come take a look at this, hun!
Yeah, that's Itomori.
It takes me back.
My husband was born and
raised there, you know.
Itomori?
Yes, of course!
That's the place!
It's nearby, right?
You don't...
Itomori was--
Itomori?
--Wait!
--But that's where--
Isn't that the area
where that comet--?
[TAKI]
Huh?
[OKUDERA] Hey, is this place
really where she's from?
No way.
Taki must've just confused
this with somewhere else.
No, I didn't.
This was the place.
This schoolyard.
These mountains.
Even this high school here!
I remember it all!
There's no way you could.
You've gotta know about that
disaster three years ago, right?
Hundreds of people died.
They died?
Three years ago?
It can't be.
There's no way.
I mean, I still have
the memos she wrote.
[gasps]
[TAKI]
They're fading...
[TSUKASA] Comet Tiamat, with an
orbital period of 1,200 years,
made a close approach to Earth
three years ago in October.
Nobody foresaw that
its nucleus would split
at its perigee.
[TAKI] The fragment that broke
off of it became a meteor
and struck Japan.
[OKUDERA] It looks like
that day was the same date
as the autumn festival.
[TSUKASA]
The point of impact was here.
At 8:42 p.m.,
it fell right around
where people were gathered
for the festival.
[TSUKASA]
Over 500 died.
It was a third of the
town's population,
and now nobody lives
in Itomori anymore.
[TAKI gasps]
Teshigawara... and Sayaka.
[gasps]
[OKUDERA]
Huh? That's her?
You were wrong. You gotta be.
After all, this girl here
died three years ago!
[TAKI]
Just two or three weeks ago
she said that I'd be
able to see the comet.
That means--!
[HITOHA] You're dreaming
right now, aren't you?
[TAKI]
I...
What... was I?
[clapping, distant cheering]
Sounds lively over there.
[TSUKASA] They only have one
room left. I'm really sorry.
It's not a problem.
How's Taki?
He's still reading
articles on Itomori.
He's going through all those
newspapers and magazines
at random. Seems obsessive.
What is it?
Oh, sorry. You smoke, huh?
Yeah. I did quit at one point.
[TSUKASA] What do you think
about what Taki's been saying?
I had feelings
for him, you know.
The way he's been recently.
I mean, he was a nice guy
before, but he's even nicer now.
Kind of... frantic. It was cute.
Although I do think what
he's been telling us
is definitely strange sounding.
But in the end, the fact remains
that Taki's met someone,
and that someone is
the reason he changed.
That much is for sure.
[TAKI]
It was all just a dream.
I recognized the landscape
because I unconsciously
remembered the news
from three years ago.
If it's not that,
is she... a ghost?
Or... did I just make it up?
The whole thing.
[gasps]
What was her name?
I can't remember.
[knocking]
Tsukasa said he was gonna
go ahead and take a bath.
Miss Okudera.
Uh... I, um--
I realize I've been saying
a lot of strange things.
I'm really sorry, and thank you.
[OKUDERA]
Braided cords.
Pretty.
That band on your wrist,
that's one, isn't it?
[TAKI]
Huh?
Oh, this thing? Guess so.
Somebody...
Someone gave it to me.
I wear it sometimes as
kind of a lucky charm.
Who was it?
It's late. Why don't you go
down and take a bath too?
Sure.
Wait.
Yeah, someone who makes these.
They once told me something.
The cords represent
the flow of time.
They twist and tangle,
unravel and connect.
And how that's what time is.
[gasps]
Maybe if I could--
[MITSUHA]
Taki.
Taki!
[MITSUHA]
Don't you remember?
[OKUDERA sighs]
[OKUDERA]
Taki.
[HUSBAND A]
Eat this bento up there.
[TAKI]
Huh?
Your drawin' of Itomori,
you did a real good job.
[thunder rumbles]
[TAKI]
They assemble and take shape.
They twist, tangle,
unravel now and then,
break and reconnect.
That's what a union is.
What time is.
[TAKI]
There it is.
It's really there.
It wasn't a dream.
[TAKI] What lies ahead...
is the netherworld.
[TAKI]
It's still here.
This was Yotsuha's,
and this was mine.
This was before the comet.
So when I switched
places with her,
it was also three
years in the past.
Our times got tangled somehow.
This is half of her.
[TAKI]
Musubi.
If it's true, and time
can be unraveled,
just give me one chance.
[gasps]
[TAKI]
A comet!
[BABY crying]
Your name's going to be Mitsuha.
[TOSHIKI]
Both of you are my treasures.
You're going to
be a big sister.
[FUTABA]
I'm so sorry, me dears.
[YOTSUHA] Dad, when is
Mommy coming home?
[TOSHIKI]
I couldn't help her.
[HITOHA]
Get a hold of yourself!
[TOSHIKI]
Who cares about the shrine?!
[HITOHA]
But you're in charge now!
[TOSHIKI] I loved Futaba!
Not Miyamizu Shrine.
[HITOHA]
Get out!
[HITOHA] Now listen to me,
girls, starting today,
you'll be living with Grandma.
[MITSUHA]
Who am I? Who are you?
Don't be full of yourself!
Like you have a girlfriend.
Must be nice.
They've probably
met up about now.
[gasps]
Why am I...?
I'm going to Tokyo.
[YOTSUHA]
What? Wait, Sis!
[MITSUHA] Grandma, would you
mind doin' me a favor?
Oh, yeah, the comet.
It'll be at its
brightest today, right?
[TAKI]
Mitsuha! Don't go there!
Mitsuha.
You've gotta get out of town
before the comet strikes!
[TAKI]
Mitsuha, run!
Mitsuha!
[gasps]
[MITSUHA]
Mitsuha. She's alive.
Let me guess, you're
touchin' your boo--
[gasps]
[MITSUHA cries]
Her sister!
Yotsuha!
[MITSUHA crying]
[YOTSUHA]
I think she's finally lost it.
Just for today,
I'm gonna head out first.
She's lost it. Really lost it.
Totally, totally lost it.
[WEATHER WOMAN A] For all you
star-gazers out there,
the comet Tiamat has been
visible to the naked eye
for about a week now.
Tonight it will finally reach
its perigee around 7:40 p.m.
and be at its maximum brightness
when viewed from
the Earth's surface.
[MITSUHA]
It's tonight.
There's still time left.
Mornin', Mitsuha.
What's this?
Hold on. You're not
Mitsuha, are you?
[gasps]
Wait, how did you...?
You already knew?
No, but watchin' the way
you've been behaving lately
stirred some memories up.
[HITOHA]
When I was a young girl,
I had some pretty
strange dreams myself.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
[HITOHA]
Though it's been so long,
the memories of who I
became in those dreams
have pretty much
faded at this point.
[MITSUHA]
Faded.
Treasure the experience.
Dreams eventually
will fade away.
i went through similar
times myself,
and so did your mother.
[MITSUHA]
What if...
...all those dreams that
the Miyamizu people had...
...it had to do with today?
Grandma, you have
to listen to me!
Tonight, the comet is
going to fall on Itomori.
You're all gonna die!
Huh?
[MITSUHA]
"Nobody's gonna believe that"?
I didn't expect that
out of Mitsuha's grandma.
It doesn't matter!
There's no way I'm gonna
let them all die!
[SAYAKA]
Mitshua!
What happened to--?
[TESHIGAWARA gasps]
What'd you--? You're hair!
Ah, the haircut?
Looked better before, huh?
[TESHIGAWARA]
No! I-It's good!
Nevermind that!
If we don't do something
about tonight, we'll all die!
[SAYAKA]
What?
[SAYAKA, TESHIGAWARA]
Uh...
[MITSUHA]
It's up to us to save everyone!
Wait! Shouldn't you
be in school?
Well, we sort of have to save
the town, or something.
Huh?
[MITSUHA]
The warning system?
[TESHIGAWARA] Yeah, those
speakers all over town.
[MITSUHA]
I get it. It could work!
Nice job, Teshi!
Hey, I don't think you should
be sittin' so close to me.
What's wrong? Uh-oh! You shy?
Would ya quit it? It ain't
proper! And you know it!
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
[MITSUHA laughs]
[MITSUHA]
Such a gentleman!
Ha! Since when?
[SAYAKA]
I bought all the snacks, guys!
Here's the change.
Sorry for the trouble.
[SAYAKA]
I didn't mind.
We oughta be gettin' paid.
Quit complaining.
So? What'd ya come up with?
Got an evacuation plan?
[BOTH chuckle]
[SAYAKA]
A... A-- A bomb?!
Yeah, we have
water gel explosives
we use for construction
at our storage site.
And the warning system?
A startup frequency can hijack
the town's warning
system pretty easily.
So we can broadcast
an evacuation warning
for the whole town
right from school!
Look, we're outside
the disaster area here,
so we'll just make
an announcement
to evactuate to the school.
[SAYAKA]
It's--
It's totally a crime.
[MITSUHA] You'll be in charge
of the broadcast, Saya.
[SAYAKA]
Why me?!
You're in the broadcast club.
And I'll be in charge
of the explosives.
While I go have a
word with the mayor.
[SAYAKA]
Why?
'Cause if the evacuation order's
not comin' from town hall,
then nobody's gonna go anywhere.
But if I talk to the mayor,
as his daughter,
I can convince him.
[TESHIGAWARA]
It's the perfect plan.
[sighs]
Fine, I don't really care
one way or the other.
This is just a theory
of yours, right?
[MITSUHA]
Uh.
Well...
Theories can be
based on reality!
Like, do you know the story
of how Itomori Lake was formed?
It's a crater!
That means a meteor hit
this area at least once
a thousand years ago!
[MITSUHA]
Right!
That's why--
Nice one, Teshi!
[BOTH]
Let's go evacuate the town!
[TOSHIKI] What on earth
are you talking about?
[MITSUHA]
Like I said,
we have to evacuate everyone in
town before tonight or else--
Enough. Shut up!
[sighs]
"The comet is going to split
in two and strike the town"?
"Over 500 will die"?
How dare you stand there
and spout such nonsense!
If you're serious,
you must be sick.
I guess wrecklessness
is a Miyamizu trait.
I'll have a car take you
to the city hospital
for an examination.
We will continue this discussion
after you've seen a doctor.
You!
You son of a--
Mitsuha.
No.
Wait a minute...
Who are you?
I'll see you guys
at the festival.
We'll meet you at the steps to
the shrine! Don't be late, okay?
--Bye-bye!
--See ya.
Later.
You shouldn't go!
You've gotta leave town!
Tell all of your friends!
What's wrong with ya?
[YOTSUHA]
Mitsuha!
What was that about?
Come on. Let's go.
What're you doing, huh?
If it was Mitsuha,
would she have been
able to convince him?
Is all this my fault?
[YOTSUHA]
Huh?
[MITSUHA]
Yotsuha!
Promise me that you'll leave
town with Grandma before dark!
What?
You're gonna die
if you stay here!
What're you talking about?
And why'd you suddenly
go to Tokyo yesterday?
You've been acting
really strange lately!
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Went to Tokyo?
[SAYAKA]
Hey! Mitsuha!
[TESHIGAWARA]
How'd it go with your old man?
Huh?
Hey! Mitsuha!
What's with your sister?
[YOTSUHA]
Dunno.
[MITSUHA gasps]
[YOTSUHA]
Huh?
Could she be over there?
What's that? What's over there?
[MITSUHA]
Let me use your bike, Teshi.
Hey!
Mitsuha!
And what do we do?
Get things ready
like we planned!
I'm counting on you!
[gasps]
[TAKI]
Oh my gosh! I'm Taki again.
But what was Taki
doin' out here?
[TAKI gasps]
The town. It's gone.
[TAKI]
So does that mean...
...they died?
[MITSUHA]
Taki.
Don't you remember?
[MITSUHA] I'm going to
Tokyo for a few hours.
What? Right now?
But why?
For a date.
[YOTSUHA]
You have a boyfriend in Tokyo?
I didn't say it
was a date for me.
I'll be back tonight.
[MITSUHA] If I suddenly show up,
will it be a nuisance?
Or a surprise?
He might not like it if I do.
[VOICE MESSAGE A] The number
you are trying to reach
is currently outside
the cellular network.
[MITSUHA]
I guess it won't happen.
But what if it did?
What would I do?
Would I annoy him?
Would it be awkward?
Or maybe... he'd be
glad to see me.
[VOICE MESSAGE A] The number
you are trying to reach
is currently outside
the cellular network.
[MITSUHA]
I guess we won't meet.
But...
...there's one thing
I'm certain of.
If we see each other, we'll
definitely know right away.
That you were the
one who was in me.
And that I was the
one that was in you.
[ANNOUNCER B] The train will
be arriving momentarily.
Please stand behind the line.
When entering the train,
please mind the gap.
[gasps]
[MITSUHA]
'Scuse me.
[ANNOUNCER B]
The doors are now closing.
[MITSUHA] That time three years
ago, before I even knew you...
[ANNOUNCER C] Yotsuya. The
platform will be on the right.
[MITSUHA]
Taki.
[TAKI]
Huh?
Uh. It's me.
Don't you remember?
Sorry, who are you?
I-I'm sorry.
[MITSUHA]
But he's Taki.
[TAKI]
What a weird girl.
[ANNOUNCER D] Yotsuya. Yotsuya.
Stand clear of the doors.
Hold on!
Huh?
But what's your name?
Mitsuha!
My name is... Mitsuha!
[MITSUHA]
Three years ago, you showed up.
It was...
...to see me!
Taki.
[MITSUHA]
Mitsuha!
Taki?
[MITSUHA]
Mitsuha!
You're here, right?
Inside my body!
Taki!
Taki, where are you?
That was Mitsuha.
I can hear her voice, but...
Taki? Where are you?
Taki!
[gasps]
[TAKI]
Huh?
Taki, are you...?
Are you there?
[gasps]
[MITSUHA, TAKI]
Magic hour.
[gasps]
Mitsuha.
Taki.
You're really here.
Taki!
[TAKI]
I came all this way to see you.
Which wasn't easy, since
you were pretty far away.
Huh? How is that even--?
Because back then...
Well, I drank some of
your kuchikamizake .
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
You-- You drank that?
Stupid pervert!
Wh-What?
Yeah! That's right!
You were touching my
boobies, weren't you?
[TAKI]
Wh--?! H-How do you even...?
'Cause Yotsuha saw you!
[TAKI] I-I just--
I couldn't help myself!
But it was just the one time.
Just the one time?
How many times isn't the issue!
Sorry.
[MITSUHA]
Wait, is that--?
Oh, yeah, it's yours, but you
vistied before I knew you.
So I didn't know who you were.
Here. I kept it for three years.
But I think it's time
you got it back.
What do ya think?
[TAKI]
Oh, uh, well...
It's not bad.
Oh, you're lyin'!
[TAKI chuckles]
Busted.
Why you gotta be like that?
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[TAKI] Hey, Mitsuha, you still
have a lot to do. Listen.
It's coming.
Don't worry. You still
have enough time.
I'll do my best.
It looks like magic
hour's almost...
...over.
Hey, Mitsuha.
Just so we don't forget
things when we wake up.
[MITSUHA]
Huh?
Let's write down our names.
Here.
Mitsuha.
[TAKI]
Hey, Mitsuha?
I was planning to tell you...
...that wherever you
are in the world,
I swear that I'll find you
again, no matter what.
[TAKI]
Your name... is Mitsuha.
It'll be okay. I'll remember.
Mitsuha. Mitsuha. Mitsuha!
Your name is Mitsuha!
Your name is--
[gasps]
[TAKI]
Who... are you?
And what did I even
come here for?
I came... I came all
this way to see her!
I came here to save her.
I wanted her to be alive.
Who was it again?
Who? Who did I come to see?
Someone precious. Someone
that I don't wanna forget.
Somene I shouldn't!
Who was it?
Who?
Who?!
What's your name?!
[MITSUHA]
Taki. Taki. Taki.
It'll be fine. I remember.
I'll never forget!
Taki. Taki.
Your name is Taki!
[MITSUHA panting]
[MITSUHA]
Teshi!
Mitsuha!
Where the heck have you been?
[MITSUHA] He said sorry
for breakin' your bike.
Wha--? Who did?
I did.
You're gonna have to
explain it to me later.
That thing is goin' to
fall, right? For real?
[MITSUHA]
For real.
I saw it with my own eyes!
What? You did, huh?
Well, I guess
it's settled then.
We're both officially criminals.
[SAYAKA]
What?
Do I really have to?
[TESHIGAWARA]
Once the town's power goes out,
the emergency generators
will kick on right away.
Use the broadcast
equipment once it does.
Don't be scared, Saya.
And repeat it as many
times as you can.
Woohoo! You can do it!
Aw, nuts. It's do or die!
[SAYAKA whines]
Shouldn't it be goin' off?
Hell if I know!
[TESHIGAWARA chuckles]
[FESTIVAL GOER A]
What was that?
That was pretty loud too.
[FESTIVAL GOER A]
Look over there!
[FESTIVAL GOERS chattering]
[TOSHIKI]
Huh?
[gasps]
--Hey, look! Up there!
--Huh? Cool!
[siren wails]
[SAYAKA]
This is Itomori Town Hall.
Reports of an explosion at
the substation are coming in.
[STAND CLERK A]
Explosion?
Did I just hear that right?
Wildfires are possible,
as well as the threat
of more explosions.
Residents in
the following areas,
please evacuate to Itomori
High School immediately.
Kadoiri district
Sakagami district...
[MAN A]
Honey, we should go.
The broadcast isn't
coming from us?
Well, who the hell is it then?
[SAYAKA]
Miyamori district.
Oyazawa district.
Let's go, Mitsuha!
[MITSUHA]
Teshi!
[SAYAKA]
This is Itomori Town Hall.
Reports of an explosion at
the substation are coming in.
[TESHIGAWARA] Everyone,
run! There's a wildfire!
[MITSUHA]
Wildfire! Please run!
[TESHIGAWARA]
Get outta here! Run!
[MITSUHA] It's not safe here!
Please evacuate!
It's not workin'.
We're runnin' outta time!
Mitsuha!
What's wrong?
What is it?
I can't remember what
his name is anymore!
What is with you?!
You're the one who
started all of this!
We can't evacuate everyone
without firefighters!
Get goin'! You gotta
convince your old man!
[SAYAKA]
This is Itomori Town Hall.
Reports of an explosion at
the substation are coming in.
[TESHIGAWARA] Everybody!
Get to the high school! Hurry!
Oh, it's Mitsuha.
[CHIEF] Why would terrorists
attack way out here?
What is Chubu Electric sayin'?
[CLERK]
They're still checking.
Any update? No wildfires yet?
You're sure? Got it.
Make them stop this
broadcast immediately!
Haven't you located
its source yet?!
Mayor! The Takayama
sensor station just called!
From the high school?
[SAYAKA] Once again, residents
in the following areas,
please evacuate
to Itomori High-- Ah!
[MR. ENDO] What're you
doing? Turn that off!
They got Saya!
[TESHIGAWARA]
Oh, no!
[crying]
What were you doin',
Natori? I swear.
[ringing]
[AIDE D]
This is Itomori Town Hall.
We are currently confirming
the reports of the accident.
We instruct all residents
to remain calm
and stay where they are
till further notice.
I guess we have to stay put.
[FIREFIGHTER A]
What is goin' on?
[FIREFIGHTER B]
So stay on standby.
[TESHIGAWARA] Come on, they said
everyone should evacuate!
The high school's
the evacuation center!
[TESHIGAWARA'S DAD]
Katsuhiko!
[TESHIGAWARA]
Huh?
Tell me. What do you
think you're doing?
Sorry, Mitsuha.
This is the end.
[gasps]
Oh my god.
It's actually splittin' apart.
[REPORTER A]
Look at that!
The comet has split
into two large parts,
and meteors are now
falling to earth!
I don't believe anyone
could've predicted this.
Either way, we have quite
the mystical view here.
[NEWSCASTER B] So what does
the comet's nucleus splitting
mean for us?
[EXPERT B] The comet's not
within the Roche limit,
so the nucleus itself must've
had a structural weakness
for this to happen.
[EXPERT A] Comet
Shoemaker-Levy 9 broke apart
and collided with
Jupiter in 1994.
There were at least
21 fragments then.
I'm going outside
to take a look.
[EXPERT B] The fragments
will likely burn up
well before reaching the ground
The probability of a
meteor actually landing...
[REPORTER C]
Scientists were already
intently examining the comet,
but never foresaw
this development.
[EXPERT C]
To predict the trajectory--
[EXPERT E] As we stand here
witnessing this spectacle,
unassisted and
with our bare eyes,
it strikes me that
living in such an age
has never felt more
fortunate than now.
[MITSUHA]
Hey. Who are you?
Who?
Who is he?
Someone precious.
Someone I shouldn't forget.
Someone I didn't want to!
Who?
Who are you?
What's your name?
Oh, no.
[MITSUHA yelps]
[TAKI] So that we don't forget
things when we wake up,
let's write down our names.
[MITSUHA]
Writing this...
...doesn't help.
I won't know your name.
[cries]
[MITSUHA]
Dad!
Mitsuha!
There you are!
Don't tell me you're back.
[gasps]
[TAKI] It was almost like seeing
something out of a dream.
Nothing more or less
than a breathtaking view.
[TAKI]
Huh?
Why am I here?
What am I doing?
[ANNOUNCER E]
Next is Yoyogi. Yoyogi.
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER E] The doors are
closing. Please be careful.
[TAKI] I'm always
searching for something.
This feeling has consumed
me for some time.
[TAKI] The reason I applied
for this position...
The landscapes people live in...
To build a city's landscape...
Even Tokyo, it might
vanish too one day.
And so, I wanna make
landscapes that--
How should I put this?
That can continue to
warm people's hearts.
[TAKI groans]
That bad? How many
does that make it?
I've stopped counting.
Doesn't sound too promising.
Who asked you?
That suit could be the problem.
[TAKI]
It looks just like yours!
Well, I have two offers.
I have eight myself.
[TAKI growls]
--[phone rings]
--Huh?
[TAKI] Is what I'm
searching for ...someone?
Or somewhere?
Or am I just searching
for the right job?
I don't even really know.
Oh!
You're job hunting, huh?
I haven't had much luck though.
[OKUDERA]
Hmm...
Hey, maybe it's the suit
that's killing your chances.
Does it really look
that bad on me?
[OKUDERA laughs]
[TAKI]
So why the sudden call today?
[OKUDERA]
I was in the area for work
and I figured it had been a
while since I saw your face.
Remember that one
time when we went
all the way to Itomori?
You were still in high school
back then, so it was...
[TAKI]
Five years ago.
That long?
It seems like...
I've forgotten a lot.
[TAKI] I don't remember all that
much either, about back then.
Maybe we argued.
She and Tsukasa went back
to Tokyo without me.
I spent the night alone
on some mountain.
That's about all I remember.
[TAKI]
But at one point in time,
I found myself strangely
drawn to the incident
involving that comet.
[TAKI] A fragment of the
comet destroyed a town
in that disaster.
But miraculously,
most of the people living
in the town were unhurt.
The town happened to be holding
an emergency drill that day,
and most of its residents
were outside the impact zone.
The sheer luck and
coincidence of it all
sparked various
conspiracy theories.
I read a lot of articles
about it back then.
I was kind of obsessed.
But whatever the reason
I had for my interest,
is a mystery to me now.
I didn't even know
anybody in that town.
[OKUDERA] Thanks for today.
This is far enough.
I do hope that at some point,
you'll find happiness too.
[TAKI] I feel like
I'm always searching.
For something.
Someone.
[WOMAN] I feel like I do wanna
go to one more bridal fair.
[MAN]
They're all the same.
A Shinto wedding sure
sounds nice too.
[MAN] You said you wanted to
be married in a chapel!
Oh! That reminds me, Teshi.
Would ya please shave
before the ceremony?
I'm goin' on a diet
for it, ya know?
She says as she's
eatin' a cake.
[SAYAKA]
I'll get serious tomorrow.
[gasps]
[TAKI] The landscape of a town
that's no longer there.
Why does looking at it make
my heart feel so tight?
[gasps]
[TAKI]
I was always searching.
[MITSUHA]
Searching for...
...someone!
[MITSUHA gasps]
Excuse me!
Haven't we--?
Have I met you somewhere?
I thought so too!
[BOTH]
Can I ask you... your name?