Fight!
[ALL] Fight on! Fight on!
Fight on! Fight on!
[MOB] Psychic powers don't
make a man appealing.
So, in order to change
this aspect of myself,
I joined the
Body Improvement Club.
[MUSASHI]
Body improvement!
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
Move it!
Fight on... Fight... on...
[MUSASHI]
Hm? This isn't good.
Guess he must be anemic.
Fi... Fight on...
[TOME] There is something
wrong with him.
I mean, who would choose
the Body Improvement
Club over us?
Let it go. What's done is done.
Let's not dwell on it.
Come on.
It's your turn,
President Kurata.
Hey, guys.
[ALL]
Oh! Hey, Musashi!
And, once again,
thank you so much for
letting us use this room!
[MUSASHI] Really, you
don't have to grovel.
Most of our training's
outside, anyway.
We just need this room
to store our equipment.
[TOME]
Uh... What's with him?
[MUSASHI]
Oh, Kageyama passed out.
Would you mind
looking after him?
We're still exercising.
[panting]
[TOME]
Now, seriously...
Why did you join the
Body Improvement Club?
Because...
I've never been the
most athletic guy,
and I'm a really slow runner.
I've always relied on my
psychic powers for everything.
Huh?
What kind of lame
excuse is that?
Besides, I don't even
know if you really do
have psychic powers. Prove it.
[ALL gasp]
So was that enough?
Do you believe me now?
Whoa, it's heavy!
[INUGAWA]
Seriously?
He could only
bend spoons before!
[TOME]
Oh!
Kageyama! Please!
Help me make my dream come true!
Huh?
Believe it or not...
...my dream is to make contact
and have initial
interplanetary dialogue
with extraterrestrial
life forms!
When first trying
to achieve this goal,
I followed an instructional
guidebook, but it didn't work.
Before I knew it, I was
just lazing around...
But now that you're here
with your psychic abilities,
I've finally got a shot!
Mob,
let's research telepathy
together, seek out new life,
and boldly go where
no man has gone before!
Can't. I've gotta
go pump some iron.
What? You're kidding.
I'm burning with passion here.
Why're you so indifferent?
[MOB] Because I've
finally found something
that I wanna do.
What, putting on some muscle?
You have psychic powers here.
So what difference
does bulking up make?
Actually, it might be
more accurate to say...
I want to become more appealing.
So, you mean...
You wanna be popular?
[gasps]
No, not really...
[TOME]
Well, you won't be.
Huh?
[TOME]
Even if you gain tons of muscle,
that'll never happen.
Not a chance!
What? Then what
should I do about it?
[TOME] Read girls'
minds using telepathy.
You have the power!
Do that, and you'll
be super popular.
[ARATAKA]
What? Telepathy?
I can't really do
anything like that.
Though, I am able to hear
the voices of spirits.
What brought this on?
Oh, I was just wondering...
Is there someone's mind
you wanna read in particular?
[gasps]
Maybe a girl?
Mob, Mob, Mob...
You are so easy to read.
Look.
Every middle school boy
wants to be popular.
It's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
It's just a fact of life.
Even yours truly has
dreams of popularity.
[MOB] It's not like I have
to be popular or anything...
I just want Tsubomi to like me.
[LOL WOMAN 3A] Young man,
may I ask you a question?
Is something troubling you?
You aren't laughing or smiling.
No...
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
I can sense these things.
You're worried about
your studies, right?
My grades are just fine.
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
Of course they are.
It's not your studies...
But, it must be hard
dealing with family issues.
[MOB]
Actually, I don't have any.
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
What I meant to say was...
It must be your health.
No...
It's about love.
That's amazing!
How did you know?!
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
If you want to resolve
these troubles, come with me.
[MOB]
I can't. I have to head home.
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
You'll be popular.
'Kay, let's go, then.
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
It so happens that I belong
to a brand-new religious order
that came into existence
last month.
[MOB]
Religious order?
[LOL WOMAN 3A]
Yes. It's called LOL.
Founded by our leader,
Master Dimple, it's the
happiest, trendiest,
most satisfying gathering
of the century!
The master has the amazing
and mysterious ability to
make anyone laugh immediately.
That's cool.
So, how do I become popular?
[LOL WOMAN 3A chuckles]
Now, now, don't be so hasty.
[LOL WOMAN 3A] LOL is in
no way a suspicious group,
so make yourself at home.
[MOB] Wow, there are
a lot of people here.
I wonder if they all
wanna be popular, too.
[LOL MAN 3A]
Oh, are you new, young man?
Huh?
[LOL WOMAN 3B] Then you
need to get up on stage.
Why would I do that?
[LOL MAN 3B]
Come on, now.
[LOL MAN 3C]
Hurry, hurry!
[LOL CROWD]
Heave ho, heave ho!
[MOB]
I have no idea what's going on.
[MEZATO]
Mob? Is that you?
Do you recognize me?
I'm Mezato, from
your homeroom class.
[MOB] Whoa, I've never
talked to her before.
[MEZATO]
Did they lure you in?
--Well, actually-...
--[LOL MAN 3D] He's here!
[LOL MAN 3D]
It's Master Dimple!
[LOL CROWD cheers]
[DIMPLE]
Let me ask you...
Are you laughing?
[LOL CROWD laughs]
[DIMPLE]
Are you warmed up now?
Why don't we take off
these masks, then?
Sparkle!
[DIMPLE]
You're all smiling so brightly.
[laughs]
[LOL CROWD laughs]
Man, what a creepy
bunch this is.
And stop!
[DIMPLE] Today, we have
three new smile-mates
joining our congregation.
Give them a hand!
What? "Smile-mates"?
Hey, what's the big idea?
In order to openly accept
the gift of happiness,
you must lower your walls
and set your hearts free.
They're locked up, you see.
Imprisoned in your own body.
Get it?
It's completely obvious
why you're unhappy.
You aren't laughing!
The key to your
freedom is laughter!
Do so, even in pain, and your
hearts will be unlocked!
[DIMPLE] And once they
have been set free,
your hearts will have the
ability to accept happiness
as it comes your way.
Like our brethren
here already know.
To have a happy life,
you must have a hearty laugh!
That is the teaching of LOL.
Huh. You really think
people can be happy
just by laughing? Get real.
[DIMPLE]
Who might this be?
We found him sleeping
on a park bench
under some newspapers.
[DIMPLE] How sad.
A victim of the recession!
You poor soul.
No wonder you lost your
smile. But worry not!
Let's put on this
smile mask and fix that.
Hey, what are you...?
Wait a minute!
This is the road to salvation.
I assure you, we want nothing
more than to make you smile.
[STAGE MAN 3A gasps]
[MOB]
Huh?
[DIMPLE]
No resistance.
And, that brings us to the girl.
It appears you have
something to say.
[gasps]
This religious order, LOL--
It was established last month?
How did you manage to
attract this many followers
in such a short time?
I don't believe it!
[DIMPLE]
Oh? And you are...?
[MEZATO]
I'm Mezato, Year 2, Class 1!
Salt Middle School's
ace reporter!
I'm here to investigate
the bad rumor
concerning this organization.
"Bad rumor," you say?
That you're using hypnosis
to brainwash people,
then forcing them
to join your cult.
[DIMPLE] What nerve,
saying that after sneaking in
by herself. Splendid.
[DIMPLE] Let me provide
you with proof, then.
Please take a look at that
gentleman from earlier.
As you recall, moments ago,
he was a very sad man.
[STAGE MAN 3A]
Sparkle!
[laughing]
Now, look at that smile!
[MEZATO]
He's laughing. Why?
He has finally let go and
is truly grasping happiness.
So, what do you
think now, young lady?
[MEZATO] He didn't
really do anything bad,
I'll give him that.
[LOL MAN 3E]
I'm sure you'll find a job now!
[MEZATO] But something still
stinks about all this.
There's a strange feeling
in the air here.
[MEZATO] I guess the rumors
I heard weren't true!
My mistake!
So, if you'll excuse me,
I'll just be--
That won't do.
You infiltrated LOL, doubting
our smiles for no reason,
insulting our beliefs
and our congregation.
I-I know, and I'm
terribly sorry.
I won't write about you
in the school paper.
That is not enough!
For it will not ease
our hard feelings!
We won't let you leave
until you laugh.
I--
I don't really feel
like laughing now.
A-And if I forced myself to
right here on the spot,
it wouldn't be sincere at all!
Start smiling. I insist you do!
No way! I don't wanna
lie to myself like that.
H-Hey!
[MEZATO whimpers]
[MEZATO]
What is this?!
H-Huh? I'm...
No! Don't! No!
Sparkle!
Look at that magnificent
smile! I just love it!
[LOL WOMAN 3D]
Congratulations!
[LOL MAN 3F]
You've changed.
No, please... No... I can't!
What is this feeling
that's come over me?
We're all smiling,
and it feels really nice.
But no!
I don't actually want to smile!
I can't control it!
Somebody save me!
[MOB]
Um, excuse me.
[MEZATO]
Mob!
[MOB] So the theme here
is smiling and happiness?
It doesn't have anything
to do with being popular?
May I leave now, then?
Who is that?
I found him looking troubled
on his way home from school,
so I brought him here.
He's having some problems
with his love life.
Well, maybe...
But this isn't gonna help.
[DIMPLE]
He's not smiling!
Does that mean the smile
mask didn't work on him?
[LOL MAN 3H]
Huh? He's not smiling?
[MOB]
Later.
W-Wait a minute!
Wanna spend the
rest of your life
with that frown?
You are missing out!
[MOB]
Hm.
My dad once told me that
"people who've never
smoked before
are missing out on
half of their lives."
It made me realize
people define
"missing out" differently.
[DIMPLE gasps] That's not
what I'm talking about.
LOL is the starting
line for me to become
the religious leader
of all humanity!
I can't let this stupid
kid mess this up for me!
You misunderstand.
I simply want you to know
just how wonderful it is
to smile, that's all.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
[DIMPLE] Th-Then would you
like to play a game
before you leave?
A staring contest
competing with three
of my smile leaders.
You'll all drink some milk,
and the first to laugh
and spit it up loses.
What do ya say?
[MEZATO]
Mob, no! It's a trap!
Are you two ready?
If ya laugh, ya lose.
[MEZATO] Why did you
accept the challenge?!
[NARRATOR] It just so
happens, Mob loves milk.
Ready... go!
[DIMPLE]
What? Why?!
[GAME HOST 3A]
Go!
[DIMPLE]
Impossible...
[SMILE LEADER 3]
Pfft. Those two are pathetic.
With my smiling powers,
I'll throw him into a smiley
maelstrom the likes of which--
[DIMPLE]
Ah, I see!
Forcing my congregation
to laugh all the time backfired!
[MOB]
I won, so I'm gonna head home.
[DIMPLE]
Wait!
You'll have to face me, now!
[LOL MAN 3I gasps]
What?
[LOL WOMAN 3E] The Master
Dimple is gonna face him?
[DIMPLE] I will not let you win,
you little troublemaker.
I will make you
spit out that milk!
Ready, go!
[grunts]
[DIMPLE]
Of course, this time...
[DIMPLE] ...the milk has
a little extra kick to it.
Ha, ha! He laughed!
[LOL WOMAN 3F]
He laughed!
[LOL MAN 3K] We expect nothing
less from Master Dimple!
[MEZATO] Even I'm starting
to have fun right now.
[MOB pants]
No, you're wrong.
That wasn't laughter.
What the--?
Where's my smile?
[LOL MAN 3L] Wait a minute--
why am I here again?
[DIMPLE yells]
[LOL MAN 3L] Oh, yeah!
Because it's so much fun!
Wait. Did you...?
[DIMPLE]
No...
He couldn't possibly have
undone my hypnosis.
But why can't I make him laugh?
I have no choice.
I'll have to go all out.
My brethren! Please!
We must all work together
to save the laughter
trapped within him!
He can't stay this way!
--[LOL MAN 3M] How wonderful!
--[LOL MAN 3N] Master Dimple!
[LOL WOMAN 3H]
Let us laugh together!
Hey! Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
You see?
You don't have a
single enemy here,
so why are you fighting?
We only want to save
you from yourself.
Come on already, get a clue.
[MOB gasps]
[BOY 3A]
Hey, Mob.
Why do you always look
so bored all the time?
Huh?
[BOY 3A]
If you are, then just go home.
I-I'm not bored. I promise!
[BOY 3B]
Hey, guys!
[BOYS laugh]
You're the only one
who's not laughing!
[TSUBOMI]
Come on, Mob.
[MOB]
Tsubomi...
Get a clue already.
You leave me little choice.
I'm forced to show
you my true power.
Now, start laughing!
[LOL MAN 3O]
There it is!
[LOL CROWD laughs]
[LOL MAN 3O]
Master Dimple's divine power!
[DIMPLE gasps]
What?
[LOL CROWD laughs]
[DIMPLE]
Why?!
Why aren't you laughing?!
Are you trying to
tell me that my powers
don't work on you?
Laugh! Come on, you little brat!
Laugh it up already!
[MOB] I see. He has
psychic powers, too.
What the hell?!
Are you a corpse?!
Your powers can't make me laugh.
It's not like I'm fighting it.
I just can't, okay?
Even if I really wanted to.
But I don't mean anything
bad by it at all.
[DIMPLE]
I see. So that's it.
Heh. You must not
have any emotions brat.
They mentioned that you were
having troubles with love.
With a personality
such as yours,
you won't be able to laugh
with the girl you like.
When feelings are shared,
typically, they're
physicalized in some way.
But you're not able
to do that, are you?
You'll never laugh
together, cry together,
or be moved
emotionally in any way.
You'll be alone forever.
This is it, boy.
I'll give you
one last chance!
Now, laugh!
[LOL CROWD laughs]
Ha, ha!
[MOB]
Why don't you make me laugh
with your psychic powers.
[DIMPLE grunts]
Ah... I see now.
So you have similar abilities...
I specifically chose to start up
a peaceful religious
order so the least
amount of blood would be shed.
But you're in my way, brat.
I have to get rid
of the outsider
who brought in all this chaos!
Thank goodness.
You're not even a person.
I'm glad that the one
who said something
as horrible as "get a clue"
was an evil spirit.
[DIMPLE]
My followers!
Do not let him leave
this place alive!
[MOB]
A strong commanding signal.
[TSUBOMI]
Come on, Mob.
Get a clue already.
[NARRATOR]
He is an esper,
blessed with psychic abilities.
A grade schooler called
"Mob" by those around him.
Even though these
tremendous powers
have been bestowed upon him,
subconsciously he's
always avoided
displaying these abilities.
As he grew older and
became more aware,
he came to realize
just how dangerous
his powers were.
When people are unable to act
or to do as they please,
or to truly express themselves,
their emotions come to a halt.
While attempting to spare
the world around him,
Mob's aversion to
using his powers
has become a complex.
The emotions locked away
deep inside his heart
expand little by little,
moment by moment.
However, there's a limit
to how much his emotions
can take before leaking
out and going wild.
And now, an emotion
is swirling around
inside him like a
torrential hurricane,
going past the limit.
[NARRATOR]
That emotion... is rage.
[DIMPLE] To think you were
such a powerful esper.
No wonder the smile
mask didn't work.
Didn't work?
So the mask itself
had a trick, too...
I didn't even notice the hex
because it was so weak.
Meh, whatever.
If the policy of your religion
is to kill outsiders,
come at me with
everything you've got.
You might find that task
a hell of a lot easier
than making me laugh.
[DIMPLE] "Come at me with
everything you've got"?
[DIMPLE cackles]
I'm only going to need
about two seconds
to make you disappear, brat!
[DIMPLE]
Emotionless livestock!
Don't act like you're
actually angry!
[DIMPLE grunts]
[DIMPLE]
You should try to cry!
[DIMPLE grunts]
[DIMPLE]
Oh, ho, ho! Flashy.
[DIMPLE yelps]
What the hell?!
I'll be damned, kid.
Never thought I'd
have to fight anyone
with the fullest
extent of my power.
You may be the real thing,
brat, but it's time to die!
What?! No way!
[DIMPLE grunts, yelps]
[groans]
[DIMPLE]
Y-You're...
[MOB] I only allowed them
to come out upon your request.
This is what happens
when I let them show.
These are my
emotions. Satisfied?
[gasps] You some
kind of monster?!
Enough! Wraither Beam!
[DIMPLE]
Yes! A direct hit!
The number of
fights I've endured
is what will decide the
victor and the loser here!
[MOB]
I'm...
...terrible.
[DIMPLE grunts]
So, you wanna be able
to get a clue, huh?
Well, social skills
like that are beyond
your level of comprehension.
Only ones capable of them have
common sense and experience.
And, after all, your whole
existence makes no sense, so...
[sighs]
[ARATAKA]
Hey, come on.
Why are you bummed out
about this now?
Because I'm always
such a downer.
This time, I ruined a whole
bunch of people's fun.
Hah! Who says their
fun has to be the same
as your fun?
Look.
You're the protagonist
of your own life.
I hear what you're saying.
But still, that whole group
is gone now because of me.
And all they were
doing was laughing.
[ARATAKA] Well, your
inability to get a clue
is pretty destructive.
[ARATAKA]
Come on, what happened?
You can tell me all about it.
[LOL WOMAN 3I]
Huh? What were we just doing?
[LOL MAN 3P]
Master Dimple's passed out.
[LOL MAN 3Q]
Did he always look like that?
[LOL MAN 3R]
I seem to remember him
trying to make some boy smile,
but it just wasn't gonna happen.
[LOL MAN 3S]
Yeah...
Who was that kid?
[LOL MAN 3T]
Let's look for him.
He might be the
true messenger of God!
Ah, I see...
Some kind of typical mind
control scheme, huh?
That's not salvation.
He just wanted all of
them to depend on him.
It's a popular con based
on crowd psychology,
usually aimed at
the weak-willed.
But with powers like
yours, it didn't work.
Oh...
[ARATAKA]
Which means you accomplished
something pretty special!
Today, you were able to save
a group of people that only
you could have saved.
So, you should be
proud of yourself.
[MOB'S MOM] Shige, wake up!
You're gonna be late.
[yawns]
[DIMPLE]
Good morning.
Lovely day, isn't it, partner?
[MOB]
Huh?
[ARATAKA] Mob gets dragged
into an idiotic event
run by idiots for idiots.
The one who appears
before him is a violent
yet handsome guy.
What are you gonna do, Mob?!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 4: "Idiots Only Event
Kin."
You're gonna buy the DVD?
That's an excellent decision!