[ISHIGURO] All four of
you are going to hell.
Shige, you're the only one
of us who can stop them!
[TERU] Kageyama!
Use all of your powers!
[MOB]
I can't just let them die.
I have no choice but to
fight with all I've got.
I'm warning you. Don't do it.
When things go south,
it's okay to run away
and save yourself!
[gasps]
[TERU] Damn it! I can't
believe this is happening.
[RITSU]
R-Reigen... He's--
This isn't good.
Stress is about to hit my
brother like a tidal wave.
There's no telling
what'll happen!
[MOB]
Honestly.
I really don't
wanna hurt people.
But if I don't,
we're going to be killed.
So I'm kinda stuck.
I realize that to protect
everyone, I've gotta do it.
Guess that pretty
much sums things up.
Brother...
And yet.
My master told me that
it was okay to run away.
So...
[ARATAKA sighs]
[ALL gasp]
No... Impossible...
Hey, don't scare me like that!
I thought you actually
cut me for a second.
[RITSU] How is he standing?
He was sliced hard!
[ARATAKA] I know you said
that katana was just a toy,
but you really
had me goin' there.
It's nothin' but plastic.
[chuckles]
Pretty sneaky.
Tell me, what kinda
trick did you use
to cut the floor earlier?
[TERU]
Hey, what's going on?
[RITSU] He's acting
like he usually does.
Bastard. How 'bout I just
chop your damn head off?!
[ARATAKA]
Ow!
Listen, real adults don't have
time to play with toy swords
It's time to grow up!
[gasps]
[TERU]
Huh...
Guess I understand how he's
Kageyama's Master now.
[MATSUO]
Sakurai, move!
Candy, attack!
[roaring]
Whoa! An evil spirit?
Hey! Mob! Do something.
That's it?
What a weak-ass punch.
Are you a plushie?
[MATSUO]
Huh?
Eat fist, mascot!
[ARATAKA] Oh, sorry! I didn't
mean to shred your costume!
[RITSU] Reigen is
actually the real deal?
Don't get cocky.
Oh, crap! He's surrounded!
[ARATAKA]
Huh? What was that all about?
Some kinda new 3D
imagery or something?
What was the point?
[MURAKI]
He nullified all of them?
Is he some kind of monster?
[ISHIGURO]
How can this be?
Someone who's this skilled
still exists in this world?
He must be eliminated.
He can't get in the way
of our global domination.
Huh? Oh, I see.
You were using some
kinda magic trick, too.
You guys are total frauds.
Just try that thing with
the black orbs again.
[RITSU]
There's a lot!
[TERU]
Is he gonna be okay?
Leave this to the adult here.
[ARATAKA]
Wow! I'm in great shape today!
[MOB]
Master really is amazing.
[NARRATOR]
"It's okay to run away."
As soon as he heard those words,
the explosive amount of energy
building up to a critical level
within Mob changed
its direction.
There are times when the power
of one's words are unfathomable.
Those with power must
choose to fight.
The thought of
that responsibility
made Mob's bridge collapse.
But sometimes,
one's heart can find
the resolution it needs
just by getting a helping hand.
As a result,
all of Mob's energy
was temporarily tossed
over to Reigen.
In essence, he'd
successfully run away
and was feeling calm
and refreshed.
All that was left in
his heart was gratitude
towards his wise master.
Are these soap bubbles?
[ISHIGURO]
My Black Orbs...
They swallow up and destroy
anything they touch.
And this man is swatting them
away with his bare hands.
How?
What happened to the man
who was trying to run away
just a moment ago?
I'll have to put my body
on the line, too.
Five Hundred Kilogram Tackle!
[ISHIGURO]
One Ton Punch!
Two Ton Guillotine!
[ISHIGURO] You still conscious?
Didn't think so.
No matter how powerful
an esper you are,
you still fall short
of excellence.
You have no desire
for domination.
The reason you're so
powerful yet so unknown
is because you're hiding
your true abilities.
Well, I am different!
I am filled with ambition!
And I'll use my powers
to go higher and higher,
and hold this world in--
Get up. Nobody wants
to hear you monologue.
[gasps]
[ARATAKA]
What a dense energy barrier!
Now I see what happened.
The reason my Black
Orbs burst earlier
was because the energy
they were trying to take in
was way over their limit!
Inconceivable.
Who in the world are y--?
[ARATAKA]
Where are your manners?
When speaking to someone,
you should take off your mask!
Head's up!
Oh, guess it came off.
Anyway, what's with
all this strength?
Could it be Mob's doing?
That's the only
plausible explanation.
[gasps]
Listen, somebody your age should
stop messing around with toys.
What could you possibly know?!
To hell with that!
Don't try and lecture me
about my place in society
when you've only
seen its good side!
When I was born,
my parents abandoned me.
I was all alone.
A big happy family?
Mother's cooking?
I got to experience
none of that as a boy.
At the orphanage, I was
bullied relentlessly.
I cursed the world!
If I hadn't, I wouldn't
have survived!
All that rage and resentment
helped awaken my powers,
and I was able to get
by because of them!
Anyone who rejects my way
of living can just-- Uh!
What's with that face?
Don't look at me like that!
You and I...
we're like brothers.
[SAKURAI]
Wait... He's the same as me?
[ARATAKA] Back when
I was in grade school...
...maybe it was
around fourth grade...
I forgot to tell my parents that
it was sports day at school,
so I was the only one
with nothing to eat.
Sure, that's sad, but
you did it to yourself.
Why bring it up now?
To show our bond of feeling
lonely at times as boys.
[growls]
Don't compare that
stupid story to mine!
Jugan Air Gun!
Behold the ultimate
weapon of destruction.
Die!
If all else fails, I can
still put you to sleep
with this cursed cologne!
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
I don't really get it, but don't
point or spray that at others.
Gimme that.
Huh?
Come on, seriously?
This crap again?
You have all these
psychic powers
and you use them
to do stuff like this?
What a waste.
What'd you say?
[ARATAKA]
It's like you're a little kid
with a knife or something.
I can't bear to watch.
Who do you think you are?
[ARATAKA] What's with all
that stuff on your forehead?
What?! That's, uh--
It's nothing.
You wouldn't get it.
[ARATAKA] And what's with
these goofy things
that look like shoulder pads?
Well, uh-- Those are there
to guard my shoulders.
[ARATAKA] Yeah.
They're fashion accessories.
They don't serve
any real purpose.
[RITSU]
Huh?
[grunts]
[ARATAKA]
You guys just don't get it.
No matter what kind of
special powers you may have,
you're still only human.
No more and no less.
It's the same for everybody.
But somehow, you've
all forgotten that.
You're so addicted to
your special powers,
you've developed tunnel vision.
You want world domination,
but you haven't seen the world!
No one's gonna
follow you knowing that!
Don't make me laugh!
First, get rid of those
ridiculous shoulder pads
and grow up!
You, too! You just wanna
escape from society, right?
If you hope to make it big,
you have to live in reality!
Consider that the
starting point!
You're telling us to
return to being commoners?
What? No way!
You're not getting it!
Why don't you understand this?!
Think about who the hell
you are for a second!
You've always been a commoner!
A cog in the population!
But Claw only allows
the elite espers to--
[ARATAKA]
Look, I'm a commoner!
And I'm much more powerful
than any of you will ever be!
So tell me! What the hell
does that make you?!
[RITSU] He dragged them
out of their delusions
and back into reality.
Shattering their dreams
and putting them in their place.
Your master's amazing!
Yep!
[ISHIGURO]
No!
That is absolutely false!
[ALL gasp]
It's the division leader's face.
Is he really that old?
I actually thought he was
a girl this whole time...
I reject your claims
that deny our greatness!
"You're only human.
No more and no less.
The same as everyone else."
That is what you said, right?
Yeah.
[ISHIGURO] It's not true! And
it's cruel to even suggest it!
We are superior lifeforms to the
rest of the dregs of humanity!
Our powers make us elite!
I'm sure you convinced
yourself of that to go on,
but the truth of the matter is
society really doesn't
care about you either way.
"Society, blah, blah, blah."
No group of average
people is big enough
for a god-among-men like me!
You rely too much on these
espers you've recruited.
The more I think about it,
the sadder I get.
[ISHIGURO] I was born with
these powers, understand?
So what's the problem with
me showing them off?!
What's wrong with
changing the world?!
Stupid ape!
That's how I see you.
No different from a monkey!
It's hard to live!
Surviving's a chore, even
though I'm so special!
It's obvious I'm amazing.
Why won't you just
acknowledge that?
I'm a gift!
This planet should put me
on a pedestal and worship me!
That is the only world
that is worthy of me!
Wrong. Having psychic powers
doesn't make you popular.
See? There you have it.
You'll never be popular.
So give it up.
[growls]
I'm going to erase you all...
Erase this whole building
and start over!
[ARATAKA] Crap.
Looks like I'm outta gas.
Mob, lend me your powers again.
Actually, I'm kinda
tapped out right now.
[ARATAKA yelping]
[ARATAKA]
Oh, no! We're being sucked in!
Disappear! Disappear! Disappear!
You just don't know
when to quit.
Hey, that's--
[ISHIGURO]
Damn it!
I've got enough for you, too!
Disappear!
[SHO] A mass of gravity,
huh? Interesting.
Imagine the gravity
going backward.
[SHO]
As neat as that power is,
that wasn't an
actual black hole.
If it's conceived
from psychic powers,
I can always find a
way to deal with it.
Sorry, Gramps.
But you're no longer needed.
[SHO]
And as for you...
Listen up.
I'm disappointed in you.
You coward.
The 7th Division
will be dissolved.
I was ordered to
inspect the place
and take anyone who seemed
useful back with me to HQ.
What're you talking about?
Weren't you a trainee?
[SHO] Sadly, there wasn't
anyone worth bothering with.
At least... not on the inside.
Well, see ya!
[MATSUO chuckles]
[MATSUO] The evil spirits have
been whittled down to one.
The poison jar has
finally been completed!
Matsuo. We're finished here.
Come out, Marshmallow! Be free!
[sighs]
The hell is that?
Dimple!
I was finally able to get out.
[burps]
[DIMPLE]
All right!
Now that I've consumed
those spirits
and regained some of my
strength, I can help here!
[MOB]
It's already done.
[DIMPLE]
Huh?
You mean the climax
happened without me?
Is this an evil spirit?
[DIMPLE]
Whoa!
How is it that you're
able to see me
when I'm not in
my visible mode?!
They're really strong.
[SAKURAI]
No.
We're weak, plain and simple.
Which leads me to this.
I've realized those guys just
might be able to do it:
Stop Claw from world domination.
[TSUBOMI]
Really? Let me see.
[STUDENT A]
Check it out!
Oh, that looks great!
Let's all go together!
[MOB]
Ah... Tsubomi...
She's as cute as ever today.
[TSUBOMI]
Huh?
[MOB]
Our eyes met!
Stare much, creeper?
Ah! Mezato!
You are such a spaz.
Look, staring at girls
is all well and good,
but today is the day that
you're going to talk to me.
[MOB] The Body
Improvement Club's today.
Fine, I'll just wait for you.
But I've got my job after that.
[MEZATO]
Ugh!
Come on, when're you
gonna tell me everything?
[SHINJI] Your older brother
came by my place last night.
Huh? What did he want?
You must've been
through quite a lot, too.
I think we both
went a little crazy.
I'm done. I'm gonna
apologize to Onigawara.
I'll go with you.
But are you sure about this?
I mean, the entire student
body's gonna hate you.
[SHINJI]
Probably.
But that's my fault for doing
something so stupid.
And now, my brother's on my
side, so I'll keep in line.
It'll be tough,
but it's for the best.
[ONIGAWARA]
What?
So it was you guys who
planted the recorders on me.
That was a crappy thing to do.
And I knew anyway, so it's
not like it really matters now.
Huh?
Wait, what do you mean by that?
[ONIGAWARA]
I mean that people didn't care
whether I was actually
the culprit or not.
They were chomping at
the bit to come at me,
a chance to kick me out.
That's where the problem was.
I realized that I was
hated by everyone,
and how weak my heart was.
It's not the best feeling
in the world, let me tell ya.
Hey.
[RITSU]
Uh?
Your brother was worried
about you, you know.
He thought I was
gonna kick your ass
since I was so pissed off.
But I'll let things slide
since you're the shadow
leader's younger brother.
What's wrong, Onigawara?
You out of energy back there?
Just gimme a damn minute!
I'm still gonna grow,
just like White T
Poison did before me.
[ONIGAWARA]
Body Transformation! Fight!
[STUDENTS]
On!
[ONIGAWARA]
Fight!
[STUDENTS]
On!
[ONIGAWARA]
Fight!
[STUDENTS]
On!
[MOB panting]
[RITSU]
Uh?
That's your older
brother, isn't it?
Is he okay? Seems like
he's about to pass out.
Yeah.
'Cause despite how he might
look, my brother is strong.
Stronger than anybody else.
[SHINJI]
He looks passed out to me.
[RITSU yelps]
Oh, by the way.
Did you give up on your search
to find telepaths, President?
Actually, I haven't
even started yet.
Right now, it's like
a wild-goose chase,
so I'm trying to get
some solid leads first.
It would be nice if you guys
tried to help me out with that.
Well, I did a search on
the internet earlier today,
but I didn't find anything.
You lazy ass! It's not
gonna be that easy!
[MUSASHI]
What's up?
[GUYS]
Musashi!
Seriously, what the heck, Mob?
Did you pass out again?
[TOME]
Inukawa, get some water!
[INUGAWA]
Right. Sure.
[GO]
So what's goin' on?
Why did you insist on
bringing us here again?
I guess you haven't given up
on psychic powers, huh?
Well, I wasn't the one
who requested you.
Actually, it was
for someone else.
[TERU]
Hey, nice to meet you.
So you guys must be the
research subjects here.
[REI]
Whoa. It's another hot guy.
I see.
Your powers are
still kinda weak,
but they're totally
worth nurturing.
Let me introduce
Hanazawa, everyone.
He helped fight the
organization that day.
What do you say?
Do you guys want to train with
me to help you get stronger?
[REI]
Huh?
[TERU] Since one of their
divisions was crushed,
I'm sure Claw will make
a move again soon.
It'll be for self-defense,
so you can fight back
when that happens.
[MITSUURA]
And I'll be here as support.
[TAKESHI sighs]
We should. Kageyama took
all the glory that night.
We barely even helped.
You're right.
Come on guys, let's do this!
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
[ARATAKA] Oh, hey.
So what brings you here?
I'm only here because
Shigeo asked me to come.
He passed out and can't help
with exorcising spirits.
Now that I think about it,
do you even need Shigeo anymore?
You awakened your
psychic powers, right?
Don't be stupid. Everything
you saw was Mob's powers.
The only thing I gained from it
is the ability to see you now.
Otherwise, nothin's
changed at all.
Back to a plain
ol' con artist, huh?
[ARATAKA] You're a rather
rude spirit, aren't you?
Okay. Then come along
and help me out.
The name was Dimple, wasn't it?
Huh? You're kidding me.
Why do I have to help you?
Isn't that the reason he had
you come over to begin with?
If he just wanted to say hi,
he could've simply
called me up.
[DIMPLE]
What? You can't be serious!
Who do you guys think I am?
[ARATAKA]
Well, unless I'm mistaken,
you're Mob's errand boy.
[DIMPLE]
I'm a high-level evil spirit!
[SHO] I'm disappointed in you.
You coward.
[MOB] Did I do something
he thought was lame?
Did I make some kind of mistake?
Really, Shigeo? Again?
I thought I told you to fix
that habit of yours.
Come on, dear,
he's just at that age.
Let him bend all the spoons
he wants. What's the big deal?
[MOB'S MOM] You always
say that, you pushover.
[RITSU]
Here. Let me see it.
What is with these kids?
There. Good as new.
Thanks, Ritsu. Appreciate it.
[MOB] Eh, who cares what
some guy thinks anyway?
[phone ringing]
[SHO]
Oh! I've been looking for you.
Hello? Yeah, I dropped my phone.
The 7th Division?
They were annihilated.
Espers infiltrated the place and
slaughtered the upper echelon.
The division leader, Ishiguro,
went down like a house of cards.
Ha. Oh, and as for
all of the underlings?
The enemy totally appealed
to their emotions
and won them over.
[SHO laughs]
Sho, what're you talking about?
I was asking you for a status
report on the inspection.
The organization
you're so proud of
isn't the best in the
world by a long shot.
Quit messin' around and come
back to Japan already, dad,
you idiot.
[SHO] Makin' me do an
annoying inspection...
I sure told him.
Yes. I'll return very soon.
[REPORTER A]
And now, the local news.
Throughout Seasoning City,
we've gotten reports
of tsuchinoko sightings.
City Hall, in a bid to
reinvigorate the area,
put a bounty on
the tsuchinoko
and is requesting
help in capturing it.
Hey, Mob, are you
free right now?
Meet me here in 90 minutes
in your exercise clothes.
Yeah, something you
can get dirty in.
[ARATAKA] We're gonna
capture a tsuchinoko.
Huh?
Come on, aren't you excited?
[MOB]
Isn't this private property?
[ARATAKA] It's the kind of
place where those suckers
are known to show up.
[MOB] Have you ever seen
a tsuchinoko, Master?
[ARATAKA]
Nope. It's just a hunch.
That's pretty random.
[ARATAKA] Don't you have
any passion for UMAs?
You know, Bigfoot,
Nessie, and tsuchinoko!
From what I understand,
there's a bounty on its head.
Well, there's that, too.
[MOB]
Master, um...
[ARATAKA]
What is it?
[MOB] I don't think amateurs
without hiking experience
should go this deep
into the mountains.
[ARATAKA]
Listen, Mob.
We might be amateurs
when it comes to hiking,
but you have psychic powers.
So to me, that kinda
evens things out.
Add that to my ingenuity,
and we've got a--
Ah! Check it out! Over there!
Get your net ready, Mob!
I knew this place was the
jackpot when we got here!
Huh? You actually found one?
No, it's a matsutake!
It's huge!
[MOB]
Oh...
After all that talk
about passion,
he's already distracted
by the matsutake.
[gasps]
[ARATAKA]
The hell is that?!
Whatever it is, it's starving
and headed right for us!
We're gonna exorcise it, Mob!
Actually, Master, isn't that
the UMA we were looking for?
You idiot! Those
things don't exist!
Quick! Quick! Kill it!
Okay.
[ARATAKA] Amazing. It shrank
so much after you exorcised it.
[MOB] Actually, that's
'cause it threw up a lot.
What the hell was that
thing anyway? So weird.
You already picked that many?
Whatever. Let's go home.
But... the tsuchinoko...
[ARATAKA]
What are you talkin' about?
Those things don't exist.
[ARATAKA] I'm gonna grill
up some matsutake.
[ARATAKA]
You'll have some, right?
[MOB]
Sure.
[ARATAKA] Guess we should
buy some kabosu , too.
[MOB]
Sounds good.