[DIMPLE]
All right. Let's do this...
From here we should split up.
[TERU]
Okay.
[ISHIGURO] There are at least
three intruders in our facility.
Terada and Koyama
have been defeated.
It's time for you,
the Awakened, to shine!
You've endured the trials
of rigorous training
and came out strong.
Now's your chance to show
just how powerful we can be!
[LACKEYS cheering]
[ISHIGURO] Though...
none of you stand a chance.
[LACKEY A]
No way!
So all the Scars were sent
after the intruders?
That's big.
They must be worried.
When are we gonna
get in on the action?
I feel like all we do is lame
grunt work around here.
Just let it go, man.
'Cause those who don't awaken
will always be stuck
at the bottom.
Eventually, we'll end up
subordinates of kids like him.
Ain't that the truth.
Speaking of...
Did you hear about the
kid who was sent here
from HQ as a temp?
From what I understand,
he's an Awakened Child that
they created on their own.
A normal kid survived that
insane awakening experiment
HQ puts them through?
[LACKEY C]
Lucky!
I wanna be in an experiment
for the big-wigs, too.
You wanna die?
Don't even think about it.
The destruction of your mind's
just the beginning
of that torture.
Really? Gen, you know about HQ?
[GEN]
Just stories, mostly.
Heard the trials are so painful
most people don't
make it out alive.
After 20 years as
a lackey around here,
I've learned HQ is bad news.
You don't want nothin'
to do with those guys.
Wait...
Hang on a sec.
What the hell do you think
you guys are doin'?
Should've known it
wouldn't be easy.
[LACKEY D] What happened
to your trainers?!
Took them out.
[LACKEY B]
What?!
Can't believe they were beaten
by a bunch of snot-nosed kids.
We'll take care of--
Let 'em go!
No way! Are you serious?
I wasn't expecting that...
Are you sure?
Yeah. Just go.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[TAKESHI] We aren't gonna get
stabbed in the back, are we?
What the hell?!
Why'd you--?!
[GEN] Shut your mouths,
you youngins!
You don't know anything
about how the world works!
An ESP-er and a normal human
are like night and day.
The difference in strength
is astronomical.
If it's a powerful one,
it's like zero versus ten.
There's no way you can win.
Damn it. If only my powers
had awakened, I could've...
[GEN]
Give it up.
If you don't awaken
the first time around,
there's no hope of it happening.
Ever.
[LACKEY C]
Wait. Seriously?
[LACKEY B] We're gonna
be lackeys forever?!
[LACKEY E] There's no way
you're fine with that, Gen!
[chuckles]
I don't think you kids are
really grasping the situation.
Claw will definitely
rule over this world.
And when they do,
all of us lackeys
who supported them
will be rewarded.
But for right now, we just
need to wait things out.
Until the day the revolution
is finally upon us!
[LACKEYS gasp]
Ah-hah. What do we have here?
From the looks of that door,
I'd say I found somewhere
or something pretty special.
Must be where they're keeping
Ritsu and the others.
[clattering]
[DIMPLE]
Hm?
[LACKEY F]
Uh?
I thought it was one of
the intruders at first,
but it's just security.
What are you
wanderin' around for?
Oh, so that's where I am!
I got a little turned around.
My sense of direction
is just terrible.
Just do your damn job, okay?
Right, sorry about that.
[LACKEY F]
Hmm...
What's over here?
I haven't actually been
inside this room yet.
Maybe I'll just have a peek
as long as I'm down here.
[LACKEY F]
Hold it!
You're lying.
You're an impostor.
[DIMPLE] I'm telling you to let
me see the room, small fries.
This guy's one of the intruders!
Everyone, release your powers!
[LACKEYS screaming]
[DIMPLE]
Whoa.
Individually,
they're no big deal,
but they're not bad
when they work together.
A normal human wouldn't
be able to escape from this.
How long do you think you can
keep this up, tough guy?!
Hey, nice effort.
[ALL gasp]
But you're still outclassed!
[LACKEYS screaming]
Now. Back to the matter at hand.
Let's see what's
goin' on in this room.
Hey, you! Explain this.
Uh. Well, th-this is the
awakening experiments room...
[DIMPLE] These look like
a bunch of torture devices.
[LACKEY F]
Yes...
Our organization discovered
that experiencing pain
is a catalyst to
being awakened.
[DIMPLE] Hmm... Actually,
they're not too far off.
But even after going
through that much pain,
all you guys can
do is momentarily
inconvenience someone.
In the end, the world really
does favor the gifted.
You'll never be A-listers.
You have a better chance
focusing on body building.
[MATSUO]
Is that so?
What do we have here?
It's not every day a ghost
wanders into our facilities.
How would you like
to become my ghost?
I promise I'll take
excellent care of you.
[chuckles]
So you wanna own me, do you?
[DIMPLE] Someone dangerous
just showed up.
Huh?!
You weren't able to find
them in their cage?!
Don't mess with me, punk!
I told you to bring 'em here!
So where are they?!
Well, you see, uh,
from the looks of it,
they got out on their own.
If you're lying to me,
I'll kick your lackey ass!
[LACKEY L]
I'm not lying. I swear!
Okay, then.
[sighs]
[TERU]
Good grief.
[TERU] I don't like imitating
those thugs from the alley,
but it seems to work
well on weaklings.
[LACKEY M]
This isn't over.
You're wide open! Ignite!
Ha, ha! With this flame, I'll--!
[TERU] Can't believe you
thought you could fight me.
Those powers are a joke.
It's funny. Everyone in
Claw seems a little--
[MIYAGAWA]
Aw, did you get burned?
[MIYAGAWA laughing]
[MIYAGAWA] What you're seeing
is true pyrokinesis.
The ability to wield
fire at will.
[TERU]
A Scar...
Are you the brat Koyama
was goin' on and on about?
How pathetic.
I'll turn your body to ash.
[MIYAGAWA]
I know what you're thinking.
"It's okay, my barrier
can withstand this!"
[MIYAGAWA laughing]
[MIYAGAWA]
The inside of your barrier
turns into an
insanely hot sauna.
So much so that your lungs
will burn when you breathe.
A stupid mistake amateurs like
you make time and time again.
[TERU]
You're the amateur here.
[MIYAGAWA]
Big talk, kid.
But in order to fight back,
you'll have to
drop your barrier.
And when you do, you'll
be burned to a crisp.
And if you keep this up,
you'll be steamed.
So that means this
fight is over.
Your options are
either burn to death
or surrender to me and hope--
[TERU]
Bring it on.
[laughs]
[MIYAGAWA]
Sure!
Prepare to die!
Now I won't spare you,
even if you beg me to!
But given how much
heat I'm throwing at you,
your pleading tears
would evaporate anyway!
[laughing]
[screaming]
Ow!
When I switched my barrier over,
my clothes got kinda singed.
It's true that you can't defend
and attack at the same time
with psychic powers.
So the solution was to put
a barrier around my attacker.
Uh? Well, guess
you're not listening.
You're causing a racket,
so I'll let you out.
[TERU]
Wow, that's surprising.
You can still move around
with all those burns?
Who knows?
Maybe people with pyrokinesis
have a higher tolerance to heat.
Either way...
Your arrogance and
lack of flexibility
led to your downfall.
And with that, I'm the winner.
[chuckles]
[TERU]
Whew! Now I'm sweating.
Maybe I was a little scared.
[SAKURAI]
I must say. Well done.
You're much stronger
than I was as a child.
However, I possess
more strength now
than you will have in
your whole lifetime.
It's the end of the road.
Just give up.
[chuckles]
Exaggerate much, buddy?
Oh, hello.
How's it goin' everyone?
So, uh... I'm looking
for my younger brother.
Apparently, he's somewhere
inside this building.
[MUKAI]
Yipee!
My dolls found one!
They found an intruder!
Hey, Tsucchi. Can I do
whatever I want with him?
Yeah, sure. You caught him,
so he's your toy now.
[MUKAI]
Yay!
I'm gonna go have a look!
If I don't hurry,
my dolls will break him
before I have a chance to play!
[TSUCHIYA]
Mukai, the puppet master.
Quite the ability she's got.
She can control all
those wooden dolls
remotely and telepathically,
holding an immortal
army in her hands.
And just look at her, so excited
over finding a new toy.
I wouldn't wanna
get on her bad side.
It's all clear now.
Then let's move. We need to
find the exit, and quickly.
[LACKEY N]
Ah-ha!
Found you, jail-breakers!
Ha! That was easy!
Sorry, you guys. Guess I
picked the wrong route.
No, don't worry.
You did just fine.
We'll force our way through.
Ya think so, brat?!
Now! Combination
Super Psychokine--
[LACKEYS grunting]
Holy crap!
It looks like their espers
aren't really all that strong.
Power-wise, they're all on
the same level as Hoshino.
What's that mean?
They're better off
punching people.
[SHO]
Not bad!
You're right about them
not being strong.
They're useless
as real soldiers.
[RITSU] I don't see a scar like
the trainers talked about.
He's not a part of
the upper echelon.
[RITSU]
Who are you?
Who, me? Wonder who I could be.
Perfect. We're dealing
with a smartass.
We're all in a bit of
a hurry right now.
We can play guessing
games some other time.
[SHO]
Now, now, no need to be so mean.
I thought we could
all be friends here.
This guy seems dangerous.
Agreed. We're finished.
It's okay. You guys
can go on ahead.
Kageyama.
I'll take care of
this one myself.
Hang on! I've got a
bad feeling about this!
Just give it up.
You can't defeat me.
[RITSU]
I don't believe that.
[gasps] Really? Why?
I mean you're not a moron
or anything, are you?
[RITSU]
Maybe...
Or maybe it's 'cause I know
someone stronger than you.
Is that so?
He must be one of the other
intruders, I take it?
Then, I suppose I'll just
have to use you as bait
and bring him out
of the shadows.
[TSUCHIYA grunting]
[MUKAI]
Tsucchi!
[TSUCHIYA]
Oh, Mukai.
You're back from
playtime already?
You're as ruthless as ever.
Wood scraps?
Hey, Mukai. What
happened to your dolls?
[cries]
That boy broke them.
He broke all my lovely dolls!
Leave this to me.
He's mine now.
[MOB]
Hm?
[TSUCHIYA]
Hey, you!
Tell me, are you one
of the intruders?
[TSUCHIYA]
He really is just a kid.
How could he possibly--?
Are you the violent-type
too, old lady?
[gasps]
You brat! Who are
you calling old, huh?!
Tsucchi!
You're not going to stop me
with telekinesis like that!
[ISHIGURO] Her ability
is hardening qigong,
which she uses to divert all of
her qi into her fists or knees
to make them more powerful.
She's a top-class fighter,
even among the Scars.
If she manages to lose,
you might actually have
to step in, Takeuchi.
And take this
intruder seriously.
[yells]
[TSUCHIYA] This could get tricky
if I give him enough time
to attack again.
[TSUCHIYA] These hits aren't
having much of an effect.
Is his qi guard
really that thick?
[TSUCHIYA]
Without any build up?!
[phone ringing]
Hey! Your damn
phone's ringing!
[TSUCHIYA]
Wait a minute. What the--?
You came this far,
so why are you crying?
Because... I really don't
wanna have to beat up a lady
during this rescue.
[MUKAI]
Huh?
[TSUCHIYA]
What did you say?
My master always told me guys
who go around beating up women
are the biggest losers
in the world.
You're quite the gentleman,
but that's an insult.
I'm giving you permission to
fight me fair and square, okay?
Give it everything you've got!
[screaming]
Stay away from me!
[DIMPLE]
Tch.
It sure looks like I drew
the short straw in this one.
[DIMPLE] I've never even
heard of this power.
This human can make evil
spirits his obedient pets.
[MATSUO]
You're good at running away.
But why don't you
leave that body behind?
It'd be easier to
move as a spirit.
[DIMPLE]
Huh?
Are you holding
that man hostage?
Forget him. He's not worth it.
[DIMPLE]
Crap!
[GUM-CHAN roars]
[MATSUO laughing]
[sighs]
[DIMPLE] This body won't
hold up much longer.
Only third-rate spirits
would let the body
they possessed be damaged.
But I have even less of a chance
of beating him in spirit form.
[DIMPLE]
In that case...
What exactly are
you trying to do?
[DIMPLE] I've noticed those
things return to their master
after they attack.
Now why would they be
trained to do that?
Maybe it's 'cause their master
isn't strong enough
to protect himself?
I see right through you!
[yelling]
[MATSUO]
He's fast!
Here, Cookie! Here, Gum!
[COOKIE, GUM-CHAN roar]
[MATSUO]
Now he can't come any closer.
What?!
[MATSUO]
Did he fall?
No, wait! He's not--?!
We can fight some other
time. See ya, dude!
I'm gonna crush you
in the next round!
[growls] Go! After that bastard!
Bring him to me!
He will be mine!
[DIMPLE]
Fooled ya, dumbass!
Oh, man, you fell for that?
[MATSUO]
Crap!
Get back here!
Three seconds should
be plenty of time.
How about a knuckle sandwich?!
[DIMPLE grunts]
[MATSUO]
Not so fast...
You're the one who
underestimated me.
What makes you think I only
have two evil spirits?
[DIMPLE] You mean... all those
around his waist are...?
Crap! There's nowhere to run!
[ISHIGURO] Looks like
Tsuchiya was defeated.
Takeuchi, I'm counting on you.
[TAKEUCHI]
Very well.
No one in the world is a match
for the power of
my super qigong.
I'll win, no matter what!
[ISHIGURO] Takeuchi,
the super qigong user.
His face changes in battle mode.
Even I can't completely
get a read on him.
What do you think?
I was thinking you should
all run away from here.
[ISHIGURO]
Why is that?
[TERU]
Simple. Because I know Kageyama.
[ISHIGURO]
Oh?
Not to mention, it's impossible
to take over the world
with psychic powers.
Use this opportunity to
wake up from that dream.
[ISHIGURO] You won
fighting against Miyagawa.
Why are you wasting your time
living among the normals when
you're such a powerful esper?
[SAKURAI] We are special
beings. And that's a fact.
Not a dream.
Long as you keep
believing that,
you will never be able
to take him down.
[groaning]
[MOB] I know you were trying to
do something, but I'm sorry.
I'm kind of in a hurry.
[MOB gasps]
N-No way...
Is that Ritsu?
What happened?
Oh, he's still breathing.
Thank goodness...
But I don't understand.
Why does my little brother have
to be put through all of this?
I just-- I don't get it.
It's unforgivable.
Well? What's the situation
here, young one?
Hope you haven't already
been defeated by others.
I haven't even used
my powers yet.
[MOB]
Did you do this to him?
[MUTO]
Not hiding your hostility, eh?
In that case,
I'll show you even greater
despair, free of charge.
[MOB]
No...
This... isn't real...
[MOB screaming]
Man, that was a close one.
He managed to amplify
the illusion Muto showed him
and reversed it.
But was it planned
or natural instinct?
[chuckles]
Gotta admit, he's
pretty interesting.
It was totally worth
using his brother as bait
to get him down here.
Not bad you two.
[ISHIGURO]
Out of the 11 Scars,
7 have been defeated
during this intrusion.
How should I explain that
situation to the boss?
[TERU] What's going on?
Kageyama actually lost?
It can't be.
The guy who carried those
two here... did he really--?
Hey, what's up?
It's okay, don't be scared!
[TERU] There's no way he'd
lose to someone like that!
Hi, I'm back! What's up?
Seems you captured
the others, too.
You look pretty happy.
[MATSUO]
Yes.
One of the intruders
is an evil spirit
who has a very strong ego.
[TERU]
They got Dimple, too?
This poison jar has hundreds of
evil spirits thrown inside it.
The one that survives
after viciously attacking
and devouring the others
becomes the ultimate pet.
What in the hell is this place?
No, wait! Stop it!
Let's talk about this! W-Wait!
You don't wanna eat me!
I have no nutritional value!
Help me, please!
I see it! There's the exit!
[GO]
Now we can call for help!
Wait! Stop, it's no use.
We've got a problem here.
What's wrong, Hoshino?
Damn! There's no way
we can get through that!
Wait a second, they're--!
What the--?
Did someone important
show up or something?
[gasps]
[TAKESHI]
That aura...
[GO]
Holy crap! Even I can feel it.
It's an insanely
powerful esper!
No way, it can't be.
There's only one person
with those powers.
[KAITO]
And that would be their leader.
[GROUP]
Claw's boss!
[ARATAKA] The boss of Claw
finally shows himself.
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry I kept this hidden
from you so long, Mob.
No matter what happens
from now on,
live your life to the fullest.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 11: "Master Leader."
The serious option C?
An excellent decision.