[RITSU]
Wow!
Feels neat!
Hey, do you think I'll
be able to do this, too?
[MOB]
Mh-mm!
Of course. After all,
you're my little brother!
[gasps]
[RITSU]
He! Hoo! Ha!
[RITSU grunting]
[ARATAKA]
Everything's ready.
We will now begin the séance.
[gulps]
--[ARATAKA grunts]
--[HITOSHI yelps]
Hey, tell me, is that you, Dad?
Do you know who I am?
Oh... Oh! Hitoshi!
I never thought
the day would come
when I would have the chance
to see your face
again, my son.
Oh, Dad.
One thing...
When did you learn to
speak English so well?
Click! Loggin' out for a sec.
Huh?
[ARATAKA] Sorry, It doesn't
seem like I'm getting
a very good signal.
Were you satisfied, though?
Of course not!
Please, call him
back this instant!
[ARATAKA]
Whoa! Calm down, buddy!
It takes a lot of concentration
to head up a séance.
By the way, where is
your father from?
He wasn't local?
No, he was from
New Jersey in America.
[ARATAKA] Foreign languages
are automatically translated.
Oh!
It's an advanced
technique that does
something-or-other
to the wavelength
of the spirit's languages
and is hard to master.
But, don't worry, there will
not be an additional fee.
Amazing! But my
English isn't bad.
I'm pretty fluent.
Now, then...
Oh! Hey, Hitoshi!
How have things been goin'?
Kinda weird, but...
Whatever.
Hey, Dad. Ya know
when I was young?
You and I used to
play ball together.
And we did that one thing that
was popular on TV back then!
Would you do it for
me one last time?
[HITOSHI]
Dad?
Uh... What the heck was that?
That was the
"Cheeseburger Tornado,"
the main character's
special move in
"Junk Food Fighter Michael,"
the super popular
show at the time.
[HITOSHI] Wait...
Dad, what are you talk--?
Get to the point, Hitoshi.
I've come all the way
from the other side.
What do you want?
Well, I...
Aw, screw it!
You were never nice
to me, anyway, Dad!
Cough up the password
to the hidden safe,
you stupid old man!
I know there's
a fortune in there!
You're dead so
you don't need it!
Uh, let me see...
I believe the password
was my birthday.
Don't give me that
"birthday" crap!
It's thirteen letters
of the alphabet!
With that kind of money,
I'll have enough cash
for the rest of my life!
Oh! Wait a second,
now I remember!
The password is...
"GETAJOBYOUGOODFORNOTHINGBUM"!
[NARRATOR]
Like the Junk Food Fighter,
this is one of
Reigen's special moves:
using his body like a spring,
he smashes his fist
into his opponent's face
with a powerful spin.
[HITOSHI yelps]
Crap! I went too far!
The client's consciousness
logged out!
What happened?
Did you just take him down?
[ARATAKA] Yeah... But,
it was all in self defense.
Self defense, huh?
[ARATAKA]
Yep. Hey, you look kinda pale.
[MOB] If it's in
self defense, is it okay
to shave off someone's hair,
rip off their clothes,
destroy their pride,
make them lose their friends,
and completely demolish
the school they go to?
[ARATAKA] I think that's going
a bit beyond "self defense."
There are some times
when my psychic powers
go outta control.
And it always seems to happen
when I'm unconscious.
I don't want these
powers anymore.
It's too much.
If nothing else, I think
they're quite useful.
The way you use them when you
work as my apprentice?
So many clients have been
helped with those powers.
So don't just focus
on the negatives.
It's all about how you
use those knives, right?
Don't suppress yourself.
You hold the keys, here.
Maximize your potential.
You do that,
and you're gonna
be just fine, Mob.
[MOB sighs]
[SALT GANG 4C]
Huh?
The shadow leader
system? Seriously?
[ONIGAWARA]
Yeah.
I completely lost
to that shadow leader
named Hanazawa, but the
guy who bested him
is from Salt Middle School.
[SALT GANG 4B]
No way! Someone that strong?
Yeah.
I'm gonna find him and
make him our shadow leader.
It was you, wasn't it?
You caused the supernatural
stuff at Black Vinegar.
Uh, well, I--
[MEZATO]
You're basically the only person
who could do
something like that.
But according to the rumors,
a kid who goes there
can throw people around
just as easily as you do.
Who knows?
Maybe that means
he's an esper, too.
You guys met up at Black Vinegar
and fought, didn't you?
That's it, right?
You two had a
psychic-telekinetic battle!
[TOME]
Twitch, twitch.
You don't wanna talk about it?
That's enough for today, then.
But someday soon, you're
definitely gonna tell me
all I wanna know.
[sighs]
No way!
That wasn't the work of aliens?
And, that aside...
...are there really
espers around here
other than yourself?
Yes, there are.
[TOME chuckles]
[TOME]
And you can find them.
But... He's the only
other one I've ever met.
[TOME] That's strange.
What about your master?
Ah...
Well, actually, I don't sense
anything from my master.
But that's 'cause his
powers aren't psychic,
they're spiritual.
[TOME]
What kind of rule is that?
Well, whatever. Let's go
on a date after this.
[MOB]
Huh?
We'll find other
telepathic people!
Then take our first
step toward connecting
with life forms in outer space!
Think about it!
But, remember?
I'm not in the Telepathy Club.
Black Vinegar Middle
School's shadow leader?
Yeah, I lost to him.
That guy had some
seriously nice muscles.
Then who was it that beat him?
It was someone from the
Body Improvement Club, right?
He's a gentleman who usually has
quite a distaste for violence.
Do not involve him
in this. Be gone.
Damn that Musashi.
Huh?
Hey...
[gasps] Um, yes?
You were picked on by the guys
from Black Vinegar Middle
School last week, right?
Well, that was all my fault.
Sorry, okay?
Huh? What do you...
I apologized! Just
leave it at that!
I'm sorry, Kageyama.
Tenga's kind of a dummy.
He can't explain things--
[ONIGAWARA]
Shut up!
Stupid idiot!
I'm the one talking to him,
so just stay out of it!
[TOKUGAWA]
Well, then...
It appears that will be all
the student council's
activities for this month.
Is that all right,
President Kamuro?
[SHINJI]
I'm glad you asked.
It's not bad for a start,
but I think we need
something with
a bit more impact.
Right, first year Kageyama?
[gasps]
You rank as one of the
smartest in the nation,
so I want to hear your opinion.
[RITSU]
Well...
In our school, there
are a few students
who would be classified
as delinquents.
If the student council
could find a way
to reprimand them, I think
we'd be able to create
a more peaceful
school environment.
That sounds nice.
"A more peaceful school."
Yes. Let's do that.
[RITSU] I have to make it
a more comfortable place
for my brother.
[MITSUURA]
Kageyama, I presume?
Thank goodness.
Guess there was a point
in waiting around after all.
Let me present my credentials.
[RITSU]
Awakening Lab?
[MITSUURA]
So, what do you think?
Why not give it a try?
This is an opportunity to
amplify your psychic powers
at my research facility!
[RITSU] Sounds like he's got
me confused with my brother.
Ah! Tome, take a look--
What is it? Another esper?!
[MOB]
No, I just thought this guy
had a really unique hairstyle.
Oh, wow! You're so right.
Stop fooling around already.
[MOB]
But... I was being serious.
[TOKUGAWA]
Oh, it's you, Kageyama.
Ah, Vice President Tokugawa.
[TOKUGAWA]
Loitering, huh?
I guess even people like you
feel like doing that
from time to time.
Like me?
I'm just an average
middle school student
you can find anywhere.
A totally simple and normal guy.
If you ask me, you won't find
a "totally simple" and
"normal" middle schooler
anywhere on this planet.
But, for whatever reason,
you want to be one and are still
trying to act out the part.
I'm not really sure I
understand what you're saying.
[TOKUGAWA] Despite having
abilities that would
always make you the
center of attention,
you consistently seem
to play the minor role
and let others
take the spotlight.
[TOKUGAWA]
Stop acting like your brother.
Hey, Captain! Kageyama's down!
[gasps] No, I'm fine.
Nice drive!
I think you're starting
to build up some stamina!
[RITSU]
Awakening Lab...
This place?
It's just an apartment complex--
Kageyama, you're here!
I'm so glad you showed up!
There's no research
facility here.
You lied to me!
[MITSUURA]
Now, now, just come in.
Welcome!
[MITSUURA]
I call it the Awakening Lab!
[RITSU]
What is this place?
[MITSUURA]
I bought an apartment complex
and remodeled it.
I've hired the front
runners in the fields
of neuroscience and engineering,
and we do research here.
On the floor above us,
all of the other
esper kids are gathered.
Did you say others?
Yeah, other people,
just like you.
Look there.
Is it another weird haircut?
[MOB]
That's an adult esper.
[MOB] What is this
feeling coming over me?
It's kind of sickening.
Sorry, Tome. I was wrong again.
Hey, Mob. Take a look!
Isn't that hairstyle
super weird?
[MITSUURA]
Allow me to introduce them!
Standing before you is a group
of real espers that
the Mitsuura Group
worked hard to bring together!
First is Takeshi Hoshino.
Step back, I'm going all out!
He's psychokinetic!
[RITSU]
That's "amazing"?
[MITSUURA]
Next, we have Rei Kurosaki.
[MITSUURA] Her powers
of clairvoyance allow her
to pick the one
correct card out of ten!
Her efficiency rate is
a staggering 62 percent!
Yay! I was right again!
[RITSU]
Wait, that's it?
[MITSUURA]
Next, we have Go Asahi.
Behold, my flames
of fury! Ignite!
Huh?
Ignite! Ignite!
Ig-- There we go!
Oh, it went out.
He uses pyrokinesis.
[RITSU] Less useful
than a cheap lighter.
[MITSUURA] And here are
the Shiratori brothers:
Daichi and Kaito.
They're telepaths who can use
their power to communicate
with each other,
even when they're apart.
[RITSU]
And less useful than email.
[MITSUURA]
This is Shigeo Kageyama.
Now be nice to him, everyone.
It's a pleasure.
Nice to meet you.
Tell me...
Has Mitsuura helped you at all?
Well, yeah, what kind of
question is that?
[TAKESHI] Absolutely.
He's been good to us.
And he's really fascinated
with psychic powers.
Huh?
Though I'm wealthy,
it's just family money,
I did nothing to earn it.
I'm nothing special.
I don't believe
in doing anything
to make big advancements
in society or science.
I just want to become
an esper myself,
so I funded this
research facility to see
if I could make it happen.
That's the reason!
[RITSU] It's a childish
pipe dream, but if he's able
to achieve that goal,
I'd be interested.
I've always wanted to know
if there's power within me.
[SHINJI'S MOM] Well, you're
finally home, Shinji.
Student council again, huh?
Make sure you don't
fool around too much.
[gasps]
[SHINJI] My brother was
the student council president,
too, remember?
[SHINJI'S MOM]
But, unlike you, Takuya was also
good in his studies.
[TAKUYA] Exactly, Mom.
I'm embarrassed, Shinji.
[TAKUYA] You haven't even
hit a test score of 70 yet!
Are you really
my younger brother?
You have no talent at all.
So you became the student
council president, right?
You should have plenty
of time to study.
How much are you going to
disappoint Mom and Dad, anyway?
Elites like--
[MOB'S MOM]
Ugh, you really need to fix
that annoying habit of yours.
[MOB]
But it just bends on its own.
Ha, ha! My farts
bend things, too!
Oh, come on!
Stop that! We're eating dinner!
Shige, you should really
try to be more like Ritsu.
[MOB]
Yeah, I know.
Ritsu doesn't do any
weird stuff like me.
And he's super talented.
Kageyama. Good morning.
President, what's
going on, exactly?
And, why did you wanna
meet me here so early?
[SHINJI] See this?
It's a girl's recorder bag.
And what would you
presume is inside of it?
[RITSU]
A girl's recorder, I guess?
That's correct.
Okay...?
[SHINJI]
She won't be needing this...
President...
What do you think you're doing?
The answer's simple.
Why, a little spring
cleaning, of course.
Spring cleaning?
You said it yourself,
didn't you?
There are trashy students here
who're classified
as delinquents.
The student council needs
to get rid of them.
[RITSU]
Hey, hold on!
I never said
anything that extreme.
Don't twist my words around--
[SHINJI]
What do we have here, Kageyama?
I believe it's the
desk of our school's
biggest piece of trash...
Onigawara, the thug delinquent.
[gasps] Are you
serious, President?
Why would an elite like
you ever stoop to that?
[SHINJI]
"An elite", you say...
That's just an imaginary persona
I was labeled with
somewhere along the way.
You've realized it,
too, haven't you?
That the praise others
lavish upon you
doesn't actually fit
who you really are.
[gasps]
[SHINJI]
Come on. Help me, Kageyama.
You got another perfect
score on your test?
Good job!
[RITSU]
I-I'm...
Ritsu doesn't do any
weird stuff like me.
And he's super talented.
Stop acting like your brother.
[RITSU]
Even I...
[RITSU] Hey... do you think
I'll be able to do this, too?
[MOB]
Mm-hm.
[gasps]
Of course!
After all, you're
my little brother!
[RITSU]
Really?
Yay! I can't wait!
[STUDENT 6A]
Huh?
[panting]
[MUSASHI] All right,
we made it to our goal.
You got some good muscles
on you, Onigawara.
[panting] Damn it.
You called me out
here super early,
so I thought you were
finally gonna tell me
who the shadow leader is!
Remember this pain.
You may feel wrecked now,
but you'll feel amazing later.
The one you're looking for
is in the same state as you.
He's fighting with himself.
So you should change in the
same way he's hoping to.
[laughs] All right, fine!
Bring it on, dude!
[STUDENT 06N]
Something weird happened!
[STUDENT 06C]
Whoa, that's creepy!
[ALL shouting]
We're so grossed out,
how are we supposed to
stay in class with that?!
Now, now, please calm down.
I promise, the student
council will find
the culprit and put
a stop to all of this.
[whispering] Now's the time
to open up Onigawara's desk.
We'll have to inspect
everyone's belongings.
If they get caught like this,
they must be pretty stupid.
Oh, the teacher's not here yet?
[ONIGAWARA]
I was about to ruin my record
of never being late or absent.
What's the matter, Onigawara?
You seem out of breath.
Huh? What's Kamuro doing here?
What's going on anyway?
Did something happen?
[RITSU]
I found them.
They were all inside
Onigawara's desk.
Huh? Who are you?
Why are you going
through my stuff?
It was you! Don't deny it!
Deny what? What are
you talking--?
Pervert.
Who the hell just said that?!
What is this?
Wanna tell me exactly what
you found in my desk?
Every one of the girls'
missing recorder pieces
all stashed away
in your desk drawer.
You were going to lick them
to get your sick kicks
when no one was looking!
You're a pervert, Onigawara!
[ONIGAWARA]
What?
Kamuro, don't make me punch you!
[SHINJI] There's still time
to redeem yourself!
Apologize!
Seriously, what kind of
sicko crap is this?
Do I really look like someone
who'd do something like that?
You're violent with other people
and act like a low-life thug.
That's reason enough for
anyone not to trust you.
Now just hold on a minute!
It wasn't me, I tell ya!
Look, if I really wanted
to lick those things,
I'd take them out of the school!
Only a complete idiot would
leave them in his desk.
Well, you are
a complete idiot...
Stop trying to pin this
crap on me, Kamuro!
I didn't do it!
[RITSU]
There were some in his bag, too.
Take a look.
Guess he did take a few
of them out of school.
[ONIGAWARA]
My school bag...
I left it wide open
in my locker.
[SHINJI]
Nice, Kageyama!
You even put some in his bag!
You're into this.
You bastard!
Stop snooping around in my bag!
[RITSU]
Violence, huh?
[STUDENT 06H]
Let him go!
[STUDENT 06J]
Poor Kagayama!
[STUDENT 06M]
So violent!
[STUDENT 06L] ...it's Tenga
the Recorder Licker!
[STUDENTS chanting]
Pervert! Pervet! Pervert!
Screw you guys! All of you!
Run, everyone!
The perv's lost his temper!
[STUDENTS scream]
[ONIGAWARA]
No...
No! I didn't do it!
Isn't...
Isn't there anybody
who'll take my side?
[MARIKO]
Guess what?
[gasps]
[MARIKO] One day, we're
gonna get married, Tenga!
That'll never happen!
Don't be stupid!
[ONIGAWARA]
That's right... Mariko!
You believe me...
Don't you? Say something!
So gross!
[ONIGAWARA groans]
--[VOICE 06A] Oh, yeah!
--[yelps]
[screams]
Get away from me, you pervert!
[NARRATOR]
On this day, after two years
of hard work and dedication,
Tenga Onigawara's
perfect attendance record
was finally broken.
[MITSUURA]
What's the matter?
Now, don't let it get you down.
I mean, everyone has
bad days now and then.
[SHINJI]
Did you see his face, Kageyama?
He didn't even know
how to handle something
he couldn't fight
his way out of!
He just stood there
like an idiot!
[SHINJI cackling]
He's finished!
What happened to me?
What am I doing?
[RITSU]
I'm going home.
Huh?
[RITSU] I don't actually
have psychic powers.
--Oh, come on...
--[door slams]
Hey!
Kageyama, wait!
[ARATAKA]
Hey...
If it isn't Mob's
little brother.
[ARATAKA] I see you're giving
me the cold shoulder, as usual.
So what are you
wandering around
near my house for?
It's for a job.
I got a request to
exorcise a creepy ghost
that's been showing
up in this area.
Ya wanna help me out with it?
Don't waste your breath.
Unlike Shigeo, I don't have
any special psychic powers.
Really, are you sure?
I figured since Mob's your
older brother and all...
[RITSU]
You figured wrong.
Why don't you get rid
of that ghost yourself?
Aren't you a psychic?
He quit by throwing a
spoon instead of a towel?
[laughs] He's got quite
the sense of humor,
I'll give him that much.
But, when it comes to talent,
he doesn't exactly seem blessed.
Actually, you might be wrong.
Take a look.
[RITSU]
Hm? What's that?
It's not a balloon. What is it?
[ARATAKA]
Ritsu continues to go wild
by pairing up with Dimple.
And then the gang leader
alliance makes its move.
Meanwhile, some scary people
try to make Mob buy a vase.
Both brothers are
in huge trouble!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 7: "Exaltation
I've Obtained Loss."
Illegal downloads?
You're gonna be cursed.