[ONIGAWARA yells]
[STUDENTS groan]
[STUDENT 4C] The guys from
Salt are crazy strong!
You must be Salt Middle School's
"Tenga the Demon"!
Come on, that all ya got?
'Cause my buddies and me were
just gettin' warmed up.
[EDANO]
Aw, crap!
[STUDENT 4D]
The shadow leader!
[STUDENT 4E]
Somebody get Teru!
Huh?
[BV GANG gasps]
[STUDENT 4F]
Whoa...
[STUDENT 4G]
That's Teru for ya.
[STUDENT 4H] Yeah, but isn't
this kinda overkill?
[TERU]
It had to be done.
They had the nerve
to stand up to me.
If you show a pack
of idiots like these
you're out of their league,
they'll suddenly
bow down to you,
like completely
different people.
The same way that
all of you guys did.
[TERU] Not to mention,
it's never a bad idea
to have a bunch of
fools indebted to me.
[TERU] Be it through power
or through people:
I'm going to take advantage
of everything I can.
After all, I'm the main
character in this world.
[MOB'S MOM] Shige, wake up!
You're gonna be late.
[yawns]
[DIMPLE]
Good morning.
Lovely day, isn't it,
aye, partner?
Surprised?
Well, you know what they say.
"Yesterday's enemy could
be today's friend."
Hm? You wanna shake?
[DIMPLE yelping] What are
you doing? Stop! Wait, wait!
Hold on!
Y-You startled me!
Wh-What was that for?!
Wanted to make sure
I wasn't dreaming.
When you think that,
you're supposed
to pinch your own cheek!
Not slam me around!
Who are you?
Who? It's me, Dimple!
The religious group guy!
Come on, we had that fight
to the death yesterday?
[MOB] So, you didn't
completely disappear.
No! Wait! H-Hear me out!
I don't plan on living
out the rest of my life
as some spirit blob!
But aren't you already dead?
[DIMPLE]
Easy, Shige...
You're not supposed to go there.
An idol! A pro baseball player!
A movie star!
Everybody out there
has some kind of dream!
And I have an ambition, too.
To stand tall at the
top of all creation...
Basically...
God's my dream!
I fantasize about the day
I finally become God!
Oh...
That's why you made that
religious organization.
[DIMPLE]
Though it was destroyed.
But that taught me
an important lesson.
In order to gain command
over people's hearts,
one must show off some
strong psychic powers.
So what do ya say?
Team up with me!
Let's shoot for the top
of the world together!
Do you have any
more final words?
[DIMPLE yelps]
Seriously--have some
compassion, will ya?!
I don't wanna leave just yet.
Please!
I won't do anything bad anymore!
Really? You promise?
Really! I promise!
[MOB]
All right.
I'll discuss it with my master.
Just don't do anything
weird here, at home,
or at my school.
[DIMPLE]
Heh. Talk about a softy.
I'll just bide my time and wait
for my chance to possess him.
Hey, Shige?
Mom says to hurry up
and eat breakfast.
Right. Coming.
Were you just
talking to somebody?
[MOB]
Nope, not me.
Okay, well... Anyway, hurry up.
[MOB]
Sure.
Your brother seems like
a totally cool guy, Lil' Shige.
My name's Shigeo, understand?
Call me "Little Shige"
again and I'll exorcise you.
[DIMPLE] Whoa! My bad!
Sorry about that, Shigeo.
[DIMPLE]
Just as I discovered yesterday,
it's hard to read
what Shigeo's thinking.
I must study his
personal and social life
if I ever hope
to figure him out.
If all goes well,
he could start to see me
as someone who
truly understands him.
Who knows?
Maybe he'll eventually
start relying on me.
[MEZATO]
Hey, you there...
You're Ritsu Kageyama from
Year 1, Class 3, right?
Yeah?
I'm Mezato, Year 2, Class 1,
from the school paper.
Do you have a few minutes?
[RITSU] You're in the same
class as my brother.
If you wanna know about
his psychic powers,
you should ask him yourself.
Aw, come on. Gimme a break.
Got something interesting
to tell you, too.
What do you mean?
Did something happen to Shige?
[ARATAKA] I accept
this spectral challenge.
I will exorcise the evil spirit
haunting the confines
of this photo.
And I'll need about two
hours to perform the rites.
[yelling]
[ARATAKA]
Graphic Exorcism!
[NARRATOR] This is one of
Reigen's special moves,
editing photos
with CG software...
[ARATAKA yells]
[NARRATOR] ...making them
look perfectly natural.
[ARATAKA]
Aw, crap!
I accidentally erased
the client's eyebrow, too!
Master.
[ARATAKA] Mob? I'm a
little busy right now.
Gimme a sec.
Wait. That's your master?
[MOB]
Yep.
He's Master Reigen,
a powerful psychic.
[DIMPLE]
You can't be serious...
[MOB]
What do you mean?
[DIMPLE] I don't feel
any spiritual power
coming from this guy at all.
That idiot Shigeo is totally
getting used by him.
I could let him know, but...
Nah, this is fine.
I'm sure I'll find
a way to make use
of this knucklehead, too!
[ARATAKA]
There we go. All done.
Master, I've had this
spirit stuck to me
since this morning.
What do you think
I should do with it?
Maybe erase it, or...?
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
Uh...
[DIMPLE] Heh. You won't be
able to see me, ya fake.
Must be too weak
for me to see it.
[DIMPLE]
What?!
To put it in perspective,
it'd be about the same
as a ladybug on your shoulder.
Do whatever you want.
Lucky you.
Now, don't cause any harm
and I won't erase you.
[RITSU] There's nothing
that triggered it.
He's always had psychic powers.
He was born with them.
As far back as I can remember,
my brother has been causing
strange phenomena to happen.
To me, Shige... was the
standard of the world.
Huh?
[RITSU] Even so, he
hasn't used his powers
in front of others
in a long time.
What happened to him, anyway?
[MEZATO chuckles]
Oh, that.
Your brother's caused
quite a stir...
Hey, that kinda looks like you.
I don't see it.
[DIMPLE]
Oh. That phone number...
Oh, I see...
Now my brethren are seeking
spiritual leadership
from Shigeo.
Are they quick to jump on
the next bandwagon or what?
[MEZATO]
Mob's hidden charisma managed
to bring out quite a bit of
adoration from a lot of people.
Pretty suddenly, too.
So much so that it
formed a new religion.
And I'm here telling
you about all this
because I think he
deserves more recognition.
With that in mind,
I'd like an exclusive
from your point of view--
Sorry, Mezato,
but I must decline.
My brother's powers aren't
some sideshow circus act.
[gasps] No, that's
not what I meant.
Well, yeah, maybe it is.
But he could get
really popular and...
[RITSU] All right, then.
I'll be going now.
[MEZATO]
Ritsu Kageyama...
His grades are at
the top of his class.
He's an attractive,
popular guy who's also great
at lots of different sports.
He's pretty much got
everything that Mob doesn't.
Jeez...
Despite what the-powers-that-be
want us to believe,
people really aren't
born equal at all.
[RITSU] Shige made my
whole world seem normal.
Psychic powers were a perfectly
ordinary existence for me.
Because I'm his little brother,
I thought that I'd be
able to use them, too.
That's what I wished for.
"Charisma"? Who cares?
"Popularity"? Give me a break!
Compared to psychic powers,
those qualities are cheap!
[MOB]
I'm leaving now.
[RITSU]
Hey, wait up. I'll go with you.
Wow, this is rare.
You usually leave early.
[RITSU] Well, there isn't
a student council meeting
this morning. Also, I wanted to
talk to you about something.
He seems to be
pretty close to you.
I was wondering...
You don't use your
psychic powers very often.
Why is that?
Well, Don't always
have the chance.
That's where you're wrong!
There are plenty of
opportunities, dude!
I guess there isn't anything
you really want, then.
[MOB]
No...
It's just that using my
powers for everything
would be pointless.
Huh?
Having them is
kinda weird, anyway.
I mean, it's not like
they're needed for survival.
They're awesome!
You're the only one
who thinks that!
Using them isn't pointless!
You just don't realize
how useful they are!
What do you mean?
You're saying there're
things you can't have,
even if you use your powers?
That's not true at all!
You can even become G-O-D!
Muscles.
[DIMPLE]
What is he talking about?
[MOB] Or understanding
girls, knowing what to do
in social situations,
reading my surroundings.
I think there's even more--
like wisdom.
And, for that,
I envy you, Ritsu.
[gasps]
[MOB]
Yeah... Like this, for example.
Psychic powers can't even
help me solve math problems.
[groans]
[DIMPLE] If those powers of his
belonged to someone else,
we would've seen something
completely different
in this world.
What did you want with the Body
Improvement Club, anyway?
This is no place for a
bunch of delinquent thugs
like all of you guys.
Unlike the lot of you
with no ambition,
wasting your little lives away,
we try to better
ourselves, Onigawara.
Yeah? What about those
guys over there?
[MUSASHI] You wanna talk?
Let's go outside.
[ONIGAWARA]
He totally dodged the question!
[ONIGAWARA] I'll keep this
short and to the point.
You guys in the
Body Improvement Club
are the strongest dudes
in Salt Middle School.
I'm here to ask you
to brutally take down
those guys from Black
Vinegar Middle School!
Listen, this is lower-body
strengthening month,
so we don't have any time.
We are way too
busy doing squats.
Squats?! Are you kidding me?
What are you--?!
Fighting's dumb, okay?!
We don't spend hours
a day honing our bodies
and strengthening our muscles
for something so petty!
[SALT GANG gasps]
What did you say?!
[yells]
[groans]
Say no to violence.
[ONIGAWARA] He stopped
Yamazaki with one hand...
With these musclebound
freaks on our side,
we'd definitely be able to win!
[ONIGAWARA]
Uh... What?
That one guy obviously
hasn't improved his body...
[cackles]
Shigeo, you aren't
actually aiming
for this mindset, are you?
[WEATHER WOMAN 4A] And now
for a look at today's weather.
Although many areas across
the country will be sunny,
there's some instability
in the atmosphere.
This brings a higher chance
of thunderstorms and high winds.
So, if you're going out,
it may be a good idea...
[ONIGAWARA]
Gotta fight poison with poison.
Here's the plan...
Salt's extraterritoriality,
the Body Improvement Club,
will fight against
Teruki Hanazawa,
Black Middle School's
shadow leader!
I kinda know what you mean,
but you've got
that saying wrong.
And the Body Improvement Club
isn't really poison.
Plus, "extraterritoriality"
makes no sense here--
I think you just wanted
to say that to sound smart.
That word and that "poison"
phrase came up in class, too.
Guess Tenga's actually
payin' attention.
Who'd of thought?
That dummy--
[ONIGAWARA yells]
[growls]
[SALT GANG 4A]
There it is! Demon Rush!
Tenga's special move
of repeated punches!
It's legendary!
Rarely seen by the human eye!
[SALT GANG 4B]
Though it becomes less rare
if he just uses it
whenever, like now!
[SALT GANG 4C groans]
[SALT GANG 4A]
You really are amazing, Tenga!
[MOB]
This is...
What does this say?
"Abhore"?
Did I offend somebody?
It's probably a love letter.
They spelled "adore" wrong.
Adore? Wha--?!
Though the whole thing
is definitely fake.
[MOB]
Huh?
This is a lie?
[DIMPLE] That's an angry
guy's handwriting.
It's clearly a fake love letter.
You're so unpopular,
you don't realize it.
[MOB]
It's not real, then?
Just let it go, Shigeo.
Just let it go.
[MOB]
A lie...
[EDANO]
We received a challenge.
The only person I
know with handwriting
anywhere near this
bad is Onigawara
from Salt Middle School.
He doesn't give up, does he?
[BV GANG 4A] Uh, what does
"you rice bastards" mean?
Think he meant to write
"you rat bastards."
[BOTH] You're so smart,
Edano! Way to go!
No, it's just that
Onigawara's stupid.
[ALL laugh]
My plan is so perfect
that I scare myself
with my own genius brain.
Now we wait for them
to take the bait,
and make our move.
I'm sure the guys from
Black Vinegar Middle School
will be there,
but will the guy from the
Body Improvement Club show up?
He might think
it's just a prank.
[ONIGAWARA]
Oh, no, he'll fall for it.
I wrote "I'm a girl"
on it to seal the deal.
And I added a heart!
[SALT GANG 4B] A girl
wouldn't write "I'm a girl."
[SALT GANG 4C] Seriously,
no one's gonna fall for that.
[NARRATOR]
But he did.
Seriously...
Well, you know,
if a girl is actually
waiting here, I'd feel bad.
[DIMPLE]
I told you, that's a fantasy!
You sure about doing
this by yourself?
You didn't even
tell the muscle guys.
[MOB] We're supposed to
train on our own today.
[EDANO]
Hey.
[MOB gasps]
You're from Salt Middle
School, aren't you?
[MOB, DIMPLE]
Huh?
Captain Musashi,
there's trouble!
I found this under a dumbbell.
Kageyama's been kidnapped!
[growls]
[MUSASHI] We're goin' to
Black Vinegar Middle School
to get Kageyama back!
[STUDENT 4J]
Finally, just the two of us.
So what do you wanna do?
What do you wanna do?
Well, maybe we can
go to a café...
[phone chimes]
Tch.
Shigeo, do you know
any of these guys?
Nu-uh, not a one.
Know what's happening here?
Uh, nope, not at all.
No matter what,
your submissiveness
doesn't go away, does it?
For the guy that Onigawara
called in to help,
he seems pretty quiet right now.
You're Kageyama, aren't you?
Sorry about this, but we've
got a reputation to uphold.
No hard feelings, but we're
gonna have to take you hostage.
He's the one.
Looks like you were tricked
by that Onigawara guy, Shigeo.
Tough break...
We've already told Onigawara.
If he wants his friend
back in one piece,
then he needs to come
get you himself.
When it comes down to it,
I'd say you're
screwed either way.
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo.
If there's one thing
thugs and politicians
care about more than anything,
it would be their image.
Get ready.
Make sure that you're prepared
to release your powers
at any time.
'Member the rule?
"Don't use psychic powers
against other people."
[DIMPLE] Ugh! He's always
so accepting of things,
but he's so staunch
when it comes to that.
In a situation like this...
...just use your damn powers!
The guys from Salt Middle School
are here to fight us!
Took ya long enough, Onigawara.
They shouldn't have
been able to recover
from their wounds yet
from the last butt-kicking!
Let's put these
punks in their place
and finish them off!
[BV GANG 4I]
Actually, we've got a problem...
Onigawara didn't show,
but these guys
in short sleeves and shorts
who I've never seen before did!
One more thing...
They're insanely strong!
[EDANO]
Who the hell are these guys?
Hey! Who are you?
Salt Middle School's Captain
of the Body Improvement
Club, Musashi Goda.
Bring Kageyama out here.
[BV GANG 4L]
Kageyama?
[BV GANG 4M]
Who's that?
[MOB] Captain Musashi?
I wasn't expecting to see you.
What are you guys doing here?
--[EDANO] That's Kageyama?!
--I'm just out running
some errands today,
no big deal.
[BV GANG 4B] This guy
wasn't a helper, at all...
[BV GANG 4A]
He was a landmine!
Damn! Onigawara tricked us!
That bastard!
It looks like you're not hurt.
All right, Kageyama,
let's get going.
[MOB]
Okay.
[MUSASHI] We need to
get back and work out.
Stop messing around, you jocks!
Do you think that we're just
gonna let you leave here?!
We're all going to beat you
into a big, bloody pulp!
Go get 'em, boys!
[BV GANG screams]
[BOTH groans]
[MUSASHI growls]
[BV GANG 4B screaming]
Somebody... Go get Teru...
I already called him.
It's been a while now.
Is he late 'cause he's
flirting with some girl again?
[TERU] Did some stray
gorillas wander in?
Do I need to tame them?
Teru! You're here!
[TERU] You aware of the
term "organized violence"?
Those pieces of trash
you see lying around
before you are the
symbols of my authority
within my life at school.
And now that you've
shattered it completely,
you've basically
thrown mud in my face.
Are you one of these
delinquents, too?
[EDANO laughs]
He's our shadow leader, the one
and only Teruki Honuhzahwa!
Teru! These guys
think they're tough,
so please teach them a lesson.
Edano...
Today marks your
last day as leader.
You just can't cut it.
Huh? No, wait a second--
[groans]
You've put my dignity
on the line here.
No way.
Looked like he just teleported.
You're just seein' things.
We got what we came here for.
We'll be going back
to training now.
[TERU] I'm the one who decides
whether or not you leave.
And don't you forget it.
Oh, well...
Doesn't feel right
to face someone
with such a frail body, but...
[TERU] Society always
underestimates me.
People never try to
look beneath the surface.
Fools.
That's why you're
so easy to control.
One doesn't take the spotlight
'cause they're the star.
They're the star because
they take the spotlight.
And once that light
finally shines onto you,
bugs with low IQs
will always flock to it.
What are you talkin' about?
[TERU] Hey, you insects
around the corner.
Stop hiding and come out.
[MUSASHI gasps]
Onigawara!
So it's you.
Hurry up and crush
that pretty boy!
[MUSASHI yells]
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
Damn you! Take this!
[ONIGAWARA screams]
[ONIGAWARA]
That's insane...
It was just a slap, but
it packed a real punch!
He's tiny, but he
swings like a bear.
Are you even human,
you monster?!
[MUSASHI]
Well, I'm impressed.
[gasps]
[MUSASHI]
You managed to blow us away
despite the weight difference.
You must have some uniquely
excellent musculature.
Musculature?
[chuckles]
[MUSASHI screams]
[JOCKS groan]
You little bastard!
I'll send you to hell!
Demon Rush!
[ONIGAWARA]
What?! My fists...
They aren't even reaching him!
Muscles and fighting
techniques, huh?
Average people are so sad.
Now it's my turn.
[ONIGAWARA]
That was close!
[screams]
Some leader.
[TERU]
Hm?
Wow, at least one of you
is pretty tough...
[TERU]
What's with this guy?
His presence barely registers,
so I didn't even notice him.
On top of that,
why's he tied up?
You shouldn't use
them against people.
What are you talking about?
[MOB] I'm talking about
your psychic powers.
The ones that you've
been hitting them with.
[sputters]
You should never
use them for fighting.
[ARATAKA] Teru, the handsome
esper, attacks Mob.
As men flee while psychic powers
and knives fly around the
thunderous battlefield,
a mysterious figure appears,
and a miracle happens!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 5: "OCHIMUSHA
Psychic Powers and Me."
Blu-ray? Another
excellent decision.