[NARRATOR]
Whether you believe it or not,
the world around you
is filled with
strange phenomena that
science has yet to explain.
And in those unfortunate moments
when people come
face to face with them,
they are helplessly thrown
into the dark depths of fear.
But, there are those who
choose to fight against
the darkness every day
shining a ray of hope
into that chaos.
These warriors
opposing the shadows
are called "Psychics."
You're in luck!
I, Reigen Arataka,
shall accept this job!
Oh, my god, really?
Thank you so much!
I had no idea who else
I could turn to!
No one would take me seriously!
[ARATAKA]
There, there. It's okay.
Now, the fee for my services
will depend on which course
of exorcism you pick.
[HANAKO]
"Which course"?
[ARATAKA] Option A, the trial
course, gets you 20 percent.
Option B, the serious course,
gets you 50 percent.
And Option C,
the all-out course,
gets you a 99 percent...
...spirit reduction.
A hundred percent guaranteed,
certain restrictions apply.
[HANAKO]
Reduction?
How should I put this...
Spirits're kinda like
carbon dioxide.
So you're saying
they're poisonous?
That's monoxide.
I mean they occupy
a sort of gaseous space.
Makes it a bit
difficult to completely
get rid of one.
That said, have no fear.
If it comes back,
I'll get rid of it
for 20 percent off!
Oh! You're so amazing!
Hold on a second!
Huh? And, who might you be?
[HANAKO] Oh, this is Taro.
He's my boyfriend.
Ah, what a calm fellow!
What's that s'posed to mean?!
[groans] Stick to the subject.
Listen up, you!
This is all super shady!
[HANAKO]
Uh...
Hanako, you should
really reconsider this.
[ARATAKA]
"Super shady," huh?!
I guess I can't blame you
for feeling that way.
I mean, all that stuff about
nightmares and ghosts?
What a stupid story.
I wasn't talkin' about her,
you snake-oil salesman!
It's you I can't trust!
[ARATAKA]
Just leave everything to me.
If I exorcise the
spirit, I'm sure
Hanako's face will
return to normal, too.
There's nothing wrong
with her face, you moron!
[ARATAKA]
I see.
So you've been
having these dreams
since you walked through that
abandoned building last week.
[HANAKO]
Yes, that's right.
They're so scary and creepy.
Here we are, Reigen!
It's that building over there!
[gasps] What an
unbelievable aura!
This will be my first
big one in a long time!
It's right over here.
[ARATAKA yelps]
Hold up.
Did you just point
at the wrong building?
[ARATAKA laughs nervously]
Hh? Ah, so it's that one!
Funny story--
An immense aura was coming from
that other building, too!
These things happen,
nature of "the biz."
It gets confusing with all these
evil spirits in
the world, you know?
Ah! Yes, that makes sense!
Come on.
There's no way ghosts are
hangin' around everywhere.
[ARATAKA]
Oh, no!
A man-shaped evil spirit
almost walked through you!
--Huh?
--[ARATAKA] Phew!
[ARATAKA]
What a close call.
You can't be too
careful these days.
[HANAKO, TARO gasp]
[HANAKO, TARO whimper]
[TARO whimpering]
[ARATAKA]
The Butt-chin Goblin.
[TARO] Aw, what are you,
eight years old?
Shut your mouth, Taro!
You're being rude!
He's the one who's
being rude here!
Making fun of people's looks...
[ARATAKA]
Now, now, Hanako...
There're always people like him.
Silly skeptics.
Anyway, shall we go?
[HANAKO]
They say this place is haunted
by the angry spirit of
a man who saw a cockroach.
He freaked out
and jumped so high,
his head went
through the ceiling!
Such a horrific way to go.
Get a grip. You believe
that horse crap?
Ah, I see.
Everything's...
becoming so clear.
[TARO gasps]
[TARO] He's so serious
all of a sudden.
Could there really be...
I'm getting creepy vibes.
Even someone like me might
not be able to handle it!
It's too dangerous!
[yelps]
[ARATAKA]
Cockroaches are terrifying!
[TARO]
Huh?
Come on!
There's no way
this guy is a psychic!
He's a complete and total fake!
[gasps]
[CEILING CRASHER]
How would you like me
to haunt your dreams, too?
A ghost!
Maybe I'll use my curse
and crash both your heads
through the ceiling.
[screams]
That's the guy who keeps
head-butting me in my dreams!
Look!
[HANAKO screams]
[ARATAKA]
Ugh. He actually appeared.
I've got this!
Salt Splash!
[NARRATOR] This is one of
Reigen's special attacks,
where he violently throws
table salt everywhere.
This is just regular
old salt, you buffoon.
If it's not purified,
it's not gonna work.
[ARATAKA]
Impossible...
I heard that spirits
were totally weak
against any kind of salt!
Well, if salt won't
melt this guy down,
I'll just call
my ultimate weapon.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Mob.
Sorry, do you think
you could swing by?
I'm bein' serious here.
Evil spirit's right
in front of me.
The client and the evil
spirit are both waiting,
so you'll need to hurry, okay?
Cool. Thanks.
[HANAKO, TARO]
Huh?
[ARATAKA]
Hey! Mob!
We were waiting for ya.
[CEILING CRASHER]
Hm?
Hmph.
Heh.
So after the salt,
you're sending in
a middle schooler?
Get your--
[NARRATOR]
He is Kageyama Shigeo,
also known as Mob.
An actual psychic, mentoring
under the questionable
expertise of Reigen Arataka...
Who also happens to be
the protagonist of this story.
Master, I asked you not to
summon me on such short notice.
[ARATAKA]
Oh, man, you're a lifesaver!
Never thought that evil spirit
would actually show up.
Here. Your pay for the day.
[MOB]
Oh, thank you.
That one today was just
a lower-level spirit,
so I really shouldn't be
paying you more than half.
But, hey, I'm a nice guy.
Think of your full
pay as a bonus.
[MOB]
Right...
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
What's wrong? Are you
not okay with that?
Oh, no.
Just don't know
why you called me
to handle such a weak spirit.
I mean, ones like that--
Uh! You just don't get it.
When you reach my level,
you get so crazy-strong,
you end up melting
everyone around you
during a simple exorcism.
That's why I ask you to take
care of the weaker ones.
Really? If you say so.
I'm also not quite
sure what you mean
by "melt," either...
[ARATAKA] Well, of course
you don't, idiot!
That's because you
lack training!
You need to learn all you can
from me, your master!
Your powers are
meant to be used.
Not doing so would be a waste.
Working for me gives you
the opportunity to
help other people
and continue training
at the same time!
Two birds, one stone!
But if you misuse a
power such as yours,
it can only lead to your
own self-destruction.
That's why I'm teaching you
how to control your powers.
You don't want them
to go berserk, do you?
[ARATAKA]
Remember your promise.
You will not use
your psychic powers
against other people.
There you go again,
always bending spoons.
You really need
to stop doing that--
it's a bad habit!
Oh, come now, my dear.
Shigeo's going through puberty.
A young man should be able
to bend a spoon from
time to time, right?
[MOB]
Sorry.
And there you go,
spoiling the boy again.
You need to learn a thing
or two from Ritsu, Shige.
He got another perfect
score on his quiz today.
Come on, Mom,
anyone can do that.
Listen, if you ever need
someone to talk to,
let me know.
I'll always be there
for my big brother.
Thanks. I appreciate
it. Will do.
And, now you're spoiling
him as well, Ritsu.
The next one you
bend gets replaced
using your allowance, you hear?
[MOB]
Huh?
Sorry, dude. Tough break.
You're on your own
when it comes to
what Mom tells you.
[MOB'S DAD laughs]
[MOB'S DAD] Now, you're in a
real pickle, aren't ya, Shigeo?
[STUDENT 1A]
'Morning!
[STUDENT 1B giggling]
Right?
[STUDENT 1B]
Good morning, Tsubomi!
Good morning!
Beautiful day, isn't it?
Oh! Guess what I saw
on TV yesterday.
[STUDENT 1B]
What?
[MOB]
Tsubomi's as cute as ever today.
[TEACHER 1A]
Okay, class.
So what would be the
answer for this one?
Let's go with Kageyama.
[MOB]
Huh?
Yes, sir!
Uh... Um...
I have no idea.
[TEACHER 1A]
If you can't solve this,
that would mean the
only thing you know
how to do is addition.
You were asleep, weren't you?
--[STUDENTS laugh]
--Forget it. Sit down, please.
[MOB sighs]
[STUDENT 1C]
Head's up!
[STUDENT 01D]
This way!
[STUDENT 1E]
Pass, pass, pass!
--[STUDENT 1F] Go!
--[STUDENT 1G] Stop 'em!
[STUDENT 1H]
Come on, pass it!
[STUDENT 01I]
Move!
--[panting]
--[phone rings]
[MOB]
Hello?
[ARATAKA]
Mob! How goes it?
Sorry to call you
two days in a row,
but could you come down
to the station right now?
Sure. What for?
Well...
We've got another job.
And it's a big one.
Right. Okay, see you soon.
[ARATAKA]
Today's job is from a local
neighborhood council.
It's over at Honeido Tunnel,
along the old highway.
It's a famous haunted place.
The tunnel's always
had some shady stories,
and though it's been
closed for years,
the bad rumors
just won't go away.
Also, a number of
college students
and bloggers have gone there
to snoop around a little
and went missing, likely
contributing to those rumors.
And this is the kicker.
[MOB] So, it's the site
of a huge group accident?
[ARATAKA]
Yeah.
The incident occurred
about 30 years ago.
From what it says here,
more than 20 people
died at once.
The bitter hatred
of all those people
must be swirling
around that tunnel.
Oh...
[gasps]
[ARATAKA]
Stay on your toes, Mob.
Never know what might happen.
[MOB]
Oh, right.
[ARATAKA]
This is it.
Well, let's take a look around.
I, Reigen Arataka, new star
of the paranormal world,
will clean this place up.
We're gonna exorcise
every last one of them!
[ARATAKA]
What's the big idea?!
What are you doing, student?!
You're coming, too!
It'll be bad if
the sun goes down.
Mob, are you listening?
Huh?
I'm gonna go melt
down a big one,
so follow me!
Okay?
Sure, if you want.
You seemed to have
it under control,
so I didn't think that
you'd need my help.
Idiot!
Who do you think's
gonna ex-- Ahem.
I mean, this is nothing really,
but stick with me so you
can learn something.
[MOB]
You're amazing, Master.
Huh?
I mean, this tunnel actually
seems pretty dangerous.
I can sense the
presence of a very
powerful spirit further down.
Usually, haunted
spots like these
end up being fake,
but, this time, it's
definitely the real deal.
If a normal person
happened to anger
the spirit in here...
[ARATAKA]
What would happen?
[MOB] They'd never make
it out in one piece.
[ARATAKA grunts]
Of course they wouldn't.
That's why you and I
are going to exorcise it.
All right, here we go!
Let me take the lead.
I'll be counting
on you to support me
however you can from behind.
Right.
It's kinda chilly down here.
Yes, it is.
Great.
We forgot to bring
flashlights with us.
[MOB] Master, don't
you feel something?
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
Well, it is pretty
humid in here.
[MOB]
No, I'm talking about auras.
[ARATAKA]
Oh, right, that.
My nose is a little
stuffy today, so...
Does that have anything
to do with sensing auras?
When you get to
my level, it does.
Do you feel anything
down here at all?
"Feeling anything" would
be an understatement.
There are 12...
...18...
No, wait, I'd say
even more than that.
Right nearby us.
[gasps]
[ARATAKA yelps]
It looks like we're
being surrounded.
They're going to attack us now.
[ARATAKA]
All right!
I'll leave the small fry to you.
Go, Mob!
Man, that's a lot of noise.
They're really
strong, aren't they?
Hm. If we were a
couple of normal people,
we might have been
in real danger.
Oh, well, I'm pretty sure
that took care of all of them.
Another piece of ca--
[grunts]
[ARATAKA] There's someone
right in front of me!
Who are you?!
An evil spirit?!
Oh, it's just a
wrestler screwing around
in the dark.
Don't scare me like that!
I thought you were
an evil spirit.
Now, go practice
somewhere else.
[MOB]
Uh, Master?
I'm sure you sense
it, but the boss
of the evil spirits is
over there, so watch out.
Okay?
Oh?
[BOSS chuckles]
[ARATAKA] Hmph, so you're
the boss here, huh?!
You may have tried to disguise
yourself as a wrestler,
but you can't fool me,
you trickster!
You fool!
In this tunnel...
When my biker gang
and I were driving
through it, the guy
in front happened
to slip on a banana peel.
We all died!
And I'm their leader!
Listen up, this tunnel...
...is my turf now.
Do you understand?!
I'll crush every last intruder!
Here we go!
I curse you!
Cigarette Burn Poltergeist!
[BOSS]
Wh-What?
My ignition attack...
Isn't working!
[ARATAKA]
Hmph.
[BOSS]
A forcefield? No way!
How could this power be
coming from someone like him?
Oh, crap!
I thought this guy was
just an average wimp!
Too late for
regrets now, spirit!
The moment you tried to take on
the genius psychic,
Reigen Arataka...
...was the moment
your fate was sealed!
You're gonna be exorcised!
Banishing Salt Punch!
[NARRATOR] This is one
of Reigen's special attacks,
where he punches the
enemy with his fist
covered in table salt.
[screams]
Hold on a second.
That didn't hurt at all.
Oh, dear.
[BOSS]
So, you are a fake.
[BOSS screams]
[BOSS]
I'm disappearing!
W-Wait! Wait!
Go back to the ozone layer.
[BOSS] We were just
being forced to do this!
Hm?
Uh--
Hey, what are you doing, Mob?
Hurry up and melt him, already.
Hold on a minute, Master.
Let's hear him out, first.
A-Ah, ah...
Sure, I may act
tough but neither me
nor my gang are anything
compared to the evil spirit
down the tunnel.
We've been getting
orders from him
all these years, and that's
why we've been scaring people
that come down here.
Heh.
Do you really think you can fool
the likes of Reigen with
such lies, you little speck?!
I'm not lying to you!
It's just-- If I
were to disappear
while being falsely accused...
My brothers, the Death Specters,
and I just couldn't
take take it!
Our memories would
never rest in peace!
That's all I wanted to say!
Now you can make me disappear,
or melt, or whatever!
So your big plan is to try
to make us pity you?
Don't let him fool you, Mob!
Those are nothing but the
typical lies of a con artist.
Melt him.
Before that, I'm gonna
go have a look.
Huh?
[MOB] It's a little weird
that the aura I felt
before coming in here
hasn't disappeared yet.
Something's still not right.
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
I-I thought so, too...
[BOSS]
Stop him!
[ARATAKA]
Huh?
No matter how strong
that kid may be,
he doesn't stand
a chance against it!
That thing is an evil
spirit that's lived
on this mountain for
hundreds of years.
Everyone that's died here
was killed by him,
you understand?!
S-So, you guys were
also killed by...
No.
Like I said, we just happened
to slip on a banana peel.
[yells]
[BOSS]
You get it now?!
If you care for that kid
at all, call him back.
Hurry!
Hey, Mob! Come back!
You listening to me? Come back!
[MONSTER growls]
[MONSTER growling]
[BOSS yells]
[gasps]
[ARATAKA]
Mob...
Ah.
Oh! You're safe.
Yeah. That evil spirit
wasn't very powerful.
No way! Wh-Who are you?
[MOB]
Huh? Oh, I'm nobody...
You idiot!
You're Mob, and you
are the student of...
...the new star of
the paranormal world,
Reigen Arataka!
Oh, right. Sorry.
[chuckles]
I thank you, Mob.
Now the Death Specters
Gang can leave
this tunnel and
pass on peacefully.
[MOB]
Oh, could this be yours?
Huh?
[BOSS]
Huh?!
[GANG MEMBER 1A]
All right, here we go, Boss-man!
Yeah!
[whimpers]
I wanna thank you!
[GANG MEMBER 1B]
Thanks, dude.
[BOSS] Now we can depart
to the afterlife!
[ARATAKA]
Mob.
Our work here is done. Let's go.
Right.
By the way, Master...
Huh?
Why didn't you do
anything back there?
Huh?!
Uh, well, you know, uh...
A-Ahem...
Didn't I tell you
from the beginning
that I'd leave the
small fries to you?
Oh, right.
[STUDENT 1J]
What do you wanna do?
Let's get somethin' to eat.
I'm not gonna last
until I get home.
[STUDENT 1M]
Sounds like a plan.
Sorry to keep you
waiting. Shall we?
Sure.
[ARATAKA]
So, does ramen work for you?
Uh-huh.
All right, well, if
you're gonna add on
chashu pork, limit it to two.
[MOB]
Okay.
[RAMEN STAND OWNER]
Here ya go.
[ARATAKA] A group of
telepaths suddenly appear
and disturb Mob's daily life.
Having doubts about
his peaceful youth,
Mob heads into a world of women.
Where's the goal?
Which way's tomorrow?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 2: "Doubts About Youth
The Telepathy Club Appears."
Watching it in real time?
Wise decision.