[ARATAKA sighs]
[ARATAKA]
Damn it, Mob.
You could've let me
know you had other plans.
Why do you think I gave you
a cellphone? Pick up, already!
You can just drop me off here.
Uh, okay then, sure.
It's 8,810 yen.
[whimpers]
[TAXI DRIVER A]
Sir!
What are you doin' so late out
in the middle of nowhere?
[ARATAKA]
Don't worry.
I'm not planning to
do anything crazy.
[ARATAKA] That kid... What the
heck is he doin' out here?
[MOB] Um... It's okay, Ritsu.
I'm pretty sure it's this way.
[RITSU]
Okay...
This is the same
place as earlier.
[MOB]
Sorry, this is all my fault
for saying we should
go exploring.
[RITSU]
Forget about it.
Let's just focus on finding
a way back, all right?
[MOB]
Hmm...
But how we gonna do that?
[RITSU]
Umm...
Oh, I know!
[MOB]
You do?
[RITSU]
I learned this in science class.
The side with moss
growing on it is north.
Moss always grows in places
where the sun shines least!
You see?
This way is north.
This direction will
take us to the river.
Then we can get back to
where we were barbecuing.
Let's go!
Yeah!
[TERU]
Looks like you're awake.
Where are we? Ugh!
Hey, are you all right?
Do you remember anything
about how you lost?
[MOB]
No, not at all.
[RITSU]
Thank goodness. Are you okay?
Were you hit on the head?
I hope it's nothing serious.
Ritsu.
[gasps]
I'm so glad you're safe.
[MOB]
You're not hurt, are you?
No, but--
[MOB]
Let's hurry home.
That sound good, Hanazawa?
[TERU]
We can't.
I'm not sure why,
but it seems we're completely
powerless in this room.
I tried repeatedly, but no luck.
Usually, I could bust a hole
in a wall like this one
with no problem.
Wow. Yeah, you're right.
But that's okay! We've got
Ritsu here with us!
[RITSU]
Huh?
Oh, yeah? What can
your little brother do?
He happens to be really smart.
I can't do anything special
without using my psychic powers.
But he can figure things out
and solve anything.
Even without his powers.
Is that so?
It sounds like you're pretty
proud of him, aren't you?
Oh, very much so.
There's nobody I admire more.
[RITSU]
No fair...
[MOB]
Hm?
[RITSU]
You won't even let me apologize.
It's just not fair.
Even after everything I've--
Thank you, Brother.
[ISHIGURO]
The sanctity of your sealed room
is as amazing as
always, Sakurai.
[SAKURAI]
Of course it is.
All Frivolities aside, what now?
Do you plan on taking them in?
Making these intruders part
of the upper echelon?
[ISHIGURO]
You're jumping the gun.
First, we need to
brainwash them thoroughly.
[SHO] Whoa, hold on
a second, you guys.
You planning to turn
decent talent into junk?
Those middle schoolers
will be recruited to HQ.
It's a done deal.
[ISHIGURO] Hm... Your name
is Suzuki, correct?
I call the shots here
in the 7th Division,
and that would include
all personnel decisions.
I'll be taking them,
especially that one.
The kid who's in the uniform.
We'll be great friends.
[SAKURAI]
I suggest you quit acting like
you're more than a temp trainee.
I'm a bit blunter
than the others.
Come on. Don't get so worked up.
You're really upset about your
coworkers being defeated?
You guys must get along
better than I thought.
Lay off the sword play, old man.
That was a compliment.
Take it easy, Sakurai.
Everyone at HQ
hates one another.
Nothing like the happy
family out here.
[SAKURAI]
Hmph.
Kids these days.
They just don't get it.
[LACKEY A gasps]
Hey! You there!
Who the hell are you?!
[LACKEY B] Do you think
he's one of the intruders?
[LACKEY D]
Quick, get the others!
Hey, what are all you
guys talkin' about?
What's goin' on inside?
[LACKEY A] First thing's first,
you suspicious jerk!
Tell us who you are!
Oh. Sure, just a sec.
[LACKEY A]
Does he have a gun?! Careful!
Ah, wouldn't you know it?
I'm completely out
of business cards.
Seriously?
His business card?
So anyway, back to
the matter at hand.
Is there something going
on inside that building?
[LACKEY A]
S-Stay back!
We have nothing to say
to some weird outsider!
Just get outta here!
Huh... That's kinda strange.
I'm usually informed
when something happens,
but I haven't heard anything.
I'll check again.
[LACKEYS mumbling]
What the heck is
he talking about?
Could he mean...?
So then, let's get straight
to the point, shall we?
Can everyone here
use psychic powers?
How does he know about that?
He's heard about
the organization?
Sorry, but I'm gettin'
nowhere with you guys.
Hold it right there,
you damned intruder!
Whoa, take it easy! I get
the feeling he might be--
I was thinking the same thing.
Let go of me.
I'm only here to discuss work
matters with my subordinate.
Your what? Wait a sec.
You don't mean--?
Everyone here works
under Ishiguro,
the 7th Division
Leader's subordinate.
But Ishiguro's a
subordinate of the boss,
which means...
[LACKEY I] Oh, crap! I was
so rude! I'm gonna be killed!
What's the matter?
Are you not feeling well?
Hey, someone help him in.
Surely you guys
have a break room.
He's-He's such a kind man!
He totally exudes superiority.
He's gotta be--!
[LACKEY L]
He's Claw's boss!
[LACKEY M]
He's come back to Japan!
[LACKEY N]
He's coming through!
[LACKEY O]
Make way!
[LACKEY P]
Pardon me. Reporting in!
[ISHIGURO]
What is it?
[LACKEY P] The boss has
arrived on-location from HQ.
[ALL gasp]
[ISHIGURO]
He's here?
He said he wouldn't be
back until next month.
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
Hey, look. Somebody just
ducked and hid upstairs.
What did you say?!
It's either an intruder
or an escapee!
Capture them!
[LACKEYS]
Yeah!
[GO grunts]
Looks like we got caught again.
Hang on, there's no need
to be violent with kids.
Oh! I'm sorry about that, boss!
Wait a second. So you're
the boss around here?
Well, I wouldn't
exactly say that.
Oh, come on. Don't be modest.
The real deal has no need
to brag to children.
We might actually be able
to get through to him.
'Scuse me! We were kidnapped
and brought to this place.
We're here totally
against our will!
Our friend is still
in custody somewhere.
Would you please help us out?
Did you guys really do
everything he just said?
[LACKEY Q] Well, uh-- Yes, but
we were just following orders.
You're blaming others for this?
[LACKEY Q]
I'm very sorry, sir!
Listen, just because you were
ordered to do something,
that doesn't mean it's
the right thing to do.
When underlings start
getting too obedient,
they're nothing but trash.
What? But, sir!
We thought we were
doing what we--!
[ARATAKA]
You fools!
[LACKEYS screaming]
[ARATAKA] Even if you're able
to rise to the top like that,
all you'll see
when you look down
is the filth you
left in your wake.
I'm not sure what you're
trying to do here,
but getting to the
top only feels good
when you do everything
the right way!
You just think about that!
Yeah, he's got a point.
I feel awful. We've been
doing such petty things.
Wow, that's crazy.
It's like they just
changed in an instant.
Oh man, this guy's in
a league of his own.
[MOB] Have you thought
of anything, Ritsu?
[RITSU] It's probably best
if we don't try anything now.
They'll stop by and
check on us for sure.
I say we conserve
our energy until then.
Sounds like a plan.
We'll have more options
when we get our powers back.
Speaking of, we can count on
your strength as well, can't we?
[MOB]
Huh?
It's my fault for involving
you two to begin with.
I'll help however I can.
Will he be okay?
Him? Oh, come on.
I was the one who was
almost burned to death.
Besides, if you really get
serious about going all out,
then two of us won't have to
put up a fight in any capacity.
[door opens]
They're here.
And they're roaming around
in a group, as always.
[MOB]
Uh?
There you are, Mob.
What the heck are you doing
in a place like this?
Oh, your little
brother's here, too.
What's up?
W-Wait a second,
who are you anyway?
And just how do you know
the Kageyama brothers?
Quiet, you!
Don't talk that way to
the big boss, got it?!
Th-The big boss?!
What are you doing here, Master?
[ALL]
His Master?!
A wig?
Hey, Mob. Who is this guy?
[TERU] So he's Kageyama's
master and the boss of Claw?!
This is our chance!
We're being held here
against our will!
Please, step aside
and let us go!
Why do you have
them trapped in here?
Uh. Well...
[LACKEY Q whispering]
I can't hear you.
[LACKEY Q]
It's top secret, so, uh...
[LACKEY Q whispering]
Oh, really?
Come on, guys. That's
a crime and you know it.
[LACKEYS]
We're very sorry, sir!
You're amazing, Master.
[RITSU] Did he really
manage to fool them?
[ARATAKA] All right,
let's get outta here.
[RITSU]
Can it be? Are we saved?
[LACKEY A]
Boss, where are you going?
[ARATAKA]
I said that we're leaving.
You should at least wait for
Division Leader Ishiguro.
Uh?
[ARATAKA]
Huh?
[ISHIGURO]
Who are you?
Doesn't look like
the boss to me.
[ARATAKA] Introduce yourselves,
criminal organization.
[ISHIGURO] I'm Ishiguro,
the 7th Division Leader
of the psychic
association, Claw.
And you are?
I'm the greatest psychic in
modern history, Reigen Arataka!
Feel free to Google me.
[LACKEY A]
What?!
So he's not the big boss man?!
[ISHIGURO] Fraud or not, you had
the nerve to disregard me
and call yourself the boss.
That's a severe offense.
Yeah, what're you talkin'
about, you shrimp?
Step aside or I'll
take care of you
with my green belt in
Shorinji Kenpo with a snap.
[TERU]
Damn, that's strong!
Uh, what is this?
You're a spirit specialist.
Stand back.
[ISHIGURO] You've gathered
some efficient pawns.
If you gather enough, you might
actually be able to oppose Claw.
D-Division Leader, wait!
If you attack him from that
angle, we're gonna die, too!
[ISHIGURO]
Like I care. Seems fitting.
That guy's your boss, isn't he?
No! We swear!
All of you,
go and hide somewhere.
Huh?
If you wanna make it big and
do something with your lives,
then you can't die here!
This is your chance
to free yourselves
from this shady organization.
So hurry!
Leave this to me and
my student and go!
You're such a kind man.
[LACKEY U]
Thank you!
Actually, I'll be going, too.
Ah! The ceiling fell!
[ISHIGURO]
You won't get away that easily.
[ARATAKA]
Whoa, what is goin' on here?
Are there seriously espers
out there other than Mob?
Unfortunately, I'm no match
for that kind of power.
It'll be a pretty tough
challenge for me, too.
And that means...
...it's up to you... Kageyama.
[ARATAKA]
Hm?
[ISHIGURO]
Yes. He's a strong one.
Let me take care of him.
I'll bet he's never
met anyone with powers
that exceed his before.
He's in for a surprise.
Let me make myself clear.
You're not getting
anywhere near me.
You'll be crushed.
Brother!
Some kinda gravity control?
Hey, Mob, what are you doing?
[MOB]
Master...
[ISHIGURO] Not bad. You're able
to resist my powers a bit.
Let's increase the gravity.
Anti-Esper Dropkick!
[NARRATOR] This is one of
Reigen's special moves.
To execute it, he dropkicks
an esper as hard as he can.
[ALL gasp]
Master...
[ARATAKA]
Mob.
Were you planning on
fighting these guys
with your psychic powers?
I told you that it's dangerous
to use them against
other people, remember?
Are you going to break the rule?
[gasps]
[RITSU]
He had a rule like that?
In order to save me,
he had no choice!
[ARATAKA]
Mob.
Is this true?
You felt that cornered?
[ARATAKA]
It must've been rough.
Listen.
Confrontation with others
is the hardest thing for him,
especially when it's
with adults like you.
Watching you guys
bully an awkward kid
who gets discouraged so
easily is hard to take
and it twists my stomach.
So show some decency and stop
stressing out my student!
Then you plan on fighting
us yourself, I take it?
Let me give you a bit of advice.
No matter the disagreement,
you shouldn't harm others.
[TERU]
But dropkicks are okay?
[ARATAKA] If you're too
stubborn or set in your ways
to take that advice,
then I'll fight you.
Either way, due to my position
as their temporary guardian,
I'm not going to
let them go at it.
So yes, I'll face you myself.
As peacefully as possible.
First off, show
me your powers...
...and I'll show you mine.
Starting with hypnosis!
Stare deeply into
this five yen coin.
Hmph. How foolish.
[SAKURAI] That's odd. I don't
sense anything from him.
[TERU]
Kageyama's master's powers...
Is he actually is an esper?
If this is a ruse,
it's gonna be dangerous.
While you're watching this
slowly swing back and forth...
...Hypnosis Punch!
[NARRATOR] This is another one
of Reigen's special moves,
where he suddenly
punches his opponent.
[RITSU]
A sucker punch?
That's not a special power,
that's just fighting dirty!
All right, guys.
[SAKURAI]
Quit messing around!
Hey! Be careful with that thing!
That's a really sharp katana!
This is Jugan.
It actually started out as
a toy sword made of plastic.
But after carrying it around
and cursing it again and
again over the years,
it became truly powerful.
Hey, hold on. Listen to me.
My little ones, time to
come out and play.
What do you think of the
evil spirts I've collected?
Think you'll be able to
handle them on your own?
No really, listen.
Ethereal Bodies Technique.
As you can see, I can freely
exit my physical body.
I'm even able to limitlessly
clone my ethereal form.
Come on, you're dealing
with children here.
[ISHIGURO]
Maybe I'll get a little angry.
Let me introduce
you to my Black Orbs.
Their varying gravity
will rip you apart.
[NARRATOR]
Reigen's plan backfired.
[ARATAKA] I was going to
try to reason with them
while they were
shocked from being hit,
but all I did was piss them off!
I blew it!
[NARRATOR]
Reigen was very confident
in defeating others
in arguments.
He'd never lost to anyone
in a verbal dispute,
no matter who they were.
[ARATAKA] But that's only
when I'm actually dealing
with normal human adults.
These irrational goons
who are full-on
trying to attack
middle school kids...
This bunch of deranged misfits
who are seriously talking about
taking over the world...
They're simply children
who failed to grow up.
How'd they end up like this?
Either way, new plan.
Mob! Run for it!
[ISHIGURO]
Die!
Ah! I'm being pulled in!
Holy crap! Pull him back!
Hang on, Master!
While I don't like the idea of
being sucked into a black hole,
don't rip my body apart
by pulling too hard!
Take it easy!
[ISHIGURO]
Maybe I went too far.
[explosion]
[ALL gasp]
That was rough...
You can defeat them
with psychic powers?
Give it a try.
Wha--?
Leave him alone!
[yells]
I'm surprised you dodged
that. Either way...
I think this look
suits you better.
Damn it. We're dealing with
some real weirdos here.
If they were evil spirits,
I'd be able to exorcise them.
Really? Ha, ha.
They are, so just try it.
Huh?
Guess you can just
exorcise them.
Bastard. I call upon
my ultimate creation.
Candy come out here!
Wreak as much havoc as you want!
Screw that, we're
gettin' out of here.
Don't bother with them, Mob!
[TERU] Kageyama!
Use all of your powers!
Just blow these guys away!
No, don't!
Now stop fighting back!
I'm the adult,
so I'll deal with them!
Mob, there's no need for
you to stoop to their level!
Shige, you're the only one
of us who can stop them!
[MOB]
Yes... He's right.
I have to defeat them now.
[ARATAKA]
No! Stop! Don't fight back, Mob!
[MOB]
Ritsu's hurt.
[TERU] We've gotta fight
power with power!
At this rate,
we're all gonna die!
We just need to run away!
Get real!
How can we run when they
won't stop attacking us?!
Do it! Use the powers you
used that time before!
No, keep it together!
Don't go head-to-head
with someone
who has murder on their mind!
[ISHIGURO] All four of
you are going to hell.
[MOB] Ritsu... Hanazawa...
Master Reigen...
I can't just let them die.
[MOB] I have no choice but
to fight with all I've got.
[MOB]
If I can save them,
I don't care what happens
to the ones attacking me!
[gasps]
I'm warning you. Don't do it.
In the end, you're the one
who's gonna be suffering.
When things go south,
it's okay to run away
and save yourself!
[doorbell rings]
[MOB] Excuse me. I saw your sign
and thought I'd stop by.
[ARATAKA]
Sure, come on in.
How may I--?
Oh, it's just a kid.
All right, young man.
So what do you want?
[MOB]
Well, um. I'm an esper.
Huh?
[MOB] There are times
when I can't control
my powers too well,
and it gets kinda scary.
Let me guess, did somebody
tell you to come here
and say that to me?
No. I haven't talked
about this with anyone.
I saw your sign and thought
you might have the
same kind of abilities.
If I tried, I could
see spirits, too.
Well, come on in.
Sure.
I was troubled when
I was a kid, too.
[MOB]
Huh?
[ARATAKA]
Uh.
Listen, just because you have
these psychic powers
and abilities,
it doesn't mean you're any less
of a human than anyone else.
There are people who are fast,
people who are book smart,
and people with
strong body odor.
Psychic powers are
just like that:
Another characteristic.
You must embrace
that characteristic
as a part of yourself and
continue to live positively.
After all, the truth behind
one's charm is kindness.
So just be a good person.
You got it?
So may I come by and
talk to you again?
Yeah, I'm not so
sure about that.
I'm pretty busy, you know?
Anyway, you should
go home for tod-- Hot!
Move! You'll get burned!
Hey... You said--
You said you could see
ghosts, too, didn't you?
Do you know how
to exorcise them?
[ARATAKA] All right. Come again
tomorrow. Same time, okay?
Yeah? Really?
I'll show you exactly
how to use your powers.
[gasps]
[MOB]
Master!
[gasps]
[MOB]
Master...
Huh? Master...?
Master?
Master!
Master, please! Wake up!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 12: "Mob and Reigen."
This was in Master's will:
"Watching the finale in real
time is an excellent decision."