[TOME] It looks like there
really aren't many espers
out here, are there?
I mean, all of these
people have walked by
and not one of them
has stood out to you.
Unless, of course, you're just
not saying anything to trick me.
No, there really
haven't been any.
[TOME]
Hm...
[TERU] Hey. So are
the two of you on a date?
[MOB gasps]
Whoa. This guy seems
pretty unique...
It's Hanazawa.
Sorry, but...
something's come up.
Cool if I borrow him for a bit?
Uh... Sure...
[MOB] Someone's
fighting under my name?
[TERU] Yeah. It's a student
from Salt Middle School.
You might even know him.
[TERU]
He's back that way.
You should go and take
a look for yourself.
[gasps]
It's you...
What are you doing, Ritsu?
Shige... What are
you doing here?
I'd ask you the
same thing, Ritsu.
[TERU]
Must be his younger brother.
[KOYAMA]
Who's this kid?
[MOB] Who are these people
piled up on the ground?
Did you do all this?
[MOB]
Ritsu...
Yes. I'm responsible.
[gasps]
[TERU] Watching two siblings
fight isn't exactly
the classiest thing to do.
[MOB] Really?
This is your doing, Ritsu?
[RITSU]
It's true.
No way.
Come on, you're
just kidding, right?
I mean... seriously? Brother...
[RITSU]
Seriously. I did this.
See, I've finally
obtained psychic powers.
Huh?
Whoa, Ritsu! What do
you think you're doing?!
[RITSU]
Not another word, Dimple.
[DIMPLE]
Tch! He's drunk with power.
This is why I hate brats.
[DIMPLE] I'm not hanging around
for a battle I know he'll lose!
--[RITSU grunts]
--Dimple?
[RITSU]
Whatever. I don't need him.
I've got the hang of it now.
Listen, Brother.
I've come to realize
something very important.
What? What do you mean?
Look, if something's
bothering you--
[RITSU grunts]
[MOB grunts]
You do have psychic powers...
[RITSU]
I missed...
Ritsu... You did it!
[RITSU gasps]
[MOB]
You've wanted them for so long!
Do you remember?
Back when you were a little kid,
you'd cry your eyes out
'cause you couldn't bend spoons.
Who would've thought that now--
The situation hadn't
changed until recently.
Now listen to what
I was trying to tell you.
I've always wanted
psychic powers.
And because you had them,
I'd always admired you, Brother.
Really? You're making me blush.
[RITSU] But that was just
a big misunderstanding.
It was?
[RITSU] I couldn't handle
my inferiority complex
and fear towards you...
So I was protecting
myself by thinking
it was simply admiration.
More than anything,
I was scared of you.
I never knew what you might do
if you got stressed out.
We could never even
have a fight as brothers.
I mean, that would
be suicidal, right?
I'd have no way to protect
myself from your powers.
So I did my best to
stay out of your way
and not cause
any trouble between us.
Now that's just
a humiliating past.
I tried so hard for so long,
no matter how crazy or
frustrated it made me...
And yet...
...you never worked hard
in your life, so why?!
But now I've obtained them.
Now I don't have to
be scared anymore.
The delusional
admiration is gone.
Actually...
...I've lost all interest
in our relationship.
So, this buddy-buddy act
of ours ends now.
It's over.
Ritsu. I can tell.
That's all just a lie.
I want you to face me!
Hit me with the full force
of your powers!
[MOB] But I guess part
of what you said is true...
I am your brother.
And that means...
...I have to help
take care of you.
[RITSU gasps]
[MOB] I'm terribly sorry that
my little brother hurt you.
He lost his temper, that's all.
Please look past this
and be friends with him.
[RITSU]
Huh?
What'd you say?
You're the older brother
of that freak show?
Yes. And I'm very sorry.
[AKAGI]
You idiot!
Think that's enough
to be forgiven, do you?!
You need to grovel down
on your knees first!
[MOB]
Oh... Okay...
[RITSU whimpers]
Stop it.
Why would you do that?
Tch! What do you
think you're doing?!
Ritsu... There isn't any use
in trying to get rid of me...
I mean, we're brothers.
[phone rings]
[KOYAMA]
Hello?
[SAKURAI]
I'd like a status update.
It's been ten minutes
since you reported
that you've found the target.
What are you doing?
[KOYAMA] Thought while
I was here, I'd observe the--
[SAKURAI]
What are you, an idiot?
Hurry up and bring him here.
[KOYAMA]
All right, fine.
[SAKURAI] Actually...
just in case, send a photo.
It'd be a real pain in the ass
if you brought back
the wrong brat.
[KOYAMA]
Yeah, yeah...
Mocking me...
There you go. Sent.
[SAKURAI]
Got it.
That's him... Shigeo Kageyama.
[KOYAMA]
Like I said...
[SAKURAI] Confirms the
"Awakening Lab's" data...
Tch. What a completely
exaggerated name.
It's embarrassing
to even have to say it.
[SAKURAI]
Now, listen. Don't mess this up.
The more information we leak,
the more annoying it'll be.
No fooling around.
[KOYAMA]
I got it, I got it...
Acting all high-and-mighty...
Let's get this wrapped up.
[GANG laughing]
The tables have turned!
[AKAGI]
White T Poison!
If you don't want us
to beat the crap
out of your brother,
then get your ass over here.
[GOZU]
[MOB] Ah. Hold it.
You shouldn't do that.
[GOZU]
Huh?
I was hoping we'd end this.
No more hurting people.
There's been enough violence.
Now, just who in the hell do
you think you are, small fry?!
[BANDAI] Only the strongest
can give out orders like that.
And the strongest will rule.
That's the way of the world.
[RITSU] Just how pathetic
are these people?
The strongest one
here is obviously...
[RITSU grunts]
[KOYAMA]
You're exactly right.
[RITSU]
Tch! Let go!
--[KOYAMA growls]
--Ritsu!
--[MEMBER A] What?!
--[MEMBER B] Who's that?!
Who the hell are you?!
[KOYAMA] Like you said,
the strongest will rule.
It's such an obvious
thing that sometimes,
you forget about it.
Let me guess...
You guys figure that if
you're strong at fighting,
you can rule your school
and turfs, right?
That's cute. Really. Nice job.
You should keep it up.
But this guy's on a
completely different level.
You punks don't stand a chance
in hell of beating him.
[RITSU yelps]
[KOYAMA] So I'm gonna take him
from the fighting grounds.
[GANG]
You can keep squabbling with
whomever else in peace.
He's comin' with me.
Hold it right there!
He's our target! You can't--
Yaugh!
[MEMBER A]
That's our business!
[grunts, groans]
How dare you treat
our boss like that?!
Wait, I got a bad feeling.
[BOTH yell]
[grunt]
[MEMBER C] This guy's
too strong... It's not fair...
[KOYAMA chuckles]
You thugs are such
simple creatures...
Pathetic.
Uh?
My little brother...
Shige...
[KOYAMA]
Did I hit him too hard?
Well, if he dies,
I'd say he was just unlucky.
--[KOYAMA] Hey, tall guy.
--[FUJI gasps]
[KOYAMA] What's with
that angry stare, huh?
It wasn't angry... I was
just looking, that's all...
[KOYAMA]
Grovel and apologize to me!
Huh?!
[KOYAMA] We're reviewing
the scene you were
playing out earlier.
I know! All of you
should grovel!
Get on your knees!
[GANG whimpering]
[KOYAMA] Oh, do you need
a little added incentive?
If you don't grovel,
I'll kill you little punks.
[KOYAMA laughs]
[KOYAMA]
What a sight to behold!
Look at all you
pathetic dipshits!
Let this be a lesson for those
who think they're badasses.
And I've got one piece of advice
for the rest of
your rotten lives.
Try to live by walking
on the side of the road,
so you don't cause
the strong ones
you can't handle any trouble.
See ya, brats.
[laughs]
Damn it!
What was that about?
[FUJI grunts]
[MEMBER D]
Look that's...
[MOB growls]
Ritsu!
[GANG screams]
[KOYAMA gasps]
[yells]
[MOB grunts]
You, too, brat?
You want some of this?!
Wait... What are you--?
I wasn't told anything
about this kid
having a brother
with psychic powers...
Let go of my brother...
or you'll regret it.
[RITSU grunts]
[KOYAMA]
So, you've put up a barrier.
Oooh, I'm shaking!
[MOB] I'm not supposed to use
these powers against others...
But this is different!
Is that all you got, little man?
[gasps]
[MOB]
I remember now!
From before...
He's that adult esper I noticed.
Love to stay and play,
but I've got other plans.
Luckily, there
are ways to deal
with little esper
brats like you!
[yells]
[KOYAMA]
Telekinetic Helix!
[MOB]
He's attacking again.
I don't wanna grow up
and become this guy.
Now, cry...
[MOB]
Huh?
[grunts]
[groans]
You're so light.
You fly like a bird!
[MOB]
It hurts... I can't exhale...
Or inhale...
My stomach is burning...
[MOB grunts]
You surprised? My powers
rip through your barrier
like an excavator
through a pile of rubble.
[grunts]
Shige!
[KOYAMA]
Stand up.
You're gonna protect your
little brother, right?
[MOB grunts]
[BANDAI]
Whoa, holy crap!
That is one hell of a beating!
[MEMBER E]
This can't be real...
--[MEMBER F] Seriously?
--[MEMBER G] He's gonna die.
Brother...
[MOB grunting]
Leave him alone...
Stop hurting him! Please!
[KOYAMA growls]
[MOB grunts]
[RITSU gasps]
Stop it, now!
[KOYAMA grunting]
Just take me!
It's what you wanted, right?!
Then do it! [grunts]
[KOYAMA]
That's a wise decision.
[chuckles]
But I don't play fair...
What's with that
look on your face?
Think I'll take this
opportunity to wipe it off!
[RITSU grunts]
[MOB]
Look what you've done...
This is the first time
this has happened
while I'm still conscious.
Can you feel it?
Rage. Burning in me.
[KOYAMA growls]
[grunts]
[KOYAMA] He brought
my hands to the ground...
A brat like that...
[yells]
[KOYAMA grunts]
[KOYAMA]
I can't get away!
[groans]
That guy is finished. It's over.
[MOB] You who attacked
my brother and me unprovoked...
You did this to yourself,
and now you're gonna pay for it.
Don't you ever show your face
in front of us again.
[KOYAMA]
Telekinetic Helix!
[KOYAMA] What?! How can it
have no effect this time?!
[GANG gasping]
[MEMBER H]
Unbelievable...
[MEMBER I]
Hey, did you see that?
[MEMBER J]
What the hell happened?
What's going on?
[gasps]
You're kidding!
[KOYAMA]
Energy Bomb!
[KOYAMA] You're actually
making me use my trump card...
Shige!
[gasps]
[KOYAMA]
Why won't he fall over?
[DIMPLE] At this rate,
things won't end well.
Oh! I know! Reinforcements!
[yells]
[KOYAMA]
Damn it! What's with this brat?!
[KOYAMA groans]
[KOYAMA]
H-He's strong!
If I don't put up my guard, I'll
be knocked out in an instant.
[GANG cheering]
[MEMBER K]
Yeah! Get him!
[BANDAI] Can't believe
a guy like that exists.
Hey, look at that!
It's-- It's a white T-shirt!
[BANDAI gasps]
That's it!
He's not White T Poison's
older brother.
He's the shadow leader
at Salt Middle School.
[GANG]
White T Poison!
[KOYAMA] Taking him on in a
battle of abilities isn't good.
I don't have a choice.
The mission comes first.
Hey, look out! He's got a knife!
[KOYAMA]
Shut up, you stupid punk!
[yells]
[MOB] If you're not
giving up, I'll end it.
The next move will be the last.
[KOYAMA]
Take this, brat!
Damn it!
This barrier's so powerful!
My knife's not
even gonna scratch it!
[KOYAMA]
Just kidding!
[MOB gasps]
[GANG gasping]
[MEMBER M]
What happened?!
[KOYAMA]
I don't like using this stuff,
but I don't have time to deal
with this crap anymore.
You've all gotten
a good look at my face.
So, I'm gonna have to
make you disappear.
--O-Oh, crap!
--Run!
[MEMBER B]
H-Hurry!
[KOYAMA laughs] You really
think I'll let you get away
after everything you've seen?
[KOYAMA gulps]
[KOYAMA] Impossible!
I can't take him on anymore!
[KOYAMA]
You're coming with me!
He left and he didn't kill us?
We did it!
--Yeah!
--All right!
Amazing! You saved our lives!
What the--?
He's unconscious,
but still standing.
[TERU]
I'd stay away, if I were you.
It's still dangerous
to be near him.
[MEMBER A] You're from
Black Vinegar Middle School.
I can't believe someone
was able to push him
over the edge like that.
That's no ordinary guy.
[DIMPLE]
He left and took Ritsu with him.
Dammit! Looks like
we're too late!
[ARATAKA] This is rock salt
from the Himalayas.
It goes great
with pasta or meat.
It'll also come in handy
for our needs in the exorcism.
Your shoulders
feel heavy, right?
Yes. A fortuneteller said
there was something dense
weighing down on them.
[ARATAKA] So they just told
her that and took the money?
How irresponsible.
I know just what to do.
Uh, why are you--?
Ghosts and spirits are
completely powerless
against salt. First,
we'll weaken them
with the rock salt powder.
And with this scraping
noise by your ears...
This'll be really
annoying to spirits
that wanna live
in a quiet place.
Eventually, they'll grow
agitated and leave.
Phase two!
We'll use the hard
edges of the rock salt
and do a massage to loosen
up your tense muscles
and improve your blood flow.
[moans]
[ARATAKA] We'll place
a hot towel on your face
to cover your eyes.
This shuts out the spirits'
visual interferences.
Along with using aroma oils
to maximize your relaxation,
we'll light some incense
that spirits hate.
[CLIENT A moans]
Such a wonderful smell!
Aroma Runaway Express!
[NARRATOR] This is one of
Reigen's special moves,
where he sends his clients
on a specialized beauty trip
that relaxes the body and soul.
Oh, my goodness!
I feel so much younger!
That's an added bonus!
[ARATAKA] I'm so glad there was
no actual spirit to deal with.
This is the first time
I can remember
that Mob didn't
show up for work.
I'm gonna have to lecture him
when I see him, again...
[RITSU]
Brother...
If there's anything
troubling you, let me know.
I'll be there to listen anytime.
Shige, somethin' bothering you?
You sure everything's okay?
If you're not feelin' right,
I'm here to listen.
Oh, it's nothing.
Really. I'm fine, Ritsu.
Thanks for asking, though.
Sure.
[MOB]
Ritsu... Ritsu... I see, now...
I'm sorry I didn't
realize it sooner.
[MOB groans]
[gasps]
Good, you're finally awake.
I was worried.
[MOB]
Hanazawa... Where are we?
[TERU]
My apartment.
Dimple told me about
everything that happened.
Hey! Looking good, Shigeo...
[MOB]
Dimple... What's going on?
Why were you there with Ritsu?
It's a long story.
[MOB]
And he was kidnapped. Dimple...
Oh?
Are you to blame for all this?
[DIMPLE]
It's a misunderstanding!
I don't know who those guys are!
He doesn't, but I do.
[MOB, DIMPLE]
Huh?
They've been trying to follow me
around for a few years now.
[DIMPLE] Huh? Is that why
you live by yourself
even though you're
in middle school?
Let me give you
a little bit of advice.
Stay away from them.
[DIMPLE]
Huh?
But they've got my brother.
You'll die.
[MOB grunts]
[TERU] It's an organization
called Claw,
formed by dangerous espers.
They want a revolution and aim
to turn the world on its head.
Their ability to
function as a group
is first-rate and
there're over a hundred
who're actively involved.
[BOTH gasp]
You're kidding, right?
Over a hundred...
[TERU] There are plenty of
facilities across the world
that are researching ways to
manufacture psychic powers.
But the only one to succeed
at such an undertaking is Claw.
Apparently, they take child
espers who have yet to mature,
brainwash them,
and raise them as soldiers.
They aren't as powerful
as us Naturals,
but if you underestimate them,
their sheer numbers
will crush you.
[DIMPLE]
You know a lot about 'em.
Got most of my info
from one of their guys
who tried to kidnap me before.
Luckily though, that time
around, I taught him a lesson.
So basically, they're
a bunch of shady espers
from a dangerous group.
Hey, Shigeo, you're lucky.
You could've been
killed back there!
[MOB]
It doesn't matter...
Ritsu, my little brother,
was kidnapped.
I'm gonna go save him.
[DIMPLE]
Huh?
[TERU]
Do you have a death wish?
No, not at all.
Then calm down and think.
[MOB]
I think I can win.
[TERU grunts]
[sighs]
Have it your way.
But how do you think they found
out about your little brother?
I don't really have any idea.
Ah! I just remembered!
There's a research facility
where people like you
were gathering.
As a matter of fact,
Ritsu was there recently, too.
Are you serious?
So the information must
have leaked from there.
Maybe we should check it out.
But I have a bad
feeling about this...
I can lead you there.
[DIMPLE]
Ah! This is terrible...
How could they do this
to civilians?
[TERU] It looks like they're
unconscious, but not dead.
[MITSUURA coughs]
[gasps]
Wh-Who are you?! Where did
he go?! That guy with the sword!
You need to answer
our questions first.
Now tell me, did you
sell Ritsu Kageyama's
personal information to Claw?
To Claw? What's that?
Ritsu Kageyama?
You must be mistaken.
The one I invited here was
a kid named Shigeo Kageyama.
You're wrong. That's me.
It can't be!
This all started with
a misunderstanding,
and yet they really
managed to awaken Ritsu.
[MITSUURA]
I don't what's going on.
Damn it all!
And we were finally seeing some
hope in our research, too.
It looks like this guy really
doesn't know anything.
Where are the other kids?
They were kidnapped.
Is all of this my fault?
[MITSUURA] To think there's
a group like that...
All right, so what
level of power
did the kids who
were kidnapped have?
'Cause I'd like to know exactly
what we're up against here.
Hold on a second.
Who are you guys, anyw--?
[gasps]
What do you think
you're doing, Hanazawa?
Introducing ourselves.
[KOYAMA] Come on, brats.
Hurry and get out.
Quit dawdling. Keep moving.
Don't make me smack you.
Now, don't scare them
any more than necessary.
They'll be useless.
--[KOYAMA] Tch.
--Kageyama.
You look rough, are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
But listen, we really shouldn't
fight back right now.
[gasps]
[ARATAKA] Trapped in a
suspicious research facility,
Ritsu plots an escape with
the good-for-nothing espers.
Meanwhile, Mob rises
to save Ritsu.
That's right, Mob!
That's what you call a man.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 9:
"'Claw' 7th Division."
Option B involves buying
the Blu-rays and the manga.