[DIMPLE]
What a surprise.
Guess there are other
middle-school-aged espers
besides you, Shigeo.
But, looks to me
like he's surprised
to discover another
one, as well.
Impossible...
Are-Are you a natural?
Someone with powers like me?
And what's that creepy-looking
ball of energy next to you?
Huh?!
[TERU]
Are you that thing's master?
No, it's haunting me.
[TERU]
Well, whatever.
There are a bunch of
questions I wanna ask you,
but first we need to
establish something.
How the hierarchy
works around here.
The what?
[DIMPLE] Now remember--
be careful, Shigeo.
Even you could get tripped up
if you don't take--
[TERU grunts]
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
What?!
Why do you keep
trying to attack me?
I haven't done anything
to you. Let's be fr--
[yells]
You've got him worried, pal.
[DIMPLE] Not that I don't
understand how he feels.
So far, I bet he's lived
his life as a big fish
in a very small pond.
And for the first time ever,
he's meeting someone who
could be his natural enemy.
If he doesn't establish
his superiority right away,
there will always be a struggle
for power between them.
But all that aside...
What's with those
weird movements?
They're kinda like wire stunts.
[MOB]
Telekinesis.
It lets you move objects
around and stuff.
So, are you up for doin' that?
Nah, makes me nauseous.
[groans]
[TERU] Using telekinesis,
I teleport to my opponents
and blow them away
with my Psycho Fist.
But, this strategy I use
against average people
looks like nothing more than
"weird movements" to him.
[TERU]
Damn it!
Shigeo...
You need to teach this
kid a lesson here.
Show him that you're not
someone to mess around with.
Come on. Look how he's standing.
He's gonna attack again.
You need to retaliate and hit
him with something big, too.
No, I can't.
You're not supposed
to use psychic powers
against people, remember?
Don't be such an idiot!
Look at who you're
talking about!
That kid's putting his
abilities to good use
and living a fulfilling life!
On the flipside, look at you.
You live quietly, one
boring day after another.
Do you really think
there's anything appealing
about you without
your psychic powers?
[ARATAKA]
Listen very closely, Mob.
You and I are different.
We were born with
special and unique powers
that other people don't have.
Even so we mustn't
let it get to our heads
and think we're special
or above them.
People who're fast...
People who sing well...
People who're book smart...
People who're good at talking...
People who can use
psychic powers...
They're all unique and you
can't put one over the other.
Confidence in your
powers is fine,
but you mustn't get conceited.
Depending on how we
choose to use them,
they can also be deadly weapons.
They're just the same as knives.
And you know what not
to do with them, right?
Point them at other people?
Then, you understand perfectly.
Don't ever forget that.
That's the moral
code people like us
with special powers
need to live by.
That gets ruined once
you know Reigen said it.
Anyway, I won't use
them in a fight.
Also, I don't wanna live a life
having to rely
on psychic powers.
I'm going to find
some other potential
within me to nurture.
Not to mention,
I started working out.
I'm gonna improve myself.
[DIMPLE]
You say that, but--
Shigeo!
How'd you like that?!
A telekinetic tackle with
all my weight behind it!
You've been given psychic powers
but choose not to
use them? How stupid!
There's no reason
to live your life
stooping to the level
of average people!
Bringing out other
potentials when you have
these powers is useless!
Working out? Studying?
Ridiculous! Leave that
crap to the masses!
[TERU] Brains, brawn, and
even the law are powerless
before a gift like mine!
I'm special--better than others!
And the entire world
revolves around me!
[DIMPLE] Jeez, I guess
there's no choice.
Hey, little boy.
How about we just end all this
and call it a draw, okay?
No way. Ending in a draw
with a guy like that
would be the biggest
disgrace of my life.
I understand you
feeding your ego,
but I can't have you
breaking Shigeo, either.
He's not going to fight back,
so obviously he's going to lose.
And that...
...won't work.
[MOB]
Dimple...
[DIMPLE] Most of my spiritual
power's been erased,
so I'm pretty much just
some leftover scraps.
Even so, I shouldn't
have any problem
serving up some discipline...
...to a cocky little
brat like you.
Shigeo's someone who
can become a god.
He's not some second-rate
loser like y--
Huh?
Dimple, no!
[TERU] I erased that thing
with my Psycho Wave
from the core.
So there shouldn't be
a single shred of him left.
Dimple's been--
He was exorcised...
[DIMPLE]
Forget about your club.
Work on your psychic
powers instead!
That Tsubomi's sure got
a nice ass, doesn't she?
Who the hell are you
calling a ladybug?!
How 'bout I send your
master to the hospital.
Come on! Listen to me!
I'll make ya popular.
Hey!
Want me to show you
how to use X-ray vision?
Ha! Fooled ya!
I don't know either, ya pervert!
Just for a sec, would
you do me a solid
and let me take over your body?
Dimple...
What's wrong?
Does it actually bother you that
your little pet was erased?
No, not really.
[TERU]
Yeah, I guess you wouldn't be.
After all, it was sort of
a pointless existence
to begin with.
'Course your existence
is as pointless as his.
Compared to someone like me,
you're third rate.
Just a small fry.
[DIMPLE]
You can become big, Shigeo!
I guarantee it!
Some idiots get the
wrong idea if everything
isn't spelled out for them.
They actually think they
can be someone "special"
if they put in a little effort.
[DIMPLE]
Be more confident!
After all, you're
the main character!
[gasps]
What's with that look?
Got something to say?
Tell me, why do you have
to belittle other people
by calling them things like
"average" or "small fry"?
Huh?
I mean, I just realized
Dimple might've been
an okay guy, that's all.
Compared to you, anyway.
What did you say?
Bastard...
I'm going to wipe that smug
look right off of your face!
I'll make you submit
to me with the power
of my psychic abilities!
So, I hope you're ready.
Nothing will stand in my way!
That's dangerous.
If it wasn't me,
you could hurt someone.
So, stop.
[TERU] Are you trying to tell
me that you won't get hurt?
I'll teach you to
underestimate my power!
[TERU yells]
[TERU grunting]
[TERU]
So...
You just gonna keep
defending yourself?
Look, I told you
to stop doing that.
Show me these powers of yours!
[TERU]
If you won't let me see them
we'll have to try
something else.
I'll know how much you can take
by administering
an endurance test.
[yelps]
[growls]
[grunts]
[yells]
[MOB gasps]
Ugh, that hurt.
The home ec room.
Knives are sharp and dangerous.
You shouldn't point them at--
Don't try to order
me around, runt.
You'll just reduce
your lifespan.
I have no intention
of killing him.
I just want him to fight back.
Will you stop this?
You'll cause an accident.
[TERU]
Huh?
[TERU] You did this
on purpose didn't you?
[whimpers]
[MOB]
It was an accident!
You're dead!
[TERU]
You're gonna pay for this.
I won't forgive you,
no matter what you say!
[gasps]
How dare you...
[TERU] You think I look
like some middle-aged
pencil-pusher now, don't you?!
Huh? I didn't say that.
[TERU]
But you thought it.
No. That's fine.
I'll admit it. It's the truth!
I look ridiculous! It's awful!
But now that it's come to this,
I feel I must know your name.
What is it?
My name's Shigeo.
Shigeo Kageyama.
[TERU]
Kageyama...
I'm Teruki. Teruki Hanazawa.
Oh, hi. Nice to
meet you, Teruki.
[TERU]
No, it's not nice.
It isn't as if we're
friends now or anything.
I just wanted to know
the name of my enemy
before I rip you to pieces!
[TERU yells]
[MOB]
Hey! Stop this already.
[TERU] If you want me
to stop, make me stop!
Come on! What's wrong?
You've gotta start
fighting back!
Stop stalling and face me!
I'm popular and the
main character of my story!
This entire world
and everything in it
revolves around me!
I am the chosen one--
me, Teruki Hanazawa!
I don't get it.
How are you able to find all
of this confidence in yourself?
[TERU]
What a stupid question!
It's my psychic
powers, of course!
I can control the
destiny and movement
of everything around me!
And you are my first enemy!
Now, attack me!
Let's have a test of strength!
No way.
Why not?! I told you it's okay!
Come at me!
Because...
I don't wanma hurt
you, that's why.
Huh?
[laughs]
Are you kidding? That's absurd!
It's not like I'm
some "Average Joe"
you're dealing with here!
I'm on a different
level than the rest
of the lowly creatures
on this planet!
Just because you're able
to use psychic powers,
you're no better than--
[TERU]
What'd you say?
Uh, I mean--
You're kinda goin'
overboard here.
[TERU]
Think so?
Well, you're the only person
who could make that argument.
That's why your very
existence pisses me off!
Hold on... That's it!
I think I just realized
why you hate me so much.
It's because you
and I are the same.
And not because we both
have psychic powers.
But the fact that you have
no confidence in yourself...
...same way that I don't.
If you take away your abilities,
there'll be nothing left.
You'll be empty.
You're scared of
that realization.
No friends, no standing out.
Just another loser who won't
leave a mark in this world.
That's me.
Don't you see?
Deep down, you're
the same as I am.
You just don't wanna
admit that you're nothing
without your psychic powers--
No!
[gasps]
Quit dreamin', idiot!
The two of us are completely
different, understand me?
We're the same.
From my perspective,
you're just an average person.
Shut up!
[MOB]
He's not using his powers.
[TERU]
What am I doing?
How did this happen?
Damn it, it's you!
This is all your
fault, you bastard!
Everything was perfect.
[STUDENT 5A]
You got another high score?
[TERU]
Long as I used my powers,
everything went just
the way I wanted.
[STUDENT 5B]
Look at that shot! Amazing!
[STUDENTS]
We're sorry! Please forgive us!
[TERU]
And yet, you took my world...
[STUDENT 05E] I-I made some
cookies, if you'd like some.
[TERU]
You... Your very existence...
...destroyed that!
Damn it!
Use them! Use your
psychic powers!
No... I won't...
I can't... use them...
...against people!
[TERU]
Is this it?!
What the hell was that?
How many times are
you gonna reject me?
Kageyama, didn't you say
you started working out?
That means, no matter
how hard you try,
whatever that was you called
a punch is all you've got.
Don't you get it?
People can't change that easily.
Just give it up.
Use your psychic powers.
Otherwise, I'm going to...
[RITSU]
Hey! Give it back!
Give us back our
New Year's money!
[THUG 5A] Don't get so
cocky, kid. I'll kill you.
[MOB]
Ritsu!
[THUG 5B]
You stay out of this, brat!
[THUGS laughing]
[RITSU]
Brother!
[MOB gasps]
[RITSU]
Bro... ther...
It hurts... brother...
[MOB]
I'm going to change.
No, I won't use them.
[MOB]
[MOB] It's coming...
I'm going to change.
[TERU]
Huh? Hey, Kageyama?
Hey! Wake up! Wait!
Don't leave me behind!
Kageyama...
[NARRATOR] The battle
between the two espers,
Shigeo Kageyama
and Teruki Hanazawa,
never reached its conclusion.
As a result of rejecting
each other's ideals,
there was no victor,
and they were only left
to fill the void in their
hearts with a feeling
of deep emptiness.
Or so it seemed...
[gasps]
What is that thing?
[TERU] Do you finally
feel like fighting?
Good!
In the end, you couldn't stay
true to your ideals, either!
Bring it! Ultimate Barrier!
[TERU groans]
[TERU coughing]
[TERU]
You used them! Kageyama!
You couldn't stand it anymore
and used your psychic powers!
[TERU laughs]
You broke down and used them
against another person!
So how does it feel?
[TERU]
Huh? Is he unconscious?
What is all this?
What the hell is this power?
What--
[gasps]
[TERU] My powers are being
sucked in by Kageyama...
No, that's not all...
All of the energy
in the atmosphere...
Are you telling me his vessel
is able to handle this much?
[NARRATOR]
Teru sensed something that must
never be touched in there.
Something incomparable,
its identity unknown.
[yelps]
[TERU]
You're kidding... What is this?!
What in the world did I awaken?
[screaming]
That's enough, I'm sorry!
I won't do it again! Please!
I won't use my psychic powers
against other people!
Oh... I guess...
I'm just an average
person after all.
[NARRATOR]
It was then that Mob realized:
He failed to change as
he had promised himself.
He caused another accident
because of his psychic powers.
[NARRATOR] He didn't know
where to direct his emotions.
His powerlessness born
from overwhelming
contradictions...
...and the feeling
he would never
be able to conquer himself...
Sadness.
[NARRATOR]
What had just occurred
was Mob's meager attempt
at resisting his inner self.
[MOB]
Hanazawa...
I-I'm sorry about
your clothes an--
[TERU]
W-Wait, Kageyama... I'm... I--
[groans] What happened?
Who won the fight?
Huh? Hey, look! It's Teru!
He's right over there.
Huh? What the hell?
[EDANO screams] He's been
beaten, stripped, and shaved!
[yelps] I'm not gonna let
that happen to my hair!
Those guys...
You saw it, Kageyama.
It's just as you said it was...
Take away our psychic powers,
and we're nothing more than--
[MUSASHI]
Kageyama!
[MOB]
Oh. Hey, guys.
We were worried about you.
You're not hurt, are you?
[MOB]
No, I'm fine. Really.
[MUSASHI]
All right, then. Good to hear.
Now let's all go back
and do some more squats!
[TERU]
There's nothing I can say.
I completely lost.
[NARRATOR] Mob searched
for about three hours,
but he couldn't
find Dimple anywhere.
[MOB]
I'm home.
[sighs]
[RITSU]
Shige?
Glad you're back.
Don't catch a cold.
[MOB]
Thanks.
You're home late today.
Wanna eat?
[MOB]
Nah. I'm gonna get to bed.
You seem kinda down.
Did somethin' happen?
If you wanna talk
about it, I'm here.
Goodnight, then.
[MOB]
Ritsu.
I'm sorry about that one time.
"That one time"?
You mean when you
got super carsick
and threw up into
the hood of my jacket?
[MOB] No... Well,
sorry about that, too.
I really can't remember
what happened...
...with that accident
involving my powers.
I've wondered... Back then...
What did I do to you, exactly?
[RITSU] Oh, you mean when
those high school kids
picked a fight with us.
Don't worry, you didn't
do anything to me.
One of the punks kicked
me away and I got hurt.
But you were there
to protect me.
Just forget about it,
it's no big deal.
Goodnight.
[REPORTER 5A] Earlier today,
sometime just after 5 PM,
countless people reported seeing
a supernatural phenomenon
in the stormy skies
above Seasoning City.
Among the rubble,
there were also
reports of what
looked like a person
flying up into the air,
but we have not
been able to confirm...
[RITSU]
Back then...
Ritsu!
[THUG 5B]
You stay out of this, brat!
[grunts]
[RITSU]
Brother!
[REPORTER 5A] The theory
that this was man-made
is gaining traction.
[RITSU] That wasn't him.
That wasn't my brother.
[MOB]
I have no appetite.
[RITSU sneezes]
[NARRATOR]
He caught a cold.
[ARATAKA]
His desire for psychic powers
makes Ritsu stray
from the right path.
Having no idea
that was happening,
Mob goes on a carefree
date with Tome.
Come on, Mob. This isn't
the time for that!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 6:
"Discord To Become One."
First-press limited edition?
That is the absolute
best decision.