[NARRATOR] Shigeo Kageyama,
also known as Mob,
second year of middle school.
[yawns]
[NARRATOR]
In one's life, the second year
of middle school kicks off
a most sensitive time.
It is commonly
known as adolescence.
Some thrive in athletics.
Some work hard on their studies.
Some devote themselves
to their hobbies.
Some polish their talents.
Some rebel.
While some fall for
the opposite sex,
tasting bittersweet, and
sometimes unrequited, love.
All those youthful desires form
the amalgamation
that is adolescence.
And, what was Mob doing
during this precious time?
Working as an assistant for
a psychic at 300 yen an hour.
The reason for your
curse is porn sites!
Wait a second. Porn sites?
Yes!
The jinx you carry on your
shoulders is a terrible one,
commonly referred to
as the One-Click Curse!
[CLIENT 2A]
A-A one-click curse contracted
from web porn?
They use illegal,
18-plus sites to curse
your shoulders while also
burdening you with their fees.
Nowadays, even
supernatural curses
are being digitized.
[CLIENT 2A]
Get real!
Who in the hell would believe
that giant tub of hogwash?
Relax and keep perfectly still.
I'll lift the curse right now.
No, there's no need to go--!
[grunts]
Your right shoulder is stiff.
The curse really
has a hold on you.
If you think I'm
payin' for this,
you've got another thing coming!
[CLIENT 2A grunting]
[CLIENT 2A]
What the--?
It actually feels pretty good!
[ARATAKA grunts]
[ARATAKA]
Sorcery Crush!
Finishing blow!
[NARRATOR] This is one
of Reigen's special moves.
He relieves the stress
from physical fatigue,
and gets rid of stiff
shoulders and back pain.
[sighs]
I believe that I was
able to lift the curse.
Do your shoulders
still feel heavy?
No! I'm sorry that
I doubted you.
Everything feels so much better!
May I come again
for a follow-up?
That'd be no problem!
Let's see...
The fee for a 40-minute
massage is 3,800 yen.
[ARATAKA] Idiot! Don't
call it a massage fee!
Call it the
"curse-dispelling" fee!
[MOB]
Two hundred yen is your change.
[ARATAKA]
Hey, here you go, Mob.
Feelin' kinda hungry?
Yes. Thanks for the food.
Master Reigen, you're
getting much better
at these massages, lately.
Well, yeah.
I've been tryin' different
things to improve,
like reading up on
some new techniques.
'Course, it's only effective
'cause of my spiritual power.
Hot!
Such a waste!
Master, I...
I've been thinking
about something...
Well, this is a rare occasion.
You don't start conversations.
[MOB]
Well...
I can use a little ESP, and I'm
different from other people,
so I came to discuss
that with you
and then I ended up
becoming your student.
At the time, I didn't
have anybody else
to talk to, so I was
and am grateful...
Because you teach me things,
and pay me on top of it all.
However, I wonder...
Is this really okay?
That's what's been on my mind.
[ARATAKA]
Does he think his pay's too low?
Or did he finally figure
out that I'm a fraud?
What do you mean exactly?
How do I put this...
Rather than waste my youth
working after school,
I have this sneaking suspicion
that there are other things
I should be experiencing
in my life.
Huh?!
Ah, so that's what
you're talkin' about!
Puberty! An important
phase in one's life.
Is there something specific
you wanna do right now?
Be in a band? Dance?
Hitchhike across the country?
No, I don't have anything
particular in mind.
Okay. Listen, Mob.
I understand what
you're going through,
but there's no need
to rush into things.
In my opinion,
the Going-Home Club
is what's best.
You're goofin' off
during the period
of your life you can
goof off the most,
and that makes you
a winner in my book.
So, I say, just keep
on bein' a slacker
and make money off me. Ya know?
[INUGAWA]
Now, hold on a second, Takenaka!
[TAKENAKA]
I get treated like a weirdo
just for being in
this stupid club!
[INUGAWA]
Take it easy!
I can't do it anymore!
[INUGAWA groans]
This isn't good.
A club's supposed have
five or more members, right?
So what should we
do now, President?
There's only one
thing we can do.
We've gotta find a new member.
And I mean now!
[knocking]
Maybe Takenaka changed
his mind and came back.
That's gotta be it! Takenaka!
[ALL gasp]
[TOKUGAWA]
I just received a submission
of resignation from this club.
It's...
[ALL]
The student council!
This club... is abolished.
Abolished?
Wow! Already?!
Sadly, I'm going to
have to ask you
to gather your things.
I recently had a
brand-new club request
for a room just like this.
Hold on!
We've only been down
to four members
for a few minutes!
I'm not gonna let you get
rid of the Telepathy Club!
The bond we share in
this Club's too strong!
The student council's
got nothing on us!
You think you're all
high and mighty
because of how you
part your hair?!
Shut your mouths.
You pissants don't really
wanna anger me, do you?
[ALL whimper]
If you're that desperate
to keep this joke
of a club going...
...then bring me
a brand new member
by the end of the
school day on Friday.
[INUGAWA]
B-By Friday? For real?
That only gives us two days.
Impossible.
[sighs]
Quit your whining!
If we ask everyone
we see to join,
we'll be able to
snag at least one!
But, that's not
gonna happen, now.
The recruiting season
ended a long time ago.
[TOME]
No! I'm gonna let this go!
We haven't overcome
obstacle after obstacle
to be shot down in such
a ridiculous way, have we?!
[ALL]
Uh, president?
We haven't done
a single thing.
[school bell rings]
[ALL panting]
I didn't even know this school
had a Telepathy Club.
It's creepy, so forget it.
Nah, I've got a job, guys.
What's the big deal?
If it's abolished,
it's abolished.
You should be studying.
Entrance exams are this year.
Well, are any guys
in your club hot?
[ALL panting]
I wanna leave time for dating.
I'd be worried about the stares,
and it seems too dangerous.
It's creepy, so forget it.
Sorry. It's creepy,
so forget it.
It's creepy, so forget it.
[ALL panting, groaning]
Creepy.
Nope.
Forget it.
Uh, no.
[STUDENT 2P]
Sounds lame. No.
Guess it really is impossible
to find new members
this time of year.
Not to mention we keep
getting called "creepy."
Now even I wanna quit.
[TOME gasps]
[screams]
[KIJIBAYASHI]
The president's lost it!
[SARUTA]
You need to calm down, okay?!
[gasps] The Going-Home Club...
[INUGAWA]
President!
I found him!
He's not in any
clubs or committees,
and he doesn't have any
friends or girlfriends.
Salt's go-homer
and all-round bum,
Shigeo Kageyama of
Year 2, Class 1.
Well, I'd say he's
basically right.
Well done, Inukawa!
Please allow me introduce
you to the other members:
Kijibayashi, and Saruta.
Nice to meet you.
How's it goin'?
And I'm the president
of this group,
Tome Kurata, Year 3, Class 5.
You can call me
All-The-Way Tome.
[INUGAWA]
She's pulling out all the stops!
Tome, huh? Hey,
what a coincidence!
That's my grandmother's name.
Uh-- See? The fates
have brought us together!
There you have it!
Please join the Telepathy Club!
I can't today.
What?!
Wait just a second, Mob!
Are you serious?
You actually have plans?
[MOB]
Mm-hm. I have to head out
to my after-school
exorcism job right now.
Exorcism? What is that
supposed to mean?
Ah! President!
I just remembered something!
This guy was sort of famous
back in grade school!
He could bend spoons
and make erasers move.
You know, like telekinesis!
In other words, he's an esper!
Stop being such a weirdo
and just join our club.
I mean, the exorcism can wait
a little while, right?
[phone ringing]
Mob. Hey, so how's
it goin' with you?
[MOB]
Uh, Master...
I'm being recruited into a club.
Is it okay if I'm a little late?
Just join and leave,
what's the big deal.
No, I have to wait until
the student council meeting
is over, then go submit
my club admission form.
Wait.
So if I told you to come
to work immediately,
you'd end up not joining?
Uh, yeah, but...
Shouldn't I try and keep
the promise I made
to the others first?
[ARATAKA] Then, it's not like
you actually want to join?
[MOB]
Not really, no.
'Kay, hurry on over.
Time for you to show 'em
how things are done
in the Going-Home Club.
He says he needs me right
away, so I'll be going now.
[TOME]
P-Put me on for a sec!
Look, I really need
Kageyama to join today
no matter what, understand?!
[ARATAKA] A girl, huh?
She must be trying to use Mob.
He's not really the type to
play any kind of sports stuff.
Probably isn't a good
idea to force him.
[TOME] We're not some
stupid sports club!
We're the Telepathy Club!
Huh? You're kidding me.
It's a club where we train
to feel telepathic powers.
Uh, that sounds shady as hell.
"Telepathic," huh?
Don't play dumb with me!
You know exactly what
I'm talking about!
I've heard from a reliable
source that Kageyama
has telekinesis and ESP!
I bet you're just
using him to solve cases
and get more customers
'cause you can't do it
on your own 'cause
you're a big phony!
Shut your mouth, amateur!
Don't you dare waste my
student's precious time
with your
middle-school nonsense!
[TOME]
What?!
Are you saying
that you don't care
if they shut down our club?
We'll get kicked out of the
room and have nowhere to go!
[gasps]
[MOB] Master, the club
president is crying,
so I think I should
join after all.
[ARATAKA] Don't be fooled!
They're crocodile tears!
Huh?
[ARATAKA] Bonds, memories,
and friendship...
It's not like any
of those things
will disappear just because
a club is abolished.
They're using you!
Trust me, they just don't
wanna lose their room,
their budget,
and their pointless
after-school time,
judging from what their
club sounds like to me.
See through it, Mob!
If that shady club goes down,
it's because it was damn
well meant to go down.
If you understand,
hurry up and come to work!
I get it. See you soon.
So, it looks like I gotta go.
Sorry about that.
I'll catch you guys later.
[INUGAWA]
Uh-- Wait a sec!
Please, just hear me out, okay?!
Now listen, the
president seriously
believes in telepathy
and all that stuff,
but honestly,
the rest of us here
just wanna lie
around and goof off.
Right now, we're
in middle school.
This is the only time
we're gonna be able
to do nothing and
get away with it!
Play cards with us in this lazy
little paradise we've
created! What do ya say?
You're not gonna find a more
carefree club than this.
We have until tomorrow
to set things straight,
so think it over?
You're our last hope, Kageyama!
Save us!
[MOB]
Mm...
[ARATAKA] So I assume you
turned them down, didn't ya?
Nuh-uh. I figured I'd take
a night to think about it.
[ARATAKA] You shouldn't
drag these things out, Mob.
[WOMAN 2A] I know, I couldn't
believe it myself when he--
You need to turn down
things you don't wanna do.
[MOB] Right now, the thing
I least wanna do...
,..is to be dressed
up like this.
Oh, there it is.
Saint Highso Girls' Academy.
It's a private
all-girls high school.
And, the clients
have asked us both
to meet up with
them on the roof.
Right.
Stop! What in the world
do you think you're doing?
[ARATAKA]
Excuse me?
You heard what I said!
Don't play dumb!
Oh, I'm just a student
here on my way to class.
Reporting from the front gate.
Suspicious individual here!
Requesting backup!
That's kinda mean, isn't it?
[OFFICER 2B]
Can it, you perverted weirdo!
I knew this wouldn't work.
But I'm glad they saw
through our disguises.
I didn't wanna sneak into
the school dressed like this.
[OFFICER 2B]
That was a close one, huh?
Now hurry along and stay
away from that freak.
Huh?
[OFFICER 2A] Don't you worry.
We'll deal with this phony.
[MOB]
Uh...
Huh?
[MOB]
What am I doing?
Won't I get in a lot of
trouble if I'm busted?
[MOB] He said we were
supposed to meet our clients
on the roof, but...
What would be the point...
[MOB]
Um, hello?
I've come from the
consultation office.
So, are you three
the clients, or uh--?
Huh? Who in the hell are you?
You don't look familiar.
Transfer student, right?
--Huh?
--[GIRL 2C] Consultation office?
You're here to see if
you can "get through"
to us thugs, is that it?
So annoying!
Do you really think
we're just gonna sit here
and let some twerp
like you lecture us?!
[MOB]
No, I'm just--
Why don't you mind your own
damn business, do-gooder?!
If you don't, we're gonna
make you regret it!
Sorry about that. My bad.
Ugh. Talk about a downer.
Let's get outta here.
[GIRL 2B]
Hmph!
[sighs]
[CHIHIRO]
Hello?
First thing you do is
get picked on by thugs.
Way to go.
We're the clients you're
here to meet with.
[CHIHIRO]
Isn't that Reigen guy coming?
He got caught up
at the front gate.
[MARI] Also, you both
came dressed as girls?
Really?
He couldn't get
permission to come in,
so we didn't have a choice.
[MARI]
I see.
We're sorry to make you
go through all that.
The school just refuses
to take us seriously
about any of this
supernatural stuff.
So that's why we called you.
What exactly was it
that you told them?
[MARI] Students' belongings
are mysteriously vanishing,
and we've been
hearing weird noises.
[CHIHIRO] Like, a
poltergeist or something.
[MARI] We heard things
have been spotted
floating through the air, too.
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah.
Apparently a bra
started floating around
in the locker room.
[MOB]
A bra?
We're sure it's not just
kids playing pranks.
It's definitely supernatural.
So we went online,
looked around,
then called the cheapest
exorcist in the area
and somehow ended up with you.
Looks like you get
what you pay for.
Huh?
Can't believe a guy
was trembling so much
just from dealing with
some high school girls.
You must be quite the
reliable gentleman.
[MOB]
Oh... Thank you.
That was sarcasm, duh!
She wasn't complimenting you!
[MARI] Are you sure we
can trust him with this?
[CHIHIRO] I have my doubts.
You seem pretty unreliable.
What's up?
Something wrong?
[MOB]
I-It's okay...
I just have to
perform an exorcism.
[MARI] Now, let us know if
you feel anything spiritual.
[MOB]
Right.
[CHIHIRO]
Well? Do you sense anything?
Maybe a little.
[CHIHIRO]
Is he being serious right now?
There. It's nearby.
[BOTH gasp]
Are you for real?
[GIRL 2C screams]
Someone help!
[BOTH gasp]
What's going on?
[GIRL 2C]
Something was here...
Something was just looking in
from the top of the door...
[CHIHIRO]
The windows are locked tight.
And we would've seen if somebody
tried to leave through the exit.
I'm going to follow the spirit.
[CHIHIRO]
Whatcha got? Anything so far?
[MARI]
So, we can trust you, right?
[MOB]
Right.
[MARI]
You still can't find it?
The spirit is angry.
[BOTH]
Huh?
And, if we keep pursuing it,
it might try something.
[CHIHIRO]
Wh-What are we gonna do?
[MARI] The basketball team
is practicing inside.
Let's end this.
[MOB]
I've trapped the spirit.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MOB]
Found you.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Huh?
[gasps]
It's huge!
[MARI]
What is that?! A ghost?!
Now you've done it,
you psychic brat.
How dare you trap me
in my own haunting grounds!
Are you going to try
to ruin my paradise?
[STUDENTS scream]
If so, then this
is what you'll get!
[SCENT GHOUL yells]
[CHIHIRO, MARI scream]
[SCENT-GHOUL grunts]
[SCENT-GHOUL]
Crap! I underestimated
his psychic abilities!
If I don't take a hostage,
he'll erase me!
[SCENT GHOUL sniffs]
You! You smell nice.
I choose you!
[screams]
Now, get back!
[SCENT GHOUL]
Huh?
[gasps]
[SCENT GHOUL groans]
[SCENT GHOUL groaning]
It's all over now.
[STUDENTS cheer]
Listen to them cheer.
Good for you, dude.
Thanks a lot.
You were pretty
reliable after all.
[SCENT GHOUL]
Damn it...
How?
How was I defeated
by a loser like you?
And I thought I'd
finally found happiness.
Honestly, you seem
to be similar to me.
Similar?
[SCENT GHOUL] The way you
get nervous around girls.
You're playing the loser role in
youth just as I did, aren't you?
[gasps]
[SCENT GHOUL]
I...
I finally started to
have fun after I died.
I was content.
But I guess that's all
over now. Isn't it...
[SCENT GHOUL]
So...
Are you living every day
to the fullest?
[MOB gasps]
[RITSU]
What's wrong?
You seem kinda out of it.
Somethin' bothering you?
Huh? No, I'm all right.
Thanks, though.
Sure. Okay then.
[INUGAWA]
Ah! Mob! You actually showed up!
We believed in you, Kageyama!
We knew you'd be back!
Now, hurry up and sign
this club admission form.
[TOME gasps]
Huh?
You're already here?
That was much faster
than I expected,
Vice President!
Well, I had to make
a little extra time
to show this room...
...to them.
[TOME gasps]
[TOKUGAWA]
This will become the club room
of the newly formed
Body Improvement Club.
And they'd like to get
set up as soon as possible.
What? Now, just
hold on a minute!
The Telepathy Club
won't be taken away!
Kageyama was about to sign all
the paperwork needed to join!
Seriously?
Are you out of your mind?
Uh...
Tell me, what grade are you in?
I'm a second year.
Have any experience
in other organizations?
No, I don't.
Do you have a close
friend or love interest
in the Telepathy Club?
I have an acquaintance.
Cram school?
I don't attend.
Do you study?
Not particularly.
[TOKUGAWA]
Any hobbies?
[MOB]
I, uh...
Don't you have anything
at all you want to do?
Huh?
If you let these
students goad you
into joining while having
no interest at all,
what exactly will
you gain from it?
Well, uh...
All I wanna do is live
every day to the fullest.
[TOKUGAWA] Will wasting time
after school with soda,
snacks, and video games
help you "live every day
to the fullest"?
If you want to join this club
of your own free will, go ahead.
However, you should carefully
think this through.
What is it you really
want to do with your life?
[MOB]
What I wanna do...
Do I have anything I wanna do?
Does everyone else
have something?
Something enjoyable?
Something I'm envious of?
What are they enjoying?
Clubs, hobbies, studying?
Now that I think about it,
hanging out with girls
might be fun.
[MOB gasps]
[MOB]
I did have a dream!
I wanted to confess my
feelings to my first love,
Tsubomi, and hold hands
as we walked home.
[MOB]
Take a look, Tsubomi!
When you make frogs float,
they start swimming.
Oh, wow! That's so cute.
[MOB] I can make the bar
all squishy, too.
[TSUBOMI gasps]
You're amazing, Mob!
[MOB]
Look!
I'm only showing you
these things, Tsubomi!
[sighs] I'm getting bored.
[gasps]
[BOY 2B]
The red team can move!
[gunshots]
You're fast, Akira!
[MOB]
That's it...
If I can change anything
by joining a club...
...then I'm gonna join!
Thank you for having me,
Body Improvement Club!
Wait, what'd you say?
Huh?
[MUSASHI]
Welcome aboard! Good to have ya!
[MOB]
Thank you!
[ANCHOR 2A]
Unable to locate the whereabouts
of the suspicious
individual who infiltrated
an all-girls' school
by crossdressing,
the whole area
is on high alert...
[ARATAKA]
Hot!
[ARATAKA] Mob joins the
Body Improvement Club.
On his way home, in an
attempt to be popular,
he goes to the main temple
of an obviously
shady-looking cult.
Are you sure about this, Mob?
Next time, on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 3:
"An Invite to a Meeting
Simply Put, I Just
Want to be Popular."
Recording it? That's also
a wise decision.