[KOYAMA] Guess we ran into
more trouble than expected.
[SAKURAI]
You mean you did.
[KOYAMA] Whatever! You only had
wimpy-looking ones to deal with.
[SAKURAI] I'm amazed this
one actually managed
to hurt you, Koyama.
He might get special treatment.
[KOYAMA]
No, it wasn't him.
Another guy got in my way,
and he was freakin' tough.
What? You're saying you
encountered another esper?
Yeah.
His psychic abilities were
really strong for a kid.
I couldn't match him in power,
so I used your spray.
[SAKURAI]
And where is that kid?
He wasn't part of the
mission, so I left him.
[SAKURAI] This is why I didn't
wanna pair up with you.
[KOYAMA]
Huh?
What's that?
Though he may not've
been your target,
our orders are to
make abducting kids
with the strongest psychic
powers our top priority!
If the division leader found out
that you messed up like this...
[TERADA laughing]
This all sounds very
interesting, indeed.
Just fill me in
on the situation.
We'll handle it ourselves.
I'll make sure
the division leader
never hears a peep about this.
[SAKURAI] This is the worst
person to overhear us.
[TERADA LACKEY A]
Pardon me for asking, Terada,
but wouldn't it be better to
bring the other Scars here?
No. I'm all that's
needed for this one.
Koyama's an idiot,
but he is powerful.
As an enemy,
that kid'll be a handful.
If he joins us, he'll
likely surpass me,
which is not an option.
So I don't consider
this a mission.
We're just gonna go nip
a little trouble in the bud.
Oh. And this is a
secret, by the way.
Let's say we're gonna
capture him, got it?
[TERADA LACKEY A]
Yes. Understood.
[TERU] What do you
wanna do, Kageyama?
This is a big organization.
Well-run too.
If you ask me,
I think you're going to need
somebody pretty special
on your side for this.
What do you mean?
[TERU] Somebody strong
and extremely smart.
You know, like somebody
right under your nose.
The Body Improvement Club!
Come on. There's no need for
you to play the fool here.
I'm talking about me!
So let's team up for this one.
Yeah? You sure, Hanazawa?
That came from outta
nowhere, didn't it?
[TERU] Look, I'm going
to end up clashing
with Claw again someday.
So I figured
I should do it now
while I still have a fighting
chance against them.
And by fighting chance,
I mean you.
You get serious about this,
and there's no way we'd lose.
[DIMPLE]
How can you say that?
We don't even have a
clue where to start.
Please! Let me help, too!
If there's anything
you need, let me know!
[TERU]
That won't be necessary.
I'm confident that
the next attacker
will be here any second.
But that's no good at all!
You should hurry and--
[bang]
[DIMPLE]
Hm?
Well, that was quicker
than I thought.
I'm looking for Kageyama.
Now which one of
you would that be?
Let's ask him some questions.
[SAKURAI] Do you think Terada
can win against that kid?
Come on, I'm stronger
than that guy.
That's not what
I'm asking you.
I wanted to know
if he could win.
Well, Terada's always
been cautious.
As strong as that kid was,
he was still only a kid.
If I hadn't let my guard down,
I could've squashed him
from the get-go.
Terada will probably
be fully prepared.
So if you ask me,
that kid's probably gonna go
through some harsh torture.
[screams]
Hurry up and spit it out.
I let my guard down!
He's tired.
Why don't you let him
catch his breath
and relax with a sip of water?
Do you have any idea how
cruel that suggestion is?
You don't have to be nice
to scum like these clowns.
But either way, it seems
like this guy won't talk.
Guess Claw's elite, the Scars,
live up to their name.
Despite fighting the boss
and ending up with a scar,
their abilities were
acknowledged,
and they became
part of the upper echelon.
And then this guy Terada
heard about the kid
who gave another Scar member,
Koyama, some trouble
and showed up.
Tough break, man. You ended up
being captured and tortured.
Now, if you feel
you're in danger,
tell us what you know, quickly.
I did! I did!
Everything you just said to me
is from the information
that I gave you!
True.
We know about their hideout,
the names, as well
as the abilities,
of all the other Scar members,
and a few other
things on top of that.
Maybe...
But I find it hard to believe
he'd tell us
everything so easily.
[TERADA]
Come on, kid. Gimme a break.
[KOYAMA]
What's the hold up?
It's past the time
for our regular upper
echelon meeting,
yet only 7 out of
the 11 are even here.
What a joke.
You've gotta wonder about
Claw's management system.
Terada knew about this
and left anyway.
So he should be fired!
Need I remind you that
you two just showed up?
[MUKAI] He's right. Makes you
about 30 minutes late.
[TAKEUCHI] This group is
comprised of numerous people
who have never worked
well with others.
As long as we do what we need
to do when we need to do it,
it's fine.
Ha! Then I guess
you're out, Koyama.
Heard you got your ass kicked
by a middle-schooler.
I didn't lose. And I
completed my mission.
You really are a simpleton,
you know that?
I suggest you stop
playing around
with these macho games and--
Shut your mouth, fugly!
[TSUCHIYA] I'll kill you,
you pierced chicken.
What?
Koyama. Go and take a seat.
The division leader is here.
[ISHIGURO]
Hope you weren't waiting long.
I just got a message
from the boss.
He's coming back to
Japan next month.
From what I've gathered,
he's going to pick
a couple of you
to be the upper
echelon back at HQ.
What? Are you serious?
[ISHIGURO] Yes, but it seems
doubtful he'd pick you,
considering how badly
you messed up today.
[MUTO LACKEY A]
That's right!
Basically, our goal
is world domination.
A skilled hawk can hide its
claws until the last second,
but we're not like that.
We're more like badass hawks
who don't hide our claws!
'Cause of that,
we'll steal all we can,
stand at the top of the world,
and lead humanity into its
rightful and glorious future!
Sound good?
Anyone wanna join us?
Any of you guys?
What morons.
Listen up, you cocky
Natural brats.
I wouldn't underestimate
the power of your trainers,
if I were you.
Remember, you noobs haven't even
been acknowledged
as members yet!
It's not a done deal!
[gasps]
Are you the person
in charge here?
No one in our group
has psychic powers.
This is a big misunderstanding,
so please let us go.
[MUTO] Did you all make
a secret agreement
to act as though you don't
have any psychic powers
in the hopes that
you would be freed?
Very well... You, come out here.
[KAITO whimpers]
The younger Shiratori brother.
[MUTO]
You have ten seconds.
Now show me your powers.
Be quick.
[RITSU]
Don't do it.
[MUTO]
All right. I understand.
Come. Nobody holds out on me.
[DAICHI]
K-Kaito!
[RITSU] They're gonna try to
brainwash us one by one.
[REI]
Why is this happening?
I just wanna go home!
[KAITO screams]
[KAITO]
Daichi, help!
Save me!
--[thud]
--[KAITO grunts]
Huh? Oh, no! What happened?
No... Kaito...
Wh-What have they done to you?
[door opens]
[ALL gasp]
[DAICHI]
H-He's dead...
[MUTO]
This will happen to all of you.
Take the evening to
reconsider your attitudes.
If you value your
pathetic lives.
[ALL whimering]
[TERU] I see it.
It's that building, right?
Yes. That's it.
[TERADA] These powers can't
be coming from a child.
[yelps]
Okay. We should go the
rest of the way on foot.
Terada's getting away.
[DIMPLE]
Should we go after him?
[TERU]
Hmm...
Considering how
badly we beat him,
I doubt he'll defy us again.
It'd just be a waste of time,
so let's continue on inside
and save your little brother.
Stupid brats.
You'll pay with your
lives for mocking me
and trampling my pride!
Telekinetic control.
Air Whips!
ith a range of 60 meters,
my powers will display
their true potential
here among the trees!
Kageyama! Are you all right?!
[MOB]
Yeah, but that startled me.
Where'd these trees come from?
[TERU]
It's that Terada guy.
He said he used telekinetic
powers in the shape of whips.
[TERADA]
Say your prayers, brats!
[TERU]
Terada!
If I let you escape me
and infiltrate the
facility like this,
my reputation will be ruined!
I've got you now, punk!
Well, I guess you aren't
so lame after all.
Oh, crap!
My powers are pretty
impressive, huh?
How long can you keep this up?
Kageyama!
I have to focus on keeping
these trees away from me.
Do something!
[MOB] I guess there're a
lot of ways to use powers.
[TERADA screams]
[sighs]
[TERU] Apparently, in the
face of absolute power,
technique and finesse
don't mean much.
You were finished
as soon as Kageyama
considered you an enemy.
This battle will
only last one night.
Let's escape.
Come on, man!
You saw what happened! If we
defy them, we're all dead!
Can't stop thinking about it.
Blood everywhere...
Shut up! Just stop it
If they're gonna torture me,
and brainwash me later,
I'd rather risk my life
trying to escape.
Maybe, but Shiratori's still
grieving over his brother.
It'll take him a while
to get over this.
Shiratori, help us
escape from this place.
Have a heart, dude!
Sure. I wanna get
outta here, too.
[TAKESHI]
Uh?
[DAICHI] Apparently,
my younger brother is fine.
We're telepaths, remember?
We can communicate
with each other
even if one of us is far away.
I was talking to him just now.
He said that he was shown a
glimpse of all of our bodies,
bloody and lifeless.
I'm not completely
sure how it works,
but I think that guy
has hypnotic powers
that show us illusions.
Must be how this organization
brainwashes people.
Through fear.
Good thing he chose
to take my brother.
'Cause together we saw
through their tricks.
So he's alive.
Yeah, but that doesn't
change the fact
that these people are dangerous.
And that's exactly why we
need to get out of here.
Let's make our move tonight.
Those trainers still
underestimate us,
and we should take
advantage of that.
Wait. Hey, what're you guys
talking about over there?
They must be workin'
on their escape plan.
Yeah whatever. They're not
gonna go anywhere.
Not the best time
for this, but...
[TAKESHI]
What's wrong?
Well, before I tell you
all of my plans,
I just wanted to know...
Uh...
What're your names again?
For real? Man! You don't
even remember our names?
What's wrong with you?!
You always were hard to read
with that gloomy face of yours.
But that is kinda rude.
[REI]
Now, now...
Let's put that behind us and
introduce ourselves again.
My name is Rei Kurosaki.
And my specialty
is clairvoyance.
Pleasure to work with you.
[RITSU]
Likewise.
Takeshi Hoshino.
I have some super strong
telekinetic powers.
Go Asahi.
I'm known as the godsend
who's able to burn down
everything in his path.
[RITSU]
By whom, exactly?
I look forward to
working with you.
My name is Daichi Shiratori.
Kaito's my little brother who
got taken away from us.
Let's hurry up and rescue Kaito,
then get the hell outta here.
[TAKESHI] But do you have any
kind of plan? We'll need one.
And don't forget, the trainers
are right over there.
[RITSU] I think they already
know we're trying to pull off
some sort of escape.
I'm sure there were other kids
who tried to do the same thing.
That would mean they're used
to dealing with escape attempts.
There goes any chance we had
of leaving this place.
Not necessarily.
If they're still
underestimating our powers,
then we can get outta here.
Really? How?
They probably let their guard
down 'cause we're kids.
They didn't check
our belongings.
A spoon? So do you just
carry that around everywhere?
Ignite!
[GO grunting]
[GO]
Now, Hoshino!
All right!
There!
[yelling]
Oh, it opened.
That was easier than I thought.
Well done, brats.
What's your next move? Huh?
Can't wait to hear about it.
Crap. Kageyama? What now?
Let me warn you;
it's safer in that cell.
[MUTO LACKEY B] Take one
step outside of there
and you'll regret it.
Kageyama?
You had a plan for
all this, didn't you?
Let's use Hoshino's
super strong telekinesis
and Asahi's fire power
to get outta here.
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[MUTO LACKEYS laughing]
Isn't that adorable?
[TAKESHI]
Listen, man...
You can't move something
as heavy as a person
with telekinesis.
It's impossible!
[GO]
I might be a pyrokinetic genius,
but even I can't set fire to
something that's moving.
Really sorry about this.
I'll take care of it, then.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MUTO LACKEY A] Ha, ha.
You'll all be held responsible.
If you think we're gonna hold
back on you 'cause you're kids,
you're mistaken.
I don't think that.
The three of you are
incompetent, disposable lackeys,
so why would I ever expect
you to have common sense?
[TAKESHI] Y-You're gonna
be killed, Kageyama.
[MUTO LACKEY A]
Oh, I see. Tough guy, huh?
Well, try protecting yourself
with that spoon-bending.
Mr. Natural!
[RITSU] Please, powers.
Do as I say. I really need you!
[TAKESHI]
Wh-Whoa... That's crazy!
Guess you didn't even
need us to open the lock.
[RITSU]
No, we needed to show them
that we were limited
in our powers.
This is a blind spot for
that security camera.
Let's have whoever's watching
think we're being disciplined
for a while and go rescue Kaito.
But even with my powers,
I don't know where he is.
Kurosaki.
At this point, we're gonna have
to rely on your clairvoyance.
Huh? My powers?
Can we count on you?
[gasps]
I'll-I'll give it my best.
[BOTH]
Oh... Give me a break...
[DIMPLE]
There're some tough-lookin' guys
by the entrance.
What should we do?
Shigeo, you really need
to think about this.
[TERU]
Wanna blow them away?
[DIMPLE] But we don't know
anything about 'em.
[MOB]
Uh. Umm...
Uh, let's focus
on rescuing Ritsu.
[DIMPLE]
That figures.
Okay then.
Oh! What's that technique?
It's the Air Whips.
I figured them out.
[BOTH screaming]
Sorry 'bout that.
[DIMPLE]
I'm not sure if you knew this,
but it's easier to possess
somebody when they're in shock.
[TERU]
You seem used to this, Dimple.
Are you a pretty
dangerous evil spirit?
No, of course not.
Right, Shigeo?
He's totally dangerous.
We might've been better off
if you'd possessed Terada,
'cause then we could've
used of his powers.
[DIMPLE] All espers have
their own mental protection.
As such, it makes it harder for
evil spirits to possess them.
That goes for you guys, too.
Not to mention,
I'm in a lot weaker state of
being than usual right now.
But normally, I'm able
to destroy people's minds
with little effort.
Honestly, you weren't a
big deal before, either.
Don't you get it?!
I was weakened then, too!
But why is that?
Oh, come on! Because
you almost exorcised--
Never mind, forget it.
[TERU]
All right! Let's go!
[RITSU]
Good.
The coast is clear. We're
counting on you, Kurosaki.
We should go this way.
[RITSU]
Let's move.
There, let's keep going.
Right.
Huh? Who're you guys?
[gasps]
[screams]
Easy! Are you
trying to kill him?
I guess we both hit
him at the same time.
Listen up, Kageyama.
Leave all these
lackey-grunts to me, okay?
Now, the first thing
we should do is find out
where they're
holding your brother.
Oh, okay. Sorry...
[TERU] He's so laid back. It's
really starting to throw me off.
Identify yourselves!
[yelping]
You abducted some
kids, didn't you?
Tell us where they are
or you're gonna get it.
Okay, okay. The children
are in the basement.
He said the basement.
There we go. That wasn't
so hard, now was it?
Thank goodness.
[CLAW SECURITY A] You fools.
We can hear you over the radio.
We got intruders.
Go capture 'em.
Hold up. Let's contact
the Scars about this.
You never know,
they might be espers.
[SAKURAI]
An emergency, huh?
[KOYAMA]
It's gotta be him.
That means Terada
got his ass kicked.
First it was Koyama,
and now Terada.
What's goin' on?
Again, I didn't lose to
that little twerp, got it?!
Terada just rushed into
things without thinking.
I'll take care of him this time.
I'm delighted beyond words
to have the opportunity
to face the little
runt again so soon.
Are you saying we should
leave the intruders to you?
Yes, exactly! Stay outta
my way, you bastards!
Don't rush things. There's more
than one intruder to deal with.
What does that matter?
You're gonna lose again.
Is that so?! You wanna
die first, Sakurai?
Stop it. You're both Scars.
[ISHIGURO]
That plan is fine, Koyama.
Find the intruders.
But you won't get away with
losing to the same person twice.
Yeah, I know.
[TERU] At this point,
we're up against the clock.
Let's split up and
look for your brother.
I'll head off to the right.
Kageyama, you take
the middle. Uh?
Lucky us. It looks like the
mini boss just showed up.
This guy again? Ah, great.
[KOYAMA]
We meet once more.
I beat the crap outta you,
and you can already move?
Well, I'm glad you're
doin' all right.
I'll kill you this
time, for sure.
And the rest of you.
Now let's both hit him together
with our full powers!
We don't have time for all that.
[KOYAMA]
Oh, yeah? Is that so?
What, are you tryin' to reserve
your stamina or somethin'?
You're gonna have to face me.
[laughing]
[KOYAMA]
Now die!
He's coming! Uh?
[KOYAMA]
What...? What's happening?
I can't move a finger.
[KOYAMA screams]
[MOB] Sorry. Didn't think
about that being so noisy.
I see.
You meant that you didn't have
time to try to hold back on him.
[TERU] Didn't expect
that from Kageyama.
[SAKURAI]
Koyama's not responding.
We're dealing with
someone powerful here.
Ha! How pathetic.
Let's go.
It's time to show
these intruders
the true terror of Claw.
[ARATAKA]
Mob infiltrates Claw's hideout
along with Teru
and all of his hair,
and the body-possessing Dimple.
They end up facing the Scars,
who refuse to hold back.
Think you can win this, Mob?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 10: "The Heinous
Aura Mastermind."
Option C involves Blu-rays,
manga volumes, and events!