[RITSU]
Hm? What's that?
[NARRATOR]
At the same time that Ritsu
was mistaking Dimple
for some sort of
creepy-looking balloon...
...the rumors going
around about Mob,
who had bested
Hanazawa, shadow leader
of Black Vinegar Middle
School, started to take on
a life of their own.
"White T Poison"...
This was the title given to Mob,
whose identity had
yet to be revealed.
[FUJI]
White T Poison...
I'll be the one to defeat him!
[MISO GANG gasps]
I'm gonna defeat this Poison guy
and make him admit
that I'm the best.
So the next target
is Salt Middle School.
White T Poison will
make excellent prey.
This is my chance to shine.
[NARRATOR]
And so, the rumor mill continued
churning out of control.
The fierce battle to see
who would take down
White T Poison was
about to begin.
Whew! Thanks for the help!
Somehow I managed
to make it back
from the particle
level all by myself.
But my spiritual
energy was way less
than it used to be.
So I couldn't get back
into the house anymore.
It appears that
low-level spirits
can't go anywhere
near this place
simply because
Shigeo lives here.
[RITSU]
What is that?
Some kinda talking
jellyfish-looking thing?
I know what needs to be done.
[DIMPLE]
Huh? Wanna shake hands?
[RITSU]
I have to exorcise it!
[DIMPLE]
Whoa, wait a second!
Stop kneeing me
in the face already!
I'm not a threat!
I'm Shigeo's friend!
You're what?
You could even
call me his mentor.
I'll let you off
the hook this time,
because you were obviously
confused and panicked.
But, that aside...
I've got a proposition.
How about you and I team up?
No thanks.
Hey, let's not be so hasty.
Wait a second, just hear me out.
You've only recently awakened
your psychic powers, right?
[RITSU gasps]
What? I have psychic powers now?
The fact that you
can see me is proof
of your newfound abilities.
The name's Dimple.
I'm what most people
would call a ghost.
So are my psychic powers
only strong enough
to allow me to see
ghosts like you?
[DIMPLE]
Well, I see you haven't realized
how to use them, yet.
Go ahead.
You should be able to do that
now, just like your brother.
[RITSU]
I shouldn't get my hopes up.
[DIMPLE]
Hm? What's the matter?
[RITSU] Doing anything like
this is way out of my reach.
[DIMPLE]
What's with him?
Does he have a
complex or something?
Well, that's understandable,
given who his
brother is and all.
[RITSU]
It... It's... It's not...
I can't do it!
Dimple!
It's not bending!
Hey, relax, kid.
[RITSU]
What the--?
Did I do that?
[DIMPLE]
Join me, little Ritsu...
Join me and I'll help you
surpass your brother.
[RITSU gasps]
[RITSU]
Surpass... my brother?
Is that even possible?
[RITSU] I can be more
powerful... than Shige?
Sure you can if you'll
let me use your body.
Ritsu's not eating with us?
I guess he's not hungry.
I wonder what could
be wrong with him.
Is he upset about something?
[MOB'S MOM]
No...
In fact, he seems oddly happy.
[RITSU] How do I get
to the point where I can
use my powers freely?
It's better to
actually try them out,
rather than explain,
little Ritsu.
Stop calling me that.
Fine, then. Plain
old Ritsu it is.
Now, how 'bout you
close your eyes,
and relax your entire body.
[DIMPLE] Prepare for
possession, you fool!
Now your body's mine
for the taking!
[DIMPLE]
Heh, heh!
What?!
I've possessed him,
but I can't control him?
Hey, Dimple. Where'd you go?
[DIMPLE] It's because
my spiritual powers
have become so weak... Damn it!
[shcool bell rings]
[STUDENT 7A]
I heard the student council
took care of the problem.
[STUDENT 7B] You mean with
the pervy gang leader?
[STUDENT 7C]
Wow, way to go.
[STUDENT 7D] They're the
heroes of the school.
[SHINJI]
Yamazaki, Year 2, Class 4.
I'd like a word with you.
Huh? What do you want?
[SHINJI]
Your coat. It isn't buttoned.
[YAMAZAKI]
So what? Buzz off.
I can do it.
Now, I can use psychic
powers, Dimple.
[DIMPLE]
That's because I'm helping
to regulate their output.
But rest assured,
these abilities
have always been
there, lying dormant.
And it's my guess
that the reason
they came out now is
due to some radical
change in your emotional state.
Have you endured some
"way-above-average"
stress levels lately?
Like pooping your
pants in public,
or getting caught peeking
into the girls' locker room?
What kind of a question is that?
I'd never do those things.
I was joking, Ritsu.
Don't be so damn serious. Oh...
That's right.
You're an honor
student, aren't ya?
Then, what is it?
Did you do something bad?
[SHINJI]
A rumor's going around that
you're stealing the
girls' gym clothes.
Huh? The hell are
you talkin' about?
[SHINJI] The student council
did some investigating.
And what'd we find
out, Kageyama?
We discovered some of
the girl's gym clothes
tucked away and
hidden in your bag.
What?! You guys are lyin'!
[SHINJI]
Deny it if you want,
but that may not
go so well for you.
You see, the school's
been very strict
with deviants lately.
[SHINJI] But I'm here to
offer you a way out of this.
Simply admit Onigawara
ordered you to do these things.
If you comply, you're
merely another victim.
Sound good? Now button up.
[NARRATOR] Using these
and other similar methods,
the whole school was cleaned up,
turning it into the optimal
environment for academics.
However, because
of the considerably
immoral strategy that
was used upon certain
delinquent students to
accomplish this outcome,
a deep scar would
be forever engraved
on their lives.
And the two student
council members
saddled with this task had
to live with that burden.
So they either became
drunk with power,
feeling a delusional sense
of accomplishment,
or they suffered greatly.
[DIMPLE]
Whoa!
Ritsu, your power's
grown even more!
[RITSU]
I see, corruption and guilt...
Those are the things
that become fuel
for my powers.
Whatever you're doing,
it is working!
What's the matter?
Something eating at you?
[RITSU] Dimple, you just
won't stop talking.
Oh?
[RITSU]
Tell me.
If I could control my
powers on my own,
would I be able to
make you disappear?
[DIMPLE] Wait, is his
personality changing, too?
Whoa! S-Seriously?
Amazing... That's
incredible, Kageyama!
Want me to keep going?
If you'd like to see
a bigger example,
I could fold your car in half.
[MITSUURA]
What?!
[MITSUURA] What in the
hell's gotten into him??
[sighs]
Excuse me...
May I help you with something?
I heard from Kamuro
that you're the one
who's been planting all
that false evidence around.
Tell me, are you the
one who framed us?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Dimple.
Leave it to me.
Even if I did do such a thing...
Now it's too late.
[grunts]
Why, you little...
Who in the hell do
ya think we are?!
[growls]
[gasps, screams]
That does it! Get him!
You're dead meat!
[chuckles]
[GIRL 7A]
A fight.
[GIRL 7B]
Scary!
[GIRL 7A] But isn't that guy's
hair, like, totally amazing?
Check it out!
[GIRL 7B]
You're right!
[GIRL 7C]
Whoa!
[TERU]
Hey, you there.
What's up?
[DIMPLE]
Gah! That's...
I think you've done enough.
If you depend on that,
you'll get hurt.
You've got the wrong
idea about this.
I know...
You think you're really special.
It's hard looking at
someone who reminds me
of the way I used to be.
Consider this a warning.
Don't try to live relying
on psychic powers.
[RITSU gasps]
Are you another esper like me?
I have no idea who you are...
...but I have no need to
take warnings from you.
Don't mess with this guy!
He's not someone you can beat!
[RITSU]
I'm sure he's not much different
from the people at
the Awakening Lab.
I wanna size up our powers.
[DIMPLE]
Ritsu?! You idiot!
Don't do it!
[gasps]
[TERU] Why, thank you
for the handshake.
I'm Teruki Hanazawa. Pleasure.
Don't try to fight him!
Let go! Now!
Having trouble
standing, are you?
You're so young.
[GIRLS scream]
Now's your chance! Run for it!
[RITSU panting]
[RITSU] I was surprised
at how strong he was,
back there.
Maybe it's 'cause his
brain's so developed.
Could that coincide
with his power level?
No.
His brain's not huge--
that was a wig.
Though I'm not sure
why he was wearing it.
[RITSU]
I'm so frustrated.
How could I lose to someone
other than my brother?
Dimple. I wanna
get even stronger.
So I won't lose to
anyone ever again.
[WOMAN 7A]
Little boy.
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
[WOMAN 7A]
This is the Vase of Happiness.
A renowned potter put his heart
and soul into making
it a one of a kind.
Anyone who buys this item
will surely be blessed.
Now it normally goes
for about 2.5 million yen,
but I'll make you a deal:
800,000 yen just for you.
I don't have that kind of money.
Then I'll drop the
price to 500,000.
[MOB] Well, I don't have
500,000 yen, either.
Running low on funds?
Just call your
mommy and ask her.
I'm pretty sure my mom
also wouldn't buy it.
[WOMAN 7A]
This isn't over yet, kid.
Hey, why don't you touch it?
The grainy texture
feels so nice.
--Here.
--[MOB] Er, I can't really tell.
[gasps]
[MOB]
That was close.
[WOMAN 7A]
How did he--?
You should be careful.
Hey, you broke it.
[gasps]
Wait! I-I didn't--!
[WOMAN 7A] What? You're going
to say it was my fault?
[MOB]
Uh-- No, but...
[WOMAN 7A]
Look, little boy...
Problems that you can
solve with money
are better than those
that you can't.
Got it?
Oh, what a run of bad luck.
Did you break that, sir?
Do you have a phone?
I-I don't...
[phone rings]
[MOB gasps]
[MAN 7A]
That rang at the perfect time.
Why don't you answer it?
[ARATAKA]
Now what are you doing, Mob?
Why'd you make me
come down here, anyway?
You know I'm taking
a meeting soon.
Would you happen to be
this boy's guardian, sir?
Oh, I get it.
[MAN 07A] It's 5,000,000
yen to replace this.
You mean that huge
piece of junk?
No way it's worth that.
Wait... What'd you say?
Listen, you don't seem
to know how things work.
Maybe I'll teach you a lesson.
[ARATAKA]
Ow! Ow! Ow!
You totally cracked my clavicle.
That's gonna cost
you, my friend.
[MAN 7A]
Huh?
The hospital will fix me up
for about a million yen.
You can't be serious, you
dumbass! That's outrageous!
[ARATAKA] Verbal abuse causes
psychological damage.
So, that's gonna
be another million.
Listen, you!
You've got bad breath.
Subjecting me to
it's another million.
[MAN 07A]
What the hell?!
[ARATAKA] Your voice is
causing me ear damage.
That'll be another million.
Look. You frayed my shirt.
Then, that's one more million
for garment damage.
Now, that's equal
to what he owes you
for the vase.
I'm no stranger to
the kind of business
you guys are running.
Come on, Mob. Let's go.
You're not goin' anywhere.
There's no escape!
This boy's misfortune
was decided
the moment he broke
the Vase of Happiness.
I'd hate for anything
bad to happen to him!
[ARATAKA]
"Misfortune"? "Bad things"?
Before I came here,
I was talking
to someone who'd been
haunted by an evil spirit.
Apparently, it can
be passed along,
and now the spirit's
haunting me.
I hear strange noises at night,
weird things keep
popping up in pictures,
doors open and
shut on their own.
It becomes unbearable.
Who knows?
The spirit might have
transferred to you guys by now.
Be careful when you
go to bed tonight.
Huh? A haunting?
Doesn't feel too great, does it?
That's pretty much exactly
what you guys are doing.
[BOTH laugh]
A ghost?
What are you, a
little kid? So scary!
[WOMAN 7A, MAN 7A gasp]
[BOTH shriek]
[BOTH whimpering]
[BOTH scream]
[ARATAKA] That sure
shut those two up quick.
And I gotta say...
That last bit was great, Mob.
Huh?
You shook the building
to scare them, didn't ya?
Nu-uh.
I thought all that was you
sending the evil spirit
after those two.
Wait a second.
Are you saying you
couldn't see--?
[ARATAKA]
Come on.
Of course I could see it.
I can't believe them.
Con artists are
terrible people.
The worst of the worst.
You said it.
Only the lowest of the
low try to take advantage
of someone's weakness and
exploit it for their own gain.
[TOKUGAWA]
What? You as well?
Yes.
He said, "So, you're
trash, too?"
And all I was doing was
chewing some gum during class.
[TOKUGAWA] Kamuro, this school
doesn't belong to you.
We still have other pieces
of trash to deal with.
Let's keep things moving.
[RITSU]
You plan to continue this?
[SHINJI]
Come on.
You're not going to
suggest we stop, are you?
[RITSU] No.
It just that you make me
feel sick, that's all.
You get off on
this, don't you?
[SHINJI chuckles]
I was correct in choosing
you as an accomplice.
If you knew, why did
you decide to help me?
[RITSU]
Because I was tired.
Just tired of being myself.
Of everything. Maybe
I wanted to find out
what it would feel
like to be a fool.
There's more to it than that.
In the end, it made
us both popular.
You and I have
become the heroes
of this entire school.
So "looks-too-old-
for-school-guy"
wanted to be popular?
[RITSU] I, on the other
hand, have obtained
a much bigger world.
By the way, President,
did you happen to find
any telepaths out there?
If I did, I wouldn't
be here now, would I?
Inukawa!
You can't put a bomb there!
That's cheating!
Kurata, would you mind being
a little quieter, please?
'Cause I've still got a few more
things I wanna say over here.
[TOME]
Oh. Sorry.
[ONIGAWARA]
Musashi, that's enough.
[MUSASHI]
No, it's not! Now, man up!
Go to class, Onigawara!
I've got no place there.
I mean, none of my friends
will even talk to me anymore.
[door scrapes]
Oh, a visitor.
[yelps]
The student council president!
I see this place is
as rotten as the rumors
led me to believe.
More to the point...
What are you doing
on campus, Onigawara?
Infiltrating the school when you
haven't been showing
up to class?
[ONIGAWARA]
No!
But I can't stay at home!
If I do, my mom will
ask me why I'm not--
[MUSASHI]
Listen to me, President.
Onigawara didn't do
what you think he did.
Should I have you all dealt with
for being his accomplices?
'Cause, don't forget,
I have the power to do so.
--[MUSASHI] What?!
--[STUDENT 7D] President...
President, some weird guy just
showed up at the school gates.
What should we do?
It never ends.
The problems pile up
one after another.
So who are you guys?
I told the other nerd that
I'm here for White T Poison!
"White T Poison"?
What on earth is that?
[KENZAKI]
Don't play dumb!
He's the talk of all
the thugs right now.
I'll deal with him, President.
That should settle things.
[KENZAKI groans]
[SHINJI]
Whoa! You really laid him out!
[RITSU]
It was done in self defense.
Not to mention,
they were students
from another school,
so it shouldn't matter.
[SHINJI] Not only is he
willing to get into a fight,
he's incredibly strong, too.
[GANG MAN 7A]
Hey...
Are you the guy that
knocked out Kenzaki?
Huh?
Who's better known
as White T Poison?
Wh-What are you--
I was just watching, I didn't--!
[GANG MAN 7A] Then who the
hell is White T Poison?!
I don't--
That's enough!
It's time to stop this!
Man, you look awful.
[SHINJI]
This is all your fault!
I became a victim
because of you!
You taught a gang leader from
another school a lesson!
Don't you understand?!
If that's true, then so be it.
He got what was coming to him.
Y-You're kidding me!
No! Not again!
Are you that White T Poison guy?
[SHINJI whimpering]
[SHINJI screams]
[SHINJI'S DAD]
Oh, it's you, Tokugawa.
Shinji doesn't wanna
see anyone right now.
Is that so?
[RITSU]
Disgusting.
For someone who wanted
to get rid of the garbage,
you should've started
with your own room.
[SHINJI gasps]
[SHINJI]
H-How did you get in here?
No matter.
Either way, we still have trash
to contend with at school.
No way!
I'm done with all of that!
Get out of here!
It's too late.
We've both done
something unforgivable
with our roles in this.
No one's going to
save us, understand?
[whimpering]
[RITSU] It seems the
puppet's been broken.
The school is finally clean.
[DIMPLE]
So now whatcha gonna do?
Ya know thugs from
the other schools
are gonna keep showin' up.
With these powers, I can
do whatever I want.
Yeah!
You could be a
psychic superstar!
Dimple...
You're trying to use me
as well, aren't you?
[DIMPLE]
Huh?!
What are you
talking about, Ritsu?
We're partners!
I'm on your side!
Oh, here they come.
More than usual today.
[TERU] I came to see what was
going on and, of course...
Are you that White T Poison guy
who beat Hanazawa and Kenzaki?
[TERU] What?! Is he
pretending to be Kageyama?
[RITSU] Think things'll
finally be settled
once I deal with you guys,
so let's just say
you found your man.
[TERU] It looks like
I'm gonna have to ask him
about this, myself.
[KOYAMA]
I found something interesting.
I believe he's the one
you were looking for.
I'll apprehend him
and head back.
But before that,
I should watch for a bit
and see how good he is.
Possession.
All right. Let's
get this over with.
[GANG MEMBERS] Oh! You think
it's gonna be that easy?!
Get ready for a pounding!
Don't stop! Go get
him, you chickens!
We would...
But, we... can't move!
Hey, Dimple. Let's go all out.
[GANG MEMBERS scream]
Now's my chance!
[AKAGI]
Huh?
[AKAGI screams]
Your magic tricks won't
work on me, White T Pois--
[GANG 7A]
Hey, what's goin' on here?
[GANG 7B]
Is White T Poison doing that?
[BANDAI] Maybe, but he
can't stop all of us!
Let's charge him!
[GANG MEMBERS gasp]
Don't worry, I won't
judge any of you.
I've come to
understand something.
When people wander
from the right path
in their lives, there
usually isn't any reason.
I guess it's always
been that way.
I'm facing enemies that
have lost the will to fight,
moving forward for
the sake of violence.
There's no reason there.
This kind of freedom is strong.
Boundless.
I'm much freer than all of you.
Why, you ask?
I'll tell you. Because
I've lost my limits.
I've obtained loss.
[footsteps]
[RITSU gasps]
It's you What are
you doing, Ritsu?
[ARATAKA]
The brothers confront each other
in an alley after school.
Suddenly, an adult esper we've
previously seen appears
out of nowhere.
Hey, Mob, that guy's
really bad news!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 ,
Episode 8: "The Older Brother
Bows Destructive Intent."
I recommend the convenient
option A with the Blu-ray set!