[wind gusting]
[groaning softly]
[wind blowing harder]
[FUBUKI]
Yumi.
Let's end this.
[BOTH grunt]
Asuka.
[groaning]
We'll never let you hurt Asuka!
♪
It doesn't matter how many
of you there might be,
I will eliminate
every single shinobi.
For Fubuki's sake.
Even if it costs me my own life!
[ASUKA]
Hey.
-At least tell me one thing.
-[KATSURAGI] Asuka.
Why are you willing to risk
everything for Fubuki?
If you must know, it's because
her mother once saved my life.
You find that bizarre,
don't you?
That I would be willing
to face death
in order to repay an old debt?
No, not at all.
I think it's admirable.
I can see where
you're coming from.
[RASETSU]
But?
But...
I can't allow you
to destroy the shinobi!
[RASETSU]
So, what do you intend to do?
Seal me away like the others?
[ASUKA]
Exactly!
Because I'm not afraid
to die, either!
Hey!
♪
So, please. Lend me
your strength, everybody!
[ALL]
Shinobi Transformation!
♪
[MINORI] Hey. You sure this is
the right way?
Yes. Last I saw, Yumi was headed
in this direction.
I'm just so worried.
I really hope
that she's all right.
[blades clanging in distance]
Look over there!
[YOZAKURA]
Shinobi Transformation!
[BOTH yell]
[grunting]
[IKARUGA screams]
[ALL grunt]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[groaning]
Now, Asuka! Do it!
Right!
Super Secret Ninja Art!
Fuma Korin!
[screaming]
It's done! [groans]
Finally,
this can all end.
[RASETSU groaning]
Rasetsu, please be careful.
They will undoubtedly attempt
to use Fuma Korin.
Of course,
I am fighting shinobi,
so I'd expect nothing less.
Besides, do you really think
I'll be so easy to seal?
Of course not.
I'll be counting
on your strength until the end.
More power.
I just need a little more power!
That's all I want.
Even if I...
[sobs]
Fubuki, this is goodbye.
[yelling, roaring]
[growling]
-[HOMURA] What the hell?
-No way!
[roaring]
Well, it's about time
you showed us
the monster you really are!
[grunts]
That's crazy!
It could destroy a whole city
in this form!
We have to stop it here!
[ASUKA groaning]
♪
[FUBUKI]
Why am I thinking of that now?
♪
[RASETSU growling]
Just hang in there, Asuka!
Whatever, Homura.
You should be worrying
about yourself, not me.
Don't be stupid.
If anything, I'm just
getting warmed up.
Hey, you're not ready
to bow out, are you?
[giggles]
Of course not.
But when I tried
to use Fuma Korin on her,
it didn't work.
So now what?
[HOMURA] It didn't work
because you tried it alone.
-Maybe we should do it together.
-What?
I said we're gonna use
Fuma Korin on her.
Homura! You don't know
how to use that technique!
[HOMURA] I've seen you do it
a bunch of times.
So, it'll be okay.
[ASUKA]
But you haven't practiced!
[HOMURA]
Give me a break.
If you can do it,
then I most certainly can too!
Listen to me,
this move could kill you!
Oh. Well, I'm not really worried
about that now.
-[ASUKA] Why not?
-[HOMURA] Think about it.
There's no way I'm gonna die.
I'll never die.
[BOTH] Not until I
master the path of the shinobi!
Okay, are you ready?
Yep! Let's do it!
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH]
Hien Ranbu!
[RASETSU grunts]
Asuka, she's weakened!
Right, this is our chance!
[BOTH]
Super-Secret Ninja Art!
Fuma Korin!
[growling]
[yelling]
[chuckling]
♪
[YUMI gasps]
[YUMI screaming]
♪
[ice shatters]
[rumbling]
♪
[whooshing]
[FUBUKI]
You two again?
What do you want?
To save somebody.
In that case,
I'm afraid you're too late.
Yumi has most likely sunk to
the bottom of the lake by now.
Well, believe it or not,
Yumi isn't the person
who needs saving.
[GEKKOU] The one we came
to help is in front of us.
It's you, Lady Fubuki.
[FUBUKI]
You help me?
You must be joking.
Sorry, we're not.
[FUBUKI]
Go on then.
Don't just stand there.
Or perhaps I should make
the first move!
What are you doing?
This is a technique
that we both learned from Yumi.
It's the justice
that Master Kurokage taught her.
She called it warmth.
Unhand me!
I had warmth, but who was it
that ripped
everything away from me?
It was the shinobi!
But if you want,
you can have that warmth again!
[GEKKOU] That's right,
because we still care about you!
I have the blood of a youma!
Human warmth can't reach me,
and it'll never be able to!
[GIRLS gasping]
Let go!
If you don't, you'll die!
No, we won't abandon you!
Not now, or ever!
We'll always be here!
[GIRLS screaming]
[GROUP grunts]
[FUBUKI]
What are you doing here?
You're all too late.
Yumi's dead.
I killed her.
[GIRLS gasp]
♪
[wind whistling]
[BOTH chuckle]
[FUBUKI]
Have you given up on fighting?
[YOZAKURA]
No.
There's no point in begging
for your life, you know.
We won't be fighting you.
That's someone else's job.
-Yep!
-Right.
In the end,
it's totally gotta be Yumi.
Are you all deaf
or did I not make myself clear?
I told you that she's dead.
[ALL chuckle]
Impossible.
♪
[gasps]
[roars]
[ASUKA]
No. We can't seal her.
Damn it.
[MIYABI]
Wow, this is pathetic.
[ASUKA]
Miyabi?
♪
[MIYABI yells]
I told you, my goal is
to become the ultimate shinobi!
What are you doing?
[MIYABI] But I still have
a long way to go.
Because I almost forgot what
I learned when I lost my mother.
-She can't be.
-But she is!
When you fight for
the sole purpose of revenge,
you'll never attain
true strength.
And so...
Fuma Korin!
[yells]
[roaring]
[gasping]
♪
[gasps]
I have no regrets,
because in the end,
I fought for Fubuki,
and that's all that matters.
Rasetsu, I'm sorry!
♪
-[RASETSU] Fubuki...
-[FUBUKI gasps]
♪
I see, Rasetsu.
[grunts]
Yumi!
[YUMI]
Let's go!
Why won't you die?
No matter what,
I'll keep on fighting!
Whatever it takes for you
to understand my power!
I... No.
You and I...
we have to work together
to end this war
between shinobi and youma!
Being an unyielding shield isn't
going to help either of us.
But a sword filled with warmth
can save everyone!
That is my justice!
The justice...
of the moon!
♪
[FUBUKI gasps]
[FUBUKI screams]
[wind whooshing]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[YOUMA growling]
-Take this!
-[YOUMA screeching]
Excellent work, as usual.
Well, annihilating youma
is the reason I exist.
It's my purpose.
For all of eternity.
[SHINOBI talking indistinctly]
Yes, I understand.
I'll be sure to tell
everyone else.
So, what's going on?
Who were you talking to?
Oh, it's Suzune-Sensei.
She said they've just
finished up at the Kikai Dome.
That's wonderful!
Yes, and everyone is safe.
Kiriya-Sensei, too?
[HARUKA]
Of course!
And Master Hanzou and Sayuri
have already sealed away
all the youma.
[HOMURA grunts]
♪
-[MIYABI grunts]
-[ASUKA laughs]
♪
[wind gusting]
[footsteps approaching]
You dropped this earlier.
All right, who's ready
to head home?
-Oh, I am!
-[YUMI] Let's go.
Yeah, it's freezing here.
[SHIKI]
I want a hot bath.
[MINORI]
Me, too!
♪
Hey, we could use more ornaments
on this side of the tree.
No problem,
just leave it to me!
Here. Give me some
and I can help, too.
I just spoke to Asuka,
and she said that she and Yumi
will be here soon.
Excuse me.
Why do I have to wear this?
The entire outfit seems
really impractical.
But...
you can't have Christmas
without a reindeer.
That doesn't explain
the squid outfit.
♪
[grunting]
She's so amazing.
Yeah. Just look at the way
the sweat is dripping
from her body.
This sucks.
It's Christmas day, after all!
Why do we have to sit here
and train?
Don't be sad, Ryobi.
Think of it
as a new kinky technique,
AKA a tech-kink, it'll make
your whole body go jingle bells!
See?
Jingle. Bells!
I'm feeling extra jingly!
[RYOBI]
That doesn't even make sense,
-you stupid dog!
-[RYONA screams]
[MIYABI]
I can't afford to rest.
No matter what, I have to become
the ultimate shinobi!
[RENKA]
Check it out!
Our giant snowman
is finally finished!
Whatevs. That thing
was like a ton of work.
Hold up. It feels like
it's missing something.
It needs some decorations!
Yeah, since it's Christmas!
Now it's the bomb!
[KAFURU]
But those are fireworks.
Don't bombs explode?
They sure do!
[laughter]
[KAFURU]
You're gonna get us killed.
-What's with all that noise?
-[KAGURA chuckles]
It's fine.
Just a Christmas celebration.
♪
[HARUKA sighs] I can't believe
we're working on Christmas.
[HOMURA]
Well, we were so busy fighting
we weren't able
to pick up any shifts.
[MIRAI] That's true,
but it's not like working today
is going to earn us
any turkeys or a cake.
That's a good point.
Cheer up, guys,
I can always make us
a bean sprout cake
for Christmas, 'kay?
It's okay, ladies,
-there's no need to worry.
-[YOMI] Huh?
I spoke to the manager,
and he said if we work hard,
that he'll just give us
whatever cakes and turkey
they have left over for free!
[GIRLS gasp]
Okay, let's get to it!
Because when the five of us
work together,
there's nothing we can't do!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[YUMI]
Hey, Asuka.
How've you been feeling lately?
Oh.
I'm just fine now,
and I'm even back
to training with everyone.
Plus the marks have
completely disappeared.
Are you sure?
You still shouldn't
push yourself too hard.
Honestly, I'm good.
The only thing I want right now
is to enjoy the holidays
with everybody.
We worked so hard to get here.
True, let's have fun.
Oh, I'm planning on it!
I can't wait.
It's Fubuki.
I'm not going to kill
any more youma.
As a shinobi, I'll risk my life
to seal them away.
No matter what anyone tells me,
I've made up my mind.
That is my plan as well.
You know, if everything
in this world has a counterpart,
then the shinobi
and youma are a pair.
Perhaps one day,
you and I will face off again.
Who knows what the future holds?
[YUMI gasps]
[FUBUKI]
I want you to have it.
Are you sure?
Yes, I don't need it.
Not like I once did.
[YUMI]
I'll cherish it.
[FUBUKI]
Farewell.
I'm off to try and find my place
in this human world.
Hey!
Fubuki, I never had
the opportunity to fight you.
One day, let's continue
the Shinobi Masters.
[chuckles]
♪
You two.
Why are you still following me?
Aren't you ever lonely
by yourself?
[FUBUKI]
No, because I'm not alone.
Somewhere, in another place,
my mother and Rasetsu
are with me.
And you have me
and Gekkou as well.
That's right.
♪
It certainly is.
Take this.
I want you to have the sword.
And I'll keep the shield
with me, okay?
Sounds good.
Thanks, Yumi!
♪
That reminds me.
There's a question
I've always wanted to ask you.
Okay, what is it?
I've always wondered what kind
of shinobi you want to be.
That's a good question.
♪
I suppose...
I want to be the kind of shinobi
that's like this falling snow.
[ASUKA gasps]
It covers the world
like a blanket
until it's warm again,
and then it melts
and disappears.
A shinobi like the snow.
That's me.
♪
Even when it melts,
the memory remains.
You're right.
That makes sense.
[BOTH laugh]
Come on, we should hurry.
Where there is light,
there is darkness.
Okay!
[ASUKA] This is the story
of a select group of girls.
♪
[YUMI/ASUKA]
They are the shinobi warriors
who live in the shadows.