[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[KYON] My ride aint swift,
'cause my gears won't shift.
[sighs] What a pain.
[KYON]
I'm home!
Man. Was it cold out--
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hi-yah! Welcome back attack!
[KYON groans] A simple greeting
that suddenly transforms
into a malicious attack.
You've got great skills, sis.
Loser. You went off by yourself
and had fun without me,
didn't you?!
Poor Shamisen was forced
to play with me all day.
He says you suck,
so that was payback for him.
For Shamisen?!
[KYON groans]
So tired.
I probably should've
just taken her with me.
[MIKURU]
Teeter-totter, teeter-totter...
Huh? I think Kyon's
tryin' to fall asleep.
We'll have him count sheep
so he can get to sleep faster.
C'mon! Jump!
Get up and jump through that
hoop so he can count you!
I can't sleep while
she's being tortured!
Uh... Where am I?
Let's see. I was lying in bed,
started counting sheep...
Played the straight man,
then after that... Oh, I get it.
I'm dreaming!
I'm really sorry, Miss Sheep...
I fell asleep on you.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
You're such a bad person.
Huh?
Hello, I'll be playing
Mount Fuji today.
[KYON]
Whoa! Weirdo in the house!
What? Is that any way
to greet your friend?
It's just, that if I admit
you're Koizumi, I'm pretty sure
a lot of people are
gonna get mad at me.
Who cares? It's just
a dream, isn't it?
[KYON] Thanks for a reminder,
Captain Obvious!
Do you like the outfit?
It's good luck to have a
New Year's dream with either
Fuji, a hawk, or an eggplant.
[KYON]
Who asked you?!
Why are you getting so upset?
Now that I'm Fuji,
the best omen you can get,
I'm going to bring you
bunches of joy and happiness.
It freaks me out to see you
in that get-up, smiling at me.
[KOIZUMI]
Naturally.
And I seriously doubt
that you could bring me
bunches of joy and happiness.
[KOIZUMI]
What?! That's impossible.
I can't believe you figured out
that I'm just a
plain old mountain.
How did you know
I couldn't bring you
bunches of joy and happiness?!
You're not Mount Fuji?!
[KYON]
Grow big!
[KOIZUMI]
He's turned into a shinjin!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] Don't say anything
to anyone about this!
I got a little carried away.
I'm glad you changed
back to your normal self.
I was gonna try yelling
at you to snap you out of it,
but I guess that would've
been really weird.
Believe me. You couldn't be
any weirder in that outfit.
[KOIZUMI]
Oh? You think?
Maybe I should go and find
the other two omens now.
[KOIZUMI] The hawk's been
up there this whole time.
[KYON]
That thing's a hawk?!
Hi, I'm a hawk.
[KYON]
No way, you're a crane!
[TSURUYA] Kyon... you shouldn't
judge a person by how they look.
Inside this crane
beats the heart of a hawk!
You're still a crane though.
[TSURUYA]
Well, yeah.
So where's the eggplant?
With the way things are going, I
bet it's around here somewhere.
Let me trying calling her.
[KYON]
You have a cell phone?!
[phone rings]
[KYON]
Huh? What's that doing there?
Hello there, Miss Nagato.
Ah-ha, so Nagato's the eggplant.
[KOIZUMI grunts]
It was lying on
the ground over here.
You should've told us
that you found Miss Nagato.
Good for you.
I was talking about the phone.
[KOIZUMI]
So was I. Look at the strap.
Why? What's on the--?
--I am the eggplant.
--It's her!
[KYON] Okay, so, now that
I've found everyone...
Well...
[BOTH]
What?!
[KYON]
I'm done! I wanna wake up!
We can't really
help you with that.
[KYON]
What's that supposed to mean?!
It means, we can't
really help you with that.
But, you did manage to find
the only person among us
who's ever been able to help
you in the past, didn't you?
Nagato! Yeah, that's right!
You know when you wink at me,
that also sorta freaks me out.
[KOIZUMI]
I know.
Okay, Nagato! Tell me how to
wake up from this crazy dream!
Go to sleep here, and
wake up in the real world.
That's it?
That's it.
[birds chirping]
[KYON exhales]
[MIKURU]
Teeter-totter, teeter-totter...
Huh? I think Kyon's
tryin' to fall asleep.
We'll have him count sheep
so he can get to sleep faster.
C'mon! Jump!
Get up and jump through that
hoop so he can count you!
Stop torturing her like that!
[KYON sighs]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[bell chimes]
[KYON humming]
[KYON]
Knock, knock. Anyone home?
[HARUHI]
Come in.
Hey.
I'm bored!
Why haven't any clients
walked through the door?!
I'm bored! Bored! Bored!
Bored, bored, bored!
[HARUHI yelling]
Uh?
[KYON]
Same old Haruhi. What a spaz.
Geez.
I'm just gonna stay
like this and fidget.
--[door opens]
--Would you calm down?
--[HARUHI] Fidget. Fidget...
--[KYON] Someone's here.
[KYON] It's your fault
we lost that one.
[HARUHI]
Dammit!
[HARUHI groans]
[HARUHI]
That hurt.
[KYON]
I bet. Can I go home?
[knocks]
Hey.
Hm? Just you, huh?
[VOICE IN GAME]
Oh, no! It hurts so good.
[grunts] Are you... playing
what I think you're playing?
[yells]
So, you like that stuff?
You know it.
Oh. Okay then.
[KYON] They say hobbies
are good for you,
and I'm really
happy you found one.
But, um, you might
want to use headphones
so you don't bother anyone.
That's what all the
good kids do, anyway.
[KYON]
Hm?
--Play with me.
--No, I'm good!
I... can't... move my body.
Ha, ha.
What will Haruhi Suzumiya
do after I kill you?
[KYON]
What are you doing, Asakura?
Now, you die.
[YUKI]
I forf--
[KYON]
Nagato, you all right?
I'm fine.
[KYON]
Really? You don't look so hot.
You won this time. But if you
think this means you're safe,
think again. I'm the weakest
of the Four Radical Lords.
And you'll be meeting
the others soon enough.
[KYON]
What a generic set-up.
[ASAKURA]
Then, there are three others
who rule over the first four...
The butler did it.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[door opens]
[MIKURU]
Sorry I'm late.
Huh? Where is everybody?
Uh... Hm.
Mikuru, are you watching?!
Waugh!
Time for your favorite
local quiz show!
Are you smarter
than the SOS Brigade?
Now, let's introduce
today's contestants!
First up, we have Yuki Nagato!
[bell dings]
[HARUHI] Uh, Yuki,
don't press the button yet.
And next is... that guy.
Uh! Say my name!
It's only one syllable.
Hey, Koizumi,
give me the camera.
This is our cameraman, Koizumi.
Pleased to meet you!
[KYON]
You introduced the cameraman?!
Let's move on to
the quiz, shall we?
The first topic is the universe.
There's nothing
local about that!
Shut it, Kyon.
Oh, okay. If you
really want local topics
then I'll just
change the question.
Let's see... Hm...
Oh!
What's the name of
that dog over there?
[KYON]
Too random!
You have 30 minutes to answer
the question, starting now.
[KYON]
Too long!
[HARUHI] Time's up.
May I have your answers?
[KYON]
Uh!
[bell dings]
[HARUHI] You only have
to press the button
during the lightning
round, okay?
The correct answer is...
[KYON]
You took so long they left.
Good try, but the correct
answer is "Gonzales"!
[KYON]
Liar!
[HARUHI] Next up we
have Truck versus Kyon.
--Who do you think will win?
--[MIKURU laughs]
[KYON]
I'm not doing that!
[HARUHI]
It's a tiny little pickup truck.
Here're some fireworks.
[KYON]
What? Why?
I don't care how small
it is! I'm not doing it.
Wait. You lit the fuses!
-[engine revs]
-Dear god, I'm a human sparkler!
Wha-What's that?
The truck's here!
[KYON screams]
[KYON] I don't want
to die like this!
[explosion]
Farewell. You will live in
our hearts forever, Kyon.
[KYON]
I'm not quite dead.
Whoa. You're still alive?
You're pretty tough.
[KYON]
I was revived.
After the fireworks exploded I--
[bell dings]
Yuki, your timing
still needs work.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Miss Nagato,
I brought your tea--
[screams]
--Oh, Kyon!
--What's wrong?
Miss Nagato... I just
saw her and she's...
[KYON]
What about Nagato?
Well, uh, it's just...
She's uh...
Never mind.
[KYON]
Hm?
[knock]
Hang in there, guys.
[HARUHI]
Uh?
Huh?
[HARUHI]
Huh?!
Hey, Kyon, does Yuki
have any sisters?
[KYON]
Huh?
[MIKURU humming]
[MIKURU]
Hm?
I've never seen these before!
Whose are they?!
Oh, I haven't seen you
reading a book in forever.
I always thought you were
more of a bookworm than--
Whoa! A strategy guide?!
You don't really use
those things, do you?
I mean, if you really wanted
to beat a game that bad,
couldn't you just hack into it?
But that would be
considered cheating.
[KYON]
Oh, right. Sorry...
Hm? Do you want me
play that with you?
Sure. I can play one round.
A fighting game, huh?
[NAGATO] Select character
and difficulty level.
Hang on. Difficulty level?
Who am I setting that for?
For me.
[KYON] Whoa. She's been
playing this a lot.
[ASAKURA laughs]
[ASAKURA] Poor Miss Nagato.
She has no clue that I've made
a back-up copy of myself.
Ryoko Achakura has returned!
[ASAKURA sighs]
This isn't good... What in
the world could've gone wrong?
[gasps]
Miss Nagato! You knew I'd
return someday, didn't you?
Let me out! Let me out!
Huh?
Ha! Now that I'm free,
prepare for your doom!
As soon as I return
to my normal size,
I will put an end
to you and him--
Save me, please!
[ASAKURA yelps]
[ASAKURA panting]
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
Miss Nagato... you saved m--
Let me out! Let me out!
[ASAKURA]
Let me get this straight.
You want me to move in with you?
[NAGATO] Yes. It will be
easier to observe you.
[ASAKURA]
I see...
[ASAKURA grunts]
[ASAKURA]
Uh, do you have another chair?
I do not.
You have to have something else!
Stack two cushions
together or something!
I only have two cushions,
including mine.
I'll take it! I'll fold that
one in half and sit on it!
[ASAKURA sighs]
[NAGATO]
I will prepare dinner for us.
[squeaking]
[ASAKURA yelps]
Oh, you decided
to use the chair.
[ASAKURA]
Let's not talk about it.
[YUKI]
Here you are.
[ASAKURA gasping]
I was joking.
[ASAKURA]
Huh?! Really?
Was it not obvious?
[ASAKURA] Well, you did
bring me here in a bag.
Considering my
current situation,
I assumed that's how you
were going to treat me.
I see. I will correct that.
[ASAKURA grunts]
[NAGATO]
Here you are.
[ASAKURA yelps]
Change the bowl!
[YUKI]
Oh.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER]
Guess what?
The computer club just made
this dodge ball video game,
and we wanna challenge
you guys to a match.
I decline!
[ALL groaning]
Man, I'm bored.
[KYON]
Do you not see the irony here?
[slurping]
[HARUHI sighs]
Speak.
O... Kay.
We just made this
dodge ball video game,
and wanna challenge
you guys to a match.
And if we win, you have to
give back all our computers!
A game, huh? And?
What?
If we beat you guys,
what are we gonna get?
Uh. Well, I...
[HARUHI] Last time ya lost you
agreed to obey my every command.
You don't have much to bet,
except your lives.
Our lives?!
Well, make me an offer.
Fine. We'll bet this.
[MIKURU screams]
[KOIZUMI laughs]
[KYON]
The price tag's on it!
It is composed of
30% chicken bones,
40% monkey bones,
and 30% turtle bones.
[HARUHI]
Ha, ha! Deal! Game on!
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER]
Uh. Really?!
--[KYON] Yep. Figures.
--[HARUHI laughing]
We'll give you a quick
tutorial on it and then--
--[HARUHI yells]
--[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER sobs]
I don't wanna play
your lame game.
We're gonna go play
the real thing!
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Uh...
[KYON]
Sorry guys.
[HARUHI]
Okay losers, it's show time!
You guys ready to
meet your maker?
Get ready, 'cause
this is gonna hurt!
Try and catch this...
If you think you can!
Go on, I dare ya!
Incoming!
[screams]
Huh?!
Are you okay?
[BOTH gasp]
I'm feeling so powerful now.
Me too!
Me three.
What's with this aura?
Haruhi Suzumiya has caused
a shift in this reality.
The humans in the area
have had their abilities
increased by 100%.
We better be careful then.
We might disintegrate
if we use full power.
Wait! That can't be okay.
I'm feelin' powerful vibes
comin' from over there.
We're gonna stick
it to 'em, Kyon.
Bad idea!
[Kyon groaning]
[KYON]
No way. I can see it coming.
Nice, Kyon!
[KYON]
Koizumi!
[MEMBER A grunts]
What the...?!
[yells]
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[KYON]
Watch out!
[BOTH gasp]
[HARUHI grunts]
Not bad! Let's see
how you dodge this one.
[yelling]
How long's this court
supposed to be, anyway?
Take this!
It's supersonic.
We're all gonna die!
Bring it!
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER grunting]
[Both]
Uh?!
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER]
Heh, heh.
Oh, yeah... I'm lovin' this.
C'mon, guys! Are we crankin'
this up a notch or what?!
Please don't.
[MIKURU]
Uh... Huh?! Huh. Uh-oh.
[KYON]
I knew it would end this way.
[NAGATO] No one's come to
collect their corpses yet.
[KYON]
That's 'cause they're not dead.
But I don't want it...
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Hey, Kyon...
[KYON]
Hm? What's the matter?
I found a bunch of
clothes on the rack,
and I can't figure out
who they belong to.
Oh, those are
probably Nagato's.
Seems like she's been getting
a lot of new outfits lately.
Oh. Yeah, I guess
that makes sense then.
[MIKURU]
I see how it is...
[KYON] Is this the start of a
cosplay rivalry between them?!
[MIKURU]
Kyon, I made you tea.
[KYON]
Uh. Thank you very much.
[MIKURU]
Huh?
Here's some more tea, Kyon.
[KYON]
Uh. Thanks?
Have another cup, Kyon!
[KYON]
Too much tea!
What's going on? Are you
guys having a costume party?
--[MIKURU wails]
--Who knows?
[MIKURU]
Kyon?
[KYON]
Hm?
[MIKURU]
I can't take this anymore.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina?!
[MIKURU] Trying to
compete with Miss Nagato
wasn't such a good
idea after all.
I'm a total failure.
[KYON]
Easy now. Don't laugh.
Oh, come on. That's not true.
You looked fantastic in
every costume you had on.
Have a little confidence.
[MIKURU]
Really?
[KYON screams]
[knocking, door opens]
Hey there. What's up? Hm?
That's cool. You beat the game.
It moved me to tears.
Yeah. I bet.
I will let you borrow my copies
of the game, manga, and novels
in the series.
[KYON]
Gee. Thanks.
Listen, I'm really flattered
that you want to loan
these out to me,
but you don't have to give
me everything all at once.
It's not a problem.
Those are my loaner copies.
[KYON]
I've heard of this!
One to store, one to display,
and one to loan out!
Besides, I have this
to keep me busy for now.
[KYON]
The sequel?!
They are also making an
anime based on the game.
[KYON] That's the most
excited I've ever seen her.
Hey, Kyon. That looks heavy.
Would you like me to help you?
[KYON]
Uh... No. I got it.
Don't tell me you're
into maid moe!
[KYON]
No! These are Nagato's.
That's just sick! Get rid of it!
[KYON] But these are
rated E for everyone!
[ASAKURA grunting]
[ASAKURI]
I can't reach any higher...
I had a feeling
this was gonna happen.
If only I have a stool
to stand on, or...
Yeah! Something like that!
That's not a stool!
--That's a baby walker!
--Oh.
[ASAKURA] It's not right
for you to always pick me up
everytime I can't
reach something.
I really should come up
with a different solution.
If only I had my own chair
or stool or something.
Yeah! Something like this.
I am not a baby!
[sighs] I guess this
will have to do.
At least I won't be
dependent on Nagato anymore.
I can move around on my own.
Wait.
My legs don't reach the ground!
Stop laughing! It's not funny!
Fine. I don't wanna be your
friend anymore, Miss Nagato.
Hey, wait! What are you doing?
We're playing merry-go-round.
What for?!
[ASAKURA] If she thinks this is
gonna cheer me up, she's wrong.
[ASAKURA] It's not that I
don't like this kind of stuff.
I mean, I do.
Is this as fast as she can go?
Anyway, I refuse to
have fun anym-- Ah!
[ASAKURA laughing]
[WOMAN ON TV]
You... saved me.
But you're the Head Maid.
Was that your stomach growling?
If you're hungry,
you really should eat.
Come on, I'll make
you something.
[ASAKURA] I've been put in
a device for babies again!
Enough!
I let you carry me in this
thing because it was useful!
But I want out of it right now!
Where does a person go to
buy something like this?
Does it even have a name?
It's a child safety bag
for children, isn't it?
It's a secret.
[ASAKURA] Fine. If that's
how it's going to be,
I won't cook
for you anymore.
[ASAKURA]
Uh?
Ah! What are you doing?
Why did you stand up like that?!
♪ This is a paradise... ♪
[ASAKURA]
Why is she singing?!
As if singing a song is
gonna make it all better.
♪ At the bottom
of a lonely heart. ♪
[ASAKURA] I am definitely not
in the mood for this nonsense.
The music is much too
upbeat for my taste.
--[ASAKURA laughs]
--[NAGATO singing]
This is so much fun!
I wanna sing next! Woo!
[NAGATO]
♪ ...or is it all a dream? ♪
♪ Trapped in these bonds. ♪
♪ Together all the way. ♪
♪ We can't let go. ♪
♪ This our destiny. ♪
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Hey guys!
Thanks for comin' out on this
beautiful day to take part
in the SOS Brigade's
Lots of Girls Field Day!
The weather's perfect!
So without further ado,
let's have some fun!
[applause]
Hey, momma?
What are all the
weird people doing?
[MOTHER]
Shh. Don't stare at them.
[HARUHI]
Hey Kyon, pay attention!
We have to divide everyone
into teams before we start.
There's a red and a white team,
so check your card.
[KYON]
Red.
Hey Suzumiya, my card's
different from everyone else's.
What's up?
[HARUHI]
Oh, yeah. That's the loser card.
I'm a loser?!
Ya have to do whatever it says
before you can draw another one.
[TANIGUCHI]
Do I sing it here, or...?
Find a corner somewhere.
You're on the red team, huh?
I'm on the white team.
Good for you, dude.
You know, Miss Suzumiya's
on the white team, too.
Isn't it strange how when
she has these drawings
you never end up on her team?
I guess I'm lucky like that.
Now that everyone's on a team,
we'll start the first event.
The scavenger hunt.
I need one person from each team
to step up and pick a card.
I'll go for white team!
Watch your back out there, Kyon!
Yeah, good luck!
Huh? I don't wanna.
All right, contestants.
Please draw your cards.
Don't open 'em yet!
Okay. When I say go.
Ready, set, go!
[KYON]
Uh?! That's not a thing!
Oh, whatever...
Come on, Koizumi.
Go!
Let's have a look at your card
and see if you're right.
[KYON]
Yeah...
Ah! An emotional barrier.
Explain your choice.
Okay, Koizumi.
I love you.
[KOIZUMI gasps]
[HARUHI gasps]
But I don't, so there's
a barrier here. See?
Your attention!
Haruhi's passed out,
so we're gonna
take a little break.
I'm afraid I'll have to
leave for a little while
and go deal with a rather large
closed space that just formed.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Shouldn't we take Miss
Suzumiya to the hospital?
Maybe she has a fever?
No. I don't think
that's the problem.
Haruhi Suzumiya managed
to hang onto her sanity.
If her mind snapped,
it would've destroyed the world.
Seriously?
[TANIGUCHI sighs]
I finished singing it.
[KYON]
Hm? Oh. Took you long enough.
Hey! Whatever, give me a card.
[KYON]
A what?
Oh. Right. That.
Go ahead, but I think
we're done now.
[TANIGUCHI]
What are you talking about?
You can't be done.
[KYON]
Huh?
[TANIGUCHI]
Hm...
Another lousy card.
What the heck? Now what do I do?
I guess you're supposed
to bring one back here.
Seriously?
[HARUHI]
Sorry about that, everyone.
I hope I didn't make
you worry too much.
But, I'm feeling better now.
I don't remember why I
passed out, but... Whatever.
I'm good.
Our next event is
gonna be tug-of-war.
We did not bring a rope
with us. It was too heavy.
Oh, that's okay!
Since we don't have a rope,
we can use Kyon instead!
Uhh!
Umm, Haruhi?
[HARUHI]
Yes, Kyon?
You're not serious, are you?
You're the only option
cause we don't have a rope.
Koizumi disappeared,
so we can't use him.
And it's way more fair this way!
[KYON]
You look like you're having fun.
[HARUHI]
Who, me?
Never! [laughs]
[KYON] You didn't
forget why you fainted!
[HARUHI]
Ha, ha! Start tuggin'!
A long time ago,
if two people wanted
custody of the same child,
they'd each grab hold of
the kid and start pulling.
Whoever worried about the kid
being in pain would let go
and got to be the parent.
But I'm the kind of person
who gets what she wants,
even if I have to break it!
[KYON]
But you just said...
You gotta be the same way, Yuki.
[KYON]
I saw that Nagato! Don't do it!
[HARUHI]
♪ See it bloom! See it bloom! ♪
♪ See the bright
red tulip bloom! ♪
[KYON]
You're scaring me!
--What... are... you singing?!
--[HARUHI] ♪ It tore apart. ♪
[NAGATO]
Tearing?
[KYON]
Yeah! Almost.
That's the end of the song!
[KYON]
My clothes!
They tore off...
[KID]
Whoa!
Kid, learn from my mistakes.
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER whimpers]
I-It broke out.
The kappa's on the loose.
[COMPUTER CLUB LEADER gasps]
[TANIGUCHI grunts]
Look, Suzumiya, I got it!
Can I... Cross the
finish line now?
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[HARUHI] Listen up, guys!
It's time for us to start
the SOS Brigade's Encounters
with the Unexpected
Setsubun Festival!
But first, everyone
needs to draw a stick.
Why?
[HARUHI] To decide who's
playing the demon.
Crap! Me again.
Okay! You have to put these on.
[TANIGUCHI]
You're kidding!
Perfect! You look like a real
demon from every angle!
Even the cops are gonna want to
haul you in for questioning!
[TANIGUCHI] Great. Now kids are
gonna cry when they see me.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Okay Mr. Demon, have
a seat there, please.
[TANIGUCHI] So I just
sit down and that's it?
[HARUHI]
Here are some roasted soy beans.
You can eat 'em if you want.
[TANIGUCHI]
Oh... Thank you?
[HARUHI]
Ha! Your lucky sushi roll!
The lucky direction
is south-southeast.
[TANIGUCHI]
You're too kind.
You guys want some?
[HARUHI]
Oh, no. Don't worry about us.
We're gonna get out of your way
and go throw some beans.
Make yourself at home, okay?
-[door shuts]
-[TANIGUCHI] Everyone's leaving?
Okay. Have... fun.
Alone. So alone.
Okay! Let's start throwing
some beans, you guys!
But instead of the usual chant,
we're gonna say
"bring on the luck!"
[ALL]
Hmm?
Let me explain.
Ever since I read
"The Crying Red Demon,"
I've decided to be nice to them.
[ALL]
Oh, I get it.
Come on, guys!
Let's throw beans!
[ALL]
Bring on the luck!
[HARUHI]
Eat it!
[KYON]
It's freakin' huge!
Ha, ha! Look at Kyon gobble it!
Go for it, Kyon! Inhale it!
[KYON groaning]
[NAGATO munching]
[distant chattering, laughing]
[TANIGUCHI]
I guess... I'll eat some beans.
[distant chattering, laughing]
[TANIGUCHI belches]
Looks like she's trying
to pick a fight with me.
Well two can play at this game!
Ahh! You can't fool me!
Wait!
Oh, she got me.
Uh. You've beaten me again.
Setting such an obvious trap
was a stroke of genius.
My lapse in judgement has proven
to be my downfall yet again.
You must have a reason for
going through all this trouble
to trap me! Well? What is it?
It's good you
catch on so quickly.
I have something that
I would like you to wear.
[ASAKURA] I'm your prisoner,
so I can't refuse your request.
Whatever it is, I'll wear it.
[YUKI]
Negations complete.
I wouldn't call what just
happened a negotiation.
I just hope the
outfit's cute, is all.
Could you've picked
a heavier kimono?!
Sorry about that. You can sit
here and relax for a while.
Oh, thank you. That's better.
[ASAKURA]
Hm...
Now I get it!
I don't care how much dessert
you bribe me with, I'm through!
Ahh! I don't believe it...
This must be the
legendary "obi spinning"
I've been hearing about!
I won't let you
get away with this!
[NAGATO] You know you want it.
You know want it...
[ASAKURA]
Oh, my!
[ASAKURA laughs]
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[HARUHI] The SOS Brigade is
going to make a melodrama.
I just wanna shake
things up around here,
cause it's startin'
to get boring.
I mean, every time
we have a quiz,
the same thing always happens.
Kyon ends up exploding.
It's not like I want to explode!
We're gonna go around
the room right now,
and I want everyone to
give me an idea for a story.
You first, Kyon.
Wait! I... What?!
You're not even listening.
Okay. Um, here's an idea.
It's typical, but could
have the main character
dying from a disease
or something.
[HARUHI]
Great idea!
[KYON]
Overreact, much?
It's genius.
A tragic hero staring
death straight in the eye.
Brilliant. Yes. Good.
Good one, Kyon.
[KYON] Oh, cut it out.
You're embarrassing me.
Okay, Koizumi. Whatcha got?
You think your idea
can top Kyon's?
I'll give it a shot.
How about a story with
a romantic triangle,
like those ones you see
in daytime soap operas?
[HARUHI screams]
[HARUHI]
Stealing someone else's lover!
Love then hate, then revenge!
It's perfect!
You feeling all right?
I'll be okay.
Just give me a second.
My vision's a little
blurry, that's all.
If your vision is blurry,
you're not okay.
Otaku.
[HARUHI]
Ah!
Or maids.
[HARUHI]
Ah!
Supply and demand!
We'll give the otaku
what they wanna see.
Welcome home, Master!
[KYON]
I'm totally lost now.
[HARUHI] All right,
I came up with a story
using all the ideas
we thought of.
I want you guys to check it out
and tell me what you think.
It's called "The Gift
of the Maid Part 2:
The Battle for Stolen Love
With Only One Month to Live."
[KYON] It sounds like
some cheesy game show.
And why is it part two?
The title pretty much gives
away all the kung fu action.
No it doesn't! There's
nothing kung fu about it!
Well, it is about stolen love.
[KYON] Okay, then. Let's go
with that. Picturing it...
[HARUHI] All the characters
in the story are maids!
[KYON]
Us too?!
Everyone in the story's a maid.
And they love maids, too.
They get into crazy
fights to decide
who loves maids the most.
They could decide in a
more maid-ly manner...
So at the end of the month,
all the characters die?
If the fighting doesn't
kill 'em first. [chuckles]
What are you saying?!
You should die.
Okay. If the story's
about stolen love,
then who's going to become
the hero couple at the end?
Well the last two maids
standing, of course.
The last two, huh?
But the only characters
left at the end
are Kyon's and Koizumi's.
Uh-huh. 'Cause only guys can
survive a fight that brutal.
[MIKURU]
Uh...
[HARUHI]
Hm?
You like that, huh, Mu-chan?
According to this,
the first battle's between
you and me, Nagato.
So it seems.
[KYON] "Scene one,
Nagato's Aerial Chop.
It has to look authentic,
so I want you to really hit him.
This attack will break Kyon's
bones in about 26 places.
Then, Kyon uses his first-aid
power-up and becomes invincible.
He wins, just barely."
Hang on, you are gonna be
careful not to kill me, right?
[NAGATO]
Chop.
[KYON screams]
[KYON]
I'm turning into light!
And we still ended
with an explosion.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[ASAKURA]
After I get up in the morning,
I usually wake
Miss Nagato up, too.
But it's Sunday today, so I
think I'm gonna let her sleep in
a little while longer.
It's too bright.
Go to sleep!
Whatever, I'll go wash my face.
Oh, no! I can't
do this by myself!
I kicked her pretty hard.
I doubt she'll be waking soon.
There's only one way to do this.
The wall-jumping technique!
[ASAKURA grunting]
Ahhh!
[ASAKURA]
Oh...
I'm feeling hungry.
What happened to you?
Oh. My face. Water...
Understood.
[screaming]
What are you doing?!
According to the
data you provided,
I chose the option that was
the easiest for you to react to.
[ASAKURA]
Don't make me react!
[growling]
Face the fury of my vengeance!
Ah!
[BOTH]
Uh...
Yuki! 'Bout time you showed up!
You're never late.
What happened to you?
[NAGATO]
I was unconscious.
You're kidding! What it
an enemy?! Are you okay?
[NAGATO]
Do not worry.
It wasn't an enemy.
I am fine now.
Everything's fine.
Everything's normal.
[NAGATO]
You sure about that?
[ASAKURA singing]
[ASAKURA sighs]
Rats. I guess Miss Nagato went
to go hang out with Kyon again.
I shouldn't be cleaning
up around here!
I'm one of the radicals!
That does it. I'm going out!
Not again!
Oh, geez. Right, door.
[ASAKURA]
Uh! Success! This is great.
Umbrellas can reach
up really high.
From now on, I'm gonna use
my umbrella for everything.
[ASAKURA laughs]
Nothing stands in the way of my
umbrella! Not even the elevator.
Better watch out, Kyon.
Because I'm coming up
to kill you! [chuckles]
Meow.
[ASAKURA] Children shouldn't
go out on their own.
The world can be a dangerous
place sometimes.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[door opens]
[NAGATO]
I'm home.
[ASAKURA]
Oh! Welcome back.
Huh?
Ah! Please don't...
Hey, Yuki! Thanks for
letting us come over today!
[HARUHI]
Ahem!
The SOS Brigade No Boys
Allowed Heart-Throbbing
Valentine's Day Chocolate
Making Party is about to begin.
[ALL]
Yay!
Okay Mikuru. Hurry up
and take your clothes off.
What for? A bath?
I was thinking we could
make a life-size,
Mikuru-shaped chocolate.
No! I don't want to!
Ha, ha, ha!
You know you want to.
A large human shaped chocolate
would be unusually difficult
to maintain and preserve.
Oh, well. Whatever.
It was worth a shot.
[MIKURU] You mean you guys
really would've done it
if it were possible?
[HARUHI]
I just realized something.
We're gonna have lots
of left-over chocolate.
[TSURUYA]
She's right!
I know! We'll be able to
use up all the chocolate
if we just make
whatever we want.
Great idea! And we
can eat the mistakes.
[MIKURU]
Is this arts and crafts?
All done!
Oh, I know this.
It's a Picasso, right?
I didn't know you were
so artistic, Haru-nyan.
It's Kyon's head.
[BOTH]
Wha?!
The likeness is 99.8% accurate.
However, people who still
rely on vision to see
will not be able to
tell the resemblance.
[HARUHI] I can't tell whether
that was a compliment or not.
[HARUHI]
Did you make a lion?
Yes, this is Mu-chan.
[HARUHI]
Wow! It looks great.
And you made a crane.
Uh-huh.
[HARUHI] I could see these
hangin' out in a garden.
Is yours all done, Yuki?
[NAGATO]
Here.
[HARUHI]
Are those chocolate bars?
[TSURUYA] They look just like
they did before we melted them.
[MIKURU] Wait. Didn't we
use up all of our ingredients?
No way! She made these out
of that lump of chocolate.
That's amazing!
I know. It's amazing
how pointless they are.
We still have a lot left over,
so let's make a couple
batches of the usual things.
I can totally handle putting
the powdered chocolate on.
And I can wrap 'em all up!
Stand back and watch
as I demonstrate
the wrapping technique
of Tsuruya's Candy Store.
What are you doing?!
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
I should be angry,
but I'm blown away by how many
you munched before we noticed.
[MIKURU]
That's amazing!
[HARUHI]
Okay guys. Now what do we do?
We're about to run
out of ingredients.
Why don't we take
what we have left,
and make two chocolate
cakes out of it?
That's a good idea!
Let's do that.
[HARUHI] They'll never
know we almost ran out.
[TSURUYA] Use what ya got
till it's all gone, Haru-nyan.
Huh?
Thanks for having us over!
See you tomorrow!
[door closes]
[ASAKURA]
Have they all gone home?
[NAGATO]
They have.
I didn't know what was going on
when you put me in that box.
I understand why you did it,
but I'm not happy about it.
Not that I ever had a choice--
--[ASAKURA screams]
--[NAGATO] Oh.
What's going on?! Tell me why
there's a spring attached to me!
I can't.
You've been wanting to do this
to me since the beginning.
Well I have news for you!
I've been going easy on you
this... whole... time.
What do you think I am?
A jack-in-the-box?!
--[clonk]
--[groaning]
[ASAKURA cries]
[NAGATO]
Here. This is for you.
[ASAKURA]
Huh? Uh!
It's a piece of
the cake she made.
[ASAKURA]
Hm...
If she expects me to
forgive her shoddy treatment
by accepting a piece of cake,
she's got another thing coming!
I mean, I'm flattered she
even saved a piece for me.
But there's no way
I'm going to be tempted
by a measly little morsel of--
[stomach growls]
[ASAKURA]
Whatever. Just this once.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[HARUHI]
Ahem! Attention!
Since today is Valentine's Day,
and since the SOS Brigade
observes all special occasions,
we, the girls of the brigade,
had no choice
but to make you boys
some chocolates.
Oh, uh, thank you!
Yes. Thank you very much.
[HARUHI]
Stop!
[KYON gasps]
Why can't I open it?
We, the girls of
the SOS Brigade,
think it's boring and archaic
in these modern times
to just hand out chocolates
and go about our business.
After all, we worked
hard to make those.
Just because you're boys,
doesn't give you the right
to eat those chocolates!
You have to earn 'em!
[KYON]
What does she want?!
[DEEP VOICE]
Too vague.
I think I understand
your intention here.
You want us to do something
for you that would make you
want to give us the chocolates
in return, correct?
Yeah. I guess that's
what I was goin' for.
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
Well? Do you have
any ideas for us?
Yes, possibly. Sorry.
Give me a second here.
I just have to fire off
this request for supplies.
Anyway, we could always try
doing nothing for our something,
and get the chocolates that way.
It's definitely worth a shot.
Huh?
[KOIZUMI] For example,
I've got a candy bar for you.
Happy Valentine's Day!
[KYON]
No thank you!
Oh, that's too bad.
You didn't accept my valentine.
But if you had taken it,
I would've been the
person giving something
instead of the one
getting something.
Therefore, you'd be obliged
to return the favor.
[KYON] Yeah, but,
if you apply that logic
to our situation with Haruhi,
you still have to do something
in order to get the chocolate.
[KOIZUMI]
You're so sharp.
[KYON]
Why you...
[KOIZUMI] I'm sorry.
I was just stalling for time.
Oh, would you mind
stepping back a bit?
Huh?
[KYON gasping]
Hello there. I'm just
an ordinary maid.
[KYON]
No way!
Here's what you asked for.
Thanks a lot for bringing it.
Mm-hm. It's all here.
[KYON]
Hm?
It's Mr. Arakawa. Oh, man.
What are these people up to now?
[KOIZUMI]
Let's get changed, shall we?
Uh? Okay.
Wait. Changed into what?
Why am I wearing this?
It's the male escort look.
Male escort?!
Well, it's the first thing
that popped into my mind
when I thought about someone
doing something for a woman.
I don't know about this.
What do you think, Miss Mori?
Do we look like male escorts?
The suits are perfect,
but you still need to have that
male escort smile
to complete the look.
The what?
Male escorts seduce women
with their killer smiles.
[KYON] But... I don't
want to kill anyone.
I have to be going now.
Seeing as to how we
don't have any other ideas
we might as well
give this one a try.
What the heck, right?
Okay. Here goes.
[ALL]
Huh?!
Wussup ladies?
I'm just ya average charmer
and the name's Kyon. Holla.
And I'm Itsuki,
the Crimson Super Ball.
Guess why they
call me that? Holla.
[screams]
What's wrong with you idiots?!
Get rid of those cheesy outfits!
You're making Mikuru cry!
[TSURUYA humming]
[TSURUYA]
This feeling... Who is that?
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
We better do somethin'
for Halloween.
It's not as simple
as going to Kyoto.
Do you know anything
about Halloween?
Like what it's about, and
what you're supposed to do?
Huh? Well, um...
I guess you need to
have pumpkins and bats?
Kyon's useless. What about
you, Koizumi. Do you know?
It would be far more
interesting if I pretended
not to know, so no.
I have absolutely no idea.
Oh, darnnit. I guess you're
in the dark like the rest of us.
Didn't you hear what he said?!
Whatever. We'll just
make it up as we go.
Hello!
Let's do a little research.
Yeah, but do you even
know where to start?
[HARUHI] For now, this is all
the information we've got.
[KYON] There are so many
things I could say right now...
Okay... Let's do this.
[BOTH]
Stare.
A-ha!
We need a guy wearing a cape
with a scary pumpkin on his head
and a bunch of bats!
I was thinking the same thing,
but there's gotta be
more to it than that.
--Look! We bought a pumpkin.
--[KYON panting]
[KYON]
I bought it.
[HARUHI]
You ready?
[KYON]
Hm?
[HARUHI yells]
Ah! What are you doing?!
Carving a pumpkin's
a lot of work,
so I thought we could just
press it against your face
and make it--
What are you crazy?! Do you know
how hard those things are?!
[HARUHI] Mikuru, your job
is to carve out a face.
Okay!
[HARUHI]
And Yuki, you give her a hand.
Understood.
[HARUHI]
I'm gonna go out for a bit
and pick up the rest
of the things we need.
I finished carving the face.
What do you think?
The right eye is three
millimeters larger.
Ah...
The left eye is one
millimeter larger now.
Ah...
The mouth is 1.5 millimeters
smaller on the right.
The right eye is
.3 millimeters larger.
[MIKURU]
Sniff.
I have returned!
I got pretty much
everything we need.
Except the bats.
I couldn't find those.
What's up, Haru-nyan?
If you want bats,
the cave behind my
house has a bunch of 'em.
No way! Really?!
[KYON] Where the heck did she
find that horrible thing?
[KOIZUMI]
I have no idea...
Perhaps she's planning
on putting the pumpkin
and the cape on it.
[KYON]
You're kidding.
[KOIZUMI] He's looking quite
sinister now, don't you think?
It's like a shrine
to some pagan god.
Now I get it!
If I knew you guys were
getting ready for Halloween,
I would've brought some candy.
Candy?
That's what
Halloween's all about!
Kids dress up in monster
costumes, go door-to-door,
and you give them candy.
Really?! So that's
what it's all about?
My bad. I was going with the
idea that we had to make up
an original god to worship
and give offerings to.
You're kidding?!
Oh, well. Let's offer
up some candy to it.
Mikuru, do you have any candy?
Huh?! Uh... Uh. Uh!
This is all I had in my pocket.
[HARUHI] I don't know if it
really counts as candy,
but, whatever.
Perfect!
[KOIZUMI]
Trick, or treat?
[KYON]
Search and destroy.
We're done with it,
so let's ditch this guy
in the Computer Club.
[NAGATO]
I'm home.
[ASAKURA]
Welcome back.
I know you just came home,
but could we go to the market?
We don't have
anything for dinner.
Oh, how I love it when
you put me in the bag.
It's so warm and cozy.
Don't put me in it!
But if I run into that cat
again, I'll be unprotected.
[ASAKURA groans]
Here we are.
We are, at that.
Was there anything in particular
you wanted to have for dinner?
I would like to have
rabbit roti with a renegade
in a sherry glaze,
and a carrot puree.
[ASAKURA] Oh, look. Potatoes
and carrots are cheap today!
We could have curry.
Five steps to the right!
Fifty centimeters straight up!
Steady now!
Release the ingredients!
Bon appetit. Dinner is served.
[yawns]
[ASAKURA] Now that I'm teeny
tiny, I can't stay up late.
You've got school
tomorrow, Miss Nagato.
You should get to bed soon,
or you'll be too...
Go to sleep!
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Hey Kyon, over here!
[KYON]
Hm?
Heads up!
What the heck are you doing?
Ahh!
Huh?
Hey! Don't you know
how scary it is
to have a balloon popped
that close to your face?!
Whoa! A main character
shouldn't make scary
faces like that, Kyon.
Here, take it.
You can try it on me,
if you want.
I'll hold the balloon this time.
You know, blow-guns
are pretty fun,
and they're super easy to use.
A-ha! That hurt!
You got me between
the nose and lip!
Gee. Sorry about that.
I guess it slipped.
[HARUHI]
You've got some nerve, Kyon.
That's a declaration of war!
[KYON laughing]
If you think I'm gonna
let you kick me around,
you've another thing coming.
Prepare for some pain!
I'm gonna shoot darts
into every hole in your body!
[KYON] Keep it clean!
We've got kids watching!
[HARUHI]
Die!
[KYON]
Incoming!
[MIKURU grunts]
Are you all right, Miss Asahina?
[HARUHI]
I'm sorry, Mikuru.
I promise I'll never aim a
weapon at another person again.
I swear it on Mikuru's grave.
Miss Asahina taught all of
us a valuable lesson today,
but she paid the ultimate price.
Thank you, Mikuru. Farewell.
Um... Excuse me,
I'm still alive.
[HARUHI] What are we going
to do about our duel?
We can't just walk away from it.
We can't use the blow guns,
and we still have a
ton of balloons left.
[KYON]
Hm...
I know! We're gonna have
a balloon art contest.
We can decorate Mikuru's
grave with our creations!
Just what I was I thinking!
Excuse me, I haven't
died yet. I'm alive.
[KOIZUMI]
And just like that,
the Asahina Cup Balloon
Art Contest is underway.
Whoever makes the
best decorations
on Miss Asahina's grave wins.
Hello there, everyone.
I'm Red Balloon Koizumi,
and I'll be judging and
providing the commentary today.
Kyon, I always wanted to settle
things with you this way.
Yeah, right. Dream on, buddy!
I knew a day like this would
come around eventually.
You know I'm totally
kidding though, right?
Get ready, balloon
fighters... Go!
Hm? What's that?
It's, uh, lotus root.
How 'bout yours?
It looks the same as mine.
It's sort of a... chain mine.
[BOTH]
I don't know how to do this!
[HARUHI]
Whatever! We made them,
so we might as well
use them to decorate.
And Miss Suzumiya
just scored 10 points.
[KYON] What?! She gets
10 points for that?!
[KYON] Oh, well. We couldn't
really do anything creative.
We just blew up balloons
and put twists in them.
But we twisted and
blew the best we could.
Yeah. We did, didn't we?
And somewhere along the way we
stopped caring about the score.
[HARUHI] This is boring.
Let's do somethin' else.
[KYON]
Okay.
[MIKURU whines]
[HARUHI grunting]
Rats.
Sorry, Mikuru, but the
balloons are so tangled
I can't get 'em off.
Wha...?!
[HARUHI] Don't worry!
I'll just pop 'em
--and you'll be good to go!
--Hey, what's up Nagato?
These things.
Hm? Yeah.
We got a lot of balloons
left over, huh?
I wonder why Haruhi
bought so many.
[HARUHI] Sorry, Mikuru, but I'm
the kind of woman who always
gives in to her desires.
May I have them?
Yeah. Help yourself. You can
take as many as you want.
--Thank you very much.
--[balloons pop]
--[popping continues]
--[MIKURU yelping]
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Oh!
Huh?
[laughing]
Balloons are such powerful
things, aren't they?!
[NAGATO]
I think not.
However, it is my
understanding that one
can create the likeness of both
animals and plants from them.
[ASAKURA] Seriously?!
Balloons are awesome.
They might be the predecessors
of artificial life.
It's a form of humanoid
transmutation!
I will now attempt to
create the likeness of a dog.
Huh?
Ah! Miss Nagato!
It's scary! Stop it!
[NAGATO]
I'm done.
The air inside has conformed
to the shape of a dog.
It's cute. I'll give you that.
But watching it transform has
left me with emotional scars.
[exhales]
[ASAKURA]
Hm. It would be wonderful
if this could move
around on its own.
Understood.
No! Stop it!
[BALLOON DOG pants]
[NAGATO]
I was able to make it move.
Aw! So cute.
Ah! Come back! [giggles]
Fooled again!
Okay, you win. I thought
I could be happy,
and just play with the balloon
dog without having to worry
about falling into
one of your traps.
You should know better.
I know I should, dammit!
Do what you will, then.
Boil me. Roast me.
Do what you want, I don't care.
[BALLOON DOG] Aw, come on.
Don't let it get ya down.
It can talk!
[BALLOON DOG]
You can call me... Hm...
Oh! How about Mr. Kimidori?
It is the color of
my body, after all.
[ASAKURA] I have to address a
balloon dog as "mister," now?
Preparations complete.
Wait. Preparations?
There's so much happening,
I don't know what's
going on anymore!
Help! I'm floating!
Get me down from here!
By injecting a gas into it
which is lighter than air,
the balloon attains
the ability to float.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Interesting phenomenon.
What kind of gas
did you put in it?
[NAGATO]
I extracted hydrogen from water,
and then I injec--
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Hi everyone!
Drop what you're doin' and
grab those pots and pans,
'cause it's time for "Haruhi
Suzumiya's Simple Cooking Show"!
Yay!
The topic for today's
show is easy to make,
super nutritious, healthy,
fresh, rich, simple,
and inexpensive cooking!
Wow... That sounds
ambitious and nutritious.
For today's recipe, we're gonna
have to boil some instant ramen.
Hey! Isn't this supposed
to be a healthy recipe?!
But you'll have to
open the package first!
Yuki!
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
That was unnecessary.
That was completely,
and totally, unnecessary.
[HARUHI]
That sucks. It's all broken.
Looks like damaged goods.
[KYON] You know...
the thing with the katana
could also be to blame.
Oh, well. Whatever.
We can just skip the step
where Yuki chops it
all up into quarters.
[KYON]
You were gonna throw it again?!
Next, we place all
the pieces of ramen
into a pot of boiling water.
Then we're gonna let
it cook for 50 hours.
What?! Cooking it for
50 hours isn't simple!
Don't worry about it.
I've got a batch of
it already cooked.
It'll look simple
to the audience,
but they'll never
know the truth.
That's not the problem!
[HARUHI] Mikuru! Bring the
you-know-what over here!
Oh! Okay!
[grunts]
[screams]
[HARUHI] Okay. We're
just gonna move on...
Miss Asahina. Duck down,
you're in the shot.
[HARUHI]
We put the noodles in a bowl.
Boiling them for 50 hours
has turned them all mushy,
but here's the good thing!
Now they're easier to digest,
so they're even better for you!
So, hang on a sec...
The noodles in that bowl were
cooked the right
amount of time, but...
Oh, never mind.
I get where this is going.
[HARUHI]
Let's set this aside for now,
and get ready to put on
the finishing touches!
I don't know 'bout you,
but I'm tired.
I'll be right back
after these commercials.
Wait! We've got commercials?!
[HARUHI]
You can do it!
[KYON]
Hm?
Hey, Nagato. What's up
with the katana anyway?
I can explain that!
Miss Suzumiya wanted a
really sharp kitchen knife
to have on set today.
So I got in touch
with my organization,
and they gave me that.
Uh! Are you trying to
get someone killed?!
[chuckles]
I've never handled a
real-life katana before.
Now that I'm holding one, I sort
of feel like cutting something.
If you don't mind,
would you please point that
at someone else for a while?
Homing mode has been activated.
You are now able to cut
a target any way you wish.
[KYON]
Yeah?
[KOIZUMI] Why don't you try
carving a human figure
out of this daikon?
Okay. Here goes no--
[KYON yelps]
Carving a detailed form will
cause a great deal of stress
on the wrists.
It is very dangerous for
humans to use cutlery.
[KOIZUMI]
Yes... Cutlery...
His wrists were bending in
all sorts of interesting ways,
weren't they?
Can you handle it without
incident, Miss Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Of course.
I can carve miniture
figures out of anything.
[KOIZUMI]
That's amazing.
Okay! Here I go again.
You don't know when
to give up, do you?
Heh. After watching
Nagato do it,
I figured out exactly where
I went wrong the last time.
Okay, then.
If you really want to.
[KYON]
You have to do the cutting
while the target's
still in the--
[screams]
--[screaming continues]
--[KOIZUMI] And he's spinning...
[sighs]
Okay, we're back. So let's hurry
up and finish the soup already.
[KYON]
She's bored...
I got a bunch of healthy
lookin' things here,
so I'm just gonna throw 'em in.
That's too vague!
Cover it up, and let the whole
thing cook for five days!
Five days?!
Okay, Mikuru. Try it again,
but without spilling!
[MIKURU grunting]
[MIKURU] The last time
I did this, I messed up.
But this time, I'm going
to do my job properly!
[KYON, HARUHI]
Uh?!
[KYON, HARUHI sigh]
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[MIKURU]
Oh...
--[TSURUYA yells]
--[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI]
Hm... Cherry blossoms.
Cherry blossom petals,
fluttering to the ground.
Blood spraying.
Uh?!
[HARUHI] Digging a hole...
Burying. Under a cherry tree.
I've got it!
A cherry blossom party!
Okay. Let's talk
about how you went from
what you were thinking just now
to having a cherry
blossom party.
[HARUHI sighs]
You'll never go far
with that attitude.
[KYON] Please don't
lecture me like that.
I'm not your son.
You'll always be a
subordinate Brigade member
if you don't change your ways.
Gotcha. I'm okay
with that though.
Really, I am, Mother.
I'm not your mother!
You wanna get smacked?!
[KYON]
You already smacked me!
Then I'm gonna call you father!
What are you talking about?!
Calm down!
[HARUHI]
You asked for it, Kyon!
Now I'm gonna show you just
how incompetent you really are!
Hey, Koizumi!
Did you call me?
[HARUHI] Mm-hm. Could
you come here for a sec?
This and that, and
that and this.
And then, after all that, what
would your conclusion be?
Cherry blossom party.
That was fast!
It wasn't terribly
hard to decipher it.
[KYON]
Oh. Yeah?
Well. How did I do?
Awesome job, Number 2!
I get it. You guys
are my enemies.
Okay! Let's go have a
cherry blossom party!
I refuse to go!
Koizumi, do you know of any
good places where we could go
for somethin' like this?
[KYON] Aren't you even
gonna try to convince me?
The thing is, anywhere we go
is probably gonna be crowded.
It's unfortunate, but true.
The best thing for us would
be if we could find a place
that's privately owned.
You can't dig holes
on private property.
Wherever we go,
we have to make sure digging
holes is okay with the owners.
That's true.
[KYON]
Just throwing this out there,
but maybe the hole digging thing
isn't really all that important?
[TSURUYA] Ha, ha. I heard what
you guys were talking about.
[gasps] Hey, I know that voice.
[KYON]
Tsuru-- Huh?
[HARUHI]
Mikuru?
[MIKURU]
Hm?
Miss Tsuruya?!
Where did you go?!
Don't disappear like that!
She just was just here, I swear.
[TSURUYA]
Ha, ha. Sorry about that.
[KYON]
Uh?! Sneaky!
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm training for an
upcoming battle, though,
so I gotta stay sharp.
Anyway, it sounds like you guys
are trying to find a good place
to go look at cherry
blossoms, right?
[HARUHI] And a place
where we can dig a hole.
Then I've got the
perfect spot for you!
It's in the cherry
blossom section of
my private Tsuryua
Park Number 32.
[KYON] Whoa! What
doesn't this girl have?!
I like to keep it
on the down-low,
'cause the place has sort
of a sinister past to it.
You'll find something
if you dig deep enough.
[KYON]
A sinister what?!
[HARUHI] Right on! We're
gonna go there this weekend!
[ALL cheering]
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[KYON grunts]
[KYON sighs]
Huh?
[HARUHI] Okay, Kyon. This
spot feels weird enough.
Start diggin'!
[KYON]
It's gonna take forever.
Would you relax? I can get
the others to come over
and help you out, so you'll
be done before you know it.
I think I get it.
Basically, everyone
else digs and you don't.
Yep! You know it.
Well, she did get the others to
come over here, that's for sure.
--But they're not much help.
--[GIRLS laughing]
Haruhi's playing
mahjong with the guys.
The girls go bored
and they came over.
Geez. They're acting
like little kids!
[MIKURU]
Hey, Kyon, look!
We found something strange.
[KYON]
Hm? Let's see.
Wow. It's awfully pretty. I've
never seen anything like it.
Maybe it's a jewel.
[NAGATO]
It is not.
That is no jewel.
A subspecies of the Data
Integration Thought Entity
lives within it.
It coexists with the
cherry trees in this area.
It clouds the mind of its prey,
taking away its
ability to reason.
It forces its prey
to stay in the area,
taking care of the cherry trees.
When the prey dies,
it decays and becomes
nutrients for the tree.
That is the reason why
this area has a sinister past.
Heh! You must be kidding!
Your story was so
long, I got lost!
Me, too!
Uh!
Does anyone know what we
were just talking about?
[NAGATO]
I do not.
[HARUHI]
Mikuru!
--[MIKURU] Huh?
--[KYON] Hm?
I'm sorry, but Miss Suzumiya's
calling for us to come back.
Are you going to
be okay if we go?
Yeah, sure. If you guys get
bored hanging out with her,
come on back.
Well, here I am.
Please tell me
you've got some idea
about how to get
this digging done?
Yes. As a matter of fact,
I've called in for some backup.
Uh!
I'm a taxi driver, just
passing through.
Arakawa?!
You were driving rather
frantically there.
I hope that
everything's all right.
Well, this is the
Tsuruya family's property.
The security was
tighter than I expected.
And, if my calculations
are correct,
I can only stay about
three minutes or so.
[KOIZUMI]
Hm.
[KYON]
I'm totally lost.
Three minutes should be
plenty of time for this!
You're gonna make Mr. Arakawa
dig a hole in three minutes?!
Not at all. In fact, I have
something else in mind.
Look. See for yourself.
[KYON]
A bomb?!
Hello. I'm just a skydiver
who's passing through.
Miss Mori?!
I had no choice but
to crash-land here.
And, silly me, I forgot
my parachute.
You don't say? That's rather
clumsy of you, isn't it?
[KYON]
Clumsy?!
I wouldn't call skydiving
without a parachute "clumsy"!
I happen to be a taxi driver.
I could give you give you a ride
back to town in my
cab if you like.
Actually, we're out
of time, so I insist.
Why thank you. I can't
refuse an offer like that.
It was nice meeting
you, gentlemen.
I hate to crash
and run like this,
but we really must be going.
They leave a path of
destruction wherever they go.
[KYON] What's up with you and
the corny action movie dialogue?
And button your shirt!
[HARUHI]
Kyon! We heard a big explosion!
Did something happen?
Whoa! Did you dig
this by yourself?
Amazing job, Kyon!
It's really amazing!
Super amazing, Kyon!
[KYON]
Yeah... Well...
Let's just say I
did it on my own.
[TSURUYA]
Right. Sure.
But that doesn't explain how
they breached our
security so easily.
[KYON]
Later, I heard Miss Tsuruya
make an unsettling phone call.
To be continued...
Wait! What?!
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Listen up!
We're gonna have ourselves
a Christmas party today!
Yay! Yay! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[HARUHI]
Dumbass!
You better take
this party seriously,
'cause if you don't, they're
gonna come and kill us all!
Who are you talking about?!
[HARUHI]
I'm talking about people
who stalk rooftops at night.
They carry sack full of
presents on their backs,
and sneak in and out of houses
without anyone noticing
they've been there.
They're the elite members
of a mysterious organization
who carry out their secret
mission once a year.
Known as...
...Santa Claus!
--[MIKURU screams]
--The SOS Brigade is the only
thing standing between them
and the unsuspecting public.
Get ready, 'cause they're
coming for us tonight!
You're kidding!
The only chance we have beating
the threat know as Santa Claus
is to have a full-proof
battle plan.
So here it is, everyone!
The Plan!
First, we're gonna
throw him off our trail.
We put up a sign in the window
of the Computer Club's room
to make 'em think it's ours.
Next, Kyon's gonna hide in
the room and wait by himself
until the target shows up.
The rest of us are gonna be
here in the SOS Brigade's room
partying until we
run out of cake.
We have to be careful though.
If we get too loud, Santa might
here us and abort the mission.
That is all.
Any objections? Besides Kyon.
[KYON]
I can't even object now?!
We're gonna need all
the help we can get,
so I got Miss Tsuruya
to give us a hand.
Hi guys! Ready to party?!
If we end up having a
show down with Santa,
she's gonna step up and
turn the tables on him.
[laughs] I can handle him!
I can't wait to practice my
fighting technique on that guy!
I'm gonna become a master of the
Tsuruya-family Fighting Style
when I turn 19!
[KYON]
No way!
[TSURUYA] What's up, Kyon?
Don't you believe me?
I don't. It's pretty obvious
you made that last part up.
[TSURUYA]
Okay then, take a look at this.
[KYON]
What am I looking at?
[TSURUYA] It's a picture
of when I fought a bear
in the mountains.
Wow! Cool!
That's so fake!
Perfect. Santa Claus
is gonna see this sign,
think we're here, and come
right through this window.
You sure that'll work?
Now we just need to find a
good hiding place for you.
A-ha!
Here, put this on.
I absolutely refuse!
Your refusal has been
refused! Put it on!
[KYON]
You're evil.
Come on. It's okay. Don't be
such a baby. Just put it on.
You're gonna look great!
I don't think I'm gonna
care how I look
with that thing on my head.
[HARUHI laughing]
[KYON]
I wanna die now...
[TANIGUCHI sighs]
I can't believe I made it
all the way over here
without being spotted.
I'm finally gonna be able
to get rid of this kappa.
I picked the perfect
night to do this, too.
No one's gonna suspect
it's me in the get-up.
It's pretty risky with Suzumiya
and the others still here.
Whatever.
Tonight's the night
this freakin' kappa's
goin' home for good.
All right. Here I go.
[KYON sighs]
I wonder if Santa's really
gonna show up tonight.
I feel so stupid. Everyone's
next door having a good time.
What the hell.
But if I wasn't here, I'd be
home spending Christmas
with my little sister.
That wouldn't be
much fun, either.
Huh?!
Who... Wha... I...? Santa...?
[TANIGUCHI whimpers]
What is that?!
[ALL]
Huh?
What was that?!
[TANIGUCHI whimpers]
[HARUHI gasps]
[HARUHI]
It's Santa!
[TANIGUCHI]
Uh!
[TANIGUCHI grunting]
[KYON]
He's so big... and ran away.
I think he's trying to find
a hiding place on campus.
Come on, guys! Let's catch him!
[KOIZUMI] Interesting. Miss
Suzumiya was picturing Santa
to be this monstrous person,
so that's exactly what she got.
Her power took what
was in her imagination,
and transformed
Taniguchi's body.
It's no use. I can't catch him.
For a big guy,
he can really move.
Hm. I know. But we
can slow down now
'cause he's heading
right into my trap.
What trap?!
[KYON]
Miss Tsuruya!
Like I said.
Leave it to me.
I can handle this guy!
[TANIGUCHI groaning]
Now!
[TANIGUCHI groans]
Awesome job, Miss Tsuruya!
And you, too, Yuki!
[KYON] The Tsuruya-family
Fighting Style is real?
[TANIGUCHI grunting]
[HARUHI gasps] No... I can't
believe it. He's gone.
He just left his clothes
behind and ran away.
Was it safe to just let him go?
I neutralized the changes Miss
Suzamiya made to Santa's body.
[HARUHI whimpering]
Come back, Santa! Don't go!
[teeth chattering]
O-Okay. So... why am I naked?
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[door opens]
I'm home.
Oh, no. This is terrible.
Mr. Kimidori has gone flat.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
It looks like the end for me.
I'd like to be bury at sea,
if you don't mind.
I cannot. If I threw a
balloon into the ocean,
it would destroy
the environment.
[ASAKURA] Miss Nagato didn't
believe any of it, did she?
[MR. KIMIDORI] Well, our
acting could've been better.
Anyway, would you please
blow me up again?
[ASAKURA]
Okay.
Mr. Kimidori pushed
me out of harm's way
and got stuck under
the refrigerator!
[MR. KIMIDORI]
The light's fading...
I want to be cremated and my
ashes scattered to the winds.
I can't burn a balloon because
of the toxins it would release!
[MR. KIMIDORI sighs]
We look pretty stupid right now.
[ASAKURA]
Might as well give up, then.
[MR. KIMIDORI] Would you please
pull out from under this thing?
Oh, I'm sorry. Of course.
[MR. KIMIDORI grunting]
Uh-oh. I think you're
caught on something.
I'm having a hard time
pulling you out.
Is something wrong?
Yes, Miss Nagato.
Mr. Kimidori is stuck
under the refrigerator.
[ASAKURA]
Careful!
If you pull too hard,
Mr. Kimidori is going to--
[screams]
[NAGATO]
Your dog is dead.
Mr. Kimidori!
It's all my fault!
If it wasn't for this
April Fool's prank,
he'd still be alive!
It's all my fault!
[NAGATO] You shouldn't
blame yourself, little one.
How dare you trick me?!
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[HARUHI]
A live-action ESPer sentai show?
Yeah! It's up on the
roof of Marutsuru,
the store my family owns.
I got a bunch of free tickets,
so I thought you and the
others might like to go.
Well, that's really nice of you.
But I don't think I want
to see fake super-heroes.
--But if they were real-- Ah!
--[NAGATO] We're going.
Oh. Okay. If Yuki wants
to go, then I'm in, too.
Let's all go together.
[NAGATO]
Mm.
[CROWD cheers]
What's the deal with
all these people?
Don't tell me you've
never heard about this.
Every year,
the folks at Marutsuru produce
an amazing sentai show.
The fight scenes
are so incredible,
everyone in Japan
knows about it.
Every person here is
a fan of the show.
Now I get it.
That explains why the girls
are all in the front row
being loud and annoying.
Listen everyone!
Our heroes can't defeat
the monster by themselves!
I need your help to call the
only person who can save them.
All together!
--Mustache Mask!
--[CROWD] Mustache Mask!
They're heroes and they need
to ask the audience for help?!
[HOST] I don't think
he heard you! Louder!
I was gonna ask you this before,
but why are you doing
a jigsaw puzzle here?
Well, I knew we'd
have time to kill,
so I brought it to
keep us occupied.
[KYON] Two guys doing a
jigsaw puzzle on a Sunday?
How depressing.
And it's got roses on it.
[KOIZUMI]
Hey. You're wokin' on it, too.
Okay, monster.
Meet your newest opponent.
Holy crap! That's Mr. Arakawa!
Oh, look at that.
It is Mr. Arakawa.
Oh, and the monster's Miss Mori.
[KYON]
You're kidding?!
Is this another one of
their secret missions?!
[MONSTER roars]
Come on!
[ARAWAKA yells]
[MIKURU] The other sentai
are just cheering him on.
I wonder why they
don't help him.
Miss Tsuruya, why
aren't the others...
There it is again.
That feeling...
Miss Suzumi, why don't the--
[HARUHI]
Yuki! Get down from there!
You can't go on stage!
No! Come on!
[MIKURU] I'll just stand
here and enjoy the show.
That's it?
Someone else does
all the fighting,
but they get to kill it?
They always seem
to get the good part.
[HARUHI]
We're back!
Man, that was so cool!
Wasn't it?
You look like you were
really getting into to.
[HARUHI]
No, not really.
I just came because
Yuki wanted to.
Hey, could you watch my bag?
I'm gonna go get an autograph.
[KYON] Yeah.
You were definitely into it.
[HARUHI] Wait here for us.
We'll be back in a bit.
[KYON]
Huh?!
[MR. ARAKAWA]
Here you go, kid.
I love you Mustache Mask!
[HARUHI]
Darn it. We're last in line.
Mustache Mask is
really popular, isn't he?
Hm?
Hey, I'll be back in just a sec.
I have to use the restroom.
Okay. I'll get an autograph
for you if you're not back.
[MIKURU] Aren't the restrooms
the other way though?
I knew there was
something shady about you.
Those weird vibes I felt
gave you away, nyoro.
Now that we're here, we might
as well make the most of it,
don't you think?
Okay, get ready!
'Cause here I come!
Don't hold back.
I need a good workout today.
[TSURUYA]
Huh?
Uh!
That didn't work...
She can move pretty
fast in that costume.
[TSURUYA] What's up? All
she does is dodge my attacks.
She hasn't even
tried to fight back!
I know.
I'll try getting her
right when she lands.
She won't even
know what hit her.
And I'll keep hitting
her till she goes down!
[grunts]
[KOIZUMI]
This is amazing.
I can't believe we're
almost finished with it.
A hundred thousand
pieces is no joke.
Okay. Are you ready to do this?
Oh, yeah. We've come a long way,
and there's no turning back now.
One more piece and this
puzzle is officially finished.
Here goes.
[BOTH laughing]
Did I get her?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
[MORI] That was a wonderful
attack. I'm impressed.
[gasps]
[MORI] I thought I could
take you on wearing
that cumbersom outfit.
But now that it's off,
I'm feeling much better.
And since I'm in such
a good mood now,
I'd like to give you
a piece of advice.
Hey, little girl...
Watch your back!
Hey, we're back! Sorry
you had to wait so long.
Uh?
Hey, uh, Kyon... What's wrong?
Koizumi?
[MORI]
Hello, it's me.
I'm on my way back now.
I hope you set my
lunch aside for me.
I've worked up
quite an appetite.
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
Huh?
[ASAKURA]
Ah!
[MR. KIMIDORI chuckles]
Guess who?
I bet you're surprised to
see me floating around.
[ASAKURA] Haven't you got
anything better to do?
Why don't you help me
clean up around here?
Huh?
Uh...
Oh, seriously Miss Nagato.
Pick up your stuff after you've
finished playing with it.
[MR. KIMIDORI sighs]
[ASAKURA]
Oh, look at that. All clean.
Thank you so much for helping
me reach all the high places.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Okay, everyone. Let's take a
break now and have some lunch.
Mr. Kimidori, would you
help me cook something?
[MR. KIMIDORI]
You got it.
Okay, time for
the salt and pepper.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Coming up.
Why thank you, Mr. Kimidori.
Having you around makes
the day go smooth.
[ASAKURA]
That's it! We're done.
You don't know how
much I appreciate
all the help you gave me today.
Hm?
I was going to ask you
earlier, Mr. Kimidori.
Why are you inside that?
You will understand
once you get into this.
[ASAKURA]
Oh.
[ASAKURA laughs]
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groaning]
[HARUHI]
Hi everyone!
Thanks for tuning in to
another fun-filled episode
of my talk show.
Haruhi Suzumiya's Room.
Let's get things started
by introducing
our guest today.
Okay. He calls himself
a horrible virus.
With contagious laughter.
Please meet Kyon.
That's a lie!
I'd never call myself
something like that!
Whoa! He just got here,
and now he's tearing into me.
What should I do? I can't
keep up with him!
You haven't got this whole
TV-hosting thing down yet.
Yeah. I'll figure it out though.
Miss Waitress.
Can we have two coffees?
Okay.
What's with the waitress?
I thought this was
supposed to be your room.
Let's get back to
the show or somethin'.
[KYON]
You're too laid back.
Very well, Kyon.
How 'bout we start the
ball rolling with a few
hard-hitting questions?
[KYON]
Okay. Shoot.
I can't think of
anything to ask you.
[KYON]
You're kidding!
Pretend you never met me
before or something!
At least make some
kind of effort
to ask me a question, woman!
The kids today have such short
fuses, don't they? Scary.
[KYON]
Oh, come on.
You're way scarier than I am.
Get serious.
Okay, fine.
I guess you're right,
I wasn't taking it seriously.
I promise I'll be
serious from now on.
It's about time.
Let's do this.
Okay! Here we go.
I'm gonna take my
show so seriously,
I won't let our guests
in a word in edgewise.
Then it's not a talk show!
It's a monologue.
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Our next guest is a person
who's a very good friend
of What's-his-name's,
Miss Yuki Nagato!
You haven't asked me anything
and you're bringing
out another guest?!
Hello.
Okay, Yuki. Do you
have any interesting,
gossip-y stories to tell
the audience about Kyon?
Yes. I might.
There really aren't any.
[KYON]
Ha! I knew it!
Kyon, you're the boring-est
guest I've ever had.
[KYON]
Now you're blaming the guest?
Okay, Kyon. Help us
out here and tell us a story.
Just make somethin' up.
It's up to me to do it?!
Let's see...
Mikuru can't help you now,
'cause it's the third time
we've done this window bit.
Okay! I'm sorry! I don't
have any stories to tell!
And stop eating!
I didn't wanna go there,
but I guess I don't
have a choice.
I'll have to whip out
my secret weapon.
Secret what?
I've prepared a scenario
utilizing every contact
in my wide-ranging
network of contacts.
[KYON] Things are gonna
get complicated now.
It's an amazing story about
a group of friends
who are aliens, time
travelers, and ESPers.
It's everything you could ever
possibly want in a show.
Okay! Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
Good job, Number 2!
[KOIZUMI]
Oh, I'm just happy to help.
[KYON]
I live that story every day!
Okay, Kyon. Go ahead
and pick a scenario.
And don't peek!
[KYON]
Just... pick one blind?
Okay. This one.
This has nothing to do with me!
Yum.
[KYON]
Stop eating!
[HARUHI]
Here we g--!
[HARUHI groans]
[ASAKURA]
Oh, this rain!
Getting laundry to dry
in weather like this
is next to impossible!
My street clothes are
never gonna dry out!
[MR. KIMIDORI] Aah, I was
wondering why you're
wearing your school
uniform today.
What memories!
The last time I wore it
seems like forever ago!
I had a purpose back then,
a reason for being.
I could reach door knobs.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Sorry, but you're turning this
into a flashback episode.
Let's not go there.
[ASAKURA]
Come on, just this once!
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Sorry, no.
[NAGATO]
I'm home.
[ASAKURA] Whoa! What happened
to you, Miss Nagato?!
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Yeah, you're drenched!
[NAGATO] On my way home,
a car splashed water on me.
[NAGATO]
Ahh!
[MR. KIMIDORI]
That's terrible, Miss Nagato.
You could've dodged
the water, though.
Why didn't you?
My priority was keeping my
laptop out of harm's way.
[ASAKURA]
Get out of those wet clothes,
and a take a nice, hot shower.
That was refreshing.
[ASAKURA screams]
I'm sorry, Miss Nagato.
I did laundry today and all
your clothes are still wet.
[NAGATO]
Oh...
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
I know what you're up to.
Very clever.
[NAGATO]
Water balloon mode.
[ASAKURA screeches]
[MR. KIMIDORI]
I can explain.
Water balloon mode
is a process where
Miss Nagato collects all
the moisture in the air
and transfers it into my body.
Doing that will remove
the humidity from the air
and the clothes will
dry more quickly!
And I get to transform
into the giant ultra-dog
I've always wanted to be!
[ASAKURA] I hate to say this,
but you just got fatter is all.
And be careful, don't get
too excited or else--
[MR. KIMIDORI screams]
[ASAKURA]
I told you so!
[MR. KIMIDORI]
I know... Sorry.
[ASAKURA sighs]
[ASAKURA]
Aw...
This is so boring!
After we finish all the chores,
there's nothing to do except
wait for Miss Nagato
to come home.
I hate to complain,
but I wish we had something
to entertain ourselves with.
[MR. KIMIDORI] If we could
go outside by ourselves,
we wouldn't have this problem.
Huh?
[ASAKURA]
Hm?
Is everything okay?
[MR. KIMIDORI]
I just remembered something.
[NAGATO] If the two of
you get bored, open this.
[MR. KIMIDORI] That's what
she said, and she gave me this.
Uh-huh... A mysterious box.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Correct.
You know there's something
totally suspicious
about this thing.
[MR. KIMIDORI] Whatever.
We might as well open it.
Be careful!
--[MR. KIMIDORI screams]
--[ASAKURA gasps]
[beep]
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Um...
I'm hearing a beeping
sound coming from it.
Is this thing what
I think it is?
[laughs nervously]
No way.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Mm-hm?
That's your typical two-wire
scenario and a pair of scissors.
[ASAKURA whimpers]
Oh, I get it.
To disarm it, I'm gonna
have to use these scissors
to cut one of the wires.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Uh. Good guess.
This is fake.
Nothing's gonna happen to us
if I cut the wrong wire.
[MR. KIMIDORI] Uh, yeah... It's
just a toy to keep us occupied.
It can't be real.
I mean, she wouldn't
do something like that.
[BOTH laugh]
It really looks like
a real bomb though!
[MR. KIMIDORI cries]
[MR. KIMIDORI]
If this thing explodes,
I don't want you getting hurt.
There's only one
thing for me to do.
[ASAKURA] Mr. Kimidori,
what are you doing?!
[MR. KIMIDORI] If anyone's gonna
get blown up, it's gonna be me!
[ASAKURA] No, Mr. Kimidori!
I don't want that!
Come back here!
[ASAKURA crying]
[beep]
[ASAKURA]
Mr. Kimidori!
[MR. KIMIDORI panting]
[ASAKURA laughs]
Come back!
[MR. KIMIDORI] Aw, come on.
Don't let it getcha down.
How about Mr. Kimidori? It is
the color of my body, after all.
The light's fading...
I want to be cremated and my
ashes scattered to the wind.
[chuckles] Guess who?
I bet you're
surprised to see me.
Okay, time for
the salt and pepper.
[MR. KIMIDORI]
Coming up.
Miss Asakura... Farewell.
[ASAKURA screams]
I am home.
[ASAKURA]
Oh! You're back!
[BOTH]
Welcome home, Miss Nagato!
Why is he burnt?
We were sorta bored,
so we pretended we were
a bomb disposal unit.
[MR. KIMIDORI] My performance
was more method than usual.
[BOTH groan]
[KYON]
Okay...
What the hell was that?
[HARUHI]
When's it gonna stop?
It sucks when it
keeps raining like this
because we can't go outside.
Right, Mikuru?
You have a point there.
Even when it's not raining,
we're always
hanging out in here.
[HARUHI]
Really? No, we don't.
[KYON] We spend more
than half of our time
in this room, playing games.
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
But there's a different
reason for that, Kyon.
When the weather's nice, we
could go outdoors if we wanted!
But we stay inside
'cause we choose to!
[KYON]
She's hopeless!
[HARUHI]
I know...
We're gonna come up with some
new ideas for outfits to wear!
[KYON]
First, why?
Second, what're you
gonna make us wear?
I wasn't talking about us.
We're brainstorming
costumes for Mikuru!
[KYON]
Uh...
--[MIKURU screaming]
--[HARUHI laughing]
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI] We're gonna use
this board for our designs.
First, I'm gonna sketch a
template version of Mikuru.
Oh, I get it. Then we
draw our designs on top.
[BOTH]
Uh...
Is that her?
I guess...
I was drawing her from memory.
I don't know why it
came out like that.
You don't have to
use your memory
when your subject's hanging
right in front of you.
Okay, this time,
I'll look at her and draw.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Hm...
Mm-hm.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
You just added the rope!
[HARUHI]
Huh?!
Hey, guys!
Is Mikuru around?
Yes! I'm up here!
What is it, Miss Tsuruya?
[TSURUYA]
Whoa!
Looks like something
interesting's going on!
Could I borrow your
notes from maths class?
[MIKURU]
Sure.
I'd get them, but I
can't move right now.
They're in my bag,
so help yourself.
Cool, thanks!
[KYON]
Well, how 'bout this?
[HARUHI]
That's not right, you dummy!
There! It's supposed
to be like that!
[TSURUYA]
What's with all the commotion?
You guys okay over there?
Hi, Miss Tsuruya.
Good timing.
We got stuck.
We need you!
I went off on a tangent,
and sort of forgot
what we were doing.
[KYON]
We're so lost right now,
we need help
getting back on track.
[TSURUYA] Are you guys tryin'
to make a monster movie?
Good try, but no.
You're way off,
but that's a good idea!
I know! We'll make our
second movie a monster movie!
[KYON]
Huh?!
They explained...
Uh-huh... Mikuru's
getting a new outfit.
You know, that's a pretty
cool idea for a project!
Tell you what,
guys, count me in!
This is gonna be
so awesome now!
Watch a learn!
My Tsuruya-style portrait
technique is so realistic,
it's like you're looking
at a photograph!
Stand back 'cause it's time
to do some drawing!
Hya!
Hah!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL]
Uh...
[KYON]
You gotta be kidding.
[TSURUYA]
Huh?
[NAGATO] This room is currently
under the influence
of Haruhi Suzumiya's powers.
Therefore, any attempt
at accurate reproduction
using artistic techniques
has been neutralized.
[KYON]
Um...
This drawing stuff
isn't really working out,
so maybe we should quit for now.
Yeah, you got a point there.
You're right. We should
try doin' somethin' else.
Something else like what?
Miss Tsuruya? You know, right?
[TSURUYA chuckles] Time to
break out our bag of tricks.
[BOTH laugh]
[MIKURU gasps]
Stay away!
You both look so evil!
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI]
All done!
[TSURUYA]
Yup! She looks awesome!
[BOTH]
It's her new monster costume!
I freaking knew it!
We were supposed to
make a new outfit for her!
[BOTH]
Oh...
[BOTH] It's her new outfit!
What do you think?
[KYON]
You just rephrased it!
That's still a
monster movie costume!
Now all she needs is
a monster to fight!
Have you done any
casting for it?
Not yet.
I wonder who could
play the rival monster.
[HARUHI gasps]
You wanna do it, Yuki?
Absolutely.
Don't you even wanna
think about it first?
I absolutely want to do it.
Remember, I have
done this before.
[KYON]
Oh, yeah.
I have to prepare for battle!
[KYON]
S-Sure. Break a leg.
[NAGATO roars]
--[MIKURU screams]
--[HARUHI laughing]
[KYON]
Hm? Are you okay over there?
You didn't get involved in
any of today's craziness.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
I didn't, did I?
I'm sorry about that.
My mind was a million
miles away this whole time.
[KYON]
Hm?
Okay, but you really
don't need to apologize.
Don't tell me it's Haruhi again.
Is she causing more
weirdness to happen?
No... This doesn't have anything
to do with Miss Suzumiya.
But... It's just that...
I guess if I told you,
it wouldn't be such
a bad thing, after all.
[KYON]
Huh?
[thunder crash]
[KOIZUMI] At the beginning
of this episode,
the caption said ten heroines,
but we only saw eight of them!
Could I be one of the
two remaining heroines?!
[KYON]
You gotta be kidding me!
Is that what you've been
thinking about this whole time?!
Wait! I got it now!
The other heroine can only be...
...Mr. Arakawa!
I don't freaking care!
--It's ready!
--You made it?!
I want you to test it.
Okay, if you insist...
[KYON]
This is from the movie!
Hmm... The Asakura route, huh?
[NAGATO]
She is difficult to complete.
If you make one wrong choice,
you will arrive
at the bad ending.
[KYON]
This is too hard!
By the way, this
type of character is
more commonly known as yandare.
[KYON]
This is getting a little creepy.
[KYON] Okay...
I've seen this setup before.
Do you consider this type
of meeting scenario boring?
[KYON] That's an accident
not a meeting!
Wait, is this the Arakawa route?
Oh, you got Miss Mori
as a P.E. teacher.
[NAGATO]
Yes.
If you complete her stage,
she will become your maid.
[KYON] Okay... That's kinda
strange, but I can live with it.
And if you can make it to
the final stage and defeat her,
you will be rewarded
with a happy ending.
What in the name of all that's
holy is this game's genre?!
[NAGATO]
A love story?
But all I've been seeing is
a lotta fighting and bloodshed.
[chomping]
Here we go!
[CHURUYA]
Nyon!
Nyoron...
Hey, Kyon! Hey, Kyon!
Do you have any smoked
cheese with you?
You already had some today.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA gasps]
[KYON]
No.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoreron...
Hey, taxi!
[tires screech]
[click]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Mikuru! Mikuru!
I was wondering, do you know
how smoked cheese is made?
Google it.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Itsuki! Itsuki!
Smoked cheese is gonna be
the big thing this year, huh?
[KOIZUMI sighs]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Haru-nyan! Haru-nyan!
Let's do a "Smoked Cheese is
Obviously Awesome
Stuff We Eat" Brigade.
You gotta be kidding me.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Nagatocchi! Nagatocchi!
Are there any books
about smoked cheese?
[NAGATO]
Who knows.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[KYON]
Here we go.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Loser takes out the trash.
One... two... three.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We're gonna have a fire drill.
Miss Churuya, you get
to put out the fire.
[CHURUYA]
Roger that!
Squirt, squirt, squirt.
Head count.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Where's Miss Churuya?
She didn't make it out in time.
Then she's dead.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Nagatocchi! Nagatocchi!
Will you play with me?
[NAGATO]
I'm busy now.
You can play with
my backup though.
Oh!
What's your name?
Ashakura.
Will
Impossible.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[keys click]
[KYON]
No.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ASHAKURA] This is the
house where Kyon lives.
I'll put this in mailbox,
and he'll know I feel.
[yelps]
[ASHAKURA]
You can do it, me.
[gasps]
[CHURUYA]
You know what I like?
I like to call smoked
cheese, "smochee."
[ASHAKURA] It's that girl from
before! Why is she with Kyon?
[
Ahh!
[grunts]
Hm?
[CHURUYA]
Huh?
Here we go.
We're goin' to town to look
for some mysterious things.
[CHURUYA giggles]
That looks pretty mysterious.
Okay, we're done.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We're gonna play baseball today!
You're out... as a player!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Let's hand out some flyers!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We're gonna go on
a trip tomorrow!
I'm ready to go, nyoro.
All the hotels are full now,
so we couldn't book a room.
[HARUHI]
Then we're not going.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Let's challenge the
Computer Club to a game!
Are you ready?
[CHURUYA]
Mm-hm!
Nyoron...
Cherry blossom party!
Miss Churuya,
go save us a good spot.
[CHURUYA]
Roger that!
They're not in bloom yet.
[HARUHI]
Then we're not going.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA sighs]
[CHURUYA]
Warm fuzzies!
We're challenging you to a game.
And if you can beat us,
we'll give you a computer.
Challenge accepted.
And if you beat us,
we'll give you Miss Churuya.
Uh, then... nevermind.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We're challenging
you to another game!
And this is the game
we're gonna play.
Now it's my turn
to shine, nyoro.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[meow]
[MIKURU]
Nya...
Hey, Kyon, check this out!
If you press the button
on my hea--
[buzz]
Isn't that cool?
To meet the needs of our
expanding mobile society,
I had silent mode insta--
[KYON]
Then, be quiet for a sec.
[buzz]
Oh, wow! What an amazing view!
Oh, look! Look! I've seen
that building on TV before!
Time for silent mode.
[buzz]
[CHURUYA grunting]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I need to tell Kyon
how I feel about him.
These chocolates
are for you, Kyon!
Really?
Are they made in Japan?
[ASHAKURA]
Huh?!
Looks like it's time for
spring cleaning again.
Yep.
[CHURUYA shivering]
[KOIZUMI]
It's too cold for her, though.
This nook is dirty,
so I'm gonna clean.
Sorry, I didn't mean to pile up
in the spaces between
your furniture, dusty.
Make sure you don't
leave any of me behind.
Clean up every
last speck, dusty.
[CHURUYA]
Gotcha.
[DUSTY screams]
Do you like my outfit?
Doesn't it look divine?
Isn't it mega cool?
Well, nyoro?
I'll take a water.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We made a figure of you.
Wow! It looks just like me!
[KYON]
Let's go back to the forest.
[CHURUYA gasps]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
May I take a picture?
Okay...
[ASHAKURA]
Hey, Kyon?
Um... You know...
Whenever I think about you,
it makes me feel funny inside.
My heart starts racing
and I can't get to sleep.
That's 'cause you're dying.
[gasps]
I got a part-time job
as a mover!
'Scuse me, Kyon.
Could you pick up that side?
[CHURUYA]
Eh...
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA panting]
[CHURUYA]
Ah!
Nyoreron...
[CHURUYA sighs]
[CHURUYA]
Hm?
Ah!
[CHURUYA]
Warm fuzzies!
One... two... three.
Here we go.
Let's hang tanzaku.
Huh?
Uh?!
[CHURUYA sighs]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA grunting]
Huh?!
[KYON]
No.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Perfect, nyoro!
Okay, let's go.
Yay!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Gotcha!
Hey...
Come on, kid.
Cut me a break, will ya?
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Wow! That's pretty!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
There's smoked cheese in
the middle of this graveyard.
[CHURUYA whimpering]
Huh?
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA laughs]
Good job, buddy.
Here we go.
I got a new dress!
Well, nyoro?
You're a double A+.
Go get 'em, me.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Dowsing mode?
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Oh, hey, Kyon! Hey, Kyon?
I was wondering if
you'd like me to make
a bento box for you tomorrow.
Why would you?
[ASHAKURA]
What does he mean "why"?
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Why did you dodge it?
Because I could.
This show has a new title,
"That's impossible, Miss Asa--"
[CHURUYA]
Today, we are at the beach.
Hey, Beach Cafe Guy,
do you have any smoked cheese?
Hell no. I got
shaved ice though.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Oh! I'll have shaved ice then.
[BEACH CAFE GUY]
Dang...
Yeah, sorry. I'm all out.
[CHURUYA]
Nyororon...
Here. Take it.
Thank you! This is cool!
[CHURUYA]
Hya!
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA grunting]
[TANIGUCHI]
I wanna be a sea shell.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[shutter clicks]
[CHURUYA chuckles]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Kyon.
Which do you prefer?
The lunch? [giggles] Or me?
The lunch.
[ASHAKURA]
Dang... it...!
[buzzing]
[CHURUYA]
Hm?
[slurping]
[CHURUYA]
I don't know why,
but when I'm eating
smoked cheese,
nothing seems to bother me.
Itchy...
Here we go!
Today's the athletic festival!
And we're gonna win
no matter what.
Sorry, that was ambitious.
Might as well have
some lunch now.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ANNOUNCER]
It's the three-legged race.
--Go!
--[gunshot]
[CHURUYA grunts, gasps]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ANNOUNCER]
It's the bread eating race.
--Go!
--[gunshot]
[CHURUYA gasps]
[grunting]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
You're so hopeless.
[CHURUYA]
Huh?
Whoa! This is high!
[grunting]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ANNOUNCER]
The calvary race!
Go!
If you can't attack 'em,
then defend yourself
till the end.
[CHURUYA]
Mm-hm!
[CHURUYA grunting]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ANNOUNCER]
Ball toss! Go!
Head's up!
Ah!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I came up with an awesome
plan for the tug-o-war!
[CHURUYA grunting]
[HARUHI] We can't lose
if we do it this way.
[KYON]
Uh-uh.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I'm good at rolling a big ball!
Heave-ho!
[grunts]
Wow, the ball's really
heavy today...
[CHURUYA grunting]
[ANNOUNCER]
The obstacle course!
Go!
[CHURUYA grunts]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA pants]
[CHURUYA]
Huh?
Hm...
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[CHURUYA pants]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[CHURUYA panting]
I did it!
[gunshot]
Nagatocchi! I ran as hard
as I could, how'd I do?
[NAGATO]
You still came in last.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Nyoron Churuyasan.
[bell dings]
Here we go.
[CHURUYA]
Hey, Kyon! Hey, Kyon!
Trick or treat, nyoro!
[CHURUYA groans]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Sweep, sweep.
[sighs]
Huh?
[CHURUYA]
Hang in there.
Let's roast yams.
And this!
[sizzling]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[click]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[ASHAKURA]
There we go.
[CHURUYA chewing]
[ASHAKURA] I'll lure Miss
Churuya away with the cheese,
then I can be alone with Kyon.
[screams]
Oh, hello there, dusty.
I came back after all, dusty.
I might be kind of
small right now, dusty.
But someday, I'll grow up
to be really big, dusty!
[CHURUYA]
Gotcha!
[DUSTY screams]
Dusty!
[HARUHI]
Here we go.
[ASHAKURA sighs]
Kyon's so dreamy...
Yeah, I forgot to write my name
on the test we just took.
What a coincidence! I forgot
to write mine, too!
[ASHAKURA gasps]
She's tryin' to make Kyon think
they have a lot in common!
The nerve!
Excuse me, may I please
have my test back?
I want to erase my name.
What are you talking about?
Don't be ridiculous.
Wait until I've graded it.
[TEACHER]
Here are your tests.
[ASHAKURA gasps]
This is great, the teacher
erased my name for me.
Look, Kyon. I forgot to--
Oh, I wrote my name
on it after all.
No... way...
You did so horribly, you'll
have to take a make-up test.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Oh, too bad.
And you, too.
[gasping]
[CHURUYA]
Hm...
Ah!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoreron...
[ASHAKURA]
Hm...
I don't think this is
the right answer...
I know!
[ASHAKURA]
I'll put that down as my answer.
I feel a lot better
about it now.
[CHURUYA]
Hm...
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
You are my backup.
Prepare for data download.
[ASHAKURA] Not now! Oh, no!
I-I can't control my hand!
[BOTH]
I'm all done!
How did you do, Ashacchi?
How about you, Miss Churuya?
[ASHAKURA whimpering]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Come on, it's time to go home.
Oh! With me?
I mean, I'd love to.
[CHURUYA] The test had
a question about smochee.
[KYON]
Really?
[ASHAKURA]
Fight on, me.
[SHAMISEN]
Beep, beep.
Me... ow!
Kyon, guess what? Guess what?
Christmas is just
around the corner!
[KYON]
Oh, man!
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Hey, Shami-nyan! Shami-nyan!
Christmas is just
around the corner!
Sorry, kid, but I don't
understand human speech.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
We're gonna decorate
the Christmas tree.
Jingle blah...
Jingle blah.
[BOTH]
Jingle all the way...
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I've got a call for
you from Santa Claus.
Wow! You're kidding!
Hi, Santa! I'd like... some
smoked cheese for Christmas!
[KYON]
That'll be 420 yen, after tax.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
[snoring]
[KYON]
Merry Christmas.
[MOUSE]
Sneak, sneak, sneak.
Squeak... Hi.
Sneak... sneak... sneak...
You don't wanna go
there, Mr. Mouse.
[MOUSE]
Oh!
Damn...
[SHAMISEN]
Beep, beep.
[snoring]
[SHAMISEN]
Ooh, smochee...
Christmas presents don't
have to be from Santa.
Anyone can give them
to people they like.
Hey, Kyon, lookit.
I got you a Christmas present.
I guess... Maybe now, you'll
have an idea about how much I...
...really... really like you!
Gee, thanks.
How much you pay for it?
[ASHAKURA]
What?!
[ALL]
Nyoron Churuyasan.
Here we go!
[CHURUYA grunting]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
Sledding is so much fun!
[CHURUYA screams]
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I hope the vacuum doesn't
suck me up again, dusty.
You have nothing to fear, dusty.
I will protect you
no matter what, dusty.
--[CHURUYA] Gotcha!
--[BOTH] Dusty!
Hey, Kyon! Hey, Kyon!
May I please have
your second button?
[KYON]
Here.
[CHURUYA]
Nyoron...
I don't want you hanging
around Kyon any longer!
I just wanna eat smoked
cheese with everyone!
You wanna have a
sleepover tonight?
Really? A sleepover at Kyon's?
[snoring]
[KYON]
Okay... This is weird.
[laughing]
[ALL]
We love smochee...
We love smochee.
I'm sorry, but I just can't
seem to find the smochee.
Today is Smochee Day, nyoro!
[laughing]
[ALL]
Hooray for smochee.