[MINA]
Sanae!
Here! For you.
[laughs]
Uh... A love letter?
Of course not!
It's just a regular letter!
Everyone's writing them to
their friends these days!
Haven't you noticed?
[SANAE]
No.
[sighs]
Don't you worry, Yukari, I'm
gonna write one for you too.
[YUKARI] That's nice of you,
just don't do it in class.
You need to focus on the lesson.
Friendship is way more
important than any lesson.
What, are the girls all suddenly
into writing letters now?
That's what it looks like.
I wonder if some of them
are writing love letters, too.
[NAKAI laughs]
Maybe. They do
seem really into it.
[TAKAO]
I'll say.
[NISHIKATA]
Love letters, huh?
I don't get the appeal.
They could just say
what they want out loud.
Why bother to write it all down?
Must have a lotta time
on their hands.
[TAKAO yelling]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[YUKARI] Sanae, you're
going a little overboard.
[MINA]
One kick was enough.
So kicking him at all's okay?
[TANABE]
All right, let's start class.
Open up your textbooks
to page seventy-six.
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi's writing letters, too?
Sometimes I forget that
she's just your ordinary girl.
[NISHIKATA]
What?
"Letter."
Is there something
wrong, Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA gasps]
No, nothing, everything's great!
[NISHIKATA]
A letter? Who's it from?
And why me?
I wonder if some of them
are writing love letters, too.
[NISHIKATA] No, no, no,
that's obviously not it!
Someone's playing a prank on me.
Oh, yeah!
This could be Takagi's doing.
No, it's gotta be her!
Takagi--
[NISHIKATA]
Wait a second.
Reign it in, Nishikata!
What if it's somebody else?
What if it isn't Takagi?
If she finds out I got a letter,
she'll just use that
to tease me again!
Yeah? What is it?
Uh...
Oh, uh...
I was just thinking.
It's nice out.
Are you hiding something?
Why would I be hiding something?
Hmm...
Dunno. But you're suspicious.
And blushing, too.
You're just imagining things.
[TAKAGI]
Well, maybe.
But why is your textbook closed?
Well. You see, I uh...
I bet it's why your face is red.
No, it's not!
And my face is not red!
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
Yes, that's why I said so!
I guess I was imagining things.
By the way,
that letter in your textbook.
I put that there.
[NISHIKATA yelling]
I knew it!
Yeah. I knew that.
I mean, duh. It was obvious.
[TAKAGI chuckles]
You liar.
What are you talking about?
I'm not lying.
I was just having fun
making you squirm.
So. You gonna read
what's inside?
You wrote something?
Well, it is a letter.
You're just messing with
me like always, aren't you?
[NISHIKATA]
Why aren't you saying something?
Okay.
I'll read it at home later.
Read it now.
What? Why now?
Because. School's over
after this period.
And I wanted an answer by then.
An answer?
[NISHIKATA] If it's a letter
that needs an answer,
then it's a letter
asking a question.
Does that mean it's not just
meant to mess with me?
I wonder if some of them
are writing love letters, too.
[NISHIKATA]
What if Takao's right?
What if it's a love letter?
Is that even possible?
[NISHIKATA chuckles]
By any chance,
would this happen
to be a love letter, or...?
[birds chirping]
[NISHIKATA]
What's with the silence?!
Why don't you just read it?
Uh, I will, just gimme a minute.
I gotta open it up first.
[NISHIKATA]
Based on that reaction,
I'd wager anything
that this is designed
just to tease me.
Whatever it ends up saying,
I have to be firm and
confident so that she doesn't
get the chance.
Be bold! Be brave!
But what if...
No, it can't be.
Why would it be?
There's no way!
But if it is a
love letter, then... I...
You could have just
asked me to my face.
But everyone's writing
letters now. It's cool.
However, I was also
curious how you'd react.
So I was right!
You were messing with me!
[TANABE]
Shut it, Nishikata!
[TAKAGI giggling]
[NISHIKATA, TAKAGI]
"First Day of School."
[TEACHER 5A]
Thanks a lot.
I appreciate it, young man.
[NISHIKATA]
Welcome. I gotta go now.
[TEACHER 5A]
Oh, one second!
What's your name, new kid?
Did I forget to say?
I'm Nishikata.
Nishikata.
Congrats on getting in!
[TEACHER 5A]
Mm-hmm.
[NISHIKATA]
Thanks.
[TANABE] You'll all be learning
alongside each other
over the course
of the next year.
I'm not gonna force you
to get along with everybody.
But I hope you realize
you're only gonna make
the experience
worse if you don't.
Oh, no, did I lose it somewhere?
[TANABE] Well, I don't want to
bore you right off the bat
with a long speech, so...
[TANABE]
Slept in on the first day?
No, I was, uh...
If nothing else,
I admire your audacity.
But... Sir, I--
What's your name?
It's Nishikata.
All right, then. Sit down.
Uh... Yes, sir.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, great, Everyone's staring.
I have to make friends with
people and clear things up
before I become known as "that
guy who was late on day one."
[TAKAO, KIMURA laughing]
[door opens]
[TEACHER 12A] Mr. Tanabe,
a moment of your time?
They called and said they're
running a little bit late.
[TANABE]
Really?
Are we pushing the
entrance ceremony back?
[TEACHER 12A]
Yes, I'll keep you posted.
[TANABE] I just got word that
the entrance ceremony
is running behind schedule.
Sounds like it's gonna take a
while before they're all set up.
So in the meantime...
...we're figuring out seating.
At least I'm not in the front.
Sucks to be you.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, come on.
I'm literally as far in the
corner as I possibly can be.
Normally I'd be happy
about being this far away
from the teacher.
It's the best spot to goof off.
But I don't know
anyone as it is!
There's no one
behind me or to my left.
Worse, I'm sitting
next to a girl.
Did you actually sleep in?
[NISHIKATA]
She's talking to me.
[TAKAGI] It looked like you
were about to say something
to the teacher.
Uh... Yeah.
No. I didn't actually sleep in.
[NISHIKATA] If only I'd
made it here earlier.
I was at the school
on time, but...
It's Takagi's fault.
Whoever that is.
[TAKAGI]
Huh?
[TANABE] All right everyone,
head to the gym.
Let's keep quiet.
And no running
[STUDENTS]
Okay.
[STUDENT 10A]
Hey!
You want to walk
there together?
[TAKAGI]
Sure.
Wait a second.
[PRINCIPAL 12A] You will
soon be given a great gift,
the right to vote.
With it, you will choose
students for positions
of responsibility.
It's important you select
politicians who are worthy
of your trust and confidence.
Similarly, your mothers
and fathers choose
their representatives
by voting...
Wasn't that speech crazy long?
[TAKAO] That dude was talking
so long I almost fell asleep!
I know, it was like when we
started elementary school.
You're pretty cool for comin'
in late on the first day.
[NISHIKATA]
I didn't mean to.
[TANABE] Everybody quit yappin'
and take your seats.
I'm sorry for getting
back late, sir.
[TANABE]
Just go sit down.
That's it for today,
but remember,
real classes start tomorrow.
Don't mess around because
I'm letting you out early.
Go straight home.
Hey, Nishikata.
How 'bout I try to guess
why you were late today?
I bet I can.
If I get it right
on my first try, I win.
Sure, I guess.
[NISHIKATA] Wait, how
is she gonna figure it out
on her first try?
You were delivering a lost item.
What? How'd you know?
[TANABE]
Hey. Quiet down, Nishikata.
I'm sorry, sir.
How did you know?
[TAKAGI giggles]
How indeed.
Uh... Wait.
You're Takagi?
You weren't here yet when
everyone introduced themselves.
[NISHIKATA groaning]
[TAKAGI laughing]
What's with that reaction?
Hey! I just said to be quiet!
[TAKAGI, NISHIKATA]
Sorry!
[TAKAGI laughing]
Thanks a lot. For picking it up.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
[TAKAGI]
"Seating Arrangement."
[NISHIKATA]
Seventy-two! Seventy-three!
Seventy-four! Seventy-five!
All this work's finally
startin' to pay off!
[NISHIKATA yells]
Oh, man.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[NISHIKATA]
She's not here yet.
Morning, Nishikata.
Oh, good morning
yourself, Takagi!
So, hey. Have you heard?
They're going to be changing
where everyone sits today.
Really? When?
During homeroom.
[NISHIKATA]
Homeroom? That's first period!
--Taka--
--Are you okay?
First period, huh?
That'll be kinda fun.
Yeah?
Well, I mean, we haven't had a
seating change in a while, so...
Yeah, sure.
I guess there are
always positives.
But if I'm being honest.
I wanted to be next to you
for a while longer.
[NISHIKATA] She's just
messing with me again.
I almost fell for it.
[CLASS chattering]
Does anyone still
need a number? No?
Then move your desks
according to the layout
on the board.
What number did you draw?
Twenty-nine.
[TAKAGI]
Oh. The far back again, then.
[NISHIKATA]
What about you?
[TAKAGI]
This time I'm front and center.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh.
We're going to be pretty far.
Yeah.
[TAKAGI]
Later.
All right! Now you can sneak
me answers on all our tests!
[YUKARI]
What? That's cheating.
I'm not doing that.
[MINA]
It's called mutual aid.
[YUKARI]
Oh, yeah?
Well what do I get out of it?
[MINA] Words of encouragement
from your friend!
[YUKARI]
Yay...
Yo, Nishikata.
Are you sittin' here?
Nah, over there.
Oh, yeah?
That's too bad.
I was hoping we'd be closer.
Yeah, me too.
[NAKAI] My vision's been
getting really bad lately.
I hope I can see
what's on the board.
Oh. So that's it.
I'm next to Nishikata, huh?
You okay, Mano?
Yeah. I'm just great.
What's up? Are you not happy?
It's nothing.
Feel free to just ignore me.
I'm just depressed because
I'm not sitting near Nakai.
I was really hoping we'd
be next to each other.
[MANO sighs]
How far away is he?
Hey.
[KIMURA]
Someone!
Anyone!
Please switch seats with me!
How am I supposed to
sneak an early lunch
if I'm right in front
of the teacher?
You aren't switching
seats unless you have
a legitimate reason.
Also, Kimura.
Please, do see me after class.
[NISHIKATA]
Right in front of the teacher?
But if I'm being honest.
I wanted to be next to
you for a while longer.
Hey, Kimura, listen!
I can't see the board
from here; let's switch!
Oh. Thanks!
But I already found someone.
[NISHIKATA]
It's not like I care.
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata. Hey.
[NISHIKATA]
What the--?
Guess what?
I'm sitting here now.
Wha--? But how?
Well, first Nakai
and Kimura switched.
Because Nakai couldn't see
the board well enough.
So Nakai was all
the way up front.
When she saw that,
Mano wanted to switch with me,
since I was right next to him.
Mano's short, so she
prefers the front anyway.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh. I see.
Nishikata.
You tried to sit next to
me up there, didn't you?
No, I...
I couldn't see the
board well from here.
Hmm?
Oh, yeah?
Mmm?
What? It's true!
All right, we're starting class.
Get your textbooks out.
Oh. That reminds me.
What was it that you
wanted to say earlier today?
What, did I read you wrong?
I thought you were
looking for an opportunity.
[NISHIKATA]
Sorry.
It took me a while
to return this.
Thank you.
From over summer break?
Uh... Yeah.
From then, and...
The first day of school?
You remembered that?
Of course I did.
You did too.
Heh! Thank you.
I made sure to wash it for you.
Oh, nothing.
I'm just kinda glad.
--Why?
--Oh. Y'know...
For a lot.
That I got to return
your handkerchief.
And that we ended up
next to each other again, oh!
And also...
Well, yeah.
I'm looking forward to this.
[TANABE] So here, we'd say,
"I do not agree."
Or you could contract it
to, "I don't agree."
That part's pretty easy.
But on the next page, things get
a little more complicated.