Well...
As I'm sure you know, summer
vacation starts tomorrow.
Try not to get into any trouble.
[class cheers]
[MINA] Summer vacation
is gonna be awesome!
[TAKAO]
Hey.
We're thinking of going to
the beach tomorrow, you in?
Yeah, you know it, dude.
[KIMURA] I suddenly have
a huge craving for watermelon!
[NISHIKATA]
I'd eat some watermelon.
[TAKAO] Perfect!
Let's get one for tomorrow!
[NISHIKATA]
Good idea!
"Tandem Riding."
Summer vacation.
You excited?
Yeah.
It feels like I've been
waiting for it forever.
Now I can play
as much as I want!
I'm a free man!
You better not forget
about your homework.
Knowing you, you'll put it off.
I bet you're thinking
"play first, work later."
[NISHIKATA]
How'd you know?
Haha! So I was right?
Well yeah.
But the whole point of
a break is to relax, right?
I wanna go to the pool, hit the
beach, and go camping and stuff.
Man, I barely have
enough time to do all that!
[sighs] I wish we could just
have summer vacation forever.
Yeah?
I like going to school,
too, though.
Because...
[TAKAGI]
It's fun.
[TAKAGI] No more of
that for a while, huh?
So hot!
But the breeze feels great!
Can you go faster? This rocks!
[NAKAI] You wouldn't be saying
that if you were pedaling!
[TAKAGI]
It's hot out.
Should we do what
they were doing?
Huh?!
Of course, you'd
have to be in the front.
No. We can't!
Uh. 'Cuz it'd be dangerous
with cars driving by, you know?
There are no cars around.
It's not even a public road.
Yeah, but.
Hold on.
Are you embarrassed
or something?
No! Of course
I'm not embarrassed!
Oh.
You can't do it, then?
What are you talking about?
Tandem riding is super easy.
I just don't think we should
do it, 'cuz it's not safe.
[TAKAGI] Let's go to
the vacant lot, then.
Huh?!
If you can't do it,
then you owe me a juice.
[NISHIKATA]
I hope you're not too thirsty,
because I got this, no sweat.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
That was just the practice run!
I can do this!
I'll take grape.
Could ya gimme a second?!
Is it really this hard to ride
with someone sitting
on the back of a bike?
Just checking, but you're
not trying to throw us
off balance on purpose, are you?
Of course not.
Are you sure.
I'm just sitting
how I usually sit.
If we can't get it to work,
then it's gotta be your fault.
I mean...
...the last time I did
this with someone.
They didn't have
any trouble peddling.
Oh, really?
That's cool.
I take it they were a girl?
[TAKAGI]
Nope.
Not a girl.
I see.
[growls]
One more time.
I think I've almost got it!
This time for sure!
What's going on?
Why do I feel so frustrated?
I'm just riding a bike!
What's up?
You're getting into this.
No, I'm not!
I just don't wanna waste
my hard earned money on you!
Yeah, that's it!
I just don't want to buy
her a drink! That's all!
Hey!
We're moving!
By the way, Nishikata,
the last time I rode on
the back of someone's bike,
it was my dad's.
I think I was four at the time.
[crash]
Take it.
Why, thank you.
[gasps]
Ahh...
That's good!
Are you not gonna get
yourself a drink, too?
Uh. Nope.
I'm, uhh, not thirsty.
I can't tell her I have
no money to buy my own.
How would that look?
Want some?
No.
I'm fine, thanks.
She'd just call it an indirect
kiss again to get me to blush.
Come on, I know you're thirsty.
Have some.
I really don't want any.
[NISHIKATA]
Endure it.
You can do it.
Endure.
[clank]
Drink this.
We can't have you
getting heatstroke.
I can have it?
[TAKAGI]
Yeah.
Besides.
I know you.
You don't want mine
because it's an indirect kiss.
Huh?!
Tha-That's not it!
I'm just not thirsty!
Right.
But you'll drink yours?
Well, you already bought it.
It'd be a waste
when it's this hot.
Thanks for the drink.
We won't be walking
home from school for a while.
Ahhh...
Got that right.
We're on vacation, after all.
I know!
How about starting tomorrow,
we practice tandem
riding here until noon?
[NISHIKATA]
Okay, I guess.
But not on the road.
[TAKAGI]
That's what I meant.
We'll just ride here.
If we're only
ever gonna ride here,
there's no point in practicing.
Yeah, there is.
You know.
Summer vacation.
It starts tomorrow.
[NISHIKATA]
What does that mean?
[TAKAGI]
All right!
Well, we should head home.
[TAKAGI]
Summer vacation.
Huh?
I'm excited.
It'll be fun!
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, obviously.
[MINA]
"First Day of Summer Vacation."
[SANAE] Why'd it have
to rain on our first day off?
[MINA]
I know.
Summer vacation's
barely even started,
and my plans are already ruined!
It's not like it's supposed
to rain tomorrow.
[MINA] I wanted
to go to the pool today.
And I'm never
getting that time back!
Please stop crying.
You know we can't do
anything about the rain.
Let's just start our homework.
--Huh?
What's with those faces?
Don't tell me you
two didn't bring yours.
I told you guys to bring
your homework over
since it's raining out!
I figured I must
have misheard you.
Unbelievable!
Why do we get assigned homework
during summer vacation
in the first place?
It's a violation
of human rights.
It's hardly a break
with homework.
Right?
Dream all you want,
we still have to do it.
[MINA whines]
Ugh! Do me a personal
favor, Yukari:
Quit doing your
homework and relax!
Seeing you do yours reminds me
that I have to do mine,
and now I can't enjoy myself!
Whatever!
Maybe you need the reminder!
[groans]
It's only the first day still.
Just forget about school.
[YUKARI] Typical, from a
person who will be crying
with regret on
August thirty-first.
You're so stubborn.
Forget you.
I'm gonna read manga.
Yeah?
Fine.
Hey, Yukari?
[YUKARI]
Hmm?
I got a great idea.
Can we write our
book report on manga?
Yes, please.
Can you two just
go home already?
[NISHIKATA]
"Test of Courage."
It stopped raining.
Awesome!
Wait, why exactly am
I happy about that again?
[approaching footsteps]
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
[chuckles]
You're here.
Yeah, we made a
promise, didn't we?
Guess so.
Something wrong?
Uh.
No.
It's nothing.
Whoa.
There are so many puddles here.
Well, you know what they say.
When it rains, it pours.
[NISHIKATA] I didn't recognize
her for a second there.
Come to think of it,
I've run into her a few times
on our days off by chance,
but this is our first
time meeting up.
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA]
No way!
This isn't like, a date, is it?
No, obviously not!
We're just here to
practice tandem riding,
like we agreed to!
Nishikata?
Huh?! What's up?
You hear me?
Hello?
No. Sorry.
What did you say?
[TAKAGI] This place is in
pretty bad riding condition.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh, yeah.
Actually,
I was planning to go out
after we practiced today.
No sense going back home.
Do you wanna hang out
with me to kill some time?
[NISHIKATA gasps]
Okay.
Is this a date?
No, no, no.
No way!
Uh. Yeah, that's fine.
But let's go someplace where
there aren't too many people.
There's no telling what
our classmates would say
if they saw us!
[TAKAGI]
Hmmm...
How about...
That's it!
[NISHIKATA]
A test of courage?
[TAKAGI]
Perfect for summer, right?
Wouldn't it be scarier
if we did it at night?
[TAKAGI]
Not by much.
I heard it gets pitch black
when you're in there.
Some say, there's a presence.
Sorry.
What?
A presence?
Well, that's what I heard.
This tunnel doesn't
have any sharp turns.
But for some reason,
a lot of cars ended up crashing
straight into the walls.
So they had to make
a new road nearby.
And since then,
every night, without fail,
a bloodthirsty ghost appears.
Looking for cars to prey upon.
But there's even more to it.
Rumor has it.
People are spirited away here.
Dozens.
Maybe more have disappeared
right in this very tunnel.
Are you going in?
Or are you chicken?
I am so not chicken!
It's the middle of the day!
Why would I be scared
of going in some dusty,
stupid, old tunnel?
[NISHIKATA]
It's way darker than I thought.
Why is the wind making
such a weird noise?
Hey.
Check out what's on the wall.
[NISHIKATA]
A talisman?
For spirits.
It keeps them away.
So clearly,
there must be
something evil in here.
[screams]
[laughs]
I'm not surprised you're scared.
I'm not!
I was just shocked, that's all!
Look!
Uh, great; what is it this time?
[TAKAGI]
Weird.
I wonder what this
steel barrel is doing here.
Uh. Yeah.
All right.
I vote you look inside.
Huh?
Are you scared?
Will you stop saying that?
I'll look.
It's not that big of a deal.
[TAKAGI]
Ah!
[laughs]
[sighs]
That's what I was
really worried about!
Takagi?
Where'd you run off to?
Quit messing with me.
[NISHIKATA]
Didn't she mention something
about being spirited away?
But that couldn't...
Takagi!
Answer me!
[gasps]
[shrieks]
What are you freaking out for?
It's just me.
Where'd you come from?
Hey.
You were looking for me
just now, weren't you?
Huh? Yeah right.
Why would I do that?
So she lured me in here
to jump-scare me a ton.
Whoa.
Look at that.
That's a big hole.
Why don't you take
a peek inside it?
[NISHIKATA] Like I'd fall for
the same trick twice.
Don't make me laugh!
Oh no, I'm stuck!
My hand's stuck in the hole!
How do you like my acting?
I've been working on it.
I'm gonna freak you out so bad!
I don't know what,
but it feels like something's
pulling me from the other side!
Help me--!
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
[shrieks]
[laughs]
Did I scare you?
No.
What is that?
I dunno,
I found it on the ground.
[NISHIKATA growls]
Oh!
Glad your hand came loose.
[NISHIKATA]
Man.
I gotta find some way to get
her before we leave this tunnel!
[water droplet]
[laughs]
As jumpy as usual.
Ahh...
Some fresh air!
This sucks.
I couldn't find anything
to get her back with.
Must be another couple on
a date in the spooky tunnel.
Don't bother them.
Let's go.
[GIRL]
Okay.
[chuckles]
She called it a "date."
She doesn't know what
she's talking about.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
What is it?
You're blushing again.
Did you have fun back there?
Because I did.
I guess.
Yeah, but...
It's almost noon,
we should go back home soon.
Yeah, let's.
What way are you going?
[NISHIKATA moans] You want
to go back through there?
[TAKAGI]
Yeah, why not?
Are you scared?
[NISHIKATA]
When am I ever?
I met my quota for the day.
Wait.
It's summer vacation.
Why do I still have just as
many push-ups to do as normal?
[YUKARI]
"Summer Science Project."
[MINA] Yes, the consommé
flavor is quite good.
[SANAE]
Don't lie.
Your eyes are watering.
[MINA]
No, they're not.
And I know it's better
than your kelp flavor.
[YUKARI]
They both sound awful.
There are so many
flavors to choose from.
Why would you pick those?
[MINA] You wouldn't
understand, miss watermelon.
[SANAE] Take risks while
you're still young, right?
[YUKARI] That's some philosophy
to apply to popsicles.
[MINA] Hey, did you
two decide on subjects
for the science project?
[SANAE]
Not yet.
[YUKARI]
Me neither.
[SANAE]
You?
[MINA]
I'm still thinking, too.
[MINA] Isn't there
something easy I can do?
Like, finish-in-a-day easy?
Just do actual research.
[SANAE]
Hmm...
A dog observation diary?
Ah! Awesome idea!
That sounds super easy!
And dogs basically behave
the same way every day.
So I can just copy the entries
and change the dates!
If you're gonna lie,
write it by hand at least.
Besides, dogs
barely do anything.
They wake up, bark
for a walk, bark to be fed,
and sleep every chance they get.
Maybe they'll wake up
and bark for attention,
but then they'll just
bark for food again.
Why would anyone
want to observe that?
You're such a
stick in the mud, Yukari.
Well she is the class president.
It comes with the territory.
Right?
[YUKARI]
Shut up.
Anyway, have you two started
to do your homework yet?
We've still got plenty of time.
Right?
[sighs]
Just so you know.
You're not copying mine.
Not even if I do your
science project for you?
On a dog?
No, thank you.
You say this now,
but you're gonna end up
sharing your answers
with us anyway.
She wants the class
to get good grades.
Right?
[YUKARI] Maybe I should
do an observation diary
on their procrastination habits.
[NISHIKATA]
"Water Tap."
So hot.
This is the worst day
of vacation yet.
[shrieks]
Are you kidding?
First, I overslept.
[NISHIKATA]
And then I had a flat tire.
But at least all this happened
on a day we're not
practicing tandem riding.
Takagi said she was going
on a family vacation.
[NISHIKATA] When's she
coming back from that?
I was gonna stay home
for a few hours and do chores,
so I could have
the afternoon free,
but of course I was
sent on a shopping trip.
Truly this is the
darkest of vacations.
That kinda sounded poetic,
I should write it down.
[NISHIKATA]
That looks like...
Yeah, it's Takagi.
Huh.
I guess she's back.
I might as well use this
opportunity to follow her.
[chuckles]
Maybe I can find a weakness
to exploit in the future.
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA]
Uh oh.
Did she see me there?
Maybe it was my imagination.
No, she did see me!
But I can see her hat sticking
out around the corner.
You think you're gonna
surprise me, don't you?
Not while I still may breathe!
I should write that down, too.
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
She... She got me!
Going somewhere?
Yeah.
Just grocery shopping.
Hey.
What a coincidence.
I am too.
We could take your bike,
ride tandem?
Come on.
We agreed no doing
that in the road.
[NISHIKATA] When did she
find out I was following her?
Fine.
Let's walk together, then.
[shrieks]
[NISHIKATA]
Oh no! I gotcha!
Are you okay?
[NISHIKATA] And the
curse of today continues.
[TAKAGI]
You're hurt.
[NISHIKATA] Nah. It's nothing.
I'll just let it be.
Don't do that.
You should wash it off.
[sighs]
[NISHIKATA]
How embarrassing.
[TAKAGI]
Does your knee hurt that much?
[NISHIKATA]
No.
It's just that I was
already having a bad day,
and now I got a cut, too.
I'm wallowing in how
much this vacation sucks.
And it's not like I can
write about my misfortunes
for my summer homework.
[TAKAGI]
Here.
Huh?
But it'll stain.
Don't worry, just take it.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh.
Thank you.
That feels nice!
[TAKAGI] So you tried
to catch me before, right?
Thanks for that.
You should come in.
The cold water's really nice.
Uh, No, I...
[TAKAGI]
You know you want to.
Cooling you down?
Uh.
You know what?
I had a good day.
Because I got to see someone.
Huh?
Wh-Who do you mean?
You'll get your
souvenir tomorrow.
[splash]
[NISHIKATA]
Hey!
Stop that Takagi,
the water's really cold!