A brand new issue.
Day-one purchase.
[NISHIKATA]
"Shopping."
[TAKAGI'S MOM]
Here you go.
[TAKAGI]
Thanks, Mom.
[TAKAGI'S MOM] I have a
few stores I want to browse,
so let's meet back here
when you're done.
[TAKAGI]
Gotcha.
[TAKAGI'S MOM] And don't get
anything too showy, okay?
I won't.
Thank you, come again.
[NISHIKATA chuckles] Volume
five of 100% Unrequited Love !
I wonder what type
I should try on first.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
Actually, what type
does he like?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
[NISHIKATA]
I can't wait to get home
and read this cover to cover!
Nishikata!
[NISHIKATA shrieks]
What are you doing here?
[TAKAGI]
Uh, shopping?
Same as you.
[NISHIKATA]
Again?
Why does she always have to show
up at the worst possible time?
I swear, she's gotta be
following me or something!
No.
Now's not the time
to think about that.
I need to focus
my energy into making sure
she doesn't find
out what I bought.
Anyway, I saw you
leaving the bookstore.
[NISHIKATA]
Here it comes!
Gotta think quick!
[TAKAGI]
Did you buy somethi--?
So you're shopping?
That's cool! Whatcha getting?
[NISHIKATA]
That was too close a call.
I hope changing the subject is
enough to get out of this alive.
Mainly, a bathing suit.
[NISHIKATA]
A bathing suit?
Are you blushing?
No, it's just hot in here!
Hey.
What kind of girl's bathing suit
do you think looks best?
Uh, what kind of...?
Why you asking me?
I-I don't know,
they're all probably fine.
You've seen 'em all?
You're quite the connoisseur.
No, you don't get it!
I mean that
I couldn't care less!
I'm not some expert!
Hot in here?
Yes, it's hot in here.
Typical. Of course,
she messes with me
the second we
bump into each other.
All right,
I'm gonna go home now.
[TAKAGI]
'Kay.
[NISHIKATA] At least, I was able
to hide the manga from her.
You just bought the new volume
of Unrequited Love, right?
Could I borrow it?
[NISHIKATA]
I was so close!
Was she watching me?
[chuckles]
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't? Was I wrong?
[NISHIKATA]
Hey, wait.
There's no way she could
have seen from outside
with the register where it is.
She's bluffing.
[chuckles]
Dodged a bullet there.
Yeah, totally wrong.
You couldn't be more off.
Oh yeah?
Then what did you buy?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh, Robot Zombie ?
Yeah, sure, whatever, that!
It's like, the last thing a
girl would be interested in!
It's way too ridiculous!
Yeah, right.
You bought Unrequited Love,
didn't you?
Yup! Sure did!
Gah!
N-No.
Let me see it, then.
[NISHIKATA] Man. She backed
me into a corner again.
[NISHIKATA]
This is what always happens.
No matter what I do, I can never
beat Takagi at her own game.
[gasps]
Wait, I take that back.
Okay, but first,
shall we make a bet?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[NSHIKATA]
We can bet on whether or not
the book I bought is
100% Unrequited Love.
I say our usual
condition applies.
If you're wrong, you have
to do whatever I tell you to.
Fine with me.
And if I get it right,
then you do whatever I want.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, okay.
So, then what is it you
think I purchased?
Heh.
It's all in the presentation.
It's your move, Takagi.
I'm sure my level of confidence
will have you second
guessing yourself.
[TAKAGI]
Huh?
Nishikata sounds so much
more confident than normal.
Maybe it's actually not
100% Unrequited Love !
[NISHIKATA] Oh yeah.
If she's gonna find out anyway,
I might as well teach her
a lesson in the process.
Think you can just
get me like that again?
Nuh-uh. I've learned.
Know what?
I'm gonna bet that it's
Unrequited Love.
Huh?
Y-You sure about that?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
Let's see it.
Awesome!
I got it right!
[NISHIKATA] I don't know how she
saw through me that time.
I should just go home
and read this.
That'll make me feel better.
Ugh. I'll see yah around.
[TAKAGI]
Where do you think you're going?
Help me out.
I need a bathing suit.
We said if I won.
I'd get to tell you
what to do, didn't we?
[NISHIKATA]
I have to help her pick one?
Hot in here?
Yes, it's still hot!
[NISHIKATA]
"Bathing Suit."
Which one do you like most?
Uh. They all look nice to me.
[TAKAGI] Will you actually
look and pick one?
You did lose our bet.
[NISHIKATA]
I don't think she realizes
what she's asking of me.
It's embarrassing
just being here!
I can't look directly
at the bathing suits!
Oh. Check it out.
What do you think of this one?
[NISHIKATA]
I guess I just have to pick one
if I want to get this over with.
I-I think that one's nice.
[TAKAGI]
Oh?
In that case,
I might as well try it on.
Huh?
Stay right there.
I'll only be a minute.
[NISHIKATA]
What am I doing?
How did I end up
in this situation?
Right now, just
beyond that curtain.
Takagi is taking off her...
How's it look?
I dunno, fine?
That's all?
I'll try on another, then.
[NISHIKATA]
You mean you're not done?
Until you tell me
I look good in one.
No, I'm not.
[NISHIKATA] Huh?
Tell her she looks good?
That's way too
embarrassing for me to say!
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
Sorry, can you hand
me that bathing suit?
Huh?!
The yellow one I was looking at.
[NISHIKATA] She's covering
herself, does that mean?
It's to the left of that one.
Uh-huh, that's it.
[NISHIKATA]
Just a few feet to my right.
She's totally naked.
Sorry again.
[gasps]
Thanks a bunch.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, gimme a break!
That was totally on purpose!
But forget that,
I need to get out of this
store as soon as possible.
If someone from school
sees me here with Takagi,
I'll never hear the end of it.
Wow, there are so many!
All right! How's this one?
Uh.
Oh. Hi, Takagi!
Hey, Mano!
Hey, Nakai.
Uh, hey, what's goin' on?
You're here
to get a bathing suit?
Yeah, I assume that's
why you're here, too?
Ow...
Hey, Mano, it's
embarrassing being here.
Can we hurry it up already?
Wha?! We've barely
been here five minutes!
If I rush, I might miss
something I'd really like!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[gasps]
How 'bout we come back later?
What? But you said--
It doesn't matter.
See you later, Takagi!
'Kay!
[gasps]
Don't worry, the coast is clear.
They're gone.
Oh. Is that so?
[TAKAGI]
You get so shy sometimes
What do you mean?
No I don't.
[TAKAGI]
Well then.
[NISHIKATA] Back to
trying on more, I assume.
We should probably hurry up
and pick one of these out.
Otherwise, you'll
die of embarrassment.
Oh, shut up. I'm fine.
[TAKAGI]
So...
...which of these
do you like better?
Uh. I dunno, whichever
you like, I guess?
[TAKAGI]
Then how about this one here?
Think this one's good?
Uh-huh.
I keep coming back
to this pink one.
Do you think it's good too?
Uh-huh.
And this one-piece?
[NISHIKATA]
Mm-hm.
Wanna go swimming
together sometime?
Uh-huh.
It's a date.
Okay.
I'll buy you something
to drink later.
You're burning up again.
Yeah, I mean,
it is super-hot in here!
They should really
fix the air conditioning!
The ocean!
We swimmin' or what?
[MINA]
Of course we are, come on!
[sighs]
[YUKARI]
Water.
"Ocean."
[MINA]
We got the waves!
We got the sun!
[SANAE]
We got the seaweed.
Stop Sanae.
It's all gross and slimy!
[MINA]
What are you doing, Yukari?
[sighs] What does
it look like I'm doing?
I'm pumping air into this.
But we're at the beach.
You should at least
go for a swim, first.
I wouldn't be doing this if
I could just jump in the water.
Ah! What, you can't swim?
You do sit out
during swim lessons.
Though you'd probably
learn if you didn't.
[YUKARI]
Whatever.
Just go have fun,
I'll be there soon.
Shoo. Shoo.
Ah! That was fun, but I'm wiped!
Yeah, let's take
a break for now.
Huh?
[MINA]
What happened?
You okay, Yukari?
Yeah, I'm okay.
But I managed to
break the pump somehow.
So I was blowing it up on
my own, and I got winded.
Man, Yukari, do you ever have
fun, or do you just suffer?
You don't know my life!
And just for that,
I'm not gonna help you
with your homework anymore!
Hope you can do it on your own!
You what?
But I can't!
Please have mercy!
I won't make fun of you anymore!
Crying won't get you anywhere.
[TAKAGI] Nishikata,
are you making progress
on your summer homework?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh...
Yeah.
I guess you could say that.
Oh?
Hey, wanna do our
homework together?
Uh. Yeah, sure, that's cool.
But I have plans
in the afternoon.
That's fine.
Let's just work on
it until noon.
You can copy my answers.
Huh?
Okay, then where
should we do it?
At the library?
Or, wait.
We wouldn't have very much
time to get our stuff, then.
You're overthinking this.
We could just go
over to your house.
[NISHIKATA]
"Room."
What is my life?
Out of nowhere, Takagi,
a girl is coming to my room!
Are we going in?
[gasps]
Sorry. Spaced out for a sec.
This place is nice.
[NISHIKATA]
You don't have to be polite.
My parents aren't here anyway.
This feels like a dream.
Is this a dream?
Takagi is actually in my room.
It feels so surreal.
What's wrong?
You spaced out again.
Oh.
It's nothing!
Hey!
It's your favorite girl's manga!
[NISHIKATA gasps]
Aww, you found me! Squeal!
[TAKAGI]
You have every volume!
Huh?!
Don't touch that!
[gasps]
S-Sorry.
[TAKAGI]
Why are you apologizing?
Well, you know,
because we were just so--
You like this, right?
If you like something,
you should just admit it.
[NISHIKATA]
What does she mean?
"This" as in her being
in my room?
How am I supposed
to respond to that?
Maybe this is a dream after all!
100% Unrequited Love.
You do like it, right?
There's really
no need to hide it.
[NISHIKATA] That's what
she was talking about?
Now that I've had a
chance to look around,
this room just screams "you."
Is that supposed
to be a compliment?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
No, not exactly.
But either way, I like it.
[NISHIKATA]
W-Want to start our homework?
Read my mind!
[NISHIKATA]
Oh right.
But I only have one desk.
Do you have a folding
table or something?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, but they're all being used
in different rooms.
[TAKAGI]
Too bad.
Then should we sit
in the same chair?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh...
Huh?!
[laughs]
I'm just messing around.
Oh, I know.
We could use your bed.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh. Um.
Move this.
And we've basically got
one big desk right here!
You okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Good idea.
Ohh?
What's the problem?
Lay off.
No problem.
Come on.
Let's start.
[NISHIKATA]
Wait, I'm sitting there, too?
So, hey, uh...
Remember what you said
about your answers?
Of course, they are right here.
Awesome, thanks a ton!
Though, I only grabbed these.
Kanji writing drills.
That's so not fair;
you tricked me!
[TAKAGI]
No, I didn't.
[laughs]
That's enough.
Let's work.
[NISHIKATA]
Wait.
If we're just practicing kanji,
was there ever any reason
to do our homework together?
[NISHKATA]
Oh no!
I saw this exact thing on
100% Unrequited Love !
[KYUNKO] Jeez. I don't
know why I have to make curry
with this jerk of all people!
He makes me so mad!
Um. You can let go
of my hand now.
Why would I want to do
something like that?
C'mere.
Let me see that face.
[KYUNKO]
Squeal!
[NISHIKATA]
I can't do that!
You can use it.
It is your eraser, after all.
That's my bad.
Uh. Okay.
[TAKAGI]
Your hand.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
Sorry!
You want somethin' to drink?
Like tea?
You want tea?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
[NISHIKATA]
Comin' right up!
[TAKAGI]
Thanks for having me.
[NISHIKATA]
All she did was mess with me.
I think.
Bye!
I'll come again.
Huh?
She'll come again?
[NISHIKATA]
Maybe... I should clean my room.