[NISHIKATA]
How to approach a cat.
Step one:
Don't make eye contact.
Step two:
Assume a crouching posture.
That do anything for ya?
You can tell by my body language
that I'm not a threat, right?
Step three:
Approach ever so slowly.
[NISHIKATA]
This is incredible!
I guess that guy
on TV wasn't kidding!
His advice is
just what I needed.
Oh, hey! Nishikata!
[NISHIKATA yells]
[NISHIKATA sighs]
[TAKAGI]
What were you doing?
[NISHIKATA]
Nothing.
[MEETA meows]
[NISHIKATA]
"Cat."
[NISHIKATA growls]
Curse you, Takagi!
I was this close to petting
that cat when you came along!
But...
On the other hand,
I'm glad she didn't actually
see me petting it.
Because if she did...
[TAKAGI]
Ooh, Nishikata's petting a cat!
I thought boys weren't
supposed to like cute things.
[NISHIKATA]
She'd never let me live it down!
[TAKAGI laughing]
[NISHIKATA] And there's no way
I'm gonna give her more ammo
to tease me with!
Look, a cat.
Really?
Oh, wow. You like cats?
Not especially.
[NISHIKATA]
Crap! That was close.
[TAKAGI]
Here, kitty, kitty.
Over here.
[NISHIKATA chuckles]
So naïve, Takagi.
Cats are very wary creatures.
There's no way one
would just waltz right--
--[TAKAGI] Come here.
--[NISHIKATA] Wh-What?!
Why? That wasn't
even a proper call!
Unless...
What is she,
some sort of cat whisperer?
That's a good boy.
You're looking cuter
than usual, Meeta.
Wait, you know this cat?
Yep. He belongs to
the old lady who lives
around the corner from us.
[NISHIKATA]
No wonder! That explains it.
Aww. So soft.
[TAKAGI giggles]
He's great.
And he really likes people.
He'll let you pet
him all you want.
[NISHIKATA]
Could it really be?
The coveted all-you-can-pet cat?
I need him!
Why don't you play
with him a little?
What? Why would I?
Come on.
You were trying
to pet the other cat.
You used that trick that
was on TV yesterday.
I think you wanna.
[NISHIKATA]
She already knows!
[NISHIKATA] I just thought
that guy on TV didn't know
what he was talking about, so...
So... You don't particularly
like cats or anything?
No. Not really.
And I've definitely never
wanted to pet a cat or anything.
Really? That's surprising.
They're just so cute.
Their coats are all fluffy.
And their paws are so squishy.
[NISHIKATA]
Are you kidding me?
This cat even lets
people touch his paws?
I wanna touch!
But I can't!
I've dug myself
too deep for that!
I know!
I really don't get why people
are always going on and on
about petting cats.
It's not like they're
really that cute.
And even if they were,
I wouldn't want to touch them.
When it comes down to it,
they're animals.
You can never be
sure what they'll do.
You're taking a risk
every time you approach one.
I see what's going on.
You're saying that
because you're afraid
of getting scratched.
[NISHIKATA]
She took the bait!
Of course I'm not afraid!
But... If you
don't believe me,
I'll just have to prove it
right now by petting this cat!
That's okay.
I actually believe you now.
Sorry I doubted you.
[TAKAGI laughing]
Your face is like an
open book, Nishikata!
You really want
to pet this cat, huh?
[laughing]
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi!
What'll it be?
You gonna pet him?
Or leave him hanging?
I want to pet him.
Is that okay?
Mm-hmm.
Though I think Meeta
has different plans.
What do you mean?!
He disappeared?!
[TAKAGI]
Yeah.
Do you want to go look
for a different cat to pet?
[NISHIKATA]
We're gonna be late for school.
[MANO] So I asked, and
Satou said she likes Tanaka
from Class 3.
[STUDENT 11A]
Oh, I called it.
Didn't I call it?
[YUKARI]
I can't take it anymore!
I want to talk about love!
[MINA]
"Taste."
[YUKARI] So I've been
doing some thinking.
And I was wondering,
what's like your type?
[YUKARI]
Was that too abrupt?
I never expected you to ask.
I happen to like
the dependent type.
As for me, I prefer a well-built
physique and long hair.
Oh, yeah?
I never would have guessed.
[YUKARI]
It's happening!
They're ready to talk
about love too!
It's funny.
You just caught us in the
middle of discussing that.
Did I really?
What a coincidence.
[YUKARI]
They've both grown so much!
All right.
I'm gonna dig deeper here.
[MINA]
What's your type, Yukari?
[YUKARI]
I'm so glad you asked!
Well, if I had to choose,
I'd say long legs
and handsome features are nice.
What about hair?
[YUKARI] She's really
particular about a guy's hair.
I tend to like longer
hair too, like you do.
[YUKARI]
Ah! This is fun!
I've wanted to have a
conversation like this
with friends forever!
[MINA]
So then a borzoi, yeah?
Uh-huh. A borzo--Eh?
I'm sorry, what are
you talking about?
Dogs, duh.
What are you talking about?
Which breed is your favorite?
I don't know, Chihuahuas?
What? But they don't fit
into your description at all!
[SANAE] Well, there are
some long-haired Chihuahuas
out there.
[NISHIKATA]
"Portrait."
You gonna draw?
[NISHIKATA]
Hm?
You're going to run out of time.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
[NISHIKATA growls]
Why does it have
to be a portrait?
Can't we just draw
whatever we want?
I'm your reference.
You have to actually look at me.
I am looking.
[ART TEACHER 11A]
Everyone?
Remember to
observe your subject.
Don't get too focused on drawing
or this'll take longer
than necessary.
You need to strike a balance.
Take twice as much time
studying your reference
as you do drawing them.
[TAKAGI]
You heard her.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, I did.
[TAKAGI chuckles]
Why are you laughing?
Oh... Oh, sorry. It's nothing.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, right.
What was that all about?
Is there something on my face?
No, there wasn't anything
there when I checked
in the bathroom mirror
during the break.
What, then? Bed head?
No, I checked my hair, too.
Is she just laughing
at my face itself?
I can't do anything about that!
Calm down, calm down!
I know.
It's just her usual game.
There's nothing wrong--
she's just making me worry
so she can enjoy my reaction.
Well two can play at that game.
[NISHIKATA chuckling]
Are you laughing at how
bad your drawing is?
I am not!
Then is there something on my
face that's making you laugh?
[NISHIKATA]
Ugh!
I didn't expect her
to just ask me flat out.
No, there isn't.
[TAKAGI]
Hm?
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, good, she backed down.
[YUKARI] Mina, I told you
a hundred times!
My eyes don't slant that much,
you're exaggerating.
But that's how I envision you,
so that's how I drew it.
Don't draw what you see
in your mind, draw me!
[NISHIKATA]
That's it!
[TAKAGI gasps]
This is supposed to be me?
[NISHIKATA] Well, yeah,
that's how I envision you.
I can't help it.
[NISHIKATA]
That'll teach her.
Okay. Only ten minutes left.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, this is gonna be good.
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
Mind if I take a look?
Nope. Go ahead.
[NISHIKATA laughs]
How do you like that?
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, no.
Did I take it too far?
I just drew that based
on how I envision you, so...
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
[laughing]
That face is too much, Takagi!
My stomach hurts already!
If you're gonna draw me weird,
you should draw that face.
Try again. You can do it. Here.
Okay.
If you can't see me well,
I can get closer.
Uh, no, no,
that's fine, you're good.
'Kay.
[NISHIKATA] When I get a good
look at her, Takagi is kinda...
Pre-- Pret--
Pretty--
There. Finished. You see?
So?
Was I really looking
sideways that much?
Oh! Forgot something.
Now it's done.
Why'd you add red?
It's not like I'm blushing!
Uh, you have been
this whole time.
No, I haven't!
It just looks like that.
I swear!
Look closely, I'm not!
[NISHIKATA]
"Fortune Telling."
[STUDENT 10A]
Oh, not bad.
This card means your wish
will more or less come true.
Really? Is that so?
You should totally get your
love fortune told too, Mina.
She's good at this.
See? Go for it!
Huh? You say you want me
to get my fortune told,
but I know you really just
want to get yours done.
What do you mean?
You don't know that!
It's obvious.
No, I just wanted Mina to do it!
This really sucks.
I just wanted to go home today.
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
What do you want?
Rock-paper-scissors.
You up for a match?
What? Why now?
The loser has to buy the
winner juice on the way home.
Sound good?
Sorry, but I just found out
I have to clean the classroom
after school,
so go home without me.
No problem, I'll just
wait here for you.
But I don't want to
make you sit around.
Okay.
How about if you win,
I have to help you clean up?
Why do you wanna play
rock-paper-scissors so bad?
I'm just in the mood for it.
All right, I guess it's okay.
Under one condition!
Which is...?
No psychological attacks
like telling me
what you're about
to choose, okay?
Sure. Fine with me.
[NISHIKATA]
That was close.
I don't need a repeat
of that day I lost to her
four times in a row
because of those tricks.
Now let's do it.
[BOTH]
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[NISHIKATA]
I-I won?
This is my first ever
victory over Takagi!
Yes! I finally did it!
I bet she's super mad!
Well... Guess I'm helping.
[NISHIKATA]
She doesn't seem to mind.
Whatever, I don't care.
I still won!
I gotta celebrate while
I have the chance.
Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
What is it, Takagi?
Do you believe in
fortune telling?
Uh, fortunes? Not really.
Why do you ask?
The girls and I
had ours told today.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh.
Is that what that deck
of cards was earlier?
They're called tarot cards.
Actually, today my tarot
reading was about love.
Oh.
[NISHIKATA]
Love?
[TAKAGI]
Turned out good.
It said I'll do well with
my current crush.
Your current crush?
Good for you, then.
What about you?
Do you have a crush?
Huh? What was that?
I said, "Do you have a crush?"
Nope! I don't! Definitely not!
[TAKAGI]
I see.
[NISHIKATA] Why did she
ask me that just now?
Could it be?
Does Takagi... like me?
What's wrong?
It's nothing! Don't worry
about it, everything's cool!
[NISHIKATA]
Why do I feel so nervous?
Unless... I...
Do I like Takagi?
No, that's just ridiculous.
Oh, by the way, Nishikata.
Yeah? What's up?
The reason I asked
if you had a crush
was because I had your
tarot reading done, too.
[NISHIKATA]
So that's why you asked me that.
Makes sense I guess.
[NISHIKATA]
Should have known.
Wait. Am I disappointed?
Yeah. And guess what?
You'll do well with
your crush, too.
That'd be great.
If you had a crush.
[TAKAGI]
You're blushing.
[NISHIKATA] That's because
I'm hard at work cleaning.
[NISHIKATA]
Just change the subject.
So what other readings
did you have done?
I asked what you'd pick if we
played rock-paper-scissors.
[NISHIKATA] Huh?
As in the match I won earlier?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
[NISHIKATA]
Clearly that didn't work out.
It's just a fortune,
not destiny.
I feel stupid for worrying.
Maybe if you didn't believe
in something as silly
as fortune telling,
you wouldn't be stuck here,
doing half my work!
It came true, though.
Huh? What do you mean?
I won that match, didn't I?
Yup. You sure did.
[TAKAGI]
Come on.
Let's get back to
cleaning this place up.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
Wait, what?
[NISHIKATA]
"Critical."
[NISHIKATA chuckles]
Today's the day.
I'm gonna beat Takagi.
Count on it!
Oh. Hey, Nishikata.
Good morning.
Back atcha. Morning.
Somebody's in a good mood today.
[NISHIKATA]
Really? You think so?
I'm in a great mood.
[NISHIKATA] You have no idea
what's coming your way.
It just so happens that
I'm invincible today.
Because according to
my horoscope this morning,
I am number--!
Is it your horoscope?
Cancer was number one today.
Huh?!
Hold on a second,
how do you know I'm a cancer?
I mean, I said happy birthday
to you this year, so...
Oh. I forgot.
I guess that makes sense.
[NISHIKATA] What, does she read
everyone's horoscope every day?
She's crafty.
But she underestimates me.
I bet she doesn't know
that in today's blood-type
fortune, I'm also--!
Also, blood type O's
number one, too.
Huh?!
Okay, how do you know
that I'm blood type O?
I had a feeling that you were.
Just a guess.
[NISHIKATA]
She's just too good.
I was the one
underestimating her.
You just can't
mess with this girl.
But just you wait.
Today I'm invinc--!
Feeling invincible today,
aren't you?
Because of what you heard
about both of your fortunes?
[TAKAGI]
Ah.
[NISHIKATA growls]
Are you freakin' kidding me?
Well then.
I hope something good happens.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
[NISHIKATA] I don't care if you
basically read my mind!
I'm lucky as can be today!
I'll get you!
[school bell rings]
[NISHIKATA]
Teased fifty times.
Which means I have to do a
hundred and fifty push-ups.
Why? This sucks!
Was it stupid of me
to get excited just because
I'm supposed to
have good fortune?
[NISHIKATA]
Ugh...
What's wrong?
Are you upset because
nothing special happened?
It's just a silly fortune.
You seemed to believe
that tarot reading
you had the other day!
[NISHIKATA] Man, I've spent all
day trying to think of a plan
to beat Takagi,
but I couldn't come up
with anything worthwhile.
Maybe I should just
call it quits for now.
Either my fortune's wrong,
or my luck is that
I only got teased
fifty times today.
Hey, Nishikata.
Let's walk home together.
Oh. Yeah, sure, why not?
[NISHIKATA] No, I can't
let it end like this!
[TAKAGI]
By the way,
what exactly did your
fortune say this morning?
Say what? You mean...
That short description
they write with your rank?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
Uh, let's see.
Something like...
[TV VOICE]
Cancer is in first place.
You'll land a critical hit!
Get 'em!
[NISHIKATA]
That's right! A critical hit!
Which means I can turn the
tables with a single blow!
It all makes sense now!
No matter how many times
she teases me today,
if I can get back
at her just once, I win!
Never give up hope!
So? "Something like" what?
Uh... I can't seem to
remember what it was.
[SAKURAI]
Hey, Nishikata!
That game Fierce Soccer's
on sale today!
We're playin' at
his house. You in?
[NISHIKATA]
Fierce Soccer, huh?
I did want to play that.
But I can't go home without
scoring my critical hit!
Then again, I haven't
exactly come up
with any sort of plan yet.
No, I should still
be able to do it.
I'm the luckiest man
on earth today!
I can do anything!
You regret it?
Turning 'em down?
Oh, that. Nah.
I wanted to walk home
with you, anyway.
[NISHIKATA] Hmm.
There's gotta be something.
Hold on!
I didn't just say something
super awkward, did I?
Uh... I remembered my
fortune which said I'd land
a critical hit today, so...
I thought today was
gonna be my best chance
to beat you at something!
So what I just said wasn't
what it sounded like!
[groans]
[NISHIKATA]
This is the worst!
I didn't land a critical hit!
I scored on my own goal!
So uh... Do me a solid.
Could'ya pretend
you didn't hear that?
[TAKAGI giggles]
I guess I can do that.
I'll pretend I heard nothing.
If you say it one more time.
[giggles]
I am not gonna say it again!
Forget you, I'm going this way!
I'll see you around!
[TAKAGI]
A critical hit.
How terrifying.