[KIMURA]
Forget the test!
I'm gonna die if I have
to study any longer!
I'm hittin' the arcade.
[SAKURAI, TAKAO]
Well, we can't let you go alone!
Hey, Nishikata, are you comin'?
I don't know about you,
but when I study for too long,
it just doesn't stick.
Uhh.
Sorry, I think I'm gonna stay.
You've made your choice!
Later!
[KIMURA]
What are you guys gonna play?
[SAKURAI] Whichever gets me
one of those cute figures.
[NISHIKATA]
Man.
I'm jealous.
But I can't think about them.
I have to get a
good grade on my next test!
Or else!
Hey.
Can I sit here?
Studying for the test?
Yeah. I am.
[NISHIKATA]
"Studying for the Test."
[TAKAGI] I just saw your
friends leaving as I came in.
Yeah.
We were all studying
together for a while.
[TAKAGI]
Ahh...
Well I heard them talking,
and I figured they were
on their way to the arcade.
Are you not going with them?
I don't have time to
play around like they do.
If I don't score within the top
fifty of my grade on this test.
My parents are taking
away my video games.
[TAKAGI]
Huuuh.
I see.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, no!
Why am I telling her everything?
Now that she knows,
she's totally gonna
distract me from studying!
Nice going, me.
I.. was just kidding?
About what?
Ugh. Forget it.
Anyway, don't interrupt
me this time.
[TAKAGI]
That's mean.
You say that like I'm always
getting in your way.
[NISHIKATA]
That's because you are!
Well, yeah. It's 'cuz it's so
fun to tease you, Nishikata!
[NISHIKATA growls]
Should I study somewhere else?
No, if I did that, I'd basically
be letting her win.
I just realized.
You're not studying?
Nope.
I like to limit myself to
two hours of studying a day.
Oh.
[NISHIKATA]
I shouldn't be surprised.
She easily scores in the top
ten of our grade all the time.
But, what does
she have up her sleeve?
This is Takagi
we're talking about.
She's definitely gonna
try to mess with me.
I mean, how could she not?
It's practically in her blood!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm? What's up?
Huh? Oh, nothing, just thinking.
It's not like
I was looking at you.
I just kinda
spaced out--
By the way,
you got that one wrong.
Problem six, where it says,
"Solve for x over negative
two plus three y." That one.
[NISHIKATA]
You mean it's not 15?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
[NISHIKATA]
What? Really?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
Substitute the numbers.
Was that wrong?
No. So then...
Here we go.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh... What are you...?
It's easier to
teach you this way.
So, x equals negative 16...
[NISHIKATA]
"Easier to."
She's teaching me?
What is she planning?
Write it out. Go ahead.
There's a negative
times a negative
and don't forget
order of operations.
It's "PEMDAS" remember?
[NISHIKATA]
Oh yeah!
Then let's see.
It's five!
Yep. That's right!
Oh! And for these next ones,
you should be able...
[NISHIKATA]
She's amazing.
She can figure it out
with just a glance.
Hey. I appreciate this.
I was really struggling
with this page before.
Why don't I teach
you from the beginning?
[NISHIKATA] She's gonna
teach me the whole thing?
I'm saved!
No, something's fishy here!
Why is she being so nice?
She's never this nice
unless she's teasing me!
[NISHIKATA]
Hey, Takagi.
Why are you being
so nice to me today?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
What do you mean?
Well, you're just being
kinder than usual.
So...
Oh... Right.
I am always teasing you
in the middle of class.
I would feel really bad if your
grades went down because of me.
Nishikata.
I'm sorry for teasing
you every single day.
Let me help you get
a better grade.
Takagi.
[NISHIKATA]
I don't believe it.
You've finally seen
the error in your ways!
All right, let's go for it!
[TAKAGI]
Thanks for the juice.
[NISHIKATA]
No, thank you.
I made huge progress on my math
today, because I had your help.
[NISHIKATA]
And now I'm less likely
to have my games taken away.
[NISHIKATA]
Maybe Takagi is actually
a good person, after all.
Really.
Thank you so much for today.
Oh, no.
You shouldn't thank me.
Since what I taught you,
won't be on the test.
Wha... Hey! Hold on!
[TAKAGI] You're good
at substitution now, right?
[NISHIKATA] Yeah,
and a lot of good that'll do!
Gimme back that juice right now!
[TAKAGI]
Oops, I already opened it.
[NISHIKATA]
You literally just opened it!
[YUKARI]
"Test."
Pass your answer sheets forward.
[YUKARI]
I think I did pretty well.
I should've
gotten a 90 at least.
[MINA]
Hey, Yukari?
[SANAE]
Can you teach me this?
I just can't seem
to do well in English.
Huh? You make it sound like
you're good at everything else.
No, I'm just
extra bad at English!
Anyway!
Help me out here!
In this part--
Sorry, no can do.
I want to review
before the next test, too.
Huh?! But you always
help me study between tests!
[YUKARI]
This time is different.
If I can get a 90
or above on everything,
my parents are buying
me any game I want.
Cool. So this part's
been really tripping me up.
Were you listening?
I don't have the time
to teach you guys
this stuff last minute.
[MINA]
Meanie!
Buzz off. Shoo.
What's more important?
Our friendship
or some stupid game?
Yeah, what she said.
Sure you can play video games,
but you can't teach them like
you can your best friends!
Yeah, what she said.
[sighs]
[YUKARI] Now that those
two academic train wrecks
will leave me alone,
I should review.
All right, I'm handing
out the next test.
Take one and pass it back.
[YUKARI] Okay, I've thoroughly
reviewed the material
right before the test.
Now that I've got
English fresh in the brain,
this'll be a--
Math?
[NISHIKATA]
"Test Results."
[TEACHER]
Here.
Did you study at all this time?
Next.
Saitou.
You're looking
nervous over there.
No, I'm not.
[TEACHER]
Takagi.
Yes!
You did very well, as usual.
[MINA]
She's so smart.
[FEMALE STUDENT]
Sounds like you did fine Takagi.
Can we compare answers later?
[TAKAGI]
Sure.
So.
You get a good grade?
Yeah, but not a hundred percent.
[NISHIKATA]
That sounds about right.
But I got this
one in the bag, too.
[TEACHER]
Next up, Nishikata!
Right!
[TEACHER] You can do
a little better next time.
Was it that bad?
[NISHIKATA]
As if you care at all!
You're the one who taught me
stuff that wasn't on the test!
All up on your high horse
because you got a good score!
Whatever!
[TAKAGI]
Hey. Hey!
Guess my score.
And I'll guess yours.
Whoever gets closer will win.
You're always proposing
this stuff out of nowhere.
But okay.
Uh... Is it around 50?
[NISHIKATA]
Hmph!
You underestimate me
too much, Takagi.
You think so?
Okay, then did you
get above 60 percent?
[TAKAGI]
I'll take that as a no.
[NISHIKATA]
How did she know?
Give her your poker face.
Confuse her with your world
class, unwavering poker face!
Did you get above 55?
[TAKAGI]
That's a yes.
[NISHIKATA]
Why?
That leaves everything
between 55 and 59.
[NISHIKATA] I have to keep her
from guessing the exact score!
[TAKAGI]
Okay, then.
Fifty-six?
Or...
Fifty-seven?
Fifty-eight?
Fifty-nine?
Yup.
I got it.
You got a 56.
Uhh. Is that the
answer you're going with?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
[NISHIKATA]
Ready to know the truth?
I got a 59!
Sucks to be you!
I guess you were
sorta close, though.
[TEACHER]
Hey, quiet down.
The only thing that
sucks is your grade.
You're right; I'm sorry.
Fifty-nine, huh?
Looks like I was off by three.
All right.
Now it's your turn to try
and guess my score okay?
If it's within two percent.
Then you're the winner.
[NISHIKATA]
Bring it on!
I'm gonna figure it out
based on her reactions.
The teacher praised
her a second ago,
so I bet that means
she got above a 90.
Is it... like, a 92?
Uh...
Huh?
What kinda reaction was that?
How about a 95?
Ninety?
Or was it 92?
Uh...
[NISHIKATA]
She is so faking it!
I'm not gonna fall for that!
She'd never make
her reaction so obvious!
She's mocking me.
I'm gonna do everything
within my power to win this!
Maybe if I focus more
on her expression.
What? What's wrong?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm? Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking
about something.
We've been staring at
each other for a long time.
Why are you turning away?
[NISHIKATA] Aww come on,
that was a cheap shot!
I can't look at you
after you say that!
Think. Just think.
Anything that could clue you in.
That reaction she gave me
before was so fake it's painful,
which means she probably
wants me to think she got a 92.
That also means it won't be
between 90 and 94
because they're all within
a two point difference of 92!
And like I thought before,
the teacher praised her
so it must be
above 90 percent.
And she said it wasn't 100,
so that means it's gotta
be between 95 and 99!
Perfect.
Flawless victory!
Takagi.
I know what grade
you got on the test.
You scored a 97 percent!
[TAKAGI]
Wrong. I got a 92.
[NISHIKATA]
Wha?! Come on!
You really don't
trust me enough.
I guess I gave you
that three-point handicap
for nothing, huh?
[NISHIKATA]
"Bookstore."
Coast is clear.
Find everything okay?
Four hundred and twenty
yen is your total.
You're quick with
that exact change.
Want a cov--?
[NISHIKATA]
No, thank you.
A bag--?
[NISHIKATA]
No, thank you.
--[CLERK] A rece--?
--[NISHIKATA] No, thank you.
[NISHIKATA]
Operation successful.
Now to begin phase two:
Get home and read it!
[TAKAGI]
Oh hey.
Good morning.
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi?
What is she doing here?
I'm taking a walk.
[NISHIKATA]
Did she just read my mind?
What are you doing
here all by yourself?
[NISHIKATA]
This is bad!
I can't let her see
what I just bought.
I'll have to deny it
all the way to my grave.
Oh, nothing.
It's just that I wanted to buy
a book, but they were sold out--
Wait, wait!
What if she saw me
at the register?
Reel it in!
So I decided to buy
Fierce!! Ultimate Soccer!!
volume eleven instead!
The perfect answer!
Boys love that series,
but I've never met a girl
who'd give it the time of day.
You won't care
to ask more about it.
I'm on a roll today.
Fierce-Soccer ?
Cool, let me see!
Huh?!
Uh, but I haven't read it yet.
[TAKAGI] Can I at
least see the front cover?
[NISHIKATA]
No!
'Cuz I haven't had a chance
to look at it yet, either.
And it's my manga.
[TAKAGI]
Then, let's look at it together.
[NISHIKATA] I happen
to like looking at it alone.
Awww...
[NISHIKATA] I wouldn't
have thought she'd be
this interested.
At this rate,
she's gonna blow my cover.
Better get away
from her and quick.
I'll see you around, Takagi.
Huh?
Hello?
Hey, we ran into each other.
Let's walk together.
[NISHIKATA]
Okay, fine.
[TAKAGI] It's pretty unusual
to run into someone
at the bookstore so far from
home this early in the morning.
[NISHIKATA] I can't let
Takagi see this manga
and yet here it is, three feet
from her in my backpack!
I feel like
my heart's in my throat.
I wish I were home already.
[TAKAGI]
Hey.
Nishikata.
Are you lying to me
about anything?
Are you lying?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh, um...
You didn't buy
Fierce-Soccer, did you?
I bet you bought something
that you're so embarrassed to
have, you had to lie about it.
Shut up.
That's not...
It's just some
manga for girls, right?
100% Unrequited Love ?
[NISHIKATA] Okay. There's no
point in denying it now, but...
...how in the world
did you figure it out?
Just luck.
I happened to be passing by
when I saw you at
the register checking out.
And I could see what you got.
[NISHIKATA] She knew the
whole time and was playing me.
[TAKAGI] Is it because
you like the anime?
I didn't know you read
that kind of stuff.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh, wait up!
Please keep it a secret,
I really don't want
anyone to know.
Catching it on TV is one thing,
but if people found out
I'm actually buying
and reading the manga,
I'll be a laughingstock.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
What should I do?
I mean, you did lie to me.
And that's extra bad,
considering I've never
lied to you before.
But I won't tell.
Huh? You're messing with me.
What do you mean?
I'm serious.
Please don't tell anyone!
Yes, sir!
[NISHIKATA]
Why are you so enthusiastic?
It feels fake!
You're so persistent.
Uh... Then how about this?
I know your secret,
so it's only fair
that I tell you mine, too.
That'll make
you feel better, right?
Since you'll have collateral.
Huh?
I guess.
[TAKAGI]
All right.
Come closer.
[NISHIKATA]
Okay.
Truth is I've always
kind of liked you.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
Huh?! What did she--?
What?
[laughs]
You're bright red!
You blush so quickly.
It's classic.
Since you lied to me
at the bookstore.
I figured I'd lie
to you as payback.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, a lie.
You shocked me for a second.
That was a lie.
Of course it was. Duh, right?
See yah!
I'm turning this way now.
"Duh," right.
I'll see you later, bye.
A lie, huh?
[TAKAGI]
Oh, and Nishikata?
I want to read
100% Unrequited Love too,
so let me know when you're
done and I'll borrow it!
[gasps]
Ahh! Don't say
it so loud, Takagi!
[NISHIKATA]
"Shelter from the Rain."
This downpour
came out of nowhere.
I wonder if it'll stop soon.
[NISHIKATA]
Hmm...
Well, I hope so.
[TAKAGI] Aww.
Even my socks got wet.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
[TAKAGI]
How about you? Are you dry?
[NISHIKATA] Oh man, I can
kinda see through her shirt.
You hear me?
Uh. Yeah, I heard you.
Yeah.
Calm down, just calm down!
If she realizes I'm panicking,
I'll be branded a pervert!
Boy, I sure hope
this rain will stop soon.
I wanna be home before five,
so I can catch an
anime that's on then.
It's Fierce-Soccer , by the way.
Oh yeah?
That's the one you bought
at the bookstore, right?
Or no, I'm mistaken.
That's 100% Unrequited Love.
You promised me
you were never going
to bring that up again!
What, I can't talk about it?
You know your own secret.
I hope this clears up fast.
Uhh. Yeah.
Aw man.
This got a little wet, too.
Hey, do you have
your P.E. shirt on you?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh. Yeah, why?
Do you mind if I borrow it?
I'll give it back.
I want to change out of this.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Wait, what?
You want to change
into my P.E. shirt?
Like, right here?
Yup. My shirt's wet;
I feel all gross.
But aren't you--?
And besides,
I know you're having trouble
deciding where to look.
[NISHIKATA]
Busted.
[TAKAGI]
Can you turn the other way?
[NISHIKATA]
Y-Yeah.
[TAKAGI] You managed
to stay pretty dry, huh?
[TAKAGI]
How? Oh.
Did you use your bag
as an umbrella?
[NISHIKATA]
Mm-hmm.
[TAKAGI]
Good thinking.
I had to hold my bike,
so I couldn't do that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
You know,
you can look if you want.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? I can look?
What are you trying to say?
[TAKAGI]
Because I'm done changing.
Why are you so flustered?
[NISHIKATA]
She's screwing with me.
Hey.
Wanna make a bet?
We can bet on whether
or not the rain
will stop by the time
the town clock strikes five.
The loser has to do
anything the winner wants.
Why not?
Okay, what's your bet?
That it won't stop in time.
Cool.
Then I bet it will.
[NISHIKATA]
If the rain stops,
I can go home and
watch Fierce-Soccer.
If it doesn't, I get
to order Takagi around.
It's win-win!
There we go.
I feel much better now
that I've changed my shirt.
Thanks a bunch, Nishikata.
Yeah, don't mention it.
It does smell
kinda sweaty, though.
Of course it does,
it's been super-hot out!
Whoa.
That shirt touched my skin
and now it's touching hers.
Agh! Stop it!
What am I thinking?
[meow]
--[TAKAGI] A cat.
--[NISHIKATA] Oh. Hey.
[NISHIKATA] Are you trying
to get out of the rain?
[TAKAGI]
Come here.
He's cute, but be careful.
He scratches.
Do you want me to give
you your shirt back?
No. I'm fine.
[TAKAGI] Why don't
you wear my P.E. shirt?
Huh?
[TAKAGI]
It did get a little wet,
but it's better than
what you've got on.
[NISHIKATA]
And now,
The shirt that touched Takagi's
skin will be touching mine.
Are you done yet?
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA] Come on,
you're not supposed to look!
[NISHIKATA] For some reason
this feels naughty.
[NISHIKATA]
It smells good.
[TAKAGI]
I guess I win.
What should I make you do?
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, well.
At least, Fierce-Soccer 'll
be on when I get home.
I'll do what she wants
and hurry back.
[TAKAGI]
Oh, I know!
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
Now that it's stopped raining,
let's go somewhere
before we head home.
[NISHIKATA]
Wait, I wanted to--
[TAKAGI] The bet was, the loser
does what the winner wants!
Let's go.
[NISHIKATA]
Why?!