[NISHIKATA]
"Calligraphy."
[TEACHER]
All right.
Now, we're
practicing calligraphy,
so write down your
favorite thing.
Due by the end of the day.
[KIMURA]
Well, I know what I'm writing.
Grilled meat.
My favorite.
Having trouble deciding?
[NISHIKATA]
Sorta.
Did you figure out
what you're gonna write?
[TAKAGI]
Hmmm... Not just yet.
I know.
How about we both
write down something
that we want from each other?
What we want from each other?
Uh-huh.
[NISHIKATA]
Hmm...
Okay.
[NISHIKATA]
What I want from Takagi?
Hmm...
[NISHIKATA]
Duh!
For her to stop teasing me!
This'll be a good way
to tell her off!
[NISHIKATA]
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
that might actually backfire.
She'd probably call me a wuss
and make fun of me more.
I need to find a way
to make her sorry
without provoking her further.
This is harder
than it should be.
You done? Because I am.
Cool.
Let's show each other.
[NISHIKATA]
Howdya like this?
"Restraint"?
Uh, yeah.
With what?
I can't really help
if you don't specify.
Uh... Well, it's, uh,
a few different things.
She clearly doesn't get it.
But then again,
at this point if she did get it,
she'd probably get upset.
This is tricky.
So what about you?
What do you
mean by "status quo"?
[TAKAGI]
Oh, you don't get it?
Well, it means you're
easy to tease,
and I want you to
stay that way, 'kay?
[NISHIKATA] Red alert!
She's going on the offensive!
It's an ambush!
If that's how she
wants this to go, fine.
Two can play at that game.
I'm ready for it now.
Are you okay with a do-over?
Yeah, sure.
[NISHIKATA]
Get set to get wrecked, Takagi!
I'm about to
fight fire with fire!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
So, did you finish?
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
Almost.
[NISHIKATA chuckles]
This should make Takagi realize
that she isn't
exactly kind to me.
Can't misinterpret this!
Forget what I said before,
now I want to upset you!
Huh... What should I write?
[NISHIKATA]
Ho-ho what's this?
Having trouble coming up
with something?
Perhaps if you
were a bit kinder,
it'd be easy to come up with a
nice, wholesome request from me.
Oh. I wanted to
tell you earlier,
you have really
nice handwriting.
It has an interesting flare.
Have you been
taught calligraphy?
Uh, no, not really.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Well, either way,
I like it a lot.
Here.
[NISHIKATA]
Uh...
Thanks.
[NISHIKATA]
That's weird.
She's being so nice
all of a sudden.
What's going on?
[NISHIKATA]
Could it be?
Is Takagi actually nice,
and I just haven't
noticed it until now?
No way.
I'd have picked up on that.
[gasps]
Nishikata, stay
still for a second.
Huh?!
Huh?
Got it.
Something was on your face.
Okay!
I think I have
something to write now.
[TAKAO] Do you like
my beautiful artwork?
[KIMURA] You're a weird
guy, you know that?
[SANAE]
What?
Okay.
I'm done.
How about you
show me yours first?
Uh... Why not
at the same time?
Just show me already.
Ahhh...
[NISHIKATA] I was a little more
obvious this time, at least.
You really do have
interesting handwriting.
That's all you
have to say? Come on.
I'm trying to
spell it out for you.
Stop teasing me.
What? I can't!
[NISHIKATA grunts] You didn't
even give it some thought.
All right, I'm sorry.
I'll hold back from now on.
Thank you.
So what's yours say?
Curious?
Then let's see.
Here.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
When she touched my face.
Didn't you just say that you'd
hold back from now on?
Yeah, but I said that
after I already set this up.
[NISHIKATA groans]
[MINA]
"Seasonal Change of Clothing!"
[MINA moans]
So hot.
Yeah, I guess so.
[MINA] We should start wearing
our short-sleeve uniform soon.
Yeah. I guess so.
Let's just tell Sanae
that we're gonna start wearing
them tomorrow, sound good?
[YUKARI]
Yeah, I guess so.
[SANAE]
You guess what?
Huh?
Hey.
[SANAE]
Long sleeves?
Aren't you hot?
[SANAE]
What?
We said that we'd all change
our uniforms at the same time!
Come on!
Wait, we did?
Yes, we did!
You forgot?
[SANAE]
Hmm?
Yeah.
Ahhhh! It's a lot cooler wearing
short sleeves, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
[SANAE]
Hey.
You guess what?
[MINA]
Hey, Sanae.
Good mor... ning.
[SANAE]
I thought you said
we were all gonna change
our uniforms together?
Uhh...
Uh...
I guess I forgot to tell you.
I wanna ask you to let me go,
but I know I deserve this, so...
[NISHIKATA]
"English Translation."
Junko says,
"That's right. Walk down this
street to the post office
and turn left there."
You will see the station.
It takes five minutes from here.
[NISHIKATA] Somehow I have
to get back at Takagi today.
But the ever-present
question is: How?
[NISHIKATA] I haven't made
a jack-in-the-box in a while.
No, I don't have
enough materials.
At this point, I wouldn't
finish in time, anyway.
Uhh.
Let's see, who should
I put on the spot?
Nishikata.
Huh?
Uhh.
Yes, sir!
Don't "Huh? Yes, sir!" me.
Hurry up.
Don't worry, it's 16.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
Sixteen!
You don't even know
what class you're in, kid?
It's English, not Math!
I told you to read aloud!
Uh... I'm sorry, sir.
[TANABE]
Forget it. Sit down.
I told you we were on line 16.
Way to drop the ball there.
[NISHIKATA] Yeah, right,
you were intentionally vague,
so I'd mess it up.
Really.
I didn't think you'd
actually mess that up.
[NISHIKATA]
Called it.
[TAKAGI laughs]
What's wrong?
Are you preoccupied
with something?
You could say that.
Mind if I ask what it is?
Ehh.
It's really not
worth mentioning.
Huuuuh...
[TAKAGI]
Then...
Were you thinking about
something naughty?
Wha...?!
No way! Of course not!
[TAKAGI]
Really?
[NISHIKATA]
I would never!
Not in a million years!
What kinda guy
do ya' think I am?!
I know. I know.
You were just trying to think
of new way to get back at me
for all the teasing I do, right?
Nuh-uh.
No idea what you mean.
I know I'm right.
You were looking
at me earlier, so...
...it wasn't that
hard to figure out.
[NISHIKATA] If you already
knew, then why'd you ask?
'Cus it's fun to see how
you react when I mess with you.
So what?
Did you come up
with a good idea?
[NISHIKATA]
Hmph!
Yup, sure did.
You see, I came up
with the perfect plan.
Oh and this time
it's absolutely foolproof.
So...
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
I'll believe it when I see it.
[NISHIKATA]
She's not worried at all.
It's like she can read my mind,
so she knows
I don't have a plan!
Spill it.
What's this plan of yours?
What idiot would tell you that?
Oh fine, how about just a hint?
I'm not telling you!
Just pay attention.
[gasps]
Wait, today's the eighteenth.
The teachers
always call on the kid
whose student number
matches the date.
And today that's Takagi!
If I can get her attention
away from class,
she might get in trouble
for not knowing
where we are in the textbook!
Hey, Takagi?
D'you eat breakfast today?
Whadja have?
Yeah, mountain yam over rice.
Why ask?
Ehh.
Just curious.
So you like mountain yams?
[TAKAGI]
Yeah, I like 'em.
I usually have energy all day
when I eat them in the morning.
Huh.
Yeah, I kinda getcha.
What'd you eat?
Me?
Uh, I had...
Bet you can't guess.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm, I wonder.
Rice?
Rice? Why's that?
Well, I didn't peg
you as a toast kinda guy.
Am I wrong?
No. You're right, I had rice.
It's working!
Just keep her attention
off of the lesson!
So uhh... you on team rice?
I want someone to read
the next page aloud.
Today's the eighteenth,
so how about Takagi.
[NISHIKATA]
Here we go! Heh heh heh.
[NISHIKATA] You don't
know where we are, do you?
Do you?
"I will not do such a thing."
[TANABE]
Thank you. Very nice.
[NISHIKATA]
What?
[TAKAGI]
Hmph.
Nice try.
[NISHIKATA]
Wh-What are you talking about?
Man, she's good!
I can never seem to get her!
Gotta come up with another plan.
Maybe I can take it
back to basics
and hit her with the
old jack-in-the-box?
No, I don't have the materials!
Been over this!
Okay.
What is it this time?
Uh? It's, uhh...
Nothing, forget it.
By any chance, were you
thinking about me again?
No, not really.
Not in so many words.
Plus, why would
I think about you?
That'd be weird, wouldn't it?
[TAKAGI] Oooh, then you were
thinking something naughty.
No! I swear!
[laughs]
I know.
I'm always thinking
about you, though.
Hey, you're blushing!
[NISHIKATA]
No I'm not.
And gimme a break.
You're just always thinking
about different ways
to tease me, aren't you?
Eh...
[NISHIKATA] Why did she
take so long to answer?
[TANABE]
Today's June eighteenth.
If I add the month
and date together, it's 24.
Number 24!
Nishikata!
[NISHIKATA]
"Pool."
It's the first day
we get to go in the pool,
but all I can do is watch.
Why'd I have to hurt my hand?
[NISHIKATA]
It's just not fair.
They're all having fun
without me.
Right?
And of course this happens
on the first day that
they let us swim.
It sucks!
So you're sitting
out too, I take it?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
For you it's because
of your hand, yeah?
How'd you hurt it?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
Well, you know, things happen.
I bet you tried to pet a cat,
but then it bit you.
Huh?! Wait,
how did you know that?
I made an effort not
to tell anyone!
[TAKAGI laughs]
I'm actually right?
I just took a shot in the dark!
You are something else!
[laughs]
So what's your excuse?
Why are you just watching
everyone swim... today?
That reminds me.
Any girl who sits out
during swimming
is usually on her period.
According to the textbook,
it causes abdominal pain
and discomfort.
[NISHIKATA] So says Takao,
the King of Health Class.
Oh, uh, it's nothing, forget it.
I shouldn't ask.
It's not really any of
my business anyway.
[TAKAGI] You wanted to ask
why I'm not swimming today,
didn't you?
[NISHIKATA]
Of course she heard me.
Oh. Hey. How about
because I figured out
your reason is your hand,
you take a shot at
guessing my reason?
[NISHIKATA]
You're not feeling good?
[TAKAGI] You have to be
more specific than that.
[NISHIKATA]
No. Forget it.
I wasn't actually gonna ask you.
Oh?
Then are you admitting defeat?
All right, fine.
I might as well take a guess.
Only one, though.
Well, not that you'd
get it with more tries.
[NISHIKATA]
She's got me cornered now.
Is she this confident because
she thinks I can't say "period"?
Because if that's it,
I'll show her!
I'll say it ten times!
But wait, this is
Takagi we're talking about.
It could be a trap!
Even if I gathered my courage
and answered, "Period"!
I know what'll happen!
No, and that's very rude of you!
[NISHIKATA groans]
[NISHIKATA]
So that's out of the question.
But knowing her,
she probably already has an idea
of what's going through my head.
I'm hesitating, that's enough
for her to figure it out.
But if I don't answer at all,
well, I think I know
how that'll go, too.
You don't even know the
reason why a girl is sitting out
when she could be swimming?
Ha! That means I win, then.
[NISHIKATA]
Is this a trap or not?
Is she making it seem genuine
so I'll fall into a trap?
Or is she making it seem like a
trap, so I'll worry and mess up?
Agh. I'm just going
around in circles here!
This sucks.
What was with that face before?
And was she gripping
her stomach or what?
Okay, what else could it be?
Maybe an injury?
[NISHIKATA] I don't know;
it doesn't seem like it.
It doesn't really look like
she's feeling too sick
to be exercising either.
Then that leaves.
What's left?
No.
[NISHIKATA] They don't know
how good they have it.
They get to goof around
and cool off in the pool.
Meanwhile I'm here in the
heat using all my brain power
to battle Takagi.
Come on, Nishikata,
we don't have all day.
You're not just
checking out all the girls
in their swimsuits, are you?
What? Of course I'm not!
Are you sure about that?
Because you know what I heard?
Boys are ususally
looking at girls' chests.
Whatever, then
I'm the exception!
[NISHIKATA]
I could never say this out loud.
But Takagi doesn't
have a very big chest.
I heard that
small-chested girls are...
...sensitive about it.
So you probs
shouldn't bring it up.
[NISHIKATA] So says Kimura,
the King of Early Lunch.
Could it be that
she's not swimming
because she has some sort
of complex about her body?
Like, she's self-conscious?
I had a feeling you
wouldn't figure it out.
That means I win today, too.
Oh, Takagi.
I do know why.
It's obvious that you're just
self-conscious about your chest!
[NISHIKATA]
Ugh! Yeah, right!
Like I could ever say that!
It's beyond rude!
It's super rude!
The only answer I have left
is that she's on her period!
But that's plenty rude, too.
What do I do?
You're still thinking it over?
We have to go back inside soon.
[NISHIKATA]
No!
They even say in the textbook
that it's nothing to be
embarrassed about!
It'll be fine!
You got this.
Just say it with
your head held high!
It's now or never!
[NISHIKATA] The reason you're
sitting out in swim class is...
...you're on your period.
[TAKAGI]
Incorrect.
[TAKAGI] And that's
pretty rude to say to a girl.
Uh! I just thought that
since it was mentioned
in our health
textbook, it might--
[laughs]
Man Nishikata,
your face is bright red!
[NISHIKATA]
Then is it actually
because she's self-conscious
about her chest?
That's all I got!
Ahhh... Too funny.
Upsy-daisy.
And for the record.
Being too self-conscious
about my chest...
...is also incorrect.
[NISHIKATA]
Wha...?!
[TAKAGI]
Excuse me!
I changed my mind,
is it okay if I swim?
[SWIM TEACHER]
That's fine!
[NISHIKATA]
Uh... I don't get it.
Then why was she sitting out?
Okay.
Now that I've gotten
my fill of funny faces.
It's time for a quick swim.
Oh, don't tell me you were
sitting out that whole time
just so you could tease me more!
Hey. When your hand heals...
...then we can swim together.
[TAKAGI]
It's cold!
[NISHIKATA]
I won't fall for it.
When we do swim together,
I'd bet anything she's
gonna mess with me again.
After all, that's the
kind of person she is.