[NISHIKATA]
The day has come.
I've waited so long!
[chuckles]
And finally,
I got my first cell phone!
[NISHIKATA]
"Cell Phone."
And contact added.
Thanks, man.
Sure thing.
[TAKAGI]
You got a cell phone?
[NISHIKATA]
Right on cue!
[TAKAGI] Oh cool,
you got the latest model?
I was thinking of upgrading
to that one, myself.
Do you mind
if I take a look at it?
Not at all.
Wow. It's lighter than mine.
[NISHIKATA]
I've been waiting for this!
With a cell phone, I can tease
her in all sorts of new ways!
Of course, I've got
one plan in mind already.
You're goin' down, Takagi.
Ooo.
That's a cool feature.
Thanks for letting me
check it out.
No prob.
Uhh...
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
Ah, it's nothing.
[NISHIKATA] I thought
Takagi was gonna ask me
for my email for sure.
What now?
[TAKAGI]
Something wrong?
Huh? Nope!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[NISHIKATA]
Man.
If I can't get in touch with
her, I can't execute my plan!
[NISHIKATA] Wait a second,
why don't I just ask her then?
Why didn't I think
of that earlier?
It's so obvious!
Hey, Takagi?
[TAKAGI]
What is it?
[NISHIKATA]
I, uh...
Uh...
Your email address?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Never mind, wasn't important!
[NISHIKATA]
What's going on?
Why am I so nervous
all of a sudden?
Get it together!
I'm just trying to get
Takagi's email address!
[gasps]
I didn't really
think about it before.
But if I'm asking
a girl for her email.
Isn't that kinda like...?
[NISHIKATA]
Yes, it is!
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
There isn't something you
want to ask me, is there?
No, not at all!
Nope! Not a thing! Really!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
Funny.
I was certain you wanted
to ask me for my email.
[NISHIKATA]
She knows!
Wait!
This might be my chance!
All I gotta do is say,
"Actually, you're right,"
and I'll get exactly
what I want!
You've grown too careless.
Uh.
Actually, yeah, you're right.
I am? Then why'd
you lie about it?
Are you embarrassed?
Or what?
Huh?
[NISHIKATA] She found a
way to flip this one on me.
Uh. Who, me?
Embarrassed? No way.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
I think you are.
[NISHIKATA] It's just good to
have in case something happens.
[TAKAGI]
If what happens?
[NISHIKATA]
I dunno something.
So who else did you ask?
I'm not the only one, am I?
Nah.
So far Kimura and Takao.
And Nakai.
That's all?
It's only been a day.
[NISHIKATA] Yeah, yeah, I'm sure
you've figured it out by now.
You're the first girl
I've asked, whatever!
Just hurry up and give it
already, this is killing me!
So what?
Do you want to message me?
Of course not!
I just want your
stupid contact info,
so I can tease you
when we're not at school!
It has nothing to do with
wanting to talk to you!
Seriously!
That's all!
It's nothing weird, I swear!
[laughs]
I knew it had to be
something like that.
[TAKAGI]
Well, your plan to tease me
has been thoroughly crushed.
Do you still want my email?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
[TAKAGI]
To make up for teasing me.
Help me clean up next week
when I'm on day duty.
[NISHIKATA]
I didn't tease you, though!
I was going to tease you!
Well, yeah.
But if I hadn't found out,
you would have eventually.
[NISHIKATA]
Y-Yeah.
Then it's a deal.
I'll talk to you soon.
When I get home.
She'll talk to me
when she gets home?
[NISHIKATA] Does that mean
she's gonna tease me
when I'm at home too?
I wish I had a cell phone.
[MINA] But I asked my mom
if I could get one yesterday
and she said I was
too young to have a phone.
Of course, she'll say no when
you ask her out of the blue.
You do say things
out of the blue a lot.
[MINA]
Hey, that's not true!
For your information,
I've wanted one forevs.
How long is "forevs"?
[MINA]
Umm...
If I had to put it into words,
a week?
So in not-Mina time, it's
been three days, give or take?
Either way, that's
still way too sudden.
[boys laugh]
Dude what's up
with that picture?
It's ridiculous!
So dumb!
It's Super Ponpoko!
Pon, pon, po-pon, pon!
But there's no denying a lot of
kids have them these days.
I guess I kinda want one, too.
I know, right?
I wish we all had 'em!
We should totally all bug our
moms till they buy 'em for us!
You want one too, right, Sanae?
No. Not really.
What?
Why the heck not?
We could message
each other and stuff!
Because, hold on,
I have one.
What? How did that happen?
Sometimes I get home
late from my club,
so my parents
wanted me to have it.
[YUKARI]
That makes sense.
Still, you should have
told us when you got it.
[MINA]
I know!
If I tell my parents
Sanae has one,
maybe they'll buy one for me!
Hey. That's not a bad idea.
I'll do the same thing.
[MINA] This time
my mom'll agree for sure!
Then I can get
a group chat going!
And I can download tons
of games and play them
until I fall asleep!
[SANAE]
Group chats are the worst
[YUKARI]
That childish attitude
is why your parents don't
wanna get you one.
[MINA]
I'm not childish!
Hit me with a scary story!
What, you think
not getting scared
means you're not childish?
[SANAE]
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. So what? It's true!
Just tell me one, okay?
Late one night.
You get a call from an unknown
number on your new phone.
You answer it
and hear something soft.
A faint groaning of some sort.
You quickly hit "end call,"
and never hear from
that number again.
[MINA]
That's goo--
But you're just so curious,
you have to call back.
[MINA gasps]
Why?
But this time,
you hear nothing on
the other end of the line.
[MINA]
What a relief.
At the end of the month.
You look at your phone bill
and find a hundred
thousand yen charge.
[YUKARI shrieks]
If that happened
my parents would kill me!
[MINA] You're gonna kill me if
you keep screaming like that!
[NISHIKATA]
"Horror."
[door slides open]
Huh? Good morning, Nishikata.
[NISHIKATA]
Hey. Morning.
[TAKAGI] I see you decided
to keep your promise.
I appreciate that.
[NISHIKATA]
Well, yeah.
[yawns]
Let me help.
Sure, thank you.
[yawns]
You're looking tired today.
Really?
Guess so.
Were you up late again?
Watching a recording
of 100% Unrequited Love ?
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? No!
[TAKAGI]
Really?
What was it, then?
Nothing worth mentioning.
[TAKAGI] Were you messaging
some of your friends?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh. Kinda.
What about?
[NISHIKATA]
That's weird.
It's unusual for her to pry
into something this much.
Wait a second.
Fun, right?
I mean, messaging your friends
when you get your
very first cell phone.
Honestly, I was hooked
when I got mine, too.
And then before you know it,
you end up getting in trouble
for doing it too much.
[NISHIKATA] Takagi messaged
someone enough times
to get in trouble?
Who does she know that well?
Oh yeah?
With a girl from class I assume?
[TAKAGI]
Nope.
[NISHIKATA]
Calm down.
She's tricked you with
something like this before.
The last time I rode on
the back of someone's bike.
I was riding with my dad.
[NISHIKATA]
I know!
Was it your dad?
[TAKAGI] Why would I get in
trouble for texting my dad?
[NISHIKATA]
Touché.
[TAKAGI]
Curious?
[NISHIKATA]
Not really.
[TAKAGI] If you tell me what
you chat about with the boys,
I'll tell you who
I was talking about.
Sound like a deal?
[NISHIKATA]
I don't care that much.
Wait...
I can kill two birds
with one stone.
Sorry about this, but your
fun stops here, Takagi.
Actually, yesterday
we were sharing videos.
Mostly funny ones, but there
were a couple others mixed in.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Like what?
[NISHIKATA] Yes, yes, by all
means, keep taking the bait.
[NISHIKATA] I'll send her
that link that Kimura sent me.
[NISHIKATA]
It's thanks to this goat
I didn't sleep well last night.
[phone beep]
[TAKAGI]
Did you send me something?
Yeah.
It's a video of a cute animal
someone sent me last night.
[TAKAGI]
It's not some pervy site, right?
Of course not!
Huh...
Let's see then.
[NISHIKATA] It's so scary that
you'll be at a loss for words!
Just give it a second.
Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah? What's up?
Do you like this stuff?
Like, do you look
at it all the time?
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Huh?!
Whoa, whoa, hold on,
why is that on your phone?
What even is that?
It's definitely not
what I sent you, is it?
[TAKAGI]
Nope. Just thought I'd ask.
Huh?!
Now then, let's take a
looksee at what you sent.
'Kay?
[NISHIKATA] This is pathetic,
she got me again!
Huh? It is an animal video.
Aww.
He's kinda cute.
Is he a goat?
[NISHIKATA] Good, good,
she's let her guard down.
Here comes the fun part.
[NISHIKATA]
That's it! That's the part!
Cower in fear, Takagi!
Oh. Scary.
Huh?!
Yeah. It is, right?
Crazy scary.
[TAKAGI]
Yeah, then again.
It's not that scary when
you watch it in the morning.
[NISHIKATA]
I'll give her that.
Huh... So this is what
you guys talk about.
Boys are into such weird things.
So I held up my end.
What did you talk about
with who exactly?
[TAKAGI]
Mmm...
Just the usual stuff.
That doesn't answer the
question, and you know it!
[TAKAGI]
It doesn't?
Well, I talk with someone
that starts with "Kuh."
Heh.
That's your clue.
"Kuh"?
Like, Kaede?
[TAKAGI]
Wrong.
After that, is "zih."
Kuh-zih?
Kazi?
Wait, Kazi?
That boy?
[TAKAGI laughs]
No, it's not Kazi, either.
But the last bit is "in."
Kuh-zih-in?
[TAKAGI laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
What?
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine!
Freakin' Takagi.
I really thought I'd be able to
get back at her for once, today.
But somehow,
she outplayed me yet again.
No.
The day's not over yet.
It didn't work in the morning,
but I bet it will at night.
There's an even scarier video
Kimura told me about
after school today.
Since it's scary,
I haven't watched it myself.
But this will surely
freak her ou--
How does she always know?
Why do I get the feeling
I'm gonna have to do more
push-ups after this call?
[TAKAGI]
Hello? Nishikata?
Yeah?
[TAKAGI]
I was thinking it's about time.
Uh. About time for what?
[TAKAGI] For you to
send me a scary video.
[NISHIKATA] Huh? I dunno
what you're talking about.
[TAKAGI]
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
Get real, Takagi.
You think I'm gonna reveal
my plan just like that?
This battle is far from over--
[TAKAGI] Just you wait until
after we get off the phone.
Huh?!
[TAKAGI]
That's what you were thinking.
What? No. Not me, I wasn't.
[TAKAGI]
Really?
Yes, of course, really.
Then, are you going
to go to sleep soon?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh, yeah. Probably.
[TAKAGI]
I see.
I was just about
to do that, too.
Oh. Cool.
This feels kind of weird.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
[TAKAGI] I don't think we've
ever talked to each other
at night before.
Kind of makes my heart flutter.
[TAKAGI]
See you tomorrow, then.
Good night.
Yeah.
G'night to you, too.
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah?
[TAKAGI]
You haven't hung up yet.
Why not?
I dunno, I think you
should hang up first.
[TAKAGI]
I called you.
So you're supposed to hang up.
And why's that?
[TAKAGI laughs] Okay, okay,
on the count of three.
We'll both hang up.
[TAKAGI]
One, two...
Liar.
C'mon, you didn't
hang up either!
[TAKAGI laughs]
[NISHIKATA] Man. Two nights
in a row I can't sleep.
[NISHIKATA]
"Picture."
[TAKAGI]
Those cats are fighting.
Give me like
two minutes, Takagi!
What are you doing?
Good. Just like that.
Stay put right there
for me, kitty-cats.
[NISHIKATA]
Yes, that's perfect!
Great.
Add that to my collection
of blurry photos.
What's with you?
Into photography now?
No, not particularly.
I'm just competing with the guys
to see who can
take the best picture.
Has anyone already
taken the lead?
[NISHIKATA] Yeah, Kimura's
unbeatable with this.
Whoa!
Gotta admire the commitment.
[TAKAGI]
Funny pictures are great.
[NISHIKATA]
Mm-hmm.
Wait! I've got an idea!
Let me take a picture
of that funny face you do!
Huh?
That can totally beat
Super Ponpoko!
Help me out!
[TAKAGI]
Hmmm...
I'll agree on the condition that
you do anything I ask of you.
Huh? What kind of "anything"?
The word pretty
much covers it all.
[NISHIKATA]
Scary!
She has what it takes
for me to win, but...
Oh. By the way...
[laughs]
That's the one!
I did the face.
That was your chance.
Wait! Do it again!
No can do.
[NISHIKATA growls]
No, it's okay.
I know her.
She enjoys this too much.
She'll want to do it again!
I'll just act as though
I'm upset to lead her on.
Hey, guess what?
[NISHIKATA]
I knew it!
Here's my chance!
[shrieks]
[laughs]
Really?
You had a toy snake on you?
[TAKAGI]
That's a great picture.
Huh!? Wait,
you took my picture?!
Hey! Delete that!
[TAKAGI]
No way!
It's too good!
If you do anything I ask,
then I'll delete it for you.
[NISHIKATA]
Come on, Takagi!
That was a cheap shot,
and you know it!
[TAKAGI] Wow.
I got such a great picture.
Do you wanna see it?
No, I definitely don't.
[TAKAGI]
Just look!
You had burst mode on?
[TAKAGI]
Cool, huh?
The way your face changes?
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi, you're the worst!
I know!
I'll take a picture
of her laughing
with her mouth hanging
wide open, just like that!
That'll teach her!
Do I look okay?
Well, we're even now.
[NISHIKATA]
We're not even close to even!
If you want me
to delete this shot,
then you gotta
delete yours, too.
[TAKAGI]
Nuh-uh.
I'll keep it.
So you don't have to
delete my picture, either.
Wait.
But that's not the point.
Well, see ya.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
She had fun.
But I didn't get a single funny
picture to show the guys.
Hey, Nishikata?
Do me a favor, and don't
show my picture to anyone.
It's embarrassing.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, right.
Like I could show
this to anyone!
What would people say about
me having a photo like this?
It's not worth keeping!
Better delete it.
[NISHIKATA]
She did say it's embarrassing.
So maybe I can use it for some
kind of blackmail one day.
[NISHIKATA]
Might as well keep it.