[TANABE]
All right, buddy,
I'm sure you know,
but you've been way too
loud during class lately.
I expect you to shape up.
Uh. Yes, sir.
Sorry about that
[TANABE]
So I'm putting you in charge
of cleaning the
science room after school.
Huh?
[TANABE] Don't forget to
wipe the desks down, too.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?!
"Cleaning Duty."
[NISHIKATA sighs]
It's not fair that it's just me.
Takagi should be
getting punished, too.
She's the one who's always
teasing me during class.
[sighs]
But I guess the problem is
that my reactions are too loud.
Let's just get this
over with and head--
[screams]
What are you doing
hiding in the closet?
[laughs]
I was trying to scare you.
Ahh...
That was so worth having
to waste time in there.
Wait.
Lemme guess, you have
to clean as punishment, too?
Why don't we
just get it over with?
Okay?
So, I have a proposal for you.
Before we start,
let's make a game out of
cleaning, so it's more fun.
A game?
[TAKAGI]
Yep.
How about we do
rock-paper-scissors,
and the loser has to clean
a quarter of the room?
You in?
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA]
Hold on.
That means
if I win all four times,
I won't have to clean anything!
[NISHKATA]
Heh! Sure.
[TAKAGI]
All right, let's get started.
Round one!
I'll use rock.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
Why's she telling me what
she's gonna choose?
Rock. So if I go
with paper, I'll win?
But she knows that, so--!
[TAKAGI laughs]
I told you I was
going with rock.
[NISHIKATA]
I hate you!
You need to trust me more.
[NISHIKATA]
I won't be tricked twice.
I'll take her word
for it next time.
Oh!
And I'm not gonna tell
you what I'm picking anymore.
[NISHIKATA]
Man.
I knew it.
She's messing with me again.
[NAKAI]
Hmm?
Nishikata!
Uh. Hey, Nakai!
What's goin' on in here?
You two just felt
like hangin' out?
No, I was loud in class,
so I have to clean
the room as punishment.
[NAKAI]
Hm. That's rough, man.
[NISHIKATA]
What about you?
Me? I'm, uh...
...just hangin' around.
You know.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh. Okay.
Hey, Nakai.
Let's not get
in their way, yeah?
Oh. You're right.
Well, we'll be on our way.
[NISHIKATA]
Cool. See yah around.
[NAKAI]
Oh, and Nishikata.
Huh?
Good luck to yah, dude!
Uh. Oh, right.
With this?
[MANO] Come on,
let's just get out of here.
Sorry, Takagi!
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hm.
See yah!
By the way,
bet you didn't know.
They're going out.
Wait, what? They are?
Seriously? I had no idea.
I mean, I did notice
them hanging out
a lot lately, but still...
It's not like they're
trying to hide it.
It's just that they're
both the kind of people
who wouldn't announce it.
True.
He said he's hanging around,
and she was with him.
But if you notice, they were
on their way to the rooftop.
The... The rooftop?
And right about now,
they're probably
all alone up there.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Just the two of them?
[TAKAGI]
You gonna clean?
Huh? Uh. Yeah!
I am.
Aww. Enjoying their time.
[NISHIKATA]
With each other.
Up there together.
I wonder what--
[TAKAGI]
I wonder what it's like.
Up there.
Right?
Yeah. I guess so.
Hey. I finished.
[TAKAGI]
Okay, then.
[BOTH]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[NISHIKATA] How did I
end up losing every time?
Well, that's finally done!
Let's go. It's getting late.
So casual.
I hope you learned your lesson
and won't tease me in class now.
I guess.
I could always
just be more discreet.
[NISHIKATA] We're gonna
get in trouble no matter what!
Yeah, well,
if it happens, it happens.
Not to mention.
I wasn't even told to
clean in the first place.
Huh? You've gotta be kidding!
Okay, for real.
Why am I the only one who
gets in trouble all the time?
So you're just here to
mess with me, like usual?
[TAKAGI]
There's that, but...
...I wanted to
enjoy my time, too.
Huh? Enjoy...
...your time?
[TAKAGI]
And on that note,
you're buying me
juice on our way home.
[NISHIKATA]
What? Why?
"Kickover."
The sun's killing me.
Yeah, me too.
I'm really thirsty.
Oh! I know.
How about a competition
and the loser buys drinks.
Yeah, why not?
Can I decide what
we compete in then?
Think I've got a good idea.
[TAKAGI]
The high bar?
Uh-huh. Whichever one
of us can't do a kickover
on the high bar is the loser.
[NISHIKATA] I just happened
to try doing a kickover
on the high bar recently.
And bam!
I was actually able to
for the first time in my life!
[NISHIKATA] Ever since then,
I've been itchin' for my chance
to show Takagi up in a duel!
To be honest, I wouldn't
be all that surprised
if she could do one, too.
[NIHSIKATA]
But!
Hey, Nishikata.
You realize,
I'm wearing a skirt, right?
[NISHIKATA]
Exactly!
Can't flip over the
bar wearing a skirt!
She's unable to compete!
I win!
Oh, well.
I call dibs on
going first, then.
[NISHIKATA]
Eh?
Really? You want to?
Yeah, it's fine.
However, I'd like
to add one extra rule.
You can't watch me.
Huh?
You're surprised?
I am wearing a skirt.
So if you look at me on my turn,
then you're the loser.
[TAKAGI]
Here I go!
Okay.
Your turn, show me what you got.
[NISHIKATA]
Did she really do it?
I have no way of knowing.
Whatever, now's not the time.
I've gotta focus
on the task at hand!
Whoa.
Well, we both
were able to do it.
So what now?
One more time. Do over.
All right.
Then I'll go first again, 'kay?
[NISHIKATA]
No hesitation.
That's not a good sign.
She's either really confident
or hiding something.
I bet she's not even
doing a kickover.
She said I lose if
I look during her turn.
But it's a different story
if she's cheating.
Today's the day
that I finally beat her!
[NISHIKATA]
No way!
She's actually doing it?
[NISHIKATA]
Shorts?!
I'm done.
You can turn around now.
[TAKAGI]
What's wrong?
[NISHIKATA]
Sorry, Takagi.
I lose.
Here.
[TAKAGI]
Thanks.
Though, I don't really
feel like a winner.
Since you disqualified
yourself and all.
Yeah, about that.
If you had shorts
on the whole time,
then why didn't you
let me watch you do it?
Pervert.
[gasps]
Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
I just wanted to make sure
you were actually
swinging over the bar!
[TAKAGI]
Really?
[NISHIKATA]
Yes, really!
[TAKAGI]
All right, then.
So you thought
I was cheating, is that it?
[NISHIKATA]
What?! No, I just... Ugh...
All right, what's the big idea?
Why are you always picking
on me, day in and day out?
It's nothing.
[KYUNKO]
Huh? Ba-dump!
Be straight.
You like being treated
this way, don't you?
[KYUNKO]
Ahh... Squeal!
I said,
"You like being treated
this way, don't you?"
[KYUNKO]
Ahh... Squeal!
100% Unrequited Love
is so good!
[NISHIKATA sneezes]
[NISHIKATA]
"Cold."
Pay attention,
this part's important.
And you can bet it's
gonna be on the test.
So make sure you remember it.
[NISHIKATA]
Morning. Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Nishikata.
I wasn't expecting you.
I thought you were out sick.
Are you feeling better?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah. I think so.
[TAKAGI]
Morning. You have a cold?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
But it's nothing.
I can handle it.
No big deal.
Nailed it!
Huh?
I bet you just stayed up
watching 100% Unrequited Love.
[NISHIKATA]
How did she figure that out?
[KYUNKO]
Squeal, squeal!
Don't say that so loud,
it's embarrassing!
[TANABE] Funny,
I only heard you screaming.
You're right. Sorry, sir!
Come on, that was
really low, Takagi.
[coughs]
[TAKAGI]
You okay?
You're coughing.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah. It's not that bad.
Man.
She won't pull any punches
even when I'm sick!
Heh...
But luckily, I have the ultimate
plan to defeat her today!
[KYUNKO] Wait, what's
a guy like him doing here?
Him and his perfect hair!
Now I'm really mad!
I'm going to give him
a piece of my mind!
Hey!
Oh wow.
You're so cute.
[KYUNKO gasps]
Squeal!
[NISHIKATA]
I can do that!
I may have caught a cold,
but it was worth it
for the invaluable
knowledge I've gained!
[NISHIKATA]
Okay, Takagi. Come at me.
Gimme your best shot!
I'll counter it
and make you blush!
Ni--
[coughs]
[NISHIKATA]
Come on!
Whenever you're ready!
[slap, slap]
[NISHIKATA]
Uh...
Uh. What?
Don't worry. 'S nothing.
[NISHIKATA]
Weird.
She isn't making her move.
I can't stay in
this pose forever.
And my right hand's on my chin,
so I can't even take notes.
[gasps]
Wait, what if she figured
it out because of the pose?
Is it too obvious
I've got a counter-trap ready
to spring on her?
[NISHIKATA]
One way to find out.
Sit normally.
[NISHIKATA grunts]
What's her deal today?
I don't understand!
Any other day, she'd have
teased me three times by now!
Is she sick or something?
Huh?
[NISHIKATA] When she's quiet,
she's really...
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA]
Uh-oh.
I think I'm starting to
second guess my plan here.
Countering with "You're cute,"
when she messes with
me might be embarrassing.
Duh, of course it is!
How did I ever think
I'd be able to say that?
I bet it's because I'm sick, and
didn't get any sleep last night.
[TAKAGI]
Are you okay?
Hey.
[NISHIKATA gasps]
Uh. Yeah.
It's all good.
Your face is a little red.
Huh?
And you look tired.
Sure you're good?
[NISHIKATA]
Yes, I'm fine.
But you're getting even redder.
Do you have a fever?
[NISHIKATA] Why are you being
so nice to me today, Takagi?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm totally okay!
Really?
[NISHIKATA]
Really!
When I said I was feeling sick,
it was more like
an excuse, anyway.
I really just woke up
at like, eight-thirty,
so that's why I was late.
I'm fine! Promise!
[TAKAGI]
Okay.
I guess I believe you.
It's about time!
So... I can tease you again.
Huh? What do you mean?
[NISHIKATA]
And of course,
she ended up making fun of
me more than usual that day.
Young love!
Squeal!
Yukari, Sanae,
what's with the snail's pace?
Power walk, let's go!
Why should I exert
myself that much for a popsicle?
Cus, it's the baked
sweet potato flavor!
It's a summer exclusive!
That's a weird flavor
for summer.
They're sold out of it
everywhere that I've looked.
But I think this one
snack store will have it.
So we gotta check
before they sell out too!
What are you doing?
There's no point
in taking a shortcut
if you're gonna drag
your feet the whole time!
[YUKARI] I just noticed
Takagi and Nishikata
are inside the store.
[MINA]
Oh hey. You're right.
[YUKARI] Could it be
that those two are...?
Mina, maybe we
shouldn't get in their way--
[MINA]
Hey! Takagi!
[sighs]
[MINA]
"Tailing."
Sha-bam!
Got my sweet potato pop!
Uh. I'm happy for you.
See you tomorrow.
They're so lucky.
Lucky how?
Well, look at the two of them.
You know.
A guy and a girl together.
It's just nice.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Why?
[TAKAGI laughs]
You didn't notice?
Don't blame me,
it was your idea.
[laughs]
Hey. Why exactly
are we following them?
We live in the
opposite direction.
[YUKARI]
Shhh!
They're gonna notice us.
Shut up!
Just tell me what you think.
Don't you feel,
I dunno, like something's
going on between them?
[MINA]
Hmm...
Oh! They've got
a bike right there!
They should be
riding it together, right?
That is so romantic!
Riding home
together after school.
Oh, but that's a tough decision,
because you can spend
a lot more time together
if you walk instead!
Maybe if you trade off
every other day?
Can I have a bite of that?
Uh. Yeah,
but just one bite, okay?
[sighs]
[SANAE]
Hey, Takagi.
You wanna race somewhere?
Are you challenging me?
Uh-huh!
We'll start once
we turn that corner.
The first one to make it
all the way to the shrine wins.
Hmm. Okay, why not?
Haha. She either has to
ride her bike or pull it.
With that flat tire,
she'll lose either way.
You have way
too wild an imagination!
I guarantee you they're not
talking about a race!
They're talking about something
more intimate than that.
I just know it!
Nishikata.
I'm up for us
racing to the shrine.
But before that...
[NISHIKATA]
Hmm?
[YUKARI]
They're gone?
Did they make it all the
way to the shrine already?
No way!
[YUKARI] Maybe they realized
we were tailing them.
[MINA] Ugh, come on,
let's go home already.
[YUKARI]
Uh. Yeah.
[MINA] I say we buy more
popsicles on the way.
[SANAE]
Will you let me have a bite?
[MINA] Just buy your own if
you're gonna keep eating mine!
[NISHIKATA]
So close.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Ah. Did we lose them?
Any idea why they
were following us
in the first place?
No.
Hey, uh...
Now that I think about it,
we should have gone
around that corner too.
It would have been a lot
easier to hide over there.
[TAKAGI]
Huh.
I hadn't thought about that,
guess you're right.
But I wonder...
Would you have
preferred if we did?
Well, no.
It doesn't really matter.
Good!
I'm glad.
Oh, I almost forgot!
We're racing to
the shrine, yeah?
Ready, set go!
Huh?! Hey, hold on!
I'm callin' you out!
That's a false start, Takagi!
[MINA] Tailing those two turned
out to be kinda fun in the end.
Takin' the long way home.
[YUKARI] They probably did
notice us following them.
I better apologize
to Takagi tomorrow.
[MINA screams]
They're out of the
baked sweet potato flavor!
It's okay!
They got red bean soup!
What is with you wanting
these flavors in the summer?
So you gonna let me have a bite?