[MINA]
"Coffee."
Ugh. Bitter.
What's goin' on with your face?
Ugh.
Huh? Wait. Isn't that coffee?
I thought you
hated the stuff, Mina.
Why would you
buy it i you hate it?
Well, I'm becoming
more of an adult now,
so I thought I should try
to get myself used to it.
Huh?
How exactly are
you more of adult now?
Ah! Hey, I may not be tall,
but I'm growing in some ways!
I'd like to see
you drink this, Sanae!
No problem.
I like it black.
Huh?
You like it black?
[gasps]
Do you wanna
trade with me, then?
[gasps]
I do. But I'm an adult, so...
Three, two, one--
[MINA]
Okay, whatever, let's trade!
Yes!
Ahhh... So good.
You sure you're okay with this?
Yeah.
There's gotta be some adults
who can't drink coffee.
You know you're a kid right?
[gasps]
Why're you so mean?
Ahh!
Ahhh! Ow!
Oh great.
Adults don't try to tackle
their friends, Mina.
[NISHIKATA]
As I've come to expect,
Takagi made fun
of me a ton today.
[groans]
[NISHIKATA]
But I'll get her tomorrow!
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi!
Oh.
On your own today?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah.
Cool. Let's walk home together.
Uh. Wait, why?
[TAKAGI]
What?
Um, sorry.
I thought I heard something.
But, um, you're
on your bike, and all.
[TAKAGI]
I'll just push.
[NISHIKATA]
"Empty Can."
That's that new drink
that just came out, isn't it?
Is it good?
[NISHIKATA]
What is this?
Some kind of trap?
I like it.
You wanna have a sip?
Can I?
[NISHIKATA]
Mm-hmm.
Great. Thank you.
Not that I really mind,
but won't it be like we're
indirectly kissing or something?
[NISHIKATA]
How's that, Takagi?
Super embarrassing, right?
You're so embarrassed!
Wha...? How?
She's not embarrassed
in the slightest!
What is with her?
Ahh...
Boy, that was good.
Thanks again.
Can't drink it?
No. Of course I can drink it.
[NISHIKATA]
It's nothing.
No big deal.
It's like an indirect kiss.
Aah!
[TAKAGI laughs]
You're so jumpy.
[NISHIKATA] There's gotta
be a trash can around here.
Man!
Wow!
That was a pretty
good shot, Nishikata.
[NISHIKATA] I just threw
it without thinking.
I didn't expect to make it in.
[NISHIKATA]
This is crazy!
I didn't know
I was such a good shot!
All right.
I wanna give this a go.
[laughs]
What are you aiming at?
You weren't even close!
You're terrible at this!
Oh? Care to make it interesting?
[laughs]
Yeah, fine.
I can't say "no" when
winning's a sure-thing.
[TAKAGI] Then, we'll each
throw one can at a time.
The first person
to make it in, wins.
[NISHIKATA] Challenging me to
a match she can't possibly win.
Takagi's really
lost her cool this time.
And it feels awesome!
So if you somehow win,
then I guess I'll do
anything you want me to.
I'm gonna hold you to that.
You better not
chicken out later.
No way.
Besides, it's not like
I'm gonna lose to you.
Glad to hear it.
[gasps]
[laughs]
If you miss, that means I win.
[NISHIKATA]
Ugh.
She totally tricked me again.
[NISHIKATA]
Just stand at the same place
and use the same angle.
Okay.
[NISHIKATA]
I can do this.
It's a walk in the park!
Oh, yeah.
So, uh, if you happen to win,
then I'll let you
have my first kiss.
[moans]
[TAKAGI laughs]
Looks like I win!
[NISHIKATA]
That wasn't fair.
What wasn't?
Whaddya mean "what wasn't"?
As I threw it, you said--
[TAKAGI]
Hmm? Said what?
Oh, forget it.
[TAKAGI]
Okay.
Well, a promise is a promise.
Now what should I make you do?
[NISHIKATA] I don't even want to
think about what she might say.
[TAKAGI]
Know what?
How about this?
You can do whatever.
Wait, where are
you going Takagi?!
Don't pity me!
I need consequences!
Letting me off like
this makes me feel like
I'll never beat
you at anything.
[TAKAGI] You never
will beat me at anything.
[NISHIKATA] Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey!
[MINA]
"Soda."
Ahh!
So fizzy.
What is it this time?
[YUKARI] Huh?
You're drinking soda?
I thought you didn't
like soda, though.
Why do sodas
have to be so fizzy?
It stings!
Is there a reason you
keep buying drinks
you don't even like?
Pretending to be an adult again?
No, not that.
I just love the flavor.
[screams]
But it stings bad!
My poor tongue
is hurting so bad!
You're so annoying.
What?
Don't act like it
doesn't hurt your tongue
when you have this stuff!
It doesn't.
Prove it. Have some right now.
All right.
Ahh!
The pain'll bubble
up inside you soon.
Yeah, not likely.
Tell the truth.
You're feeling it, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
[MINA]
Hmm...
[YUKARI]
What pain is she talking about?
I'm fine.
Oh no.
I'm about to burp.
Ha! You feelin' it now?
[YUKARI]
Nuh-uh.
If I burp right now,
she's gonna make fun of me.
[YUKARI] But this stupid
fizz is still coming up.
I can't hold it much longer!
Agh! It's so tingly, I hate it!
Ahhh...
What's your problem?
Nothing.
[MINA]
Why am I still drinking this?
[TAKAGI laughs]
See you tomorrow!
[NISHIKATA grunts]
Just you wait, Takagi.
Including the walk home,
she teased me 15
times in total today.
[TV TRAINER] Each time I make
a mistake during a game,
I make a note of it.
Then I train ten times
harder for each one.
I believe that will lead me
to my next victory.
[NISHIKATA]
That's it!
Today I had 15 losses.
And that times ten is 150!
Uh... That might be
too much for my first go.
Okay.
Let's try three times first.
One, two, three.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
[NISHIKATA] This is a
lot harder than I thought!
Maybe I shouldn't do so many.
No, I have to!
This is my punishment
for letting Takagi mess
with me so many times!
[NISHIKATA]
I'll savor this agony
and use it as motivation
to get back at her next time!
I can do this!
[NISHIKATA]
"Muscle Training."
What's wrong?
Is your arm hurt?
Pull a muscle?
Huh? Oh, no,
it's nothing like that.
It's just extra sore is all.
Huh?
[shrieks]
I just said it was sore!
That really hurts!
Does that count as
her first teasing of the day?
I should probably be
holding myself accountable.
So I guess that's one.
Hey!
[laughs]
That was way too easy!
You must be really sore
if flinching hurts.
Okay, well that
was definitely teasing,
no doubt about it.
So... wanna tell me why
you're sore all of a sudden?
Uhh. I started to work out
yesterday, so you know.
Interesting.
I hope you don't quit
after like, three days.
[NISHIKATA]
Hah. Go ahead.
Laugh it up now.
[NISHIKATA]
Why?
She teased me 23 times today!
Is that a record?
Either way, it's much
more than yesterday!
[NISHIKATA]
One, two, three.
[TAKAGI] Hey, whatever happened
to working out, Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Nothing, I still do it daily.
Oh wow.
So you didn't
quit three days in?
Yes, thanks to you.
Oh! But you know what I heard?
Huh? No, what?
They say if you work out too
much during your growth spurt,
it'll stop you
from getting taller.
Uh, wait?
Huh?! Oh no!
I think I did hear that
somewhere before!
That's not good!
If she ends ups taller than
me because I'm stunting
my own growth,
I'll never heard the end of it!
She'll make fun of me forever!
What do I do, what do I do?
But that is just a rumor.
Just a rumor?
In fact, I've also heard
moderate exercise
actually supports your growth.
So, that being the case,
you should keep working out.
Nothing to worry about.
It's a good idea.
And to be honest,
you kinda look
a bit more muscular.
[NISHIKATA]
You think?
What's wrong?
You're quiet.
Don't tell me
that you're blushing.
I'm not blushing.
But your face is red.
[laughs]
Yeah, you're definitely
blushing all right.
Why do you always have
to tease me every single day?
Because I like seeing
your reactions, duh.
By the way,
I wasn't lying when
I said you look muscular.
Honestly, you've
looked pretty good lately.
[laughs]
You're even redder now!
Whatever! It's just
because it's hot outside!
Hey!
Takagi!
Come back!
The count is 54 today.
Oh, 55 including this last one.
But I'm starting to think that
I should keep working out
even if Takagi doesn't tease me.
[MINA]
"Dubbing."
[SANAE] Chester dear, are you
eating dinner at home tonight?
[MINA] Well, I reckon'
that depends on work.
If we go too late, I'll just eat
with Jirou on my way home.
[SANAE] I'm glad you've
found a close friend in Jirou,
but you should have
dinner at home sometimes.
It's starting to
feel lonely without you.
[MINA] Yeah, but it's mah job,
what can yah do?
[sighs]
Can we please just go home?
No way! We're havin' fun!
[YUKARI] Why are you
still talking like that?
So annoying.
Uh...
You jerk!
Am I really so
unimportant to you?
[MINA] Aww, Puddin',
don't be like that.
I'm doin' mah best here.
[SANAE cries]
Why are you cryin' mah darlin'?
Well, it's as if Jirou
and your work have taken
you away from me.
I just...
I don't think
I can take it any longer.
Emotions are running high.
[MINA]
Ahh jeez, I'm sick o' this!
[SANAE] How could you
say such a thing, Chester? Oh!
[MINA]
Listen here.
If yer gonna act like this.
Then so will I!
Uh... Hold on.
Did you realize those
cats are both male?
[MINA gasps]
[SANAE]
Hey, whaddya know, it's Chester!
[MINA]
Well, if it ain't Jirou!
Wanna grab a bite to eat?
[YUKARI]
I really want to go home.
[NISHIKATA]
"Umbrella."
Aww! Of course it starts
raining right when school ends.
Huh?! No one told me it
was gonna rain today!
If I knew, I would
have brought my raincoat!
Dummy.
Hey, don't be so mean to Mina.
You want to take
the bus home, then?
[MINA] I don't have
any bus money either.
See what I mean, dumb.
Oh, you be quiet.
I'll lend you some cash,
don't worry.
[NISHIKATA]
Man.
I got teased a ton today, too.
Huh? Aren't you
heading home, Takagi?
Not yet.
I didn't bring a raincoat
or an umbrella.
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
You are such an airhead!
You really didn't know it
was gonna rain today?
How ditzy can you be?
[NISHIKATA]
No comeback?
[TAKAGI]
Oh.
Come to think of it, your
umbrella is pretty big, right?
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
We look like a couple
under this umbrella together.
How in the world
did this happen?
I feel so weird!
It's super awkward!
What should I do?
Fill the silence, I guess.
So, uh, what about your bike?
It's still at school,
but I'll walk tomorrow.
Oh. Okay.
[NISHIKATA]
It's even more awkward now
that I tried
to fill the silence,
and it worked for
all of five seconds!
Ugh. I'm so embarrassed that
it's getting hard to breathe.
I need to distract
myself somehow.
Hey, Takagi!
[NISHIKATA]
How's this?
Are you scared?
Surprised?
Give me something!
Aww. He's so cute!
[NISHIKATA]
Excuse me?
Ugh, what was I thinking?
This is Takagi I'm dealing with,
of course she's fine!
Wait, what?
[shrieks]
[laughs]
Don't freak, it's just a frog.
By the way, Nishikata.
Is your shoulder
getting wet over there?
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, sort of.
It's not that bad, though.
[TAKAGI] Getting wet
at all can lead to a cold.
I'm gonna scoot closer,
so get yourself all the
way under the umbrella.
[NISHIKATA]
My heart's pounding so fast.
It feels like
it's about to burst!
Calm down, calm down, Nishikata!
If she finds out you're nervous,
she's gonna make
fun of you again!
Just talk about something.
Anything!
So hey, uh...
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
It's pretty unusual for you
to forget your umbrella
when it's supposed to rain.
Could it be that you
really are an airhead,
and I was right all along?
[NISHIKATA]
Was that too harsh?
[TAKAGI]
Hmmm...
Yeah, maybe.
I do tend to be
sort of forgetful.
[NISHIKATA]
Did I hear that right?
Did she just admit
she has a fault?
What a rare occasion!
I feel like I've won for once!
I'm having trouble remembering
something right now, actually.
Oh, yeah?
Do you need help?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
The two of us, all close,
sharing the same umbrella.
We must look like a...
What was the word for it?
I just can't seem
to remember it.
Uhh.
Wait, you don't mean...
It's on the tip of my tongue!
Uh... We look like a couple?
Huh? What was that?
I didn't quite hear you.
Oh, I remember!
It was "couple"!
Come on, there's
no way you forgot that!
Oh, what about that
thing that couples do?
You know.
It's a way they
express their love.
When they take their lips
and then press them up
against each other?
[NISHIKATA] If I don't
answer her, then I lose!
A... A kiss?
Huh? I can't hear you,
the rain's too loud.
What do you mean?
It's not raining
that hard anymore.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
So don't pretend
you didn't hear me.
I said it's a kiss.
Ahh. That was it.
So how about that
phrase they always use
to show their feelings?
Know that?
You know.
That one.
Not I "like" you, but...
Pretty sure
it starts out the same.
"I" something.
Uh, I dunno.
[TAKAGI] I think the next
word starts with "L," too.
[NISHIKATA]
I said I don't know!
Nah, you know this one.
"I"...
The next word starts with "L-O."
"I lo"...
What's the next letter?
You know it.
Th-That's enough.
Oh! The last word is "you."
You're not gonna
let up, are you?
Ugh, man!
Hey, check it out,
the rain stopped!
Yeah, you're right.
[NISHIKATA]
I'm saved!
There was no way
I could survive that treatment
until we reached her house!
Well, my place is this way.
Now that the skies are clear,
I'll be going.
Where are we?
I don't know how
to get home from here.
Ugh!
Will you ever give me a break?