[NISHIKATA groans]
There's gotta be some way I can
beat Takagi at her own game.
I gotta get that last laugh!
Or, at the very least,
I have to do something
to stop her from
teasing me every day.
[gasps]
Sorry, I didn't see you--!
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
Good morning.
Oh. Ah. Good morning.
Uh. Something wrong?
Oh, no.
Not at all.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
Well, you want to go
to school together?
Uh...
Sure.
[NISHIKATA]
"Who's Taller?"
Did she see that?
Did she see me
apologize to a pole?
Hey, Nishikata.
Yeah? What's up?
Want to tandem ride?
You already know my answer.
We'll get in trouble
if we're seen.
You're just too embarrassed.
No, I am not!
Yeah. Right.
[NISHIKATA] Well, she hasn't
said anything strange.
Guess she must have
just missed seeing me.
Phew.
Took you long enough.
Breaking out the winter uniform?
Yeah. It's been getting
colder lately,
so I thought the time
was just about right.
Wh-What?
Did you grow?
Huh?
I think that uniform looked
a little bigger on
you last spring.
[NISHIKATA] Now that I think
about it, she might be right.
This thing feels like it
was tailor-made for me.
I didn't even notice.
Could it be?
Am I finally having
a growth spurt?
[chuckles]
Man.
I'm growing so much lately,
I might need a new uniform soon.
Must be one of those
"growth spurts."
But by comparison,
you sure haven't changed much,
have you, Takagi?
[TAKAGI]
That's sexual harassment.
"Haven't changed much."
[NISHIKATA]
N-No!
That's--
Come on, you know that's
not what I was talking about.
Uh. I was talking
about your height.
Huh? Well, yeah, I was too.
Why, what did you think I meant?
N-Nothing.
Oh?
Now what?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
You know what?
I take it back, maybe
you haven't gotten taller.
Huh?!
What do you mean?
I totally grew!
In fact, I'd be willing to bet
I'm taller than you now, Takagi!
Yeah? Do you care
to find out for sure?
[NISHIKATA]
Why're we doing it here?
[TAKAGI] So we can take
our shoes off to be fair.
[NISHIKATA]
We're gonna be late for school.
[TAKAGI]
Nah, this'll be quick.
Here, turn around.
[TAKAGI]
Let's see.
[NISHIKATA]
She's kinda... warm.
[TAKAGI]
Uhh...
[NISHIKATA]
So, Takagi?
[TAKAGI]
Huh?
Normally, wouldn't
you stand against a wall
and make a mark
to measure height?
Yeah, but I think
it's more accurate
if we stand together like this.
[TAKAGI] I think we're
about the same height.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Really?
Really.
If you don't believe me,
check for yourself.
No way, you're right.
Told yah.
Hey.
You're not like,
on your tiptoes are you?
[TAKAGI]
Why? You don't trust me?
All right then.
Is this better?
You'll be able to tell
if I'm cheating now.
Uh. Yeah. I guess.
Wait.
Now it kinda looks like.
I'm taller.
That's because I was
on my tiptoes before.
[NISHIKATA] So you were
cheating, I called it!
You're a liar!
[laughs]
I never said I wasn't
on my tiptoes.
Good for you though.
You're taller after all.
[NISHIKATA]
Yeah, walk away.
You're acting all
cool on the outside,
but on the inside,
I bet you're really bitter!
Oh. By the way,
if you think I'm bitter,
you're wrong.
Know why?
When your body grows too fast.
You might run into things.
Like, utility poles.
Huh?
Wait! Does that mean
you saw me do that?
Are you ready?
School's a-waitin'!
Takagi.
Hey.
Takagi?
So cold.
I dunno, I feel fine.
You're so sensitive
to the cold, Yukari.
Take that!
[YUKARI]
Mina, your hand is freezing!
[SANAE]
"I Hate the Cold"
[YUKARI]
Jeez.
You do that again,
and I'll hate you forever.
[SANAE]
Forever?
[YUKARI shrieks]
[laughter]
[YUKARI]
Will you stop it?
Why?
[YUKARI]
Because I hate it!
Why are your hands
so cold anyway?
[laughs]
You know why.
You just don't
want to accept it.
People who have cold
hands have warm hearts!
I don't think a person
with a warm heart
would enjoy torturing
their friends for kicks.
Now, now.
There's no need
to hold a grudge.
[YUKARI]
I'm not kidding.
If you do it again,
I'm gonna be really mad.
[MINA]
You're already mad.
[SANAE]
Gotcha.
[shrieks]
So cold!
[laughs]
Stop it!
I said stop, Sanae!
That's the "My heart
is so warm" attack.
[MINA]
Help me, Yukari!
[YUKARI]
Take this!
Now let's see how you like it!
Your hands are so warm.
It's scary.
That must mean
you've got a cold heart.
[YUKARI] That is not what
it means and you know it!
Stay away, cold-heart!
[YUKARI] Prepare for the
"Cold heart frozen soul" attack!
[SANAE]
Equally as fearsome!
[MINA]
It's not even close!
[TAKAGI]
Hey.
So cold!
What'd you do that for?
Get me back if you can.
[MINA]
You get back here!
[YUKARI whines]
Stop that!
Quadruple cold hands!
[MINA]
Four times the power!
No way can I do that.
[screams]
Will you stop it?!
Your hands are cold as ice!
Leave me alone!
Did you know
they say that people
with cold hands
have warm hearts?
[NISHIKATA growls]
Nope!
It's Takagi and
Nishikata, again.
I saw them show up
to school together today.
Those two are so close.
Well, maybe they are going out.
[TAKAO, KIMURA]
"Invitation."
[YUKARI]
I really can't help but wonder.
Do you think they're going out?
Who knows?
You don't sound very interested.
They're so close,
it makes me want to know.
Why is that?
Are you jealous of them?
[gasps]
Am I jealous?
Well, not exactly, but...
Mina.
Yukari says she wishes she
had a boy she could flirt with.
That's not even
close to what I said!
Hey.
You listening?
[SANAE]
Mina?
Sanae!
I'm on the toilet. Don't talk
to me right now, please!
You're gonna make me
lose my concentration!
Huh?
You are too much
sometimes, Sanae.
It's good.
You should watch it later.
[STUDENT]
Really? Cool, I will!
[SANAE]
Hey, Takagi?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[NISHIKATA chuckles] I just
came up with the perfect plan!
It's the ultimate, fail-proof
plot to tease Takagi
on our way home from school!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
What are you smirking to
yourself about over there?
Something pervy?
No.
It's nothing dirty
or weird or whatever.
Dirty or weird?
That's what I said!
[laughs]
Your face is turning red.
[NISHIKATA]
Whatever.
Just you wait
until after school!
By the way, Nishikata.
Later, do you wanna
walk home together?
Yeah, sure!
[NISHIKTA]
Oh, no!
Was I too eager?
Did she realize
I'm up to something?
[coughs]
I mean.
Yeah, sure.
Isn't that what you just said?
Uh-huh.
That a problem?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
No.
But just in case you change
your mind before school's out,
you can give me a
definite answer later.
See ya.
[NISHIKATA]
Well that was weird.
As long as she isn't on to me,
I guess it's fine.
[KIMURA]
Hey, Nishikata!
We were gonna play
"Super-Pro" at my house today.
You want in on that?
Um...
Sorry. I can't today.
You spending time with
your girlfriend again?
My "girlfriend"?
Takagi, right?
I called it.
Huh?! What are
you talking about?
We're not like that at all!
[MINA] It's true, Takagi and
Nishikata are not going out.
I know 'cuz we just asked
her in the bathroom
Aw, really?
Yeah!
Oh man, I seriously gotta go.
Bathroom, here I come.
Uhh... What was she doing
in the bathroom before
if she has to go now?
All right, putting that aside,
if you're not
going out with her,
why are you walking
home with her for like,
the hundredth time?
Well, because she asked me to?
Asked you?
And you're sure that's not
because you're going out?
Uh.
I don't think so, at least.
[TAKAO]
Hmm?
Okay, whatever.
Hey, isn't next
period in the lab?
You're right, let's hurry!
[NISHIKATA]
No way.
I don't buy it.
Takagi just wants to tease me.
[MINA]
Ready to get going?
Yeah. But we're going
straight home today, okay?
Huh?!
But I had it all planned out!
I wanted to get
a Ponkan Popsicle!
Don't you think it's
a little bit cold for that?
Not when you go inside
and pump the heat it's not!
You said it.
[NISHIKATA] If she's not
gonna say anything about it,
then to give her
my "definite" answer,
I've gotta ask her myself.
[NISHIKATA]
That's kinda embarrassing
now that I'm face
to face with it.
I've never been the one to ask
her to walk home with me before.
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
Yeah? What's goin' on?
Oh, good!
If she asks me,
all I have to do is say yes!
That's easy!
[TAKAGI]
You know what?
Earlier today someone asked me
if I was going out with you.
Huh?!
And...
After I told them we weren't,
they said that they
thought I liked you.
I'm always asking you
to walk home with me.
Maybe that's why
they thought that.
[NISHIKATA]
I should have known!
This is what you were
after the whole time!
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[NISHIKATA]
You orchestrated everything,
so I have no choice but to ask
you to walk home with me!
Just so you can watch me squirm!
You okay?
[NISHIKATA]
Try to sound calm.
Just say something like,
"Oh yeah? That's funny."
Oh yeah? Tha-That's funny!
Nice!
Uh.
So, anyway.
About your request
from this morning.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Uh.
I don't have any plans, so uh...
Let's...
"Let's" what?
[NISHIKATA]
Hang in there, man!
If you can get through this,
then you get your chance
to mess with Takagi!
Let's walk home together.
I'll have to think about it.
Huh?!
[laughs]
I'm just kidding.
Let's go.
[TAKAGI]
I can't wait.
Because... it looks like
you're scheming something.
[NISHIKATA]
She's on to me!
[TAKAGI] If she's already
suspicious of me,
should I hold
off on my plan?
But I came up with
such a good idea!
Not that I've thought about
how to carry out said idea
to begin with, though.
[TAKAGI]
Want to get some juice?
Now that I think about it,
my mouth is dry.
[TAKAGI]
Aww.
Most of them are sold out.
[NISHIKATA groans] I really
wanted to get something cold.
But all they have is...
Sweet red bean soup
and whatever that is!
What do we do?
[NISHIKATA]
I need something,
but I'm in a no-win
situation here!
[NISHIKATA]
A "no-win situation"?
Should we find another
vending machine?
[NISHIKATA]
Nah.
I'm thirsty, so I guess...
...I'll just go for this one.
Gross.
[laughs]
With a name like that, duh.
[NISHIKATA]
On any other day,
I'd completely
regret buying this.
But now I know for sure
that my new plan will work!
Hey, Takagi.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Say there's one juice
that's really tasty
but gives you a fever.
And another that's
just plain disgusting.
Which would you choose?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm...
[NISHIKATA]
"Two-Choice Question."
One juice that's really
tasty but gives you a fever
and another that's
just plain disgusting?
Hmm...
[NISHIKATA]
How's it feel?
You can't decide, can you?
Feel the unease!
I want to see
your face contorted
with conflicting emotions!
'Kay, question.
So if I drank the tasty juice
and got a fever.
Would you come and visit me
while I'm stuck at home?
What?
What's the point
in asking me that?
Does it affect your answer?
Significantly.
You wouldn't visit, then?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh.
Hey. I didn't say that.
Don't put words in my mouth.
If you were out sick,
then I'd visit you.
Then I'd take the tasty one.
[NISHIKATA]
Well, this is weird.
What's going on?
I expected her to be conflicted,
but she doesn't have
a care in the world.
Hold on.
I feel a little weird now.
Am I the loser here?
Has my "two-choice
question" plan failed?
No, it's still too
early to give up!
'Kay!
Next question!
[TAKAGI]
Okay.
No more allowance
for your whole life,
or no more teasing me ever?!
No allowance for life.
So quick!
I'd be fine.
I've been saving up
my New Year's money
and anything else I've
gotten for a while.
And once I'm in high school,
I'd just get a job.
Clearly, the better
choice is to keep teasing you.
[NISHIKATA growls]
I underestimated her!
I'll need a better
question than that.
Nishikata.
What?
Well, you've asked me
two weird questions in a row.
What's your angle?
Are you just trying
to give me a hard time?
Huh?
Not really.
Fine.
Then I'll ask you one, now.
Would you rather
that I disappear
or that you'd have to
be teased by me forever?
What'll you choose?
Huh?
What do you mean "disappear?"
Poof, I'm gone.
[NISHIKATA] I don't want to be
teased for the rest of my life
but for her to disappear?
That feels like a step too far.
I'd, uh, choose to be teased.
Thought so.
You do like being teased.
No, I don't!
Why would anyone like that?
It's just...
I don't exactly want you
to disappear either.
That would suck.
You want to be with me?
That it?
That's not...
[laughs]
Made you blush!
[NISHIKATA] Man, why does
she always have to do this?
Is it that fun to see me
uncomfortable?
I gotta come up with a good
question to get back at her.
Question two.
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? You're not done?
You get zeroes on all
tests for the rest of your life,
or you have kiss me.
Which is it?
A "kiss"?!
Gotta choose one.
I'd get a zero even
if I study well?
Yep.
It doesn't matter what you do.
[NISHIKATA]
I couldn't live with that!
My parents would take away
my allowance immediately,
and there's no way
I'd get into high school!
But if choose the kiss,
she's gonna make fun of me
like there's no tomorrow!
Hard decision, huh?
[NISHIKATA]
Man!
The more I struggle to choose,
the happier she gets!
I gotta choose quickly.
All zeroes for life is too much!
But!
I have no choice!
I'll pick not getting zeroes
on my tests.
Sorry, which option
was that again?
Th-The one with the kiss.
Ho, ho?
Is that so?
Okay, then.
[TAKAGI]
Aww, man.
Looks like you were right.
You are taller than me.
What's with that look?
I was just making sure.
[NISHIKATA sighs]
She's messed with me
so many times today.
But I have this
all figured out now.
One option has to be
something she'd never choose,
and the other just has to be
something I can
make fun of her for picking!
That way, I win no matter what!
Okay, Takagi. I got one--
All right, next question.
You have to go around the school
while doing a handstand,
or you and I--
[NISHIKATA]
Whoa, hold on a second!
I can't even do a hand stand,
that option doesn't work!
And when can I ask
the questions again?
[TAKAGI] As soon as you're done
answering my questions.
[NISHIKATA]
What? Why?