If you're ready, hold on tight.
Sure.
[NISHIKATA]
When we first started practicing
tandem riding, the hardest part
was Takagi holding on to me.
[gasps]
Don't tickle me; you're
gonna make us fall over!
I wasn't tickling you.
I just held on a little.
But if you thought I was,
your ribs are ticklish.
It's just because of how
your hands are touching them.
Change the way
you're holding on.
[TAKAGI]
How's this?
[gasps]
Don't you think
that's a bit too close?
No.
I'll fall if I'm not close.
Oh, come on.
Don't get self-conscious.
[gasps]
I'm not!
I'm just overheating when
you're right up against me,
it's already a
thousand degrees.
Anyway, just do me a favor
and don't grab on so tight.
But you literally told me to
hold on tight a minute ago.
All right, then.
Why don't you just show me how
you want me to hold onto you?
Hurry it up.
We're gonna run out
of time to practice.
Uh. I guess something
like this works?
[NISHIKATA] But now
we've overcome our hurdles!
And finally...
[TAKAGI laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
...we've mastered tandem riding.
Yeah.
Looks like we're done.
I mean, we wanted to learn
to ride together, and we did.
So there's no need
to practice anymore.
Uh. Mm-hmm.
Are you, by any chance,
like, kinda bummed?
Huh?! I dunno.
Relieved, then?
[NISHIKATA] It'd be rude to
say I'm relieved we're done,
but if I say I'm bummed out,
she's just gonna
tease me even more.
A little bit of both options.
Hey. No fair.
Well, what about you, huh?
What about me?
Well, I'd say
I'm not that bummed out.
Oh, cool.
[chuckles]
Tomorrow, let's finish up
our homework at the library.
Huh?
We can check each other's work.
Uh. Okay.
Vacation's ending. Real soon.
On the other hand,
our next term is starting.
Yeah.
I wonder when we're
actually getting that typhoon.
[NISHIKATA]
"Typhoon."
Oh man, it's so windy!
[NISHIKATA]
Whoa, that's really high!
This typhoon is crazy!
[laughs]
I don't know why,
but I feel really excited!
[laughs]
Now wind,
blow harder and harder!
[NISHIKATA]
Perfect timing!
I feel like I'm controlling
this huge gust!
So awesome!
Now, gale.
I command thee...!
[shrieks]
Morning, Nishikata.
Good morning, Takagi.
[TAKAGI] This wind is
really something, huh?
I probably should have
tied my hair back.
Uh. Yeah, I bet that
would have helped.
I was just checking
the direction of the wind.
You realize I didn't
ask what you were doing.
[NISHIKATA]
Come on!
Why does she always have to see
me at the worst possible times?
[TAKAGI]
So what were you doing?
I just said, I was checking
the direction of the wind.
Weird.
That's not what
it looked like to me.
[laughs]
"Now wind, blow
harder and harder!"
I could have sworn I heard that.
Me? No way, that would
just be ridiculous.
Watching someone else do it
makes me realize how
embarrassing it is.
So, why were you checking the
direction of the wind, then?
I just thought it'd
be good to know.
Given that the wind's so strong.
So I won't fall over!
Yeah?
But you had both hands
raised up so high.
Like, "Wow!
I feel like I'm controlling
this huge gust of wind!
So awesome!"
I'd bet that's what
you were thinking.
[NISHIKATA]
That's even more embarrassing.
By the way, do you
notice anything different?
You're not riding your bike?
That it?
Uh-huh.
Question is:
Why do you think
I'm not riding it today?
Because there's a typh--
If you guess right,
I'll keep quiet about your
little performance earlier.
I won't tell a soul.
[gasps]
We've been over this, I was
checking the wind's direction.
[TAKAGI] You have until that
plastic bag gets here.
Are you serious?
I have a time limit?
I have no choice
but to get this right.
She wouldn't be asking
such a simple question
if there wasn't a twist.
So I can rule out
anything obvious like,
"It's dangerous to ride
a bike in a typhoon."
[NISHIKATA]
Think. Think!
Some other problem that
a strong wind would cause.
Bike.
Wind.
[gasps]
Could it be her skirt?
Your... Your...
[NISHIKATA] I can't bring
myself to say that out loud!
It's too awkward!
And... you are out of time.
The correct answer is
that it's dangerous to
ride a bike in a typhoon.
Sorry!
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
What?
Seriously?
You read into things too much.
Okay.
Let's get going.
This wind is so strong.
Yeah.
Kinda gets you
excited, doesn't it?
Yeah. I mean, I don't really
know what you're talking about.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Come on.
Doesn't it make you
want to shout?
Raise your hands to the sky!
[laughs]
"Now wind,
blow harder and harder!"
[NISHKATA groans]
This sensation!
It's like I'm
controlling the storm!
[TAKAGI] I am the great
Wind King, ruler of this world!
I shall blow the school away
to the far ends of the earth!
[laughs]
Hey, I never went that far!
[gasps]
So you weren't just
checking the wind's direction.
Uh...
Well, whatever.
Huh?
Let's race to school!
Hurry up!
So strong!
[NISHIKATA]
Huh? Wait up, Takagi!
You always try
to get a head start!
For some reason, Takagi was
really energetic this morning.
[NISHIKATA]
"Marathon."
All right!
Let's do this!
How are you so full of energy?
I thought you hated marathons.
Nah.
I'm looking forward to it!
In fact, let's race, Sanae!
Okay.
How about if I win, you
don't get to eat any lunch?
Yeah.
Bring it on!
Wait. You sure?
You know Sanae is
really fast, don't you?
Yeah, but I'm in the zone!
Uh-huh...
[sighs]
What's the point of
running a marathon?
It's not like we're ever
gonna run this much
after we're finished
with school.
It doesn't make any sense.
So lame.
You said it, dude.
You look
enthusiastic, Nishikata.
[chuckles]
[TAKAGI]
Nishikata.
You sure you're up to this?
Ha! 'Course I am.
It was my idea to begin with.
'Kay.
See ya later!
You and Takagi
sure are close.
Huh?!
Are you going out with her?
What are you talking about?
Don't get the
wrong idea, Kimura!
I'm only competing with her
because the winner gets
to order the loser around!
Wait.
You're racing each
other in the marathon? But...
It's none of your business.
Judging by that reaction,
I wouldn't put money on
the two of them going out.
Yeah, I mean,
if they were going out...
Nakai! How are you feeling?
Pretty darn good!
And it's all thanks
to you training
with me every single day!
Let's destroy this marathon!
Yeah!
[KIMURA] They'd be acting
something like that.
[TANABE]
All right, gather 'round!
[sighs]
I'll never understand
why we have to do this.
Just accept it already, Kimura.
[NISHIKATA]
Empty your mind.
Run with an empty mind.
Calm yourself and avoid
wasting unnecessary energy.
[NISHIKATA]
I've got you this time, Takagi.
I've jogged every evening
for over two weeks
just for this day!
[NISHIKATA]
Come rain.
Come wind!
There's no way I'm gonna
lose after all that prep.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh! Empty your mind.
Empty your mind.
Hey, Nishikata!
I figured you would have
sprinted way ahead of the pack.
Oh yeah?
Sorry, but pacing
yourself is the key.
But clearly you don't get it.
You look unfazed, but you sped
up because you couldn't see me
ahead of you
and panicked, right?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
I was running slow until now
because I wanted to
give you a handicap.
Handicap?
Wait, did she just read my mind?
Well, I'm going on ahead.
Huh?
[MINA groans]
I can't have lunch.
And I'm already so hungry.
I started out too fast.
[NISHIKATA]
That's right.
You'll see, Takagi.
If you keep running that fast,
you're gonna lose
your pace just like her!
And all I have to do
is keep up my pace.
[NISHIKATA]
Wait.
But what if Takagi is actually
good at running marathons?
If she is, I'm screwed!
[NISHIKATA] I don't have
the time to empty my mind!
Is she already running back?
She's that much
faster than the boys?
I lost my pace, but I caught up.
If you manage to touch me,
then you can be the winner.
[NISHIKATA] I can't touch her
in front of all these people!
Who knows what they'd
think was going on?
Takagi, you sneaky little...
You deliberately
made me lose my pace!
Ugh...
[NISHIKATA]
Takagi.
I'll give you a different
win condition, too.
If you can run 50 meters ahead
of me, the crown is yours!
You mean that?
[NISHIKATA]
Hook, line, and sinker!
I hope you're ready!
Because I'm gonna
destroy your pace this time!
You're finished!
Cool!
I win, then.
All the girls are supposed
to turn back here.
Good luck!
You boys still need
to run two more kilometers.
[NISHIKATA]
Oh, that is so not fair, Takagi!
[TAKAGI] That's why
I asked if you were sure!
We're recording your time
Nishikata; don't stop running!
What'd I say?
Your sides start to hurt
and you get hungry.
As far as I'm concerned,
absolutely nothing positive
comes from running a marathon.
If you used all that energy
to run instead of complaining,
you might be able
to go a little faster.
Why would I do
something so pointless?
You really think running is
more pointless than complaining?
I just wanna eat lunch.
[KIMURA]
I'm hungry too.
[MINA]
I'm starving.
[NISHIKATA]
"Ribs."
[NISHIKATA] Takagi messed
with me a ton today.
Again.
Man.
You'll get yours.
What's up?
Stop staring.
[NISHIKATA laughs]
I can't get over that.
You have such ticklish ribs!
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA] She does this every
time there's an opportunity.
Yeah, sure,
my ribs are ticklish.
But aren't everybody's?
I'm not special.
[gasps]
Hey, Takagi.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Wanna make a bet?
I'm thinking whichever one
of us laughs first is the loser.
Yeah, why not?
If it's all the same to you,
I'd like to start right now.
Okay.
[NISHIKATA]
I've got you now!
You have no idea what
I've got in store, do you?
Looks like both your hands
are occupied holding your bike.
Too bad.
You're at a disadvantage.
If you think you
can protect your ribs
with only your elbows you've
got another thing coming!
Oh. By the way,
so you know, my ribs
happen to not be ticklish.
[TAKAGI]
Made you look!
Wow. No laugh?
[NISHIKATA]
That was too close for comfort.
And did she say
she's not ticklish?
That's a bluff
if I've ever heard one.
She's wide open!
Then could she be
telling the truth?
No.
My best option remaining
is to just go for it
and find out that way.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
All good. It's, uh, nothing.
[NISHIKATA]
This is kinda embarrassing.
Should I really
touch her like that?
Wouldn't it be
sexual harassment?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Better hurry up,
or I'll get you again.
Huh?!
[NISHIKATA]
What the heck?
I thought I had the
perfect plan all worked out.
How did I not realize it
had such a pitfall!
It's too risky
to go through with.
I'll keep my distance and
maybe this can end in a draw.
Hey.
[laughs]
That face isn't fair!
I win.
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA] I'm really
dropping the ball today.
I can't believe
I forgot that Takagi makes
such good funny faces.
Well then, what should
I make you do this time?
[NISHIKATA] Huh?
There's a penalty for the loser?
You said, "Wanna make a bet."
Of course there is!
Now, let's see...
You can't eat rice
for the rest of your life.
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
That's brutal!
[TAKAGI]
Don't worry, I'm just kidding.
[TAKAGI] You can't read
100% Unrequited Love.
Huh?
[TAKAGI]
That's pretty cruel, too.
Well how about this, then?
You have to poke my ribs.
Uh?
Uhh. Wait, that's my punishment?
[TAKAGI]
Mm-hmm.
Okay, then.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
[NISHIKATA]
That's it!
I see what's goin' on here!
She wants to enjoy me
getting embarrassed
and struggling to touch her.
Not on my watch!
Come to think of it.
This might actually be the first
time I've ever touched her.
Anywhere but her shoulder,
I mean.
No, don't think about it.
You're just poking her!
It's not a big deal!
You okay?
See?
Told you.
My ribs aren't ticklish
in the slightest.
Yeah.
My armpits are
pretty ticklish, though.
[shrieks]
[NISHIKATA] I definitely
can't touch her there!
[SANAE]
"Regret."
[screams]
I totally forgot!
About?
This is absolutely terrible!
What's terrible?
We didn't do our test of
courage over the summer--ah...
Oh yeah, I guess we didn't.
Let's do it today after school!
We just gotta!
Uh, I guess that's okay.
[shrieks]
You feel that?
It's so haunted!
Ooooh...
Are we really going in there?
[MINA, SANAE]
Yes!
They're too excited for
this to be a test of courage.
[laughs]
It's so dark!
[SANAE]
Uh-huh.
Oh!
A hole!
Oooh.
Huh? A paper talisman!
For the spirits!
Yeah.
Look at that!
What's a steel barrel
doing in here?
Uhh?
This isn't scary at all.
What? No.
It's super scary!
Yeah, no.
[MINA]
Whoa, look!
I found a Frisbee!
Lucky!
That's weird to
find this deep in.
It's kinda chilly in here!
You think it's a ghost?
No, we're just out of the sun
and the wind is blowing through.
[MINA screams]
This is so fun!
[SANAE]
Oooo!
[MINA laughs]
Whaddya doing; don't chase me!
Are you happy we did it?
[MINA]
Mm-hmm.
It was such a classic summer
vacation adventure!
Sure, whatever that means.
But it sucks.
Summer vacation isn't
coming back any time soon.
[SANAE]
Yeah.
[YUKARI] I'm not used to you
being so bummed out Mina.
Talk about a downer.