[NISHIKATA chuckles]
[TANABE]
So here, we say,
"I am Hanako."
As opposed to here,
where we say, "He is a teacher."
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Stop accusing me, Takagi.
I'm learning.
I swear.
[TAKAGI]
Right.
[NISHIKATA]
"Eraser."
This'll work well as a spring.
[NISHIKATA]
Now I have all the pieces I need
to make my desktop
jack-in-the-box!
[NISHIKATA]
Just you wait, Takagi.
Huh?
Hey. What's goin' on?
I'm not sure.
My pencil case just won't open.
Maybe it got dented
when I dropped it earlier.
Do you think you could
try opening it, Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Uh.
Yeah, sure.
You must have loosened
it or somethi--
[shrieks]
What is it, Nishikata?
Huh? Oh, it was nothing.
I'm sorry for shouting.
[TAKAGI laughs]
[TAKAGI]
Seriously, Nishikata,
you should see your face.
Ugh.
Just shut up.
[laughs]
You suck.
She totally got me.
And worse, she got me with what
I was about to get her with!
[NISHIKATA]
Now that I think about it,
it's unusual for Takagi
to ask me for help.
Why didn't that raise
any red flags in my mind?
I have to plan my next move.
But how am I supposed to
embarrass her of all people?
Hey.
Uh.
What's up?
Can I borrow your eraser?
I forgot mine.
How did you forgot your eraser?
Takagi, you're such
an airhead sometimes
Guess so.
Thank you very much.
That reminds me.
[NISHIKATA]
Hmm?
Know what I heard?
If you take your eraser,
write the name of your crush
on it, and use it all up,
they'll like you back.
Yeah, I've heard
that before too.
Only a little kid would
actually believe it, though.
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
A kid, huh?
Huuh...?
[TAKAGI]
Hmm?
Ahh.
Huh?!
What do you see?
Huuuh?
Huh? Ohh...
Wha...
What are you doing?
[laughs]
Nothing's written
on there, right?
C'mon.
I'm not some dumb little kid
who'd believe that works.
Oho? You sure about that?
There's no way.
You're just making fun
of me again, aren't you?
Yeah?
You think so?
[NISHIKATA]
Did I actually?
Did I actually write
something on there?
And then just forget that I did?
You're done with it,
so can you give it back now?
[TAKAGI]
Sure.
It wasn't me, I swear!
Someone else must have gotten
a hold of it and then...
I knew there was nothing
written on that thing!
Hey!
You didn't forget your eraser,
it's right there!
No yelling in class.
I'm sorry, sir.
[TAKAGI laughs]
Not only did you freak out,
but you got in trouble!
I think that's enough
messing around for one class.
I should be the one saying that!
[TAKAGI]
Mr. Tanabe?
May I go to the bathroom?
[TANABE]
Fine.
[NISHIKATA]
There's gotta be something.
Something I can do
to embarrass her.
Anything!
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
That's it!
I'll write someone's name on
Takagi's eraser and make fun
of her for it when she comes
back from the bathroom!
Genius!
Just one question:
Whose name should I write?
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
There's a name on it already?
Should I not look, then?
Maybe just a tiny peak.
[NISHIKATA]
"Lo"? "Lo"?
Then that means...
[NISHIKATA]
...it's not my name.
[NISHIKATA] Not that I'm,
like, upset or anything.
[NISHIKATA]
Come on!
I'm gonna look at it!
I have to know!
[NISHIKATA]
I can't believe it!
She got me again!
[TAKAGI] Nishikata,
that face was priceless.
And man, you acted
exactly how I thought.
I just have to tease you.
I can't help it.
Oh yeah?
Well just you wait, Takagi!
Mark my words, one of these
days I'm gonna get back at you
and embarrass you so bad!
Like that'll ever happen.
[NISHIKATA] You don't
think I can do it, huh?
[TAKAGI]
Well, yeah.
[NISHIKATA]
I'm serious!
You better be on your guard.
I think it's impossible.
But keep dreaming.
You can't even win
fifty-percent odds.
[NISHIKATA]
"Fifty-percent odds"?
Whaddya mean?
[TAKAGI]
Not telling.
Man, day duty is
such a pain in the butt.
[yawns]
Why do I have
to go to school early
to clean the blackboard
and write a lesson log?
I take it back,
day duty's awesome!
I guess what they say is true.
The early bird gets the worm!
I thought this was money,
not some stupid arcade token.
[NISHIKATA]
"Day Duty."
I just got a great idea!
I should use this opportunity
to rig Takagi's desk
with some kinda prank.
Just thinking about it
woke me up a little.
Ta...
[moans]
My plan is ruined,
she's already here.
Wait, why?
I don't see anyone here.
That's weird.
Did I just imagine
it or something?
[NISHIKATA]
No, she's definitely here!
My Takagi-sense is tingling!
But where is she hiding?
[NISHIKATA]
And that was a close one.
I was about to let my guard
down and start humming.
But not today!
Where are you?
Show yourself.
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA] You're making
this too easy, Takagi.
I can see the name on
your shoes under the desk.
You're probably
planning to surprise me
when I go up to
clean the blackboard.
But I won't give you the chance.
Ahh...
Day duty is such a pain, I don't
feel like doing anything!
Not like anyone will notice if
I don't clean the board anyway.
[NISHIKATA]
Ooo, stings, doesn't it?
You must be mortified that this
silly plan of yours didn't work.
[NISHIKATA]
I can hardly contain myself!
I wanna see the look
on her face so bad.
But wait...
Would Takagi really make
such an amateur mistake?
This is hide-and-seek 101!
No!
She wouldn't!
Which means that's a trap!
That was close.
She's devilish, that one.
Gotta stay on my toes.
So if she's not there,
where is she?
She's gotta be nearby.
She wouldn't miss
the opportunity.
[NISHIKATA]
I don't see her in the hallway,
so there's only one place left.
[NISHIKATA]
Welp!
I guess I'll go to the bathroom!
Now pretend I'm not here.
I got you!
[NISHIKATA]
What?
She's not there!
Huh?
[NISHIKATA]
Well that was a waste of time.
What the heck was I doing?
Hey!
[gasps]
[laughs]
Are you okay?
Come on!
I didn't look
behind the curtain?
Totally fooled you, didn't I?
If you're up real close,
you can see through the curtain,
so I saw you the whole time.
[NISHIKATA]
Not fair!
She looks so happy!
This sucks!
[TAKAGI]
Ahh, that was fun.
Just thinking about the look
on your face makes me wanna...
[laughs]
This was worth
waking up early for.
[NISHIKATA]
Just to mess with me?
Yup!
[NISHIKATA] I can't
believe she got me again.
[TAKAGI]
Hey, Nishikata.
Huh?
Know what?
It's just the two of us
in this quiet classroom.
Doesn't it feel like we're
the only ones in the world?
I think it does,
and I hope it stays this way.
Then, uhh, Takagi?
Does that mean that you,
maybe, like, like...
Good morning everyone!
How about this
weather am I right?
[YUKARI]
Jeez.
I'll never understand
how you feel so energetic
in the morning, Mina.
[MINA] Huh? And how else am I
supposed to feel, smarty-pants?
[SANAE]
Tired?
[MINA]
You too, Sanae?
Saying you're tired makes
your happiness go away!
I saw it on TV!
Not everything on TV is true.
You can't actually believe that.
[MINA]
Well, I do!
It's better to be
cheerful anywa--
Stop it.
[MINA]
Ow, ow, ow.
That hurts, can you like, not?
Just leave her alone.
[MINA] You two would
feel better if you smiled!
See?
Ignore them.
You were saying?
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
It was nothing.
Forget it.
Huuuuh?
Speaking of forgetting things.
Did you clean the board?
Ahh! I forgot!
[laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
"Funny Face."
[NISHIKATA] How am I gonna
pull one over on Takagi?
What am I gonna do?
Think!
[NAKAI]
Hey, Nishikata.
What are you staring
at the mirror for?
Oh, hey, Nakai.
You practicin' putting on
a cool face or somethin'?
No, that's lame.
A funny face, then?
[gasps]
[NISHIKATA]
Of course. That's it!
So like this?
By the way, I've been
meaning to ask you something.
You're pretty close
with Takagi, aren't you?
So I was wonderin',
like, you into her?
[NISHIKATA snickers]
Well, he's clearly ignoring me,
which means I must
be on the right track.
Yo, dude.
You totally like
Takagi, don't you?
[laughs]
That face was so weird, man!
[NISHIKATA]
I had no idea I had
such talent lying
dormant within me.
Okay, everyone settle
down, let's get to work.
Open your books to page 36.
[NISHIKATA]
This is perfect!
We just so happen to
have the scariest teacher,
Mr. Tanabe, right now!
I'll use my funny face to
make you laugh so hard,
you'll get in deep
trouble, Takagi!
[chuckles]
[NISHIKATA] Oh man, I
wanna make Takagi laugh now.
No. I have to be patient.
I have to wait until she starts
a conversation to mess with me,
like I planned.
The best moment to mess
with someone is when
they're about to mess
with someone, themselves.
They'll never expect it then!
And that's when I strike!
All right, girl, come at me.
I'm wide open!
Hey, uhh, Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Here it is!
Whatever do you need, Takagi?
[NISHIKATA]
Take this!
Huh?
[TAKAGI]
Hmmm...
[NISHIKATA]
Huh?
[NISHIKATA laughs]
Hey.
How many times do I have
to tell you to be quiet?
I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
[NISHIKATA]
He's so scary.
[TAKAGI laughs]
[NISHIKATA]
This sucks!
I wasn't sure what you
were trying to do at first,
but now, I get it.
You're not very creative.
Wha?
If you really wanna be funny.
You should push
your eyebrows up, like this.
Oh, and do this
with your cheeks, too.
So like this?
[TAKAGI]
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, you're getting there.
Honestly, it's looking better
than before already.
[NISHIKATA]
What is happening?
Now stick your lips
out like a duck bill.
That'll be super funny.
[NISHIKATA] I wanted to make
a silly face to make her laugh.
And now I'm getting pointers
on how to do it from my target.
It's kind of humiliating.
Whatever!
All I want is for Takagi
to laugh and get in trouble!
I couldn't care less who
helps me make that happen!
Like this?
Yeah, that's perfect!
It looks way better now!
[NISHIKATA]
Okay.
Then why aren't
you laughing yet?
I'll laugh really hard
if you turn to your
left right now.
[NISHIKATA]
All right.
This is the moment.
Here we go!
What are you doing, Nishikata?
[NISHIKATA]
Sorry!
I'm really sorry, sir!
[TANABE]
Always with the antics.
Take my class
seriously, will you?
I will.
And sorry again.
[TAKAGI laughs]
My stomach hurts from laughing!
[NISHIKATA] I guess I
technically got her to laugh,
like I wanted.
But she won that round.
Hey. Hey, Nishikata.
[NISHIKATA] Okay,
that's enough playing around.
If I make Mr. Tanabe
angry again, he'll kill me!
I gotta make sure
I don't get involved
with Takagi for
the rest of this class.
You finally decided
to look at me.
We should totally
have a staring contest.
One. Two. Three.
[NISHIKATA laughs]
That face is so weird!
[TANABE]
Nishikata!
What did I say?
[NISHIKATA] Whenever Takagi
gets my heart racing,
things don't play out
the way I want them to.
[MINA]
"One Hundred Yen."
Ugh.
I'm exhausted, yet again.
What did I say?
Don't say you're tired,
it'll make things worse!
It takes your happiness away!
Yeah, whatever.
[gasps]
What's up?
Are you doing okay?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
You two go on ahead.
Why?
I'm just feeling
a little tired, is all.
By your rules,
there goes your happiness.
Huh?
[chuckles]
Yeah, guess you're right.
Mina.
Care to tell us what you're
hiding under your foot?
Whatever do you mean?
I always stand like this.
Wait, no fair!
I found that hundred yen!
What happened
to finders keepers?
You are so greedy.
[SANAE]
Mina.
Come on.
It's a token.
[sighs]
It must have turned into
that when I said I was tired.
I told you it was real.
[YUKARI sighs]
You know that's not
how the world works.