Kakyoin: Have your injuries
improved any, avdol?
Avdol: They have.
As relieved as I am,
i’m even more relieved
knowing you’re all right.
Kakyoin: Yes,
well, i’m fortunate
there was no significant damage
to my cornea.
I’m expected
to make a full recovery.
This takes me back
to middle school.
During what should have
been an ordinary game,
one of my classmates
took a baseball to the eye.
He was good as new the next day,
and as it turned out, his eye
had only lost a bit of fluid.
Polnareff: Wait.
Are you serious?
Joseph: No!
Kakyoin: I’ll get
these bandages off in no time,
and i’ll catch up with you
in a few days.
In 800 kilometers
are Cairo and dio.
Everyone,
you must remain vigilant.
Polnareff: Now let’s see.
What kind of language
is this hospital bill
written in, anyway?
I guess
it’s supposed to be arabic,
but, man,
if this crap isn’t confusing.
The zero is a five,
the decimal is a zero,
and the seven is a six.
And what the heck
is this wormy-looking
thingamajig supposed to be?
Avdol: It’s a four,
so the amount we owe is--
polnareff:
46,350 Egyptian pounds?!
That’s insane!
- ( Women cooing, squealing )
- Woman: How adorable!
Woman #2: What kind
of dog is he?
Woman #3: He’s so funny-looking.
Woman #4: Look at that. Why in
the world is he chewing gum?
He must be waiting for someone.
Woman #1:
Such a good little doggie.
Avdol: And here I thought
iggy was waiting for us outside.
Jotaro: Good grief.
Polnareff: Looks like he’s
a hit with the ladies.
Woman #2: Should we tell him
doggies don’t usually chew gum?
Woman #4:
What a peculiar little puppy.
Polnareff: Hello there, ladies.
Women: Hmm?
Polnareff: Here’s a little bit
of friendly advice
for you girls.
Step away if you know
what’s good for you.
I know he comes across
as a charming fur ball at first,
but deep in his soul, he harbors
an extreme hatred for people.
If you’re not careful,
- when you least expect--
- ( Iggy growls )
( Polnareff screams )
What the hell are you doing?!
Get off of me, you damn mutt!
( Gags )
( Women laughing )
Woman #2: Such a cutie!
Woman #2:
Aww. You get along so well.
Polnareff: In your dreams!
We don’t get along at all!
Damn it, iggy! Would you
get the hell off of me?!
Joseph: We’ll catch
you guys later.
See you, lovebirds.
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar,
please help me!
Hey, hang on a minute,
would you?!
( Iggy farts )
Polnareff: What the hell?!
You nasty little mutt!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: In ancient times,
Egyptians were in the habit
of burying their dead
on the west bank of the nile,
where the sun sets.
That’s the reason
Egyptian cities
stand on the east side
of the nile.
On the West Side, however,
you’re likely to find graves
and mortuary temples
scattered about.
But our enemies don’t care
about east or west.
They’ll come from whatever
direction is most advantageous.
Man: Look, I know you
didn’t ask for my opinion,
but your cows
are far too lethargic.
Although, they’re strong.
I’ll give ’em that.
( Man #2 chuckles )
Man #3: Hey, chaka,
move your ass, boy!
And would you stop
dragging the rear already?!
( Chaka groans )
Man #3: What a disgrace.
Some man you are.
How are you my son?
( Man #2 laughs )
Looks like your son
and your cow
have something in common.
( Men laugh )
Chaka: Uh...
( Chorus vocalizing )
A sword?
What’s something like this
doing out here?
Man #1: Hey, look! It’s a sword!
Father: Give me that!
Look at that.
Must have been dropped.
Man #2: I can’t believe
no one’s come back to claim it.
Father: Their loss is our gain,
’cause this sword
is probably worth a fortune.
Man #1: Hey, what if the owner’s
still in the area?
Poor guy must be panicking
right about now.
Man #2: On the off chance
it’s some kind
of fancy-schmancy artifact,
shouldn’t we give it
to the police?
Father: You idiot, this sword
could be the end of all of
our money troubles! ( Laughs )
Chaka: But i’m the one
who found it.
Man #2: It won’t be worth
a damn thing if it’s blunt.
Pull it out
so we can take a look.
Father: Right!
( Grunting )
Man #2: What’s wrong?
Father: The damn thing
won’t budge.
Why the hell won’t it come out?
Man #1: That’s weird.
Let me try it.
Father: Take it.
Man #1: You hold this end.
Man #2: Right.
( Men grunting )
Man #1: It’s no use.
The blade hasn’t moved
a single centimeter.
Chaka: Father, let me have a go.
Father: Ah, shut up!
If I can’t free it,
what chance does an idiot
like you have?!
- ( Man #1 yelps )
- Father: Huh?!
Man #1: M-my hand!
What happened to my hand?!
( Screams )
My hand,
why is it spewing blood?!
( Wails )
How the hell
did the sword cut me?!
We pulled on the damn thing,
but the blade wouldn’t come out.
All I did
was grab it by the hilt!
Man #2: There’s something
strange about that sword.
Chaka: Hey, uh, you think
now’s a good time for me to try?
Father: You know what?! Fine!
Go ahead,
and try it if you want!
♪
( Men gasp )
Chaka: It came out so easy.
I didn’t put the slightest bit
of effort into it.
( Soft ringing )
What? I can hear it.
This makes no sense.
I can hear the blade ringing.
Man #2:
I’m by no means an expert
when it comes to swords
or things of that nature,
but I don’t think
i’ve ever encountered
a blade this beautiful.
It’s like
a rare Japanese katana.
It glistens, like it’s
cloaked in ice-cold water.
Father: We’ve been graced
with an amazing discovery!
Hand it over, my boy!
A dolt like you has no business
wielding
such a valuable treasure!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Men gasp )
( Chaka wails )
Father: Oh, god!
Chaka, why?
Why would you do this
to your own father?!
Chaka: I don’t
know what happened!
- You were standing behind me...
- ( Father screaming )
Chaka: And before
I knew it, the sword--
it’s not my fault, I swear!
Man #2: Why are you
just standing there?!
We have to hurry and get him to
a doctor before it’s too late!
( Yelps )
( Man #1 screams )
This sword is evil!
It’s almost as though the blade
has a mind of its own!
( Chaka gasps )
( Sword ringing )
Sword: Be calm.
Still your heart, chaka.
Their deaths mean nothing,
nothing whatsoever, chaka.
Chaka: Just--just who are you?
I can’t see you,
but I can hear your voice.
Anubis: I am the stand
of the god Anubis,
ruler of the underworld,
deity of embalming,
and lord of the dead.
- You have unsheathed me.
- Anubis also: You are my flesh!
- Thus you
shall be my stand user.
- You are a virtuoso.
- So I shall make you
master of the sword.
- No one in the world
is stronger than you.
- You shall wield me,
and you shall kill!
- Kill, kill, kill...
Chaka: Father and that man
deserved to die,
so they should be thrilled
that I killed them.
I think i’ll hack you to pieces
while i’m on a roll.
Man #1: Wait a minute, chaka!
You don’t really wanna do this!
Please let me live, okay?!
I don’t wanna die!
( Chaka yells )
( Man #1 gags )
How the hell did he do that?!
Somehow the cow’s
completely unharmed.
- ( Gags )
- ( Cow moos )
♪
( Chaka chuckles )
Anubis: Slaughter Joseph.
Slice polnareff.
Cleave jotaro in two.
You are a fighting genius,
a master of the sword.
No one in the world is a match
for your blade, no one!
( Chaka chuckles )
Polnareff: Kom ombo? Come on.
Do we really have time
to lounge around in this place?
Joseph: Would you
quit complaining?
Avdol: They’ve been kind enough
to allow us passage
on their ferry,
so we must show our respect.
( Polnareff sighs )
I don’t know about you guys,
but i’m starving,
so let’s get something to eat.
Joseph: Wow,
you never stop, do you?
Here. This should
tide you over for now.
( Polnareff groans ) You know
damn well that’s iggy’s!
Joseph: Would you
just take the gum, already?
Hey, where’s the bathroom, huh?
Avdol: Shall we look for it?
( Polnareff growls )
Man: Hey, mister, over here!
Vendor: Wanna buy some papyrus?
Polnareff: Huh?
Vendor: This papyrus
is the original paper.
Want a piece
of Egyptian history?
Here. Take a look.
This is 100% bona fide papyrus!
Polnareff: Papyrus, huh?
Vendor: I’ll give you
a good price.
Polnareff: Are you positive
this is the real thing?
Vendor: Of course, my friend.
I’ll have you know a famous
Egyptian craftsman drew this,
- so it’s quite genuine.
- Polnareff: Hmm.
- ( Vendor screams )
- Polnareff: This crap is fake,
- and you know it.
- ( Vendor whimpering )
Polnareff: If this
were actual papyrus,
it wouldn’t rip so easily.
I’m no fool.
You should try
a little harder next time.
What the--for the love of--
where’d Mr. Joestar
and the others go?
- ( Iggy pants )
- Polnareff: Huh?
♪
( Polnareff gasps )
( Iggy grunts, barks )
Polnareff: Was that iggy?!
Why you--get back here,
you little mutt!
Vendor: Hey!
What about my money?!
Polnareff: Stupid dog.
He managed to get away.
♪
Gotta say,
if my hunch is correct,
then you’ve got
a lot of balls, my friend.
Seems like you’re
planning to attack me
while we’re in a crowd
of innocent bystanders.
Guys like you are a rare breed.
Stand users
don’t usually show themselves,
let alone face
their attacker head-on.
It’s kind of noble.
I didn’t think
you guys had that trait.
Tell me your name.
Chaka: My name is chaka,
and my stand is known as Anubis,
the one true ruler
of the underworld.
Now then, Jean Pierre polnareff,
prepare to surrender
your life to me.
( Polnareff laughs )
You want me
to surrender my life?
Man, oh, man, you sure don’t
mince words, do you, chaka?
If nothing else, your confidence
is more impressive
than your other companions.
♪
Give me your best shot.
Let’s see if your Anubis stand
is all it’s cracked up to be.
Come out, chariot.
He’s brandishing his sword,
but is he really planning
to fight me with that
instead of his stand?
♪
Something’s off.
His movements,
his grip, his stance,
they’re the dead giveaways
of an amateur,
but that doesn’t make sense.
I need to keep
my distance from him.
( Gasps )
( Winces )
( Screams )
( Polnareff screams )
What the hell is going on here?
His sword passed
right through the pillar,
and if that wasn’t enough,
he cut me without leaving even
a single tear in my shirt.
If I hadn’t stepped back when
I did, I would have been killed.
You bastard! Chariot!
( Roars ) Damn it!
Why don’t you show yourself
and face me like
a real fighter, you coward?!
( Gasps ) Huh?
( Gasping )
♪
Merde.
This can’t be happening.
I lost him.
He could be hiding
behind any one of these pillars.
Judging from his attacks,
his sword can pass
through solid objects.
And unfortunately for me,
my chariot’s striking range
is only about one meter.
Damn it. He’s tougher
than I thought he’d be.
I honestly can’t believe
this asshole
is actually giving me a run
for my money in a sword fight.
But Mark my words.
You won’t have
the upper hand for long.
Hey, chaka, are you listening?!
I’ve got a nice view,
so let’s see what you’ve got!
There’s no way
you can sneak up on me
if i’m not behind a pillar,
unless you’re planning
on popping out of the ground.
( Laughs )
( Chaka laughs )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Chaka laughing )
What the--
he’s behind the pillar?!
Chaka: My sword doesn’t need
to pass through objects!
With the power of this blade,
I can cut
through the pillar itself!
Now die, polnareff!
( Gags )
Polnareff:
Man, that was a close one.
That technique is so secret that
not even jotaro knows about it.
Silver chariot
can launch its rapier.
The downside
is I only get one shot.
If my opponent dodges,
i’m history.
A last resort once i’ve
exhausted my other options.
While it’s true
I didn’t kill you,
I highly doubt you’ll be getting
back up for another round.
Hmm?
( Gasps ) That’s peculiar.
How the heck did it get
back into its scabbard?
Did it slip in by chance?
( Gasping )
( Chorus vocalizing )
I didn’t notice before,
but now that I see it up close,
I fully appreciate
the sword’s beauty.
I have to unsheathe it.
- ( Iggy barks )
- Polnareff: Huh?
Jotaro: Hey, there, polnareff.
Thought we’d lost you.
Joseph: We were worried when you
up and vanished by yourself.
We thought you’d
been ambushed by the enemy.
( Iggy barks )
( Polnareff groans )
Joseph: Wait. Are you okay?
- Polnareff: Huh?
- ( Iggy barking )
Polnareff: Oh. Oh!
It’s you, Mr. Joestar.
I’m so fuzzy,
I can’t think straight.
Maybe it’s
from being tossed around
or my injuries
are worse than I thought.
( Iggy growling )
Joseph: Polnareff, why are
you squatting like that?
You didn’t step in poop,
did you?
Jotaro: Huh?
Avdol: Polnareff, how did you
come across that sword?
Did something happen out here?
Polnareff: Yeah.
I had a showdown with
some dirtbag that attacked me.
Joseph: What?
An enemy stand user?!
Polnareff: It’s all over now.
He said his stand
was known as the god Anubis.
It was able to literally phase
through objects and cut them
once it had a target
in its crosshairs.
He was a strong foe.
Narrator: "But despite
his formidable power,
"when all was said and done,
he was no match
for the likes of me,"
polnareff reassured himself.
Polnareff: He was using
this sword as his weap--
- where did it go?
- ( Rats squeaking )
Where’d those rats come from,
and why are they
making off with the sword?!
Get outta here!
Jeez, talk about creepy.
No one told me even the rats
steal stuff in this place.
If you guys wanna steal
something, steal some cheese.
( Grunting )
That’s unusual.
The sword’s stuck
in the scabbard.
It’s jammed in here
really tight.
Joseph: Hey, polnareff,
while i’m relieved
that you’re all right,
don’t ever run off
by yourself again.
Got it? It’s dangerous.
Avdol: The enemy
will find a way to attack you
even if you’re just alone
for a few seconds.
- ( Iggy growling )
- ( Ferry horn blows )
Joseph: Oh, crap, I forgot.
That’s the sound of our ship
taking off without us.
We need to hurry
and get onboard.
We’re heading to edfu today.
Wha--c-come on, guys.
Wait for me!
( Overlapping chatter )
Jotaro: Polnareff,
so you decided
to bring the sword
with you after all?
Polnareff: Yeah. I’m gonna
turn it in to the police.
This thing is
a dangerous weapon, you know.
Joseph: Hmm. That’s a good plan.
Anyone could pick it up
at those ruins,
- so we can’t take any chances.
- ( Iggy growling )
Avdol: It’s probably
worth a small fortune.
( Iggy barks )
- Polnareff: Huh?
- Jotaro: Hmm?
( Iggy growling )
Avdol: Quiet, iggy.
You can’t make noise in here.
Joseph: If you keep this up,
we could get kicked out.
( Iggy barks )
Polnareff: What the hell
is wrong with that mutt, today?
Ah, well, since the damn dog
won’t shut up,
I guess i’ll just take the sword
to the cops now.
Avdol: Polnareff,
weren’t you listening
when we told you
not to go off on your own?
Joseph: Seriously,
we talked about this earlier.
Jotaro, tag along, and keep him
out of trouble, would you?
Jotaro: Gotcha.
( Iggy growling )
( Polnareff humming a tune )
Jotaro: Hey,
shouldn’t our first stop
have been the police station?
( Polnareff laughs )
Oh, take it easy, jotaro.
Barber: A man’s got to look
his absolute best,
as the saying goes.
Polnareff: Oh, before I forget,
old man, you mind putting this
over there out of the way?
Barber: Sure.
Polnareff: That thing’s
a dangerous weapon.
All right,
back to what I saying earlier.
I did a fair amount
of rolling around
and ended up
getting kinda dirty.
Make this face gorgeous again,
Mr. Barber.
Barber: Will do.
Polnareff: Ow! Ow!
Hey, would you watch it?!
In case you haven’t noticed,
that razor’s dull!
Come on, Mr. Barber!
Sharpen that thing!
This is supposed to be
the most relaxing part
of the haircut!
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
You’re such a prima Donna.
Barber: You’re right, sir.
My apologies.
♪
( Razor scraping )
( Footsteps )
Polnareff: Mmm.
( Chuckles )
( Blade scrapes )
Oh. Mm, better.
Much better.
Now that’s a shave, Mr. Barber.
That’s what i’m talking about.
Barber: Thank you.
I’m glad to hear it.
Polnareff: Tres bien, barber.
Tres bien, man!
And now if you wouldn’t mind
getting under my chin.
Barber: Sure.
Right here...
Under your chin, yes?
Polnareff: Mm? Huh?
( Gasps )
♪
Barber: You did say under
your chin, right, polnareff?!
Polnareff: What the hell?!
( Barber slurps )
Remember me, you fool?
I’m the Anubis stand,
and this time,
you’re going to die!
♪