Joseph: They’re about
to exit the tunnel!
No! Not good!
D’arby’s ahead
and by a full car length!
D’arby: Our speed is
about to be doubled.
It looks like I win!
kakyoin: No!
The fact of the matter
is I still have more speed
than you, d’arby.
( D’arby gasps )
Kakyoin: You’re in for it now.
( Joseph yells )
I can’t believe what i’m seeing!
Kakyoin had enough power
to spin his car around
and knock d’arby’s car
clear off the racetrack!
He used his speed
to his advantage.
( D’arby gasps )
Joseph: He’s out of there!
And kakyoin’s car
is safely on the ground.
You did it!
Kakyoin: The weaker car
loses in a collision.
Giving up power to ram me
will prove to be
a costly mistake.
Instead of gloating,
you should have
paid more attention
to my plan to stay behind
and knock you off course
with a spin attack.
D’arby: So you say,
though the same
could also be said of you.
( Kakyoin gasps )
D’arby: Losing power
was not an accident.
You’re so self-righteous.
In your hubris,
you didn’t realize
i planned for you
to knock my car off course.
( Kakyoin gasps )
d’arby:
Everything rests on this.
Look closely. Do you see
where my car is headed?
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- Joseph: Ohh!
Kakyoin: What?
Joseph: He landed
on the other side,
farther ahead, at that.
Kakyoin: Impossible.
D’arby: Yes, ordinarily.
Even at one’s top speed,
a move like the one I just did
usually would result
in a crash.
You wouldn’t make it
by jumping over the curves,
but it’s
another story completely
if you’re catapulted over them.
All I needed was your help.
From the moment
we left the tunnel,
my plan was to get you to hit me
by sacrificing my power.
That said, I think it’s time
we continued our race.
- Don’t you?
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
Jotaro: Don’t let this guy
get to you, kakyoin!
Stay focused!
♪
Joseph: Kakyoin!
D’arby: There.
Now his soul belongs to me.
The poor fool admitted defeat.
( Laughs )
He finally realized that it was
pointless to continue racing.
( Kakyoin gasps )
D’arby: Still, I must say,
you, kakyoin,
are the first opponent to ever
make me perspire like this.
Given its source material,
this doll will make
a most exquisite addition
to my growing collection.
He was the very first opponent
to muster up the courage
to conquer his fears
and resist cracking
under such colossal pressure.
( Joseph groans )
No. Kakyoin.
( Jotaro growls )
( Kakyoin gasping )
D’arby: I will treasure
his good company always.
( Joseph growls )
D’arby: Careful.
It would be in the best interest
of all involved
for you to keep
your emotions in check.
harming me
is out of the question.
You see, dying is something
I simply can’t do
if you want your friend back.
Slipping on a banana peel
and hitting my head,
choking on gum,
or even suffering a heart attack
from the shock
of popping a bag of popcorn,
if any of those things
sent me to heaven,
kakyoin’s soul would go, too.
( Jotaro growls )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: What the--
hey, jotaro, wait!
D’arby: What’s this?
Joseph: Hey, jotaro,
why the hell
are you sitting down?
we should be
kicking geppetto’s ass.
- I’ll play him next.
- Jotaro: Old man,
have you ever actually played
any of these games?
if not, the odds
wouldn’t be in your favor.
( Joseph gasps )
Jotaro: Stay out of it, old man.
This isn’t your average game
of gin rummy, after all.
( Joseph groans )
Jotaro: We’re playing baseball.
that’s the game I choose
to settle this once and for all.
As collateral,
i’ll bet my soul.
D’arby: All right. Then I would
like to bet kakyoin’s soul.
( Atum hisses )
D’arby: My stand atum
has released your arm.
You may thank me
at your leisure.
Now that kakyoin’s soul
is in my collection,
there’s no longer
reason for me
to keep your arm
in my stand’s clutches.
And suffice it to say i’d be
at a bit of a disadvantage
if I faced you
with my stand one-handed.
i’m well aware
of your star platinum’s
incredible speed and precision.
( Laughs )
Really, out of all the games
you could have chosen to play...
( Laughs )
it’s unfortunate for you
that we’re playing my specialty.
Joseph: D’arby, just you wait.
the moment jotaro
wipes the floor with you,
i’ll throttle the life
out of your pompous ass,
and that is a promise.
announcer:
"Oh! That’s a baseball!"
Joseph: Doesn’t look like he’s
tampered with this game either.
You’re good to go.
( D’arby chuckles )
Before we begin,
you’ll need to pick your team.
Jotaro: Jaguars.
Announcer: Jaguars!
d’arby: Yes, I see.
You’ve decided to go with a team
that has
a strong offense, eh?
And two with a batting average
over .400.
if that’s how
you’re going to play it,
i’ll choose the red dragons.
Announcer: Red dragons!
D’arby: Offense or defense?
Go on. Take your pick.
Jotaro: Offense.
D’arby: In that case,
the jaguars will bat first.
- ( Jotaro scoffs )
- D’arby: Next,
you can begin designing
your own players
by drawing their faces
on the screen.
This handsome devil
is star platinum.
Now that we’ve gotten
the preparations
out of the way,
play ball?
announcer:
Jaguars versus red dragons!
Umpire: Play ball!
( Crowd cheering )
♪
D’arby: I’ve chosen
number 15 as my pitcher.
january fifth
is my birthday, you know.
Now, here we go.
announcer:
The pitcher is winding up.
( Joseph grunts )
Announcer: The first pitch.
Joseph: What?!
Umpire: Strike one.
Joseph: Uh, hey, I don’t get it.
What’s wrong?
That was a pretty
amateur move back there.
It’s great that you
swung the bat and all,
but it was before
he even threw the ball!
D’arby: Hmm?
♪
joseph: Hey,
what’s this all about?
There’s no need for you to
practice your swing, is there?
Hang on. Jotaro, is this
the very first time
you’ve ever played this?
In fact, have you ever played
a video game in your life?
You answer me right now,
jotaro!
Jotaro: Relax. I already know
how to play baseball.
i’ll figure out
the game controls as I go.
D’arby: Huh?
Joseph: W-what are you saying?!
In case you haven’t noticed,
your timing is totally off.
Your swings are pathetic.
don’t lie.
This is your first time
playing, isn’t it?
- Umpire: Strike two.
- ( Joseph gasps )
and now you’re
actually swinging the bat
after the catcher
has caught the ball.
You don’t know
what you’re doing!
Damn it, jotaro. I was right.
You don’t know a video game
from a hole in the ground.
Umpire: Strike. Batter out.
joseph: Jotaro,
it’s time to get serious!
Stop trying to act cool,
and use your blasted head!
You bet your soul on this game,
so if you think you can back out
due to lack of experience,
think again.
Jotaro: Good grief.
This is the worst pep talk
i’ve ever heard.
You should be more encouraging.
try something like,
"it’s only the first inning.
You can still
make a comeback."
Joseph: What the hell’s going
through that head of yours?
You can’t possibly rely solely
on star platinum’s reflexes
to win this game, can you?
Think about it.
You don’t know the first thing
about video games.
how are you
supposed to beat him?
What’s your plan, jotaro?
Answer me, damn it!
do you have a way
to beat this weirdo or not?
D’arby: Jotaro...
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- ( Joseph groans )
d’arby: Listen,
if your strategy is to trick me
by pretending
to be an amateur,
let me inform you
that it isn’t going to work.
I’d never be foolish enough
to let my guard down.
Even if you were
a helpless child,
it wouldn’t happen.
A soul is at stake.
Jotaro: Old man.
Joseph: Eh? Huh?
Jotaro: Since you wanted
to know, I don’t have a plan.
However, if I did have one,
the only thing it would involve
would be knocking the nose
straight off the face
of this condescending,
over-inflated
douche bag of a prick
taking up space beside me.
all I care about is
getting kakyoin’s soul back.
I’ll do whatever it takes.
D’arby: You talk a big game,
but it’s still
the top of the first inning,
and you have one out.
The match is far from over.
and since you haven’t
played before, you should know
that if you fall more
than 11 points behind, you lose.
announcer:
Second batter, number 3.
Umpire: Strike.
joseph: Damn,
he’s getting even worse.
That time, he swung the bat
over 40 centimeters
above the ball.
How’s he so bad?
Umpire: Strike two.
joseph: What?
It wasn’t even close.
Umpire: Strike three.
you’re out.
Joseph: It’s all over.
Jotaro’s no match
for someone like d’arby.
This massacre is like
being forced to watch
a group of high school
baseball champs
go head-to-head with kids
from the knitting club!
It’s pathetic.
Umpire: Strike one.
Strike two.
D’arby: So it wasn’t a bluff.
He really is a beginner.
This is too easy.
In the same way a judo pro
can Gauge his opponent’s skill
simply by looking
at the way he wears his gi,
I can read him like a book,
and chapter one is called,
"jotaro, the video game novice."
all the same,
I refuse to let my guard down.
I’m aware of the weaknesses
of every batter in this game.
Next will be a low pitch
to the outside.
I’ll throw my best pitch,
the four-seam fast ball,
and strike him out.
It’s the first inning.
Two outs, two strikes,
and no fouls.
- Here comes my next pitch.
- Jotaro: Go right ahead.
I’ve pretty much gotten the hang
of batting with the controller.
d’arby: Wait.
What did he just say?
I must have heard him wrong.
What does he mean,
"got the hang of it"?
Surely, he couldn’t have...
What is he talking about?
What does he mean?
What?!
Joseph: Jotaro!
Jotaro: All right. I’m really
starting to enjoy this game.
Joseph: What in the--
it can’t be!
it’s going!
The ball is still going!
D’arby: It just
doesn’t make sense.
What did he mean by,
"got the hang of it"?
"Got the hang of it"?
( Joseph yells )
He--he did it!
I don’t know how,
but he did it!
( Laughs )
Announcer: Home run!
( D’arby sputters )
Joseph: Home run!
It’s a home run!
( Laughs )
( D’arby growls )
Jotaro, damn you.
( D’arby grunts )
jotaro...
Did I really hear you correctly?
say something.
It sounded like you’d,
"pretty much gotten
the hang of batting."
Jotaro: I don’t feel
like repeating myself.
D’arby: He was a beginner
when we started this game,
and yet he’s claiming
to have learned
proper swinging technique
in only eight pitches.
Jotaro kujo has all the speed
and dexterity of star platinum.
Now I know why master dio
finds him to be problematic
and why my brother lost.
( Groans )
( Chuckles )
Interesting.
I couldn’t have asked
for a more fitting opponent.
But as naturally gifted
as you may be,
you made a critical mistake
by revealing your talents
so early in the game,
a mistake
that will cost you dearly.
( Chuckles )
Let’s resume the game, jotaro.
♪
Joseph: Yes, he did it!
That’s my boy!
Another home run
right out of the park!
Talk about a comeback.
Four runs in the first inning.
looks like you’ve got
this game in the bag, jotaro.
Keep it up, and we’ll be
out of here in no time.
hey, d’arby,
you’ll just ignore me,
but i’ll say it anyway,
because i’m a nice guy.
I’m giving you an out.
All you have to do
is return kakyoin’s soul
and take us to dio
of your own volition.
If you cooperate,
no harm will befall you.
- huh?
- Jotaro: Hmm?
D’arby: For all his faults,
my brother was a master gambler.
He made conning people
into an art form.
You’d think his younger brother
would be perfect
to practice on,
but you’d be wrong.
he never asked me
to play one game of poker.
No, I was never asked
to play any games
of the gambling persuasion.
Any guesses why?
( Both grunt )
D’arby: When I was 15,
I caught my brother
putting his oh-so-predictable
moves on my girlfriend.
he was ten years older,
but I beat him to a bloody pulp.
I broke his ribs
and proceeded to kick him
until he spat blood.
The last thing my brother
said to me was how sorry he was.
Any idea why?
Joseph: Would you please
cut to the chase already?
D’arby: Even as kids, my brother
had the good sense to realize
that he’d never have
what it took to beat me.
The reason for that is about
to become abundantly clear.
At this moment, you have
a false sense of confidence
due to the home run you hit,
but deep down,
you feel a sense of unease,
not unlike
what my brother felt.
My prowess is beginning
to worry you, isn’t it?
Right now you’re coming
to a daunting conclusion
about the game’s outcome,
aren’t you, jotaro?
Joseph: What the hell
are you talking about?
D’arby: Changing pitchers!
Number 15 is out,
and number 77 is in.
77 is a power pitcher
with a Max pitch speed
of 165 kilometers per hour.
Also, i’ll tell you
the pitch i’ll throw.
( Jotaro scoffs )
D’arby: Number 77
will throw a forkball,
and he’ll throw it
right down the middle.
Joseph: What the hell?!
Why would he declare
what he’s throwing?!
D’arby: A forkball is about
to come barreling down center.
But will you
believe me or not?
joseph: Jotaro,
he’s just spouting nonsense
to shake your confidence.
do yourself a favor,
and ignore everything he says.
Joseph: Throw it, d’arby.
D’arby: Will you believe,
or will you doubt?
( Chuckles )
Joseph: I knew it.
It’s a fastball,
and it’s coming right at you.
Let’s see. Is the ball
going to change direction?
the suspense
is driving me crazy!
You swung!
You bought his act
and bet on the forkball!
it’s still going.
It actually is a fastball!
oh, great.
He hit the bottom of the ball.
Umpire: Out.
Announcer: First inning,
three outs. Change.
( Crowd cheering )
Joseph: Idiot. How could you?!
Leave it to a rookie
for something like that.
i can’t believe
you swung for a forkball.
( D’arby chuckles )
Jotaro: No.
He had already seen through me
and knew I would swing
expecting a forkball,
so he switched it up
to a fastball.
But he has a point, though.
Something’s been gnawing at me
ever since we stepped foot
in this mansion.
i’m not sure how,
but he knew star platinum
would throw a right punch
in our earlier skirmish.
Joseph: What? Impossible!
Are you trying to tell me
that he can read your mind?
No offense, jotaro,
but that’s crazy talk.
d’arby:
Oh, would you look at that?
It’s my turn at bat.
♪
Joseph: Eh?
d’arby: This is
going to be a home run.
Keep your eye on the birdie,
as i’ll be hitting it
into the left-field bleachers.
( Laughs )
Jotaro: Old man,
are you absolutely sure
the game and console
haven’t been tampered with?
joseph: Yeah,
i’m positive it’s clean,
and that’s not all.
I haven’t seen him make
a single funny move either.
Jotaro: Then his secret weapon
has to be that stand of his.
his stand
doesn’t just take souls.
It must have
some other ability.
( Thinking )
This’ll be my target.
now i’ll get
to the bottom of this.
Joseph: Has he lost his mind?
he’s going to try
to hit the batter on purpose?
D’arby: And where might you
be aiming now, jotaro,
an inside pitch?
Will you throw it high
or low, perhaps?
Or maybe you’re planning
some kind of underhanded trick?
Well?
Joseph: What the--
he pulled back
when jotaro threw the ball!
( D’arby chuckles )
Joseph: He predicted it.
he knew exactly
what would happen. But how?
There’s no way he could have
seen that pitch coming
unless he read jotaro’s mind!
Announcer: Home run!
( D’arby chuckles )
That’s one run.
Joseph: Damn this bastard.
we’ve faced all kinds
of opponents on this journey,
but never one
who could read our minds.
If he really can read minds,
then it doesn’t matter
how clever we think we are.
we won’t stand
a snowball’s chance in hell.
Jotaro, what are
you going to do?
( Atum chuckles )
( D’arby laughs )
Joseph: Why, that--
damn, the punk’s
declaring another home run.
D’arby: Let’s see.
Heh. An outside pitch?
Or maybe you’re
going to aim low?
or something
in the vein of a fastball?
( Chuckles )
( Atum laughs )
( Bat strikes ball )
Announcer: Home run!
D’arby: Four to two.
( Chuckles )
joseph: Damn.
A person’s body language
and the surrounding environment
go a long way
toward helping predict
an opponent’s next move,
but there’s no way
to do it perfectly,
and yet his stand
predicts jotaro’s pitch
with 100% accuracy.
And technically
he’s not cheating.
Another home run!
It’s four to three.
How are we supposed to stop him
from reading our minds? How?
( Jotaro sighs )
( D’arby chuckles )
At this rate, i’ll be
in the lead in no time.
now what’s next?
An inside pitch, a fastball,
a high pitch,
or maybe a curveball?
What’s up your sleeve?
Huh?
Joseph: Your hat...
( D’arby scoffs ) You idiot.
Do you honestly take me
for a cheat like
my ne’er-do-well brother?
Joseph: Jotaro,
you’ve got it wrong.
Hiding your face is useless.
I don’t know what he’s doing,
but he’s not watching
the reflection of the screen
in your eyes.
I get that it’s hard
not to go there now,
but there’s no way he can see
what you’re pressing
or what pitch you’re choosing.
trust me. I’ve been
watching him the entire time.
That’s not what’s
been going on here.
Jotaro: I only took off my hat,
because i’m sweating,
- no other reason.
- Joseph: Huh?
D’arby: Could you throw your
next pitch sometime this year?
jotaro: But i’m not
going to be sweating anymore.
- I’ll tell you my next pitch.
- ( Both gasp )
Jotaro: I’m throwing
a high, outside fastball.
D’arby: You’re joking.
Joseph: Jotaro, do you hear
what you’re saying right now?
Jotaro: Of course I do.
finally starting
to lose your hearing, old man?
Obviously I just told him
my next pitch.
A high, outside fastball,
that’s how i’m gonna win.
♪
Joseph: Eh? Jotaro?
Will you believe me,
or will you doubt me?
( D’arby scoffs )
You’re not too bright, are you?