♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator:
Let’s rewind a little bit.
While Joseph and avdol
were battling Mariah,
jotaro and polnareff were...
( Children humming )
Girl: And here’s
your drink, ma’am,
a super-duper tall glass of
whiskey and soda on the rocks.
Enjoy.
Girl #2: It looks delicious.
Gulp-gulp, gulp-gulp,
gulp-gulp, gulp.
Girl #1: Oh, my. Somebody’s
dying to quench her thirst
early this morning.
Scandalous.
Girl #2: Darling,
how you do go on.
My husband’s
gone away on a business trip
and won’t return
for another week. ( Laughs )
Girl #1: In that case, how about
enjoying a piece of cake?
Girl #2: Oh, don’t trouble
yourself, dear.
I’m quite all right. ( Laughs )
( Polnareff laughs )
Kids are great, huh?
So innocent.
Jotaro: Hey, it’s almost 9 A.M.
( Sighs ) The old man and avdol
are taking way too long.
Polnareff: Mm.
Jotaro: They may have had
a run-in with the enemy.
Polnareff: You think we should
see where they ran off to?
Jotaro: I guess.
Ah, good grief.
Polnareff:
It’s time to go, iggy.
( Iggy groans )
( Barks )
Polnareff: Yeah, yeah,
I know you’re hungry.
You’re not the only one,
believe me.
( Iggy grumbles, barks )
Polnareff: Hey, iggy,
where in the world do
you think you’re going?
Jeez, what a stupid mutt.
- Jotaro: Let’s go.
- Polnareff: Hmm?
♪
Boy: Hey!
Make some room, would you?
I wanna play, too!
Girl #2: No way we’d ever play
with a jerk like you.
- ( Girl #1 grunts )
- Boy: Oh, yeah?
You guys are the jerks around--
( girls gasp )
Boy: Ah, man,
that really hurt. Mm?
♪
( Mud dripping )
Uh...
( Alessi sighs )
Attaboy. You didn’t
shed a single tear.
That’s impressive.
You sure you’re okay?
Boy: Uh...
Alessi: So, kid,
how old are you?
Boy: Uh...
Alessi: Four years old, hmm?
Attaboy.
What about your daddy?
Where is he now?
Boy: Uh, he’s at work.
Alessi: I see.
So your daddy’s at work,
is he? Attaboy to you.
And where’s your mommy?
Boy: She’s at home
doing laundry.
Alessi: Attaboy.
So you came here
all by yourself?
Boy: Mm-hmm.
Alessi: Good! Then there’s
no one around to stop me
from bashing your face in
for ruining my pants!
You gonna pay to get
the mud cleaned off?!
Or maybe you’re gonna get a job
for the cash to pay me back,
because you think I have years
to wait for some little punk
to work his way through debt!
You little shit stain!
( Girls gasp )
( Alessi grunts )
- ( Girls scream )
- ( Blows thump )
Boy: Mommy! ( Sobbing )
( Alessi scoffs )
Joseph and avdol
are in the middle
of doing battle with Mariah,
so I, alessi, shall take on
the great honor
of killing jotaro and polnareff.
They’re tenacious, to be sure,
but i’ll do whatever it takes
to achieve victory.
( Sighs )
Attaboy, alessi.
( Laughs )
Narrator: Enemy’s name--alessi.
Stand--set,
god of storms and chaos.
Favorite phrase--"attaboy."
♪
Jotaro: Polnareff,
keep your guard up.
Polnareff: Have you forgotten
who you’re talking to?
Hmm.
Seems Mr. Joestar and avdol
already left,
and it doesn’t really look
like there was a struggle.
( Jotaro sighs )
Old man, avdol, you here?
( Sighs )
Polnareff: Hey, jotaro,
i’m starting to get
a bad feeling about this.
Jotaro: Me, too.
( Overlapping chatter )
Woman: Ah, that looks yummy.
Come on. Let me have a bite.
Man: All right.
Just leave me some.
( Iggy grunts )
( Barks )
Man: Th-that dog
took my sandwich!
Hey, get back here this instant,
you mangy flea bag!
♪
( Metal clattering )
( Iggy grunts )
Mariah: So you think
I have nowhere to go?
You boys truly haven’t
realized it yet, have you?
You only thought
you were hunting me,
when really I was luring you
here the entire time!
I’m afraid you’re going
to fry this time, joestar!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Joseph groans )
Hermit purple!
( Groans )
Mariah: Avdol might be able
to defend himself for now
with his flames, but not you.
Time to die, joestar.
The goddess bast
is the perfect trap,
and it’s also far more powerful
than your hermit purple!
( Overlapping chatter )
♪
( Bells jingle )
Polnareff: Hmm?
( Alessi gasps )
Polnareff: Hmm.
Alessi: Oh, dear,
that’s not good.
I dropped my change.
Now, where’d it go?
Not over here.
I’d lose my own head
if it wasn’t attached
to my shoulders.
Polnareff: Hey, what do you
think you’re doing?
I can tell you’re following us.
( Alessi groans )
Polnareff: I can already see
the evil in your eyes,
so don’t lie. Got it?
Alessi: Hmm? Hmm?
I am so sorry, my good man.
Were you talking to me?
I’m not sure I understand
what you meant by "evil eyes."
My loving, non-evil parents
gave me these baby blues. Eh?
Well, what do you know?
It’s the change
I was looking for.
Polnareff: Is that so?
Then prove it!
It’ll be easy to prove
that you’re not a stand user,
unless you really are one.
Connard!
( Gasps )
Merde, that was a close one.
So I was right,
and you are a stand user!
( Alessi scoffs )
Polnareff: He’s running?
Hey, jotaro, it’s the enemy!
I’m hot on his trail!
Jotaro: Hmm?
Polnareff.
( Sighs )
Polnareff, where did you go?
Polnareff: Over here, jotaro!
♪
Come back here, damn you!
( High-pitched )
Wait!
What the hell?!
This guy is quick!
How can he be so fast?!
Man, he’s already so far ahead.
Huh? That’s strange.
What happened to my voice?
( Gasps )
( Groans )
Ow!
( Gasping )
W-what the heck is up
with my shoes?
They’re ginormous.
Man: Hey,
watch where you’re going.
Don’t you know running around
in the street like that
can get you hurt or worse?
You’re lucky
I wasn’t the front end
of some out-of-control car.
Polnareff: Shut up, idiot!
Why don’t you go
and lecture someone else
with that big mouth of yours?
Now out of my way!
I’m in the middle
of chasing someone!
Hey! What do you think
you’re doin’?!
Let go of me!
What? It’s really high up here!
He’s lifting me up
with one arm?
Just how tall is this guy?!
His face and hands are huge.
It’s like he’s a giant!
Man: All right, listen here,
you pint-sized pissant!
I’m gonna teach you
to go around
shooting your ignorant little
mouth off to adults that way!
( Slap thumps )
( Polnareff groaning )
Man: You think you’re a big man
just because you’re playing
dress-up in adult clothes?
Annoying,
good-for-nothing brat. Hmph.
Polnareff: You bastard.
( Dog barks )
Agh! Wh-what the hell?!
Cyclist: Move it, kid!
- ( Bicycle bell rings )
- Get out of the way!
( Polnareff gasps )
W-wait a minute.
What the hell is going on here?
Why does everyone
look like giants?!
( Gasps )
What?!
♪
( Gasps )
W-w-what the--
why am I a kid?!
( Whimpers )
Is this really me?!
I’ve been turned into a kid!
How is something like this
happening to me?!
Polnareff: C-could this
really be happening to me?
There’s no possible way
this kid could really be--
could really be me!
Oh, my god, this kid is me!
I turned into a little kid!
( Laughs )
No way! No way! No way! No way!
It must be his stand’s power.
That creeper
must have found a way
to put a curse on me
during our fight earlier.
I have a sneaking suspicion
it happened
when his shadow stand
lunged at me.
How did I let him
do this to me?!
Shit, this is bad!
This is really bad!
What am I gonna do?!
Eh?
Jo--
jotaro: Hmm?
Polnareff: Jo, uh--
( jotaro groans )
Polnareff: Uh, j-Jo--
uh, n-no, Jay!
Jackie! J--
uh...
W-what was his name?
I can’t remember his name!
But I know this guy.
He can help me!
So why can’t I remember it?
Why can’t I remember his name?!
Jotaro: Hey, there, little boy,
you, uh, didn’t happen to see
a French guy come through here,
did you?
This guy is about yea tall,
and he’s got the exact
same haircut as you do.
Polnareff: Yeah,
you’re talking about me!
It’s me! It’s me!
( Jotaro sighs )
Ah, good grief.
Asking a kid was an awful idea.
Polnareff: Huh? Uh,
hey, hold on!
( Gasps )
( Alessi laughs )
I take it you’ve realized
that your body
has been changed into a kid’s.
Both your mind and your body
have regressed,
and soon you’ll lose
all of the memories
that you’ve built up
during adulthood.
Polnareff: He can’t
seriously be able to erase
everything I knew as an adult.
( Gasping ) It’s true.
It’s all becoming a blur.
( Alessi laughs )
Guess it’s about time, huh?
I love picking on the weak.
It’s so amusing.
Attaboy, alessi. Attaboy.
Uh-uh!
You’re not getting away,
you brat!
( Laughs )
I can’t say this too loudly,
but picking on the weak really
gets me going, maybe too much.
( Chuckles )
I may be a bit sick in the head,
but, hey, c’est la vie.
Am I right?
It’s like everyone says,
"if you think you’re
a little loony upstairs,
then there’s a good chance
you’re probably not."
It’s my confirmation
that i’m totally sane,
and you can’t imagine
how good it feels
to know that i’ll
never lose to some kid.
( Polnareff gasps ) Mister!
Whatever your name is,
you have--
( groans )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Hmph.
( Polnareff groaning )
Alessi: As you no doubt know,
my mission is to wipe you and
your good-for-nothing cohorts
from the face of the planet.
Polnareff: Damn thing
won’t come off!
Alessi: Unfortunately...
( Polnareff gasps )
Alessi: I don’t have time
to savor the fun.
( Polnareff whimpers )
Alessi: Heh.
( Polnareff groans )
Alessi: Huh?
What do we have here?
Silver chariot, eh?
I should have expected as much.
Seems you were able
to summon your stand as a kid.
But...
Polnareff: Huh?!
Just how strong
is this stupid stand user?!
Even silver chariot is a kid!
Silver chariot: Pami!
Pami!
Polnareff: And he’s
just as weak as I am.
He bent his sword
blocking those bullets!
Alessi: My stand, set,
reverted you back
to your childhood state,
which means that all
of your mental abilities
were reverted
right along with you.
Your stand has gone back to
a child’s stand, the form it had
before you two were
fully attuned to each other!
( Laughs )
Do you get it now?
Good. It seems
like you understand.
Alessi: Attaboy, kid.
♪
- ( Silver chariot whimpers )
- ( Polnareff whimpers )
Alessi: But, as weak as it is,
your stand
is still at your disposal,
so I shall use my stand
for your execution.
( Polnareff gasps )
Alessi: Time to die, polnareff!
You’re mine!
Silver chariot and polnareff:
Oh, no!
Polnareff: It broke in two!
( Alessi laughs )
Eh?
( Wails )
Polnareff: Hurts, doesn’t it?!
I meant to do that!
Alessi: Ow! Ow! It hurts!
( Wailing )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Woman gasps )
Little boy, are you all right?
Polnareff: Uh...
H-he’s gone.
So that guy runs for the hills
as soon as there’s
another adult around.
I’m safe for now, but that freak
was off his rocker.
Woman: Don’t run off,
little boy.
Polnareff: Huh?
Woman: It looks like
you’re hurt. What happened?
Polnareff: Huh? I, uh--
well, the thing is, you see--
woman: What are
you mumbling about?
Those wounds need to be treated.
Why don’t you come with me
to my house,
and i’ll fix you up, okay?
( Polnareff gasping )
Should I go?
If I don’t defeat
the stand user,
I won’t turn back into an adult.
If the past is any indication,
he won’t attack me
with this lady around.
I can use that time
to think of a plan.
Woman: Come on. Hurry up.
Polnareff: Whoa.
Woman: Oh, that’s right.
Polnareff: Huh?
Woman: You’re hurt,
so climb on my back,
but make sure you hang on tight.
Polnareff: Uh...
( Chuckles )
( Woman chuckles )
( Polnareff sighs )
She smells good.
( Alessi gasping )
This hurts like a bitch!
Damn that little
crotch-sniffer!
I’m not going to take this
from a snot-nosed kid!
He’ll pay dearly for this.
I swear i’ll butcher that brat!
Polnareff:
From the looks of things,
he doesn’t seem
to be coming after me.
Woman: All right, little boy.
We’re going to take a bath,
so let’s take
those clothes off, shall we?
Polnareff: Huh?!
Woman: You’re completely
covered in grime.
I’ll clean those wounds up
and put some medicine on you.
( Polnareff gasping )
( Laughs )
♪
Woman: What are you
staring at, sweetie?
Take your clothes off.
Better yet,
i’ll take them off for you.
Here. Raise your leg.
Polnareff: Hey, wait!
What are you doing, lady?!
Woman: But what’s wrong?
Polnareff: Uh, nothing at all.
( Woman giggles )
Polnareff: No, it is something.
It most definitely is something.
I don’t know why,
but I get the feeling
that I should be really
embarrassed about all this.
Wait. Oh, no. What if my--
agh! It’s so small!
I don’t know why,
but for some reason,
that makes me sad!
( Crying )
Woman: Hey, don’t cry.
After we get
all that dirt off of you,
you’ll be as good as new again.
Here. Lift your leg.
( Polnareff gasps )
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
I-i-i’m so happy!
Are you positive it’s okay
for me to touch you like this?!
Woman: Of course
it’s okay, silly.
If we don’t
clean up those wounds...
- ( Polnareff slobbering )
- They could get infected.
Oh, you’ve got dirt
on your wee-wee, too.
( Polnareff squeals )
Oh, boy! I can’t explain why,
but i’m just so happy
all of a sudden!
I guess it’s all part
of being a kid.
( Laughing )
Woman: All right.
You be a good boy, okay?
Polnareff: Okay! ( Laughing )
♪
Alessi: The fool’s delirious.
Enjoy your stupor while you can,
because i’m going
to chop your face in two!
( Polnareff laughing )
( Woman gasps )
( Woman chuckles )
♪
What could you be
grinning about, you silly boy?
Now, I think it’s time
we wash your hair.
Polnareff: Huh?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I hate using shampoo!
( Woman chuckles )
Polnareff: It gets into my eyes,
- and I hate it!
- Woman: Rock-paper-scissors,
- go!
- Polnareff: Scissors!
Woman: Monkey, monkey, monkey,
monkey, monkey, monkey,
both: Monkey, monkey do!
Monkey, monkey do!
( Polnareff groans ) I lost!
( Crying )
Woman: All right, sit still.
( Bubbles popping )
( Scrubbing )
( Polnareff groaning )
Alessi: Does it sting?
Polnareff: Yeah,
it stings a lot.
Alessi: Can you wash your hair
all by yourself?
Polnareff: Uh-huh,
but not as good as you.
Alessi: Oh? Attaboy.
( Polnareff groans )
( Alessi cackles )
Yes, that’s the way, kiddo!
Attaboy!
( Polnareff wails )
That’s impossible!
( Screams )
♪