Joseph: Everyone, hold on!
Yaah!
Oh, no!
- ( Men groaning )
- ( Iggy snoring )
Avdol: It sunk into the sand.
We should all be all right
as long as we don’t move
and don’t make a sound.
( N’doul chuckles )
It’s much too late to try
hiding from me at this point.
I know where each of you landed.
There’s no escaping now.
( Footstep echoes )
♪
Four--no, five steps.
I get it. You’re walking
quietly to avoid detection.
But you can’t hide from me.
Avdol: Tsk, tsk.
It appears these "steps"
have thrown him for a loop.
Go ahead,
you accursed water stand.
Just try to attack us,
because the moment
you reveal yourself,
i’ll vaporize you with the power
of my magician’s red.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
- ( Soft scraping )
- Avdol: He’s here.
♪
N’doul: Hold on. What’s this?
He only moved
five steps forward.
How strange.
Why has he suddenly
stopped moving?
Now!
Magician’s red!
What?!
- ( All gasping )
- Joseph: Avdol!
( Iggy grunts )
( Avdol groans )
How can he be so--
( gasps )
So quick?
Polnareff: Avdol!
( N’doul sighs )
I have to admit
that plan was actually
a stroke of brilliance.
I have to pay more attention
to their vibrations from now on.
Those weren’t footsteps at all.
It would seem as though he threw
some kind of metal rings.
And judging by these burns...
( Chuckles )
I’d say avdol did the deed.
( Avdol gasping )
N’doul: But c’est la vie.
Farewell...
♪
Avdol.
Hmm? What’s this?
Someone started running.
Joseph: Jotaro,
what are you doing?!
You know we can’t
just run around!
N’doul: His stride
says he’s about 190--
no, 195 centimeters tall.
There’s a youthfulness
in his stride,
so he’s not Joseph.
It must be jotaro then,
but where exactly is he going?
( Polnareff gasps ) It dove in!
I think it’s going after jotaro!
Joseph: This can’t be happening!
I’m grateful he’s not
attacking avdol anymore, but--
jotaro! He’s catching up to you!
N’doul: I hear
jotaro’s star platinum
is the fiercest
of the enemies’ stands.
Master dio will be
beside himself with joy
if I take care of him
here and now.
In the name of master dio,
i’ll use every fiber of my being
to finally vanquish jotaro.
( Iggy grumbles, gasps )
( Yelps )
N’doul: Hmm.
If I heard correctly,
jotaro just picked something up
off the sand.
Let’s see.
What was at that location?
Last I checked, it was--
( gasps ) Wait. I remember!
The dog! Jotaro grabbed the dog,
which means he knows!
Jotaro: I’ve finally
figured you out, mutt.
I know you jumped out of the car
before the stand attacked it.
You can smell it, can’t you?
You know where it’s gonna be
before it gets there.
Joseph: Gah!
Don’t stop moving, jotaro!
Jotaro: Now, iggy, I think it’s
time for you to earn your keep.
Where’s the stand coming from?
Just show me, already.
Show me, or we die,
and how would you
get your gum then?
Joseph: Huh?
( The fool squeals ) Iggy!
Jotaro: Iggy!
You’ve gotta be kidding me.
He can fly, too? Not so fast.
( The fool grunts )
Jotaro: Go ahead,
and pant all you want.
You’re not
getting out of this one.
Star platinum’s
as fast as they come.
If you’re thinking
of dropping me,
i’ll snap your neck
before you can blink.
( Iggy yelps )
N’doul: What?
It’s like he jumped
and suddenly disappeared.
This is impossible.
They must have landed somewhere.
Joseph: That’s brilliant.
We can’t move around,
so to bypass that handicap,
jotaro’s using iggy
to find the stand user.
If we can find whoever’s
controlling the stand,
we might actually have
a chance of defeating him.
( Bubbling )
N’doul: He’s vanished.
I can’t hear jotaro’s footsteps.
Where is he? Where did he go?
Why can’t I hear his footsteps?
( Iggy panting )
Polnareff: Oh, no.
They’re flying lower and lower.
This isn’t gonna end well.
It looks like the fool
can’t travel long distances.
Joseph: The damn thing is
gliding like a paper airplane!
( Jotaro groans )
My legs are
about to touch the ground.
- ( Iggy farting )
- Jotaro: Hey, mutt,
quit tensing up like that.
You’re starting to fart again.
For your sake, you better
not let out a big one.
( Sighs ) No choice.
We need to get more air,
and at this point,
there’s only one way to do it.
Jotaro: Ora!
- ( N’doul gasps )
- ( Iggy howls )
Jotaro: That kick
got us a lot closer
to our destination for sure,
but the sound of it definitely
gave away our strategy.
Now the user will know
that we’re flying
to avoid detection.
N’doul: So that’s why
I wasn’t able to locate them.
The dog’s stand
has the ability to fly.
But now I know
what they’re up to.
They’re headed directly for me.
I have to eliminate jotaro
before he gets any closer!
Polnareff: His stand’s
on the move,
and it’s going after jotaro!
He figured it out
when jotaro kicked off!
Joseph: There’s nothing
we can do about it.
The only thing we can do now
is trust jotaro.
Jotaro: He’s coming.
I know he was able
to bring down a helicopter,
but he shouldn’t be able
to find our exact location
since iggy’s stand
barely makes a sound.
I just have to get
to the stand user
before landing,
and it’ll be lights out.
There he is.
The stand user’s
about 400 meters away.
And from the looks of things,
our enemy is blind.
( Sand clattering )
Damn it.
Sand’s falling from the sky.
Of course. The stand user
must be trying to find us.
He’s using the sand
bouncing off the wings
like a submarine uses sonar.
♪
( N’doul chuckles )
Because of the falling sand,
I can hear you now.
And i’ve discovered
your exact location, jotaro!
( Jotaro groans )
N’doul: Time to die!
Jotaro: Star platinum!
Star platinum: Ora!
- ( Iggy yelps )
- ( N’doul laughs )
Star platinum’s speed won’t
be of much use, i’m afraid!
If you can’t tell where
my attack is coming from,
then my stand has the advantage!
( Jotaro gasps )
( N’doul laughs )
Here comes another!
( Iggy groans )
Iggy: Iggy.
Iggy.
- ( Iggy groans )
- Jotaro: Shit.
You damn mutt!
( N’doul laughs )
What a dog! He’s dragging jotaro
right into my trap!
It seems like he’ll do anything
to save his own hide! ( Laughs )
Even abandon his master!
( Laughs )
Jotaro: Bastard.
Just you wait.
N’doul: That’s what you get
for relying on such
a fickle creature, jotaro.
Your end has come,
and now it’s finally time
to put you out of your misery.
( Iggy yelps )
Star platinum: O...
Jotaro: Ora!
( Iggy howls )
( N’doul gasps ) What’s this?
It feels like he
just threw something at me!
I can’t make out
what it is at that speed.
Jotaro: I tossed iggy at you.
Get a move on.
You’d better use your stand
to defend yourselves,
or else you two
are gonna be closer
than you ever wanted to be.
N’doul: Such insane velocity.
( Iggy squealing )
N’doul: Damn it!
It’s going to hit me!
I can’t believe it.
He actually threw the dog.
( Groans ) Blast it!
I was so close
to putting an end
to that wretch once and for all.
Huh?
( Iggy panting )
N’doul: No. I was so busy
worrying about that damn dog,
I completely lost
jotaro’s location.
Where? Where is he?
♪
It’s like he vanished,
and he’s
staying absolutely still.
That must have been his plan.
Where the hell are you?
You can’t hide forever.
Show yourself, jotaro!
♪
Jotaro: I’m right here.
( N’doul gasps )
( Iggy yelps )
N’doul: I see.
I didn’t realize
you’d slink so close.
If I hadn’t had the foresight
to protect myself
with this water shield,
you would have already
knocked me out from behind.
I suppose
I should count myself lucky
it makes
for such a good defense.
Given that we’re now
in such close proximity,
I no longer need this cane
to hear you.
However, I will require its use
when I return home.
♪
Iggy: Iggy. Iggy.
Iggy.
Iggy. Iggy. Iggy.
Iggy!
♪
Star platinum: Ora!
( N’doul gags )
( Star platinum roars )
( N’doul groaning )
( Coughs )
Jotaro: It’s hard to believe,
but you actually managed
to knock off my hat.
You can relax a little.
I was holding back.
You’re not going to die.
( N’doul chuckles )
Jotaro: What the?!
Why the hell would you
use your stand to--
explain. Why did you do it?!
( N’doul groans )
Jotaro...
You--you thought you could--
you thought
you could manipulate me
and force me
to tell you information
regarding the other eight
stand users, didn’t you?
( Groans )
I’m very well aware...
That Joseph joestar’s
hermit purple...
Can view
into the minds of others.
( Groans )
You’ll never get inside my head,
and i’ll never tell you
anything that you could use
against my master.
( Laughs )
Jotaro: Dio.
I don’t understand why
you’re so loyal to him.
Are you honestly telling me
that you’d die for him?
N’doul: Jotaro, you’re right.
You don’t understand.
Fear of death
holds no place in my heart.
( Laughs )
Because of the power
of my stand,
i’ve always been able
to live a life unencumbered
by such inconsequential fears
like death.
I could always win any fight.
I could have and do
whatever I wanted.
Killing and stealing were
absolutely meaningless to me.
You should talk
to the mutt about it.
I’m sure he knows how I feel.
Dio was the first person
who was able to look deep within
my soul and find something more.
He was the one
who gave me a desire to live.
That glorious force of nature...
He was so strong,
so wise, so beautiful.
He was the one and only
person in my life
to ever see a purpose
for my existence.
( Gasps )
I waited such a long time
for an opportunity to meet him.
I will gladly die
for my master’s sake.
( Coughs ) But no matter what,
I refuse to do anything
that would disappoint him.
( Coughs )
And after all, evil or not,
a scoundrel needs someone
to put his faith in.
( Laughs )
I’ll tell you this before I go.
You should know
that my name is n’doul,
and my stand hails from Egypt,
the birthplace of the tarot.
It’s referred to as one
of the nine gods of Egypt,
geb of the great ennead.
We call it
the god of the earth.
Jotaro: Nine Egyptian gods?
What does that mean?!
( N’doul laughs )
Sorry, but i’ll only
tell you about my stand.
It’s only fair,
since you’re the one
who ended up stopping me.
But info on my compatriots
goes with me to my grave.
♪
( Footsteps crunching )
Jotaro: Dio brainwashes people
like a cult leader.
Just who is this guy, exactly?
And what’s this crap
about the nine gods of Egypt?
It’s all a mystery...
But for now, we just
have to keep moving forward.
( Iggy growls )
Jotaro: Hey, you don’t
have to be defensive.
It’s not like i’m angry
with you or anything.
Makes sense you’d be pissed.
I doubt you wanted to be
dragged out into the desert
and forced
into some human crap.
Your position must suck ass.
No one can blame you
for being upset.
Iggy, here. You want some gum?
( Iggy growling )
Jotaro: Would you
calm down already?
I’m trying to apologize.
Take it.
( Iggy barks )
Jotaro: Good grief.
That dog is a pain in the ass.
You can stay out here
in the desert for all I care.
- Iggy: Iggy.
- Jotaro: Hmm?
( Iggy whimpering )
Jotaro: Huh.
Well, what do you know?
You went back
and fetched my hat for me.
Maybe you’re
not so bad after all.
Thanks.
( Squish )
( Iggy chuckles )
Jotaro: You put gum in here?
You good-for-nothing, little--
you’re no ordinary mutt.
Joseph: Hey!
Jotaro!
- Jotaro: Huh?
- Polnareff: Jotaro!
Are you all right?
( Iggy howls )
( Barking )
( Jotaro sighs )
Good grief.
♪
Man: Ah, sweet! Hey, there.
Is that a comic book
you’re readin’, little man?
I’ve never seen one here.
So Egyptians read comics
just like the rest of us.
You want some mini doughnuts?
Hey, mind if I see
your comic book?
If you’ll let me, I promise
i’ll be super careful with it.
I’m a comic book artist
who’s searching for inspiration.
Nothing gets me jazzed up more
than checking out
rare books and comics.
Let me borrow it,
and you can use my binoculars.
Boy: Hmm?
Artist: What the? How peculiar.
The story’s about these
two eerie-looking brothers?
I don’t see the creator’s name.
Wow!
These are all
such bizarre drawings.
But this is fantastic
print quality,
not to mention
it’s in full color!
Boy: "There once
lived two brothers
who got along very well."
Man #2:
"’my name is zenyatta.’"
boy: "’my name is mondatta.’
"mondatta, the younger brother,
was very shy
"and wouldn’t do anything
unless zenyatta was with him.
"He was always alone.
"One day, while his big brother
zenyatta was away,
"mondatta met a kind traveler
near the side of the road.
"He gave mondatta yummy snacks
and let him use his binoculars.
Mondatta had more fun
than he’d had in a long time."
Artist: "’oh, it’s 10:30!’"
boy: "But unfortunately
the very kind traveler
was impaled on a telephone pole
and died a horrific death."
Artist: Quite a weird comic
you’ve got.
Is this comic especially popular
in this place?
If you ask me,
it’s really strange.
The other pages are all blank.
It’s like they forgot
to print the rest.
Must be a dud.
But somehow I feel as though
I have a connection to it.
It’s totally pulled me in.
This is gonna sound crazy,
but would it be possible for me
to buy this book from you?
- Man: It’s not for sale!
- Artist: Huh?
Man: Are you deaf or somethin’?
My bro’s book’s not for sale!
Now get out of my sight.
Artist: This kid
is your brother?
Man: I won’t tell you again!
( Artist wails )
Man: Hey, what have I told you
about talking to strangers?
There’s lots of bad people
roaming the world these days,
you know?
Conductor: Last call!
The bus for aswan
is getting ready to depart!
Man: That’s us.
They’re on their way
to the hospital in aswan
to drop off their friend
and have his injuries treated.
Hmm?
Ah. You don’t say?
If that’s how it is,
we’ll just have to wait
for the next bus.
( Sirens blaring )
♪
( Passengers murmuring )