♪
( Dio chuckles )
Joseph: What are
you doing, kakyoin?
Kakyoin: I understand now.
I know now how to uncover
the secret of dio’s stand.
Joseph: What?
♪
Narrator: For noriaki kakyoin,
hierophant green
served as a poignant reminder
of a time long past.
♪
Teacher: It’s noriaki.
He doesn’t attempt to socialize
with the other children.
It’s not that he’s disliked,
per se.
He just seems
a bit too reserved.
As his teacher,
i’m very concerned.
mrs. Kakyoin:
I’m ashamed to say it, but...
i’m afraid
I don’t understand it either.
Kakyoin: I always
had the same thoughts.
Life is full of interactions
where we meet
all sorts of people,
but how often do those meetings
involve deeper thinking?
How often do we make
genuine human connections?
All of my classmates
have address books
filled with
their friends’ names.
Each of them must have a book
of 50, no, 100 names.
Mom has dad, and dad has mom.
Kakyoin echo:
But I have no one.
Kakyoin: I’m sure rock stars
and TV celebrities
have tens of thousands
of friends.
Kakyoin echo:
But I have no one.
kakyoin:
I’ll never have any friends.
No one will ever understand me.
i’m the only one
who can see hierophant green.
how am I supposed
to truly relate to someone
if they can’t see the real me?
It’s impossible.
that’s how I
used to think about life
until I met Mr. Joestar,
jotaro, polnareff, and avdol.
Whenever I think
about avdol and iggy,
it makes the hairs on the back
of my neck stand on end.
I’m sure it’s because
they were the first
to treat me like a friend.
My friends and I were
on a journey to defeat dio,
and while it may
have been short-lived,
they’ve understood me
better than anyone.
narrator:
Looking at hierophant green
was a revelation for kakyoin.
kakyoin:
I’ll make hierophant green
invisible to everyone,
like it used to be.
I’ll use its invisibility
to my advantage
and reveal dio’s secret before
finishing him off for good!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Polnareff: Hey, jotaro!
The truck is completely totaled.
Jotaro: Up there!
I can sense the old man and dio
racing across the rooftops.
dio: I’ve only dealt
with kakyoin and Joseph so far.
Interesting. They’re attempting
to strike from both sides,
which means jotaro and polnareff
must be waiting in the wings
to attack me from behind.
( Chuckles )
How futile.
This is--
( gasps )
It’s kakyoin’s
hierophant green!
He turned it into a web?
( Groans )
Hmm?
So you’ve laid a...
Kakyoin: That’s right.
Anything that touches this web
is instantly fired upon,
and you’re surrounded
for 20 meters on all sides.
you’re done, dio!
I’ve snared you and your stand,
and I can sense your every move.
( Dio scoffs )
( Joseph sighs )
♪
Kakyoin: Now die!
20-meter-radius emerald splash!
Dio: You’re a fool, kakyoin.
with my stand, I have
the ability to rule the world!
What can you do in the face
of such overwhelming power?
kakyoin:
All right, here it comes.
Dio: Behold, the world!
( Kakyoin gasps )
Joseph: Huh? What?
Kakyoin!
He went flying through the air
like a rag doll.
But how?!
Kakyoin!
♪
Kakyoin: I don’t understand.
What just happened?
Did he really hit me?
I can’t even move
a single finger.
I can’t speak, either.
It must have been a fatal blow.
( Gasps )
It’s 5:15,
which means that it’s
midnight back in Japan.
I wonder what mom and dad
are doing right now.
knowing them,
i’m sure they’re sound asleep.
I’m sorry for worrying you.
Narrator: Despite his
brief moment of reflection,
noriaki kakyoin’s last thoughts
were not of his parents.
His mind shifted and homed in
on the question
weighing heaviest on his mind.
He had to find an answer
before nothingness took hold.
Kakyoin: I should be able
to instantly sense
any movement
within hierophant green’s web,
but somehow dio managed
to destroy the entire web
in the blink of an eye,
and it wasn’t
one strand at a time.
It was instantaneous,
not even
a split-second difference.
How did he shatter
a 20-meter-radius area
all at once?
How?
There wasn’t even
a slight delay.
What’s his secret?
Damn it.
Joseph: Kakyoin!
Shit. I’ve had enough of this!
Hermit purpl--eh?
Eh?
dio: You’re next
on the chopping block, Joseph.
In order for jonathan’s body
to become mine completely,
i must drink
the blood of a joestar,
and I think now’s as good
a time as any to partake.
Joseph: Dio!
Kakyoin: How did he
destroy them all
without the slightest delay
in time?
Time.
- ( Clock ticking )
- time.
Time.
The time!
( Gasps )
That’s it.
Something as outlandish as that
doesn’t seem possible,
but there’s
no other explanation.
I have to find a way
to tell the others.
They need to know the truth
behind such
a terrifying ability.
If I can’t tell Mr. Joestar
what i’ve learned...
The friends i’ve come to love
are going to die.
Joseph: You’re gonna pay
for what you’ve done.
Just you wait!
I’m taking that body back
in the name of granny erina.
dio: Erina? Ah,
you mean that backwater shrew?
Nonsense.
( Chuckles )
I’m going to drink your blood,
then eliminate you vermin.
( Kakyoin gasping )
( Gags )
( Joseph groans )
Dio: Now, Joseph joestar, die!
( Chorus vocalizing )
- Joseph: Huh?
- Dio: Hmm.
Kakyoin: That was
my final emerald splash.
Make it count.
( Joseph gasps )
Dio: But why? That attack
was utterly pointless.
well, I suppose
you’re now just a dying hero
longing to make his Mark
on the world. Heh.
Joseph: As if! Kakyoin wouldn’t
waste the time he has left
with some meaningless attack.
Why’d he go after the clock?
Was it some kind of sign?
was he trying
to tell me something?
( Kakyoin gasping )
It’s a message.
I don’t have the strength
to give you another.
Mr. Joestar...
You have to decipher it.
You have to let
the others know.
Joseph: Kakyoin.
narrator:
Noriaki kakyoin has died.
Joseph: Hermit purple!
Now take this!
Hamon of the sun!
Dio: You old fool!
Out of all the stands i’ve seen,
yours is the weakest!
No, you don’t!
♪
Joseph: Kakyoin, why did you
destroy the clock earlier?
Wait. You were trying to send me
a message, weren’t you?
But how does it relate
to the clock tower?
( Kakyoin gasps )
That was Mr. Joestar!
And dio’s closing in.
Where the hell is kakyoin?!
( Jotaro grunts )
joseph:
Could that be it, kakyoin?
Did you figure out the secret
of his stand’s ability
in your dying moments?
You destroyed the clock
with emerald splash...
- ( Clock ticking )
- But you aimed for the hands...
( Ticking slows, stops )
Which stopped the clock.
Huh?!
No way! That’s impossible!
Dio’s stand, the world,
has the power to...
stop time
whenever dio commands it to!
Kakyoin: Now die!
20-meter-radius emerald splash!
Dio: Behold, the world!
( Ticking slows, stops )
♪
now witness
the power of the world.
That’s right. I’ve caused time
to stop for you,
which means you won’t see
or feel any of this.
( Chuckles )
Now die, kakyoin!
You don’t even realize
you’re about to die.
In a way, you’re lucky.
You won’t know
what happened here,
only that you’re dying.
( Dio scoffs )
joseph:
I understand now, kakyoin.
That’s what you were trying
to tell me in your message.
I’m not gonna waste this chance!
Joseph: Freezing time
is bad enough,
but dio being able
to move around, too,
is a deadly combo.
Unbelievable.
we might not have
what it takes to beat it!
Just calm down.
Calm down, and think.
I don’t know the meaning
of the word "panic."
There has to be
a way to beat him,
and if anyone can find it,
it’s me.
He’s gone.
Eh?
( Gasps )
Say, what’s the matter?
Aren’t you gonna hit me, dio?
Or don’t you care about
drinking my blood anymore?
Dio: You’re running hamon
through your body
to protect yourself,
quite the strategy.
You’ve wrapped your body
with hermit purple,
but you’ve infused it
with hamon,
like a cloak
of high-voltage wires.
Very clever.
A geriatric genius.
Joseph: Well, it seems
i’m not the only clever one.
It’s just like you said.
i’ve been using this
little trick to protect myself.
But thanks to kakyoin’s message,
i’ve learned something
about your stand.
Dio, you can bring time
to a standstill,
but there’s a limit
to the amount of time
you can use that power,
only three to four seconds,
i’d say.
if you could do it
for a longer period than that,
instead of chasing us
around town all night,
you would have wiped us all out
back at the mansion.
Tracking us down tells me
everything that I need to know.
dio: So you’ve
finally figured it out.
That’s an impressive
accomplishment.
Ha! Congratulations.
♪
Joseph: You should
congratulate kakyoin.
he gave his life
to give us a fighting chance.
dio: So what?
Am I supposed to care?
it doesn’t matter
if you know my stand’s ability.
What can your pathetic hamon do
against my power?!
Joseph: Hermit purple and hamon!
Dio: Idiot! I can kill you
with or without
going through your hamon.
( Joseph yells )
- Men: Hmm?
- Man: Eh?
Hey, what’s with him?
man #2:
I’ve heard of it raining men,
but never old geezers!
woman: Hey,
what if he’s Santa claus?
Man #3: The hell were you
doin’ on the roof?
spying
on the pretty girls below?
( People laughing )
Jotaro: Old man.
Joseph: It’s jotaro.
- Stay back!
- Jotaro: Mm?
Joseph: You have to stay
far away from me!
Dio: Jotaro. What good timing.
but he’s staying
outside of my stand’s range,
so Joseph goes first.
( Cat screeches )
joseph: Jotaro!
Dio’s stand, the world,
gives him the ability
to control time!
Whatever you do,
stay out of it’s ran--
dio: Once more, the world!
( Ticking slows, stops )
♪
When I began using this power,
I was only able to freeze time
for the blink of an eye.
that said, as my neck
began the process of healing,
I found that I could stop time
for two seconds and even three.
Now I can stop time
for five seconds.
Then again, time is stopped,
so from my perspective,
it only feels like five seconds.
( Scoffs )
Soon, i’ll be able to stop time
for a minute, then an hour,
and later, as long as I desire!
how amusing.
I’ll have the ability
to stop time
to my heart’s content!
Oh, I almost forgot.
He’s covered himself with hamon
for protection.
A hundred years ago,
hamon was a concern.
Now, thanks to the world,
it’s little more
than an irritation.
( Chuckles )
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Joseph, grandson of Jonathan,
your demise is at hand!
One second left.
Zero.
( Joseph gagging )
( Woman wailing )
- ( Woman #2 squealing )
- ( Man #3 gasping )
Jotaro: Old man.
Joseph: Run away.
G-get out of here, jotaro.
Don’t even try to fight.
Please keep your distance.
Stay far away from him.
( Gasps )
He’s invincible.
( Sighs )
♪
( Jotaro growls )
Dio: Come now. Don’t worry.
At least he’s joining kakyoin.
Polnareff must be hiding
around here somewhere,
though I guess
it doesn’t matter.
You’re next, jotaro.
Time to die.
Damn you.
Dio!
Dio: Oh, so you
still want to fight?
It would appear pigheadedness
runs in the family.
How ungrateful can you be?
You’re blatantly ignoring
your grandfather’s wishes,
even after he gave his life
to tell you
about the power of the world.
Surely his pathetic pleas
warranted a bit
of consideration.
Jotaro: I have to move closer
if I wanna beat
your sorry ass to a pulp.
Dio: Really?
okay, then.
By all means, come closer.
Star platinum: Ora!
Dio: You’ll have to be faster.
My stand is more powerful
than any other.
Even without the world’s
tremendous power and speed,
it would still outclass
your pitiful star platinum.
Jotaro: Your stand has a lot
in common with my star platinum.
We’re not long-range fighters,
but we have incredible power
and precision.
Dio: If i’m being honest,
i’ve always had a desire
to see how much
stronger the world is
compared with star platinum,
but it seems pointless
to compare them now.
Jotaro: Wait. Are you serious?
all you did was
give me a love tap on the leg,
and you ripped
my 20,000-yen pants.
Dio: For the life of me,
I can’t figure out
why you joestars
are so stubborn.
Fine. I shall accept
your cheap provocation.
Let our comparison resume.
( Star platinum grunting )
Ora! Ora!
- ( Yelling )
- ( The world grunting )
( Dio chuckles )
Comparing our punching speed?
( The world yelling )
( Star platinum yelling )
♪