Jotaro: Before we
get things started,
there’s something I wanna check.
How about you go ahead
and shuffle those cards?
♪
D’arby: And shuffled, they are.
what, pray tell,
do you have in mind next?
Jotaro: Now draw a card
from the deck.
Which one it is doesn’t really
make a whole lot of difference,
but don’t show anyone.
( D’arby scoffs )
Very well.
Jotaro: And now i’ll call it.
It’s the six of hearts.
Next, I think i’ll name
the cards from the top down.
Five of spades,
queen of diamonds,
Jack of spades,
ace of hearts,
seven of diamonds,
plus the six of clubs,
king of clubs,
and two of diamonds.
( D’arby grunts )
( Avdol gasps )
He guessed them all!
and that’s
after d’arby shuffled the deck!
How did you do that?!
Jotaro: I could rattle off
the entire deck if I wanted to.
Remember my request
from earlier?
while you
were shuffling the cards,
star platinum was busy
memorizing their order
in the deck.
d’arby: Quite
the interesting strategy.
That said, defeating your plan
is a simple matter
of shuffling the cards
in a manner that obstructs
your vision of them.
Jotaro: Are you that dense?
Cheating is gonna be
damn near impossible
as long as you have me
as an opponent.
Just somethin’ I thought
you should be aware of.
( D’arby grunts )
okay.
♪
Narrator: The security seal.
an unbroken seal
is an irrefutable confirmation
that the deck has not
been tampered with in any way.
( Shuffles cards )
jotaro: Well,
there’s only one joker here.
Don’t see anything unusual.
- It’s a normal deck.
- ( Avdol grunts )
d’arby:
The page number is 538.
540. No, page 556.
I’ve still got it.
My ability to discern
page numbers by touch
is as sharp as ever.
it’s true
that jotaro’s star platinum
has incredible visual prowess,
but I can remember
the placement of anything
simply through
the use of touch.
Shuffle them all you want.
I still know the exact location
of every card.
Okay, open the game.
looks like
it’s the ten of hearts.
jotaro:
I drew the seven of cubs.
D’arby: Then it seems
like i’ll be dealing.
( Chuckles )
All right.
i need to shuffle
so star platinum can’t see.
If you would cut the deck...
D’arby: Thank you,
and now i’ll deal.
One for jotaro. One for me.
( Screaming )
avdol: Huh?
I-I don’t understand!
What happened?!
Jotaro, his finger!
Why the devil would you
use star platinum
to break d’arby’s finger?
Jotaro: Like I said,
you’re not gonna cheat
while you’re playing against me.
Avdol: Huh? He tried to cheat?
But he was only dealing
the cards, wasn’t he?
I didn’t notice him
do anything suspicious.
Jotaro: That’s what
he wanted us to think,
but take a good look
at the cards in his left hand.
Avdol: Ahh! I see now!
The second card is sticking out.
Jotaro: That’s the card
he tried to deal me.
the entire time, he was
pretending to deal the top card,
but the truth is
he was dealing me
the second card from the top.
That being the case,
it means the top card
would have gone to him.
If he’d gotten his hands on it,
the cheating bastard would
have had a total of three tens.
Narrator: This maneuver
is known as the second deal,
a devious
sleight-of-hand technique
involving the dealer
throwing out
the second card in the deck,
instead of dealing the top card
as one would expect.
when the technique
is executed by a professional,
the cheat is almost undetectable
to the naked eye.
And if that wasn’t enough,
d’arby can discern
the location of every card
in the deck by touch.
D’arby: You brutish imbecile!
How dare you break my finger?
( Gasps )
Jotaro: I was playing nice
with that attack.
You should count yourself lucky
I didn’t rip it off.
( D’arby grunting )
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
I guess I can’t let you
cut the deck anymore.
someone else
is gonna do it from now on.
That boy on the hill
looks up to the job.
( D’arby groans )
Have it your way.
Jotaro: Hey, avdol,
ask him over.
Avdol: Right away.
- D’arby: Most impressive.
- Avdol: Hmm?
D’arby: Successful cheating
requires
the element of surprise,
and it takes more
than sharp eyes to prevent that.
It appears I underestimated you,
as you saw through
my second deal.
I’ll accept my fractured finger
as proper punishment.
But from here on, i’ll devote
my full concentration
to winning the game, jotaro.
i’ve not done so
since my colossal gamble
on may 17, 1986.
I was playing
against a Japanese man
known as shozo mayama.
As the Victor,
my spoils included
his eight Tokyo properties
and his soul.
I will say this for mayama.
Wealth didn’t dull
his gambler’s instincts.
It’s only fair that I warn you
i’m not here
on behalf of lord dio!
I am here due to the simple fact
that I am a born gambler!
Avdol: W-what do you
think you’re doing?
Those souls are Mr. Joestar’s
and polnareff’s!
( Both gasp )
D’arby: I’ve done nothing more
than split their souls
into six chips each.
I’m sure you know this,
but in poker,
if you’re
on the verge of losing,
it’s perfectly acceptable
to fold.
However, if you use up
all the chips for the ante,
there’s no way to bet,
and the game doesn’t work.
To put it plainly,
winning back six chips
is the equivalent of winning
the soul of one of your friends.
Make sense?
All right then, jotaro,
if you still want to play,
you’ll have the opportunity
to win back the chips,
but before that, I need
to hear you say the words.
Jotaro: With pleasure.
I’ll bet my soul
on the game’s outcome.
D’arby: Okay.
Avdol: Jotaro!
D’arby: The pure white chips
in front of you
are a physical representation
of your soul.
Once i’ve procured
all six of those chips,
your soul will be added
to my collection.
♪
( D’arby chuckles )
For my opening action,
I shall bet one chip
of polnareff’s soul.
( Chuckles )
Let’s begin.
Narrator: When beginning
a new game of poker,
each player is dealt
a total of five cards.
Players can improve their hand
by swapping out cards.
Though it seems straightforward
on the surface,
it’s the betting aspect
that makes poker
a game of determination
and psychology.
D’arby: Now then, what to do?
Ah, I think i’ll raise.
Jotaro, you should bear in mind
that those six chips beside you
are your soul.
Make sure you think carefully
before making a move.
- Boy: Eh?
- Avdol: Listen.
It’s okay if you don’t
understand what’s going on.
Don’t worry yourself.
You just focus your attention
on cutting and dealing
the cards, all right?
Boy: Uh, mm.
Jotaro: Give me three cards.
♪
D’arby: Would you look at that?
Such a serious glare.
Behind it must be
an outstanding hand.
i suppose
i’ll play it safe for now
and bet one more polnareff.
Jotaro: Call, one.
Avdol: If you don’t fold,
you’ll need three chips
per game, at the very least.
D’arby: All right,
bring it on, jotaro.
Jotaro: Two pair,
with eights and nines.
D’arby: Hmm.
That’s too bad.
Two pair, Jacks and queens.
( Avdol gasps )
oh, no!
d’arby: My,
that was a close one.
I was on the verge
of a crushing defeat.
( Laughs )
But as it stands...
♪
( Laughs )
Avdol: H-he only has three left.
Jotaro, what are you...
Jotaro: Okay, next game.
deal the cards.
♪
d’arby: You should
be careful what you wish for.
the next game
may well be your last.
( Chuckles )
I’ll change one card.
Huh?
( Grunts )
Boy: Huh?
d’arby:
What’s the problem, jotaro?
Hurry up, and check your hand
so you can make a decision as to
whether you’ll change or fold.
Avdol: Hey, jotaro?
Jotaro: No, it’s fine.
These cards will do.
- Avdol: Wha?!
- Boy: Eh?
D’arby: So sorry. Come again?
There must be some confusion.
Perhaps I misheard you.
I could have sworn I heard
you say, "these cards will do."
Jotaro: No, you heard right.
I’m fine with these cards.
I’ll play the round
with this hand.
- D’arby: Obviously!
- ( Slams table )
What i’m trying to ask is do
you intend to play those cards
without so much
as glancing at them?!
Jotaro: These cards will do.
D’arby: Enough subterfuge!
Answer me!
How can you play a round
with any sort of confidence
if you don’t even look
at the cards in your hand?!
Jotaro: Need a favor. You in?
- ( D’arby growls )
- Avdol: Favor?
of course,
but answer something first.
why are you hellbent
on not looking at your cards?
D’arby: Damn it, jotaro!
I demand that you answer me!
Jotaro: Let’s see now.
Raise you another two.
And while i’m at it,
i’ll throw in avdol’s soul.
D’arby: Argh! What?!
( Growls )
avdol: I admit you’re
an impressive opponent, d’arby.
Sure, you’re no match
for our stands physically,
but under pressure,
you can be
amazingly calm and clever.
Suffice it to say, i’m not much
in terms of being a gambler.
It’d be easy for you
to read me like a book,
so I could never defeat
someone like you,
but I have
the utmost confidence in jotaro.
i don’t know why
he won’t look at his cards,
but that’s none of my concern.
If he asks for my soul,
i won’t hesitate
to put my life on the line.
My soul is in jotaro’s
more than capable hands.
D’arby: So that’s
how we’re playing this.
It’s become apparent
that the two of you
have succumbed to the pressure
of our little game.
You there, I believe
you owe me another card.
Hurry, and deal me.
Boy: Y-yes, sir.
D’arby: Hmm.
boy: I dealt just
as you asked, master d’arby.
His hand is worthless.
There’s no doubt about it.
My skills as a dealer
never fail.
You’ve won. I know you have.
D’arby: Jotaro’s
under the assumption
the boy has nothing
to do with this,
but little does he know
everyone in this cafe
and within sight of this place
works for me...
Even the bartender
and those men.
No matter what, I can’t fail,
as my directive is to make sure
jotaro’s hand is weak.
Still, not looking at the cards
was a bold move.
He caught me by surprise,
albeit briefly.
it’s clearly a bluff.
How dare he bluff against me?
Does the fool really think
i’ll lie down and fold?
Hah! Very well.
If that’s your game,
i’ll match you
with six polnareffs, and...
I raise you joseph’s soul.
What do you think?
15 chips total.
( Both gasp )
Avdol: What?! Hold on a minute!
that’s not fair!
How can you raise your ante
when jotaro doesn’t have
any more chips?
d’arby:
He’s out of chips, you say?
There’s an easy way to fix that.
Avdol: What do you mean?
d’arby: Rectifying
your chip conundrum is simple
as long as my stand
has a written contract.
Once the deal is done,
it’ll have carte blanche
to take a soul.
Avdol: And exactly whose soul
are you talking about?!
( D’arby chuckles )
Kakyoin’s in the hospital.
Why don’t you
simply bet his soul?
Avdol: What?!
D’arby: Panic, fool.
Show me your doubt and fear.
Let me see you lose
that cool composure.
How dare he try to bluff me?
After i’m finished with him,
that poker face
will be a contorted ball
of anguish and misery.
Jotaro: Sounds like a plan.
I’ll see your bet
with kakyoin’s soul.
( D’arby gasps )
Avdol: Wait! Jotaro, you can’t!
Betting a man’s soul without
his knowledge is so uncouth!
Jotaro: Well,
it is kinda selfish.
( D’arby gasps )
hey, jotaro,
what did you just do?!
Jotaro: What did I just do?
What do you mean by that?
D’arby: You lit a cigare--
( groans )
Jotaro: What’s wrong with you?
Not feeling well or something?
D’arby: Impertinent--
why is he so confident?
could he have--
could he have used star platinum
to swap the cards
without my knowing?
♪
( Boy panting )
( D’arby groans )
Stupid brat.
What are you thinking?
don’t look at me
with that worried grimace
if jotaro finds out you work
for me, i’ll murder you.
( Gasping )
Compose yourself.
I have four kings.
The only hands that could
beat me are four aces,
a straight flush,
or a joker-led five of a kind.
In order to get his mitts
on any of those hands,
jotaro would have to switch
all five cards,
a challenge, indeed.
With star platinum’s speed,
there’s a chance he could have
switched a card, but five?
could he really do that
right under my nose? Impossible.
There’s no way I could have
missed him replacing all five.
I’m the great d’arby,
the king of games,
master at the art of gambling.
I’ve had enough of this, jotaro.
Your time has come.
He lit that cigarette
to psych me out,
so now I know he’s bluffing.
( Gasps )
Ah, you’re kidding me?!
You got a drink, too?!
When did you have a chance to--
you bastard!
How dare you make fun of me?!
Let’s finish this!
My hand is unbeata--
jotaro: Hold it!
Why are you jumping the gun
when I haven’t
raised the pot yet?
- ( D’arby gasps )
- ( Boy gasps )
- ( Avdol gasps )
- ( D’arby trills )
Raise the pot?! No!
You don’t have anything
to raise it with!
( Jotaro exhales )
That’s where you’re wrong.
i’ll raise you
with my mother’s soul.
D’arby: What?!
Avdol: Are you
out of your mind?!
Jotaro, why would you bet
your mother’s soul?!
♪
Jotaro: The entire reason
i came to Egypt
in the first place
was to save my mother,
so if I end up losing here,
she’ll die anyway.
She won’t mind
if I bet her soul.
So then, d’arby, for your sake,
I hope you have something to bet
that matches my mother’s soul.
- ( D’arby panting )
- Jotaro: I know.
For your ante,
I want you to tell me
the secret of dio’s stand.
( D’arby gasping )
avdol:
Judging from his reaction,
he indeed knows dio’s secret.
Unfortunately for him,
dio doesn’t take treason
sitting down.
if he tells us
the information we want to know,
he’s as good as dead.
Jotaro, if you’re
confident enough
to bet your mother’s soul,
you’re sure your hand
will win, aren’t you?
You wouldn’t let us down,
would you?
you’ve got
the winning hand, right?
Jotaro?!
( D’arby panting )
( Boy gasping )
( Jotaro spits )
come on!
are you gonna
call my bluff or fold?!
decision time!
Spit it out already! D’arby!
( D’arby wails )
( Gasping )
( Laughs )
I’ll say it.
- ( Crazed laughter )
- ( Boy gasping )
( Avdol panting )
D’arby: I’ll say it, damn it!
( Gasping )
I’ll say it!
I’m the world’s
greatest gambler!
I can do this. I’ll call!
Call, call, call, call, call,
call, call, call, call.
I’m going to call!
Ca--
( gasping )
C-c-c-c-c-ca--ca--
( coughing )
( Growls )
( Groans )
C-c--
( wails )
( Both gasping )
( D’arby coughs )
C-c...
( Wails )
( Gasps )
C-c--
I can’t do it! I’m petrified!
I’m too terrified
to say the words!
C-c-c-ca--
i--i can’t--
I can’t breathe.
( Gasping )
C-c-c-c--
( gasping )
- ( Avdol and boy gasp )
- jotaro: Hmph.
D’arby: Ca...
Avdol: That’s unbelievable!
his eyes rolled
into the back of his head!
( Boy gasps )
How is it possible
for someone to faint
while they’re on their feet?
Jotaro: He’s completely lost it.
The pressure was too much.
( Boy and avdol gasp )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar
and polnareff’s souls
are returning to their bodies!
Thank heavens.
( Both groaning )
jotaro: Mentally,
he’s already forfeited the game.
Deep down, he knew he had lost.
that’s why
the souls were released.
Avdol: F-four kings?!
are you telling me
he had four kings all along?
jotaro, I have to know
what cards you had in your hand
to inspire such confidence.
( Both gasp )
Boy: Like I thought...
( Avdol groans )
Boy: Your hand was shit,
absolute shit!
Jotaro: Even with
star platinum’s
incredible speed, he wouldn’t
have been able to swap cards
in front of an expert gambler
like d’arby.
It’s a good thing my bluff
and intimidation worked so well
with such a worthless hand.
good grief.
Had I known it was this crappy,
I would have freaked.
Avdol: What? What do you mean
you’d have freaked?!
Jotaro, don’t tell me
that you bet our souls
on that worthless hand!
Joseph and polnareff: Eh?
( D’arby laughing )
Avdol: It would appear as though
his collection of souls
has been released.
D’arby: Come on, everyone!
Let’s play a game of mahjong!
( Laughing )
Backgammon is a lot of fun, too!
Or we could play a game of dice,
even though I don’t have any!
Narrator: D’arby of
the osiris stand, retired.
( D’arby laughing, babbling )
Avdol: I doubt
that we’ll be able
to pry dio’s secret
out of him in this state.
jotaro: That’s true.
He was a formidable opponent.
It’s humbling to admit this,
but he almost took us all out
singlehandedly.
The guy was a force
to be reckoned with.
avdol: Indeed,
he was a fierce adversary.
( Polnareff groans )
I feel like death warmed over.
Joseph: Well,
I guess we can’t be
the heroes in every episode.
( Iggy barks )
♪