♪
Polnareff: You’ve
finally come out, dio.
( Dio laughs )
A job well done, polnareff.
you managed
to avenge your sister,
but what’s most impressive
is that you also found
the time to track me down.
( Polnareff scoffs )
I’ll gladly kill you
to celebrate,
but I think we should
start with this first.
( Spits )
( Dio laughs )
I’ll give you
a chance to rethink.
descend now,
and not only will you live,
you’ll be given
the chance to serve me again.
Or you could choose
to rise forth.
However, you’d be
ascending to your doom.
( Polnareff grunts )
When the two of us first met,
fear consumed me like a curse.
It gave your evil carte blanche
to manipulate me like a puppet.
That fear was the beginning
of a futile existence
with no end in sight.
It was a fate worse than death,
a wretched life
devoid of any desire
other than doing your bidding.
( Spits )
But that fear
has been eradicated,
leaving only
the burning will to fight.
I’ve spent 45 days traveling
with Mr. Joestar and the others,
and in honor of those
who died on that journey,
i’ll never fear you again.
( Dio slurps )
My, aren’t we confident?
Climb these stairs, and put
that bravado to the test.
Quite the interesting decision,
polnareff.
( Chuckles )
You’ve backed down after all.
Is that your clever way
of telling me
you want your former life back?
( Polnareff grunting )
( Gasps )
What in the hell?!
But I went up the stairs.
I’m sure. What happened?
Dio: Problem? You seem
to be shaken, polnareff.
But why is that?
Could the winds of fear
have extinguished
your burning resolve?
Perhaps the only steps you took
were in your mind,
and in actuality fear
overrode your consciousness,
wrestling control
from your brain,
causing you
to descend down the stairs.
Polnareff: No way!
i’m positive
I just walked up those stairs.
( Grunts )
( Gasps ) What?
Is he doing this with his stand?
No! It couldn’t be.
Dio’s stand is...
The world?!
What am I supposed to do now?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Dio: I’m curious, polnareff.
Have you ever wondered what
the human soul desires most?
- Peace of mind.
- ( Footsteps )
Subconsciously, all humans
wish to overcome their fears.
They seek fame, money,
and dominance of others,
all to obtain a sense
of everlasting security.
What a farce.
they create bonds
as a means of self-preservation.
They say they wish
to help others
purely for the sake
of love and justice,
but it’s only to settle
their feeble minds.
Humanity’s greatest desire
is to latch on to Serenity.
So why? Why refuse to serve me?
What greater Serenity is there?
Return to me, and all
I speak of will be yours.
You don’t want to challenge me.
There’s just no point
in running headlong
into a meaningless death.
You deserve much more.
Polnareff: No,
am I seriously
letting him draw me back in?
dio: You’re
a talented stand user.
It would be a shame to kill you.
Turn your back on joestar,
and live as my right hand.
I promise you unending peace
starting now.
Polnareff: I have to resist.
avdol, iggy,
I need your courage.
( Groans )
Cut the bullshit, dio!
i’ve already
stared death in the eye!
And i’ll gladly do it again
if it helps uncover
your stand’s abilities!
( Dio scoffs )
How disappointing.
Hmm.
Time to meet your end,
polnareff!
Polnareff: So that’s your stand,
the world! Bring it!
Dio: Muda! Muda! Muda!
Muda! Muda! Muda!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Polnareff: Huh?
Dio: Mm? ( Chuckles )
♪
Polnareff: It’s Mr. Joestar!
Joseph: There’s no need
to worry, polnareff.
( Dio sighs )
Men: Dio!
Joseph: That was dio!
After him!
Polnareff: I have to tell you
something first!
It was only out in the open
for a moment or two,
but I saw him use his stand.
uh, well,
I didn’t actually see it,
but I did feel it
in a manner of speaking.
It’s complicated, but here’s
the long and short of it.
I was heading up the stairs
to beat the life
out of that bastard
when suddenly I was
back where I started.
believe me,
I know what i’m saying
doesn’t make any sense at all.
i can’t wrap my head
around what happened either.
i feel like i’m
losing my mind over here.
I’m sure he wasn’t using
any sort of hypnosis.
I’d say super speed,
but there’s no way.
All I know is that I sensed
something utterly terrifying.
♪
jotaro: Hey,
where are iggy and avdol?
( Both gasp )
( Polnareff gasps )
They didn’t make it.
They’re both dead.
They died trying to save me.
( Jotaro shudders )
Joseph: Is that so?
( Kakyoin sighs )
We should go.
Look, Mr. Joestar.
The sun is setting.
Let’s hurry.
Yeah, you’re right.
( Vampire yelps )
Kakyoin: All right, out with it!
What’s waiting for us upstairs?
Vampire: The--the towers!
there’s also
another room at the top!
It’s where lord dio
dwells during the day!
kakyoin: Is there
another staircase to the tower?
Vampire: No, this is the only
set of stairs that leads there.
Kakyoin: In that case,
lead the way.
♪
- ( Joseph grunts )
- ( Jotaro grunts )
Star platinum: Ora!
( Vampire shrieks )
Joseph: So that’s him.
The two of us have never met,
but i’ve known
about this monster
for longer
than I care to remember.
How could I not know this fiend?
the thought of him
has been burned into my mind
ever since the day I was born.
Same for jotaro.
We’d hoped this day
would never come,
that we’d never
have to face dio,
but as joestars,
we knew we’d eventually
have to destroy him.
Kakyoin: I have no regrets.
I came on this journey
of my own free will,
so I can live with whatever
happens from here on out.
Polnareff: I’ve never
seen things more clearly.
It’s like a light of clarity
has washed over me.
My friends are that light,
while dio is darkness.
My body may be
broken and battered,
but the fear has vanished.
Virtue and light
has purified my soul.
Joseph: We’ll attack
the moment dio
steps out of the coffin.
Stay at the ready.
We don’t know what tricks
he has up his sleeves.
It’s time, loser.
Open the coffin.
( Vampire whimpers )
Whatever happens, lord dio,
you have to know
I never betrayed you.
i only led
these degenerates here,
because I knew you had the power
to easily dispose of them!
As certain as a man
wetting himself
when pissing in the wind,
your victory is assured.
You are all-powerful.
Please don’t be angry with me!
Joseph: Enough of the groveling!
Open the damn coffin!
( Vampire laughs )
Please, i’m begging you,
give these bastards
a cruel and horrifying end...
Lord dio!
( Lid grinding )
Joseph: Get ready, everyone.
- ( Men gasp )
- Vampire: Huh?
Why?
( Men gasp )
vampire:
I don’t know what’s going on.
How’d I get in here?
I was just opening...
Joseph: What the hell?!
how did he--
my eyes were locked on loser boy
the entire time.
Did anyone else see him
get in the coffin?
Wait! Did someone put him
in there without us knowing?
polnareff: No, I was
watching him just like you were.
He’s opening the coffin
one second,
and the next, he’s inside it.
kakyoin:
You’re right, polnareff,
but I don’t believe
it’s a mind trick,
and it’s
not super speed either.
Jotaro: Good grief.
Is he playing games with us?
♪
( Men gasp )
Joseph: Get out of here!
( Polnareff grunts )
damn you!
Joseph: What are you doing?!
Come on!
Polnareff: Let me go!
Kakyoin: Okay, what was
that feeling back there?
The ominous presence
it was giving off
was far more powerful
than any stand
our group
has ever encountered before!
It was like knowing a bulldozer
is coming after you
just from the sound
of its roaring engine!
Joseph: Yeah, I sensed it, too,
an insane lust to kill us.
It felt like somebody
shoving an icicle up my ass!
If we hadn’t escaped
when we did,
whatever that was
would have killed us for sure!
♪
Damn it! Just look at the sun.
It’s almost gone
below the horizon.
Kakyoin: Dio will have
the advantage in the dark.
( Jotaro sighs )
Polnareff: Hang on. Come again?!
Please don’t tell me
you guys are planning
to run away
and hide until dawn.
Listen to me, Mr. Joestar.
I’m finishing this.
There’s no way i’m packing up
and heading for the hills.
Kakyoin: You’re right. We have
to see this through to the end.
( Joseph groans )
I wanna get this over with
as much as you do,
but the tide of battle
has turned.
While not up close, we’ve faced
his stand, the world,
but we still have no idea
what its powers are.
We’re fighting blind here.
Think of it this way.
It’s like mountain climbing
without knowing the route.
If we try to fight dio
right now, we’ll all die.
That fact is as inevitable
as burping after knocking back
a couple of colas.
( Polnareff grunts )
Joseph: Dio would be a fool
not to come racing after us,
but he only has
until sunrise to kill us.
in the meantime,
we need to learn the extent
of his stand’s power
and find a way to put him down.
If we can just hold out
until then--
polnareff: No way!
I’m not going back on my word!
Avdol and iggy died
because of my weakness!
I have to kill dio.
I’ll go to hell and back
to do it,
but what I won’t do is
run away from my obligation!
joseph: No!
Come back, polnareff!
Jotaro: Forget it.
He’s not gonna listen.
Kakyoin: Jotaro, what do
you think we should do now?
Jotaro: He went down there
to fight dio.
as we retreat,
we’ll also be fighting him,
which means we’ll be attacking
from both sides at once.
( Both gasp )
Joseph: Hey, buddy,
let us buy this truck off you.
What do you say?
Driver: The hell
is wrong with you?!
This baby’s my bread and butter!
No way i’d--
it’s all yours.
Joseph: Buckle up, kakyoin.
♪
( Dio chuckles )
Polnareff: There you are, dio.
Think i’ll just run ’til dawn?
You’ve crossed
the wrong frenchmen.
I’ll settle this on my own
if I have to.
So what if I don’t know
how dio’s stand works?
i’ll just find
another way to defeat him.
He’s dead.
Jotaro: Hold it, polnareff.
I had them let you go,
’cause convincing stubborn guys
like you is a pain in the ass,
but the old man and kakyoin
insisted I stay close and
watch your back, so here I am.
Polnareff: Jotaro!
( Jotaro chuckles )
Oh, good grief.
♪
( Car horn honks )
Dio: The automobile,
such impressive power and speed.
When I was young,
all we had were
shabby horse-drawn carriages.
Man: Don’t move! What do
you think you’re doing?
This car belongs to U.S. senator
Mr. Wilson Phillips,
and touching it
results in a beat-down!
Huh?
( Screams )
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
( Whimpering )
Wilson: Hmm.
My, my.
young people these days
are so full of piss and vinegar.
Time’s are a-changin’.
( Chuckles )
Eh? ( Grunts )
( Screams ) Why would you?!
dio: Stop talking now,
and proceed to the front seat.
It’s time to drive.
Just who the hell are you,
sicko?!
After i’m finished with you,
you’ll rue the day
you ever barged into my vehicle!
Yeah, this is unforgivable.
No one gets away with doing
something like this to me.
i was valedictorian
in both high school and college,
not to mention captain
of the college wrestling team.
Even after graduation,
people respected me.
That’s how I became
a politician.
I own a villa on a thousand-acre
plot of land in Hawaii,
my gorgeous model of a wife
is 25 years younger,
and I pay more taxes
than anyone else!
I’ve destroyed every enemy
who’s ever stood in my way,
and someday
i’ll become president!
I’m the senator Wilson Phillips,
damn it!
listen to me,
you punk band reject!
I’m gonna make sure
you rot in prison
for the rest of your miser--
dio: Hear this,
as I won’t repeat it.
( Wilson groaning )
Dio: Drive the car.
( Wilson grunting )
( Thinking ) This psychopath’s
gonna kill me.
I have to get the hell
out of this car.
If I don’t, i’m a goner!
Someone, help me!
Huh?
What the hell?!
What was that?!
i’m positive
I jumped out of the car,
so what the hell
am I doing back in the car?!
I don’t get it!
What’s going on?!
dio: Your job is
to catch up to that truck.
Fail to do so, and you die.
Wilson: Uh, yes, sir!
How am I still in the car?
Of course. That’s it.
I’m a senator.
What can’t I do?
Yes, it makes total sense now.
( Crazed laughter )
Joseph: I still sense
dio’s sinister blood lust.
Its presence is overwhelming.
He’s coming for us.
You can bet your ass
he’s on our trail.
Kakyoin: Are you saying that dio
somehow knows
our precise location?
Joseph: Not quite.
He stole the body
of my grandfather,
Jonathan joestar.
I can sense his body,
but I can’t tell
if he’s nearby or far away.
I have a general feeling, but I
don’t know exactly where he is.
It’s like when we got to Cairo
and, while I knew he was here,
I couldn’t pinpoint his lair.
lucky for us,
the same thing goes for dio.
all he knows
is that we’re nearby,
but he’s unable to tell
the difference between us,
and he probably doesn’t know
we’ve separated,
which is good for now.
Polnareff: Why the hell
isn’t this working?
Cars always start up
when they do
this kind of thing in movies.
( Jotaro scoffs )
( Car horns honking )
Wilson: Seems like
there’s a traffic jam.
I’m sorry, sir.
the evening commute
is always bumper to bumper.
Dio: Move it.
wilson: Uh,
but we’re stuck here.
There’s just too much traffic.
Dio: Have you forgotten
there’s a sidewalk? Use it.
Wilson: The sidewalk?
B-but it’s covered with people
heading home from work.
Dio: And your point? Go.
Wilson: Yes, sir. ( Gasps )
- Dio: Faster.
- Wilson: Yes, sir!
( Engine running )
Jotaro: Okay, it’s running.
Hurry up, and get on, polnareff.
Polnareff: Oh. Yeah.
( Wilson cackling )
Oh, the things I do for you!
but i’ve done
everything you’ve asked,
so you’ll spare my life, right?
There’s no need to kill
a helpless senator!
Dio: Wrong.
( Wilson cackles )
( Thinking )
I have to be dreaming.
What other explanation
is there?
As if a senator like me
could be killed.
Whoo-hoo-hoo! It’s just a dream!
( Laughs )
Dio: Found you.
now get closer.
We need to catch up to them.
I can’t use the world
if i’m this far away.
Look. Here he comes.
You see that car?
That’s dio’s ride.
Kakyoin!
♪
Dio: Hmm. It’s kakyoin’s...
Hierophant green:
Take this, dio!
Emerald splash!
( Gasps )
( Wilson yelps )
Hierophant green: Unbelievable!
He deflected my attack
with a flick of a finger.
He barely moved.
But how do you like this?!
( Wilson yelps )
Hierophant green: He even dodged
the concentrated splash?
damn it!
( Gasps )
When did he bring out his stand?
How could I have missed that?!
( Grunting )
Dio: Well, that’s a shame.
He’s too far away now.
My punch seems to have thrown
him out of the world’s range.
( Wilson yells )
What’s happening?!
dio: And what
precisely would I gain
by explaining
this situation to you?
Pay attention to the road,
and drive. ( Chuckles )
( Kakyoin panting )
Joseph: Be careful, kakyoin!
You were way too close to it,
kakyoin: Please, forgive me.
I didn’t mean--
it was only a few months ago
when dio asked me
if I was, "really going
to vomit out of fear."
That monster had the audacity
to tell me I should relax.
Bastard, never again.
I’ll never lose to you again.
joseph:
Are you all right, kakyoin?
Did you catch a glimpse
of the world?
Kakyoin: Yes, I saw it
when I attacked dio
from ten meters away.
If I had gotten any closer,
I would have been done for.
But we know one thing
for certain.
His stand holds a power
more horrific than we
could have ever imagined.
However, we know
two things about it.
First, his stand
doesn’t have the reach
of my hierophant green
or your hermit purple.
It’s a close-range power stand,
like star platinum,
and has a range
of about ten meters.
Second, it attacked
with its fist,
so it doesn’t use projectile
weapons, like bullets.
that being said,
if we can sneak up on him
and get within range,
we just might have a chance
of finishing him off.
joseph: We have
to figure out his secret.
Even so, we have to exercise
extreme caution
when approaching this bastard.
Hold on.
Why’d his car suddenly stop?
( Kakyoin grunts )
incoming!
We’re about to be hit!
( Joseph groaning )
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar!
♪
( Dio chuckles )
Joseph: What are
you doing, kakyoin?
Kakyoin: I understand now.
I know now how to uncover
the secret of dio’s stand.
♪