♪
Joseph: This room looks like
it was on the receiving end
of a tornado.
I don’t understand how this hole
could be perfectly spherical.
What is going on?
Kakyoin: I’m not sure,
but the destruction
spreads into
the other room, too.
Joseph: It’s safe to say
avdol and the others
made contact with the enemy.
Here we go.
Break down this door, jotaro.
- We’re going in.
- Jotaro: Roger.
Star platinum: Ora!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Polnareff: Au revoir, iggy.
( Iggy yelps )
( Whimpers )
( Silence )
( Clang echoes )
♪
( Cool ice panting )
( Grunts )
Polnareff, the blood
that stains my body
is avdol’s handiwork,
not yours.
( Panting )
My plan was to eradicate
you both simultaneously,
but due to avdol’s intervention,
your demise was postponed.
Anyone else would have
instinctively saved himself
over risking life and limb
to come to the aid
of an oblivious comrade.
that alone makes him
responsible for my injuries.
He may have been able
to injure me,
but it’ll take far more than
that to send me to the grave.
Now i’ll set my sights
on the other interlopers.
i’ll kill them
in the name of lord dio.
- ( Gasps )
- Polnareff: Damn it.
I told you not to use
your stand, iggy,
but you just had to show off,
didn’t you?
Stupid dog.
Why’d you have to do it?
Cool ice: Polnareff?
Narrator: As far as cool ice
was concerned,
iggy was nothing more
than a filthy stray
without resolve or pride,
but by its very nature, a stand
is a manifestation of the soul,
and iggy’s had acted
of its own volition
with something compelling it
from deep within.
( Iggy gags )
( Polnareff gasps )
His sand, its spirit is gone.
How could this have happened?
Damn it.
All that’s left
is a lifeless husk.
The chill of death
is in the air,
and another life
has been cut short far too soon.
Why am I the only one
who survived?
( Chorus vocalizing )
Ig--( Sobbing )
Iggy!
( Cool ice roars )
Polnareff: You’re too slow
for your own good, cool ice,
but you know something?
You’re right.
I had some pretty
selfless friends, huh?
I was supposed
to look out for iggy,
but instead he saved my ass.
( Silver chariot grunts )
Polnareff: Damn it.
How could this be happening?
I’ve only just begun to realize
what he meant to me.
This is how it always is.
i don’t get it
until after they’re gone.
You were a miserable
little mutt from the start,
but despite that,
you never failed
to find new ways to impress me.
You were a proud bastard who
lived life by your own rules,
and we were the ones
who mistook your self-respect
as indifference.
I told you not to save me.
Damn it, flea bag, why’d you
have to be so stubborn?
( Crying )
( Cream growling )
Polnareff: I knew it.
I’ve figured out
what you are, cool ice.
( Cream yells )
( Silver chariot yells )
( Cool ice screams )
♪
( Cool ice growls )
Polnareff: I knew there was
something was strange about you.
You’re an immortal.
Dio somehow found a way
to transform you.
( Cool ice roars )
( Gasps )
W-what the hell is this?
What’s happening to me?!
polnareff:
Obviously your precious master
made the changes
without your knowledge.
He gave you his blood,
didn’t he?
Guess he left out the part about
you turning into a vampire.
- ( Cool ice gasps )
- You’re just like dio now,
a disgusting, soulless vampire.
Cool ice: You bastard!
( Gasps )
Polnareff: Since you’re
only feeling it now,
the change must have started
after I stabbed you. Come on.
You made a vow to protect
your lord and master, right?
What are you waiting for?
bring it.
( Cool ice snarls )
Polnareff: Go on! Do your worst!
Hey, what’s the holdup,
cool ice? I’m waiting.
cool ice:
You’re not going to defeat me!
polnareff:
Now go to hell, asshole.
♪
( Gasping )
- ( Avdol grunts )
- ( Iggy grunts )
Polnareff: A-avdol, wait.
I-iggy!
( Groans )
Was--was that my imagination?
Or was it really...
I don’t have time
to sit and ponder.
All that matters now
is making it upstairs
and finding dio.
Mourning can wait.
I can’t fall apart after
everything they sacrificed.
( Gasping )
( Overlapping chatter )
Narrator: Japan.
43 days had passed
since jojo and the others
began their journey to Egypt.
Suzie q: Rosas, stop the car.
Hit the brakes.
I want to get out.
Rosas: Madame joestar,
I don’t mean to overstep,
but is now really the best time
to stop at a soba stand?
Suzie q: Well, of course.
I haven’t been to Japan
in a while.
I’d like to grab a quick bite
before visiting my little girl.
Hon, would you be a dear
and hold on to my turtle?
rosas:
Please, madam, you mustn’t.
Places such as these
are for common businessmen.
Ladies of your pedigree should
only dine at fine restaurants.
I am begging you, madam.
Don’t go in there.
Suzie q: Lighten up, rosas.
it’s so quaint,
I just have to record it.
Oh, the local flavor
is simply to die for.
Oh, this’ll be a good shot.
( Squeals )
( Rosas sighs )
- Guard: Mr. Rosas.
- Rosas: Huh?
guard: Judging by
the madam’s cavalier attitude,
I take it you’ve not told her
about holly’s condition.
( Rosas sighs )
suzie q: Hey,
what’s the holdup, rosas?
Get over here!
rosas: Oh,
i’m right behind you, madam.
♪
No, I haven’t uttered
a single word.
As far as she knows,
her daughter is battling
a severe case of pneumonia.
I’ve worked for the joestar
family for the past 30 years.
As for miss Holly,
i’ve known her
since she was a little girl
in grade school.
Believe me, I know that I
have to tell her the truth,
but I just
don’t have the heart.
even coming to Japan
hasn’t given me the courage.
Guard: Holly doesn’t have long.
If she’s not saved,
she’ll likely die
within the next few days.
Would you prefer that I
told madam joestar, sir?
Rosas: No, thank you, but i’ve
made my bed with the falsehoods
i’ve told the madam,
and now I have to lie in it.
I have to be the one
to inform her.
( Guard sighs )
rosas: Tell me,
are you absolutely sure
the curse afflicting miss Holly
will be lifted if dio is killed?
Guard: I am. Dio’s demise
will end this. Trust me.
holly’s body
is reacting to energy
from something known as a stand,
but only people with said stands
can observe the phenomenon.
Put simply, dio’s dark energy
is slowly destroying her,
but madam cannot see the stands.
instead,
she’ll have to bear witness
to her only daughter
in the throes of death.
she must know.
The time for secrets is over.
Rosas: Yes. Yes, you’re right.
Suzie q: There you are, rosas.
what are you
still doing out here?
Instead of sulking around,
come have some curry udon.
- ( Rosas sighs )
- ( Guard grunts )
Rosas: Please, listen, madam.
There is something
that I need to tell--
suzie q: Oh!
Oh, I must get some footage
of this delightful little
health-drink vending machine.
Another good shot!
Would you like me
to get you one, rosas?
Rosas: Wait! Madam joestar,
you have to stop this.
Despite appearances,
those aren’t drinks. Madam,
please,
you have to listen to me!
Suzie q: My! What is it?
Rosas: Well, uh,
it’s about miss Holly.
suzie q: Ooh!
Look at this Japanese man’s
unique fashion sense.
very nice.
Hi there. How are you?
Give me a big smile,
if you would.
Man: Huh? What the hell
are you doin’, lady?
Who gave you permission
to videotape me, huh?
( Rosas screams )
Please, madam, get in the car.
- Suzie q: Nice to meet you.
- Man: Come back here, damn it!
We’re not done!
I’ll be taking that camera
from you before you leave.
Who do you think you are?!
You’re just a damn foreign hag.
You lookin’ to see some blood
today, you rich bitch? Huh?!
Rosas: All right, that’s enough.
I forbid you to lay
another finger on madam.
( Man groans )
( Crashing )
rosas: Madam,
you should try learning
a bit more
about Japanese culture.
Suzie q: Okay.
( Guard sighs )
Rosas: I couldn’t do it.
I couldn’t tell her miss Holly
only has a few days left.
It would break her heart,
and that’s the last thing
I would ever want to do.
♪
we’ve almost arrived,
and I still haven’t told her.
I can’t put this off any longer.
We’ll soon be in sight
of the kujo house.
She needs to hear this from me.
( Groaning )
Suzie q: It’s okay.
I know there’s something
you want to tell me.
You don’t need
to pretend anymore.
i’m well aware
of what’s troubling you, rosas.
My daughter’s life is
in grave danger, isn’t it?
( Rosas and guard gasp )
♪
Suzie q: I called Holly
from New York a few times.
She put on a brave face
and pretended to be
cheerful and lively.
She tried her best to convince
me it was only a mild cold.
Whenever Joseph phoned,
he would tell me
his business trip
kept him very busy,
but that I had
nothing to worry about,
but I knew they were keeping
something important from me.
deep down,
I knew something terrible
was happening
to my daughter and husband.
I’ve been married to Joseph
for 50 years now,
and my sweet Holly
is my own flesh and blood.
( Men sigh )
Suzie q: I never pressed them
for more information,
because I was afraid
of what they’d say.
I wanted nothing more than
to see my precious daughter,
but the thought of what i’d
find here was almost too much.
Guard: You know this much,
so you also have the right
to know the rest.
As it stands, your daughter only
has a few days left to live.
That’s why Mr. Joestar
and the others went to Egypt,
to end the source
of her illness,
but there’s been
no news for a while.
rosas: Please,
can you find it in your heart
to forgive me
for not telling you?
there was nothing
we could do for miss Holly,
so I wanted to spare you
from the pain, but I was wrong.
I should have told you.
It was cruel of me not to.
( Crying )
Suzie q: I don’t want to hear
any more of that foolishness,
rosas.
No matter how grim things seem,
there’s still one thing
we can do for Holly.
( Men gasp )
♪
( Holly gasps )
( Chuckles )
Suzie q: Hi, sweet girl.
Holly: I’m so glad you’re here.
Suzie q: Listen to me
very carefully, rosas.
Right now, the one thing
we can do for my daughter
is have faith.
i don’t understand
everything that’s happening,
but here’s what I do know.
Joseph and my grandson jotaro
are putting their lives
on the line
in the hope of saving Holly,
and I believe they will find
a way to do just that.
He’s never failed me,
not once in the 50 years
I have known him.
he’s kept
every promise he’s made
since the two of us
met in Italy.
Once he’s made up his mind
to do something,
nothing in this world
can stop him.
Rest and believe in jotaro
and your father.
You’ll be better
before you know it,
and our family
will be together once again.
Holly: Thank you, mama.
( Rosas crying )
Madam joestar, miss Holly,
please hang in there.
( Crying )
( Running footsteps )
( Footsteps echoing )
Man: That cool ice,
Billie Jean,
even d’arby younger--
( Laughs )
I knew they were nothing
but incompetent fools.
( Laughing )
I shouldn’t laugh,
but knowing
they got what they deserved
feels so satisfying!
( Laughs )
That’s what the fools get
for calling me a loser.
But at least now we know
I wasn’t one after all.
Cool ice: Don’t be absurd.
you can’t
possibly defeat the joestars
using that pathetic power.
D’arby: Out of the way, loser.
vampire:
Hey, but that’s not fair!
I want a chance
to fight them, too!
Cool ice: You’re merely
an ordinary vampire.
billie Jean:
You’d best stay out of our way,
or we might end up killing you.
d’arby: Do try
to behave yourself, loser.
( Vampire groans )
i’ll be the one
who finishes off jotaro.
♪
( Kakyoin gasps ) Stop.
There’s something
up ahead to the right.
( Both grunt )
( Woman gasping )
Joseph: A woman.
( Woman screams )
Please have mercy on me.
I’m begging you,
don’t suck my blood!
Anything but that!
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Woman crying )
I swear i’ll do
whatever you want.
Just let me live.
That’s all i’m asking.
Joseph: Hey, easy now.
You need to calm down.
Woman: I won’t run away anymore.
You can trust me.
Please have mercy.
Joseph: Just breathe.
We aren’t dio’s minions,
and we’re
certainly not vampires.
We’re the good guys, so just
calm down, and let us help you.
Woman: You’re good guys?
( Gasps ) Good guys?
you’re really
not those evil vampires?
You’re actually going to help me
get away from here?
Jotaro: That’s right.
we’re good.
( Woman sighs )
( Groans )
Jotaro: Real good...
At punchin’ evil in the face.
( Woman squeals )
Joseph: If you still want help,
we’ll be happy to oblige.
We’ll help by sending you
on a one-way trip to hell.
- Sound good, kakyoin?
- ( Kakyoin grunts )
( Woman groaning )
Vampire: How? Damn it.
How? Tell me. How? How?
How did you figure it out?
My power is impossible to crack!
Kakyoin: Would this power
have anything to do
with the face of a woman
on the back of your head?
Joseph: For future reference,
when you flip your head,
you should make sure
your hands match, too.
- Vampire: Eh?
- Woman: Huh?
Both: Eh?
( Vampire gasps )
Shit. You’re right.
I never noticed.
I’m an idiot!
Jotaro: No, you’re a loser.
Now where is dio’s room?
out with it.
Kakyoin: Jotaro, try not
to knock him unconscious.
He can take us to dio.
( Vampire growls )
how dare you?
Don’t you call me that.
You’re just like
those other guys,
so you’ll meet the same fate.
I’ll kill you!
Lord dio’s power’s
made me immortal,
and i’ll use all of it
to rip you to pieces!
( Hisses )
Eh?
Jotaro: So unless I heard wrong,
you just said
you were an immortal,
so you’re a vampire like dio,
in which case, I can use you
as a practice dummy
for when I fight
against the real thing.
Joseph: Eh? Oh, my god.
( Star platinum yelling )
( Vampire screams )
( Grunting )
Jotaro: So you
really are immortal.
vampire or not, we can
still rip you into little pieces
and scatter them
around the room.
Well, are you takin’ us
to dio or not?
The sun is about to set.
Vampire: Okay, but can I
at least ask you one thing?
Jotaro: Hmm?
vampire:
How the hell did you know
the other stand users
used to call me "loser"?
Jotaro: Oh, man. Good grief.
♪
( Footsteps echoing )
( Polnareff winces )
I gotta hand it to him.
dio’s got
some pretty nice curtains.
( Winces )
All right, now I can walk and
even jump around if I need to.
It still hurts a bit,
but now’s not the time
to worry about a little pain.
Hmm?
♪
Dio: Ah, greetings, polnareff.
What a pleasant surprise.
Polnareff: Dio.
At last.