Boy: Ah, looks like
new pages are appearing.
I wonder what’ll happen next.
The brothers delayed their trip
and took a bus four hours later,
so they managed to avoid getting
into an accident. Yippee!
What adventures
awaited them now?
Once in aswan,
they made their discovery.
"Oh. There they are,
the five bad guys,"
cried the brothers.
But the brothers wondered,
"what could they
be talking about?"
The bad guys seemed so worried.
Man: Hmm. I think that’s them.
Boy: Little did they know
they had drunk poison tea.
( Gulps )
( Chuckles )
Brother, check it out.
Earth to big bro?
Man: Huh?
Huh?
( Chuckles )
So I just have to poison them.
Listen, little bro,
you and I are practically
invincible together.
Between your
clairvoyant comic stand
and my face stand’s
transformative ability,
no one can get in our way!
Those guys are as good as dead.
We possess the cards known
as thoth, the god of writing,
and khnum, god of creation,
and together we are
the bestest brothers ever!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Man humming a tune )
( Gags )
♪
Zenyatta: It’s here
in this cafe.
( Slurps ) Right at that table.
That’s where those guys
will drink their poison tea.
Mondatta: Yeah, my stand,
thoth, the god of writing,
has never been wrong
about anything
when it comes to predictions.
( Laughing )
Polnareff: Well,
are they gonna pull through?
Joseph: Luckily, avdol’s
major arteries weren’t damaged,
so he’ll probably
be released by tomorrow.
But, kakyoin, on the other hand,
has serious injuries
that need to be treated.
There’s a chance
he could go blind.
Polnareff: That’s a raw deal.
Joseph: I hate to say it,
but if his condition
doesn’t improve soon,
we might have
to leave him behind.
Polnareff: Hmm?
♪
Hey, since there are
so many cafes nearby,
how ’bout we
get ourselves a drink?
Joseph: That’s a great idea.
Which one did you have in mind?
Polnareff: Hmm.
There you have it.
The cigarette has spoken.
( Sighs )
Zenyatta: Hello, there.
Tell me, sirs,
how may I be of service?
Polnareff: Well,
tea sounds good right about now.
Jotaro: Same.
Zenyatta: Right, so three teas.
Be back in a jiffy.
Joseph: Actually, scratch
that order, if you would.
- Polnareff: Huh?
- Joseph: Hear me out.
We’re in enemy territory here.
This is dio’s dominion,
and since we don’t know
when enemies will attack,
we have to be cautious.
If we let our guard down
even for a second,
someone could poison us.
From this point on,
we’re only drinking
from bottles and cans.
Polnareff: Come on.
Are you serious?
Joseph: Completely. Hey, there,
you can forget the tea,
- and bring us colas instead.
- Zenyatta: Huh?
Cola?!
Jotaro: That’s right.
Something wrong?
Zenyatta: Not at all.
Okay, three colas coming up.
Joseph: Hmm?
Zenyatta: I’ll just
go and grab them.
Joseph: Oh, by the way,
if you don’t mind,
we’ll open them ourselves,
and to make sure
we’re not falling victim
to any funny business,
give us the third,
fourth, and fifth ones
from the far-right side.
Zenyatta: Now they want
unopened colas?
How am I supposed
to put poison in those?
Was the prediction wrong?
No, that can’t be it.
My brother’s comic
is always right.
Damn it.
I’ve got to get it together.
I just have to believe.
If I don’t have absolute faith
in little bro,
we won’t stand a chance.
Mondatta: Yes, my predictions
are foolproof, brother.
Man: You in the apron,
is this warm cola
your idea of a cold drink?
You must assume i’m
a real halfwit or something
to think i’d pay
for this excuse of a beverage.
Joseph: Wait. What?
The cola’s really not cold?
Zenyatta:
Sorry about the hassle.
The fridge is down, so...
Polnareff: Hey, don’t you think
you’re being a little paranoid?
Let’s say,
for the sake of argument,
that guy was our enemy
and he was trying his damnedest
to slip a little poison
into our drinks.
How would he have known
to come to this exact cafe?
I mean, this city’s not lacking
in places to get a drink,
and I chose this one on a whim.
I’d understand
if this were the only cafe,
but there are tons of ’em.
Joseph: My point is we can’t
be too careful around here.
Polnareff: Well,
if you’re that worried,
let’s go somewhere else then,
maybe the place
across the street?
Joseph: Mm.
- ( Man yells )
- Man #2: Fire!
Man #1: What do I do?
My cafe is on fire!
( Wails )
Some fool left
a burning cigarette in the road,
- and it ignited the trash.
- Polnareff: Uh, oh ,boy.
Joseph: You know what?
I think we’ll take
those teas after all.
( Zenyatta laughs )
Mondatta: Yes, we did it.
Polnareff: Ah, zut alors.
What kind of jerk would toss
a lit cigarette near the trash?
Really,
the nerve of some people.
♪
Zenyatta: Finally,
they’re drinking it.
Mondatta: Drink it. Drink it.
Drink it until it’s gone.
( Brothers laugh )
They drank it!
( Woman screams )
A dog just took my cake.
Man: Who the hell brought
a mangy mutt to a freakin’ cafe?
Men: Iggy.
Woman: Whose dog is this?!
Man: Will somebody please
get this dog outta here?!
( Brothers gulp )
( Iggy barks )
Joseph: Damn it, iggy!
Polnareff: Get back here,
you fleabag!
Zenyatta: Damn it!
They were just
about to swallow the poison.
Dumb mutt.
So what the hell’s
supposed to happen next?
Mondatta: Well, thing is
the page hasn’t appeared yet.
Also, while off, it wasn’t
entirely wrong. Be patient.
Thoth only has the ability
to see the near future,
so Patience is key.
Zenyatta: Next time, then.
When the next premonition
is revealed,
we’ll use it to destroy them.
This is what we
were meant to do.
Together, we’re
the bestest brothers ever, baby.
"’we failed to kill them
because of that darn dog.’"
mondatta: "’we were so close,’
fumed the brothers.
"The brothers were
beside themselves with anger,
"’cause their plan failed,
"but the brothers
didn’t give up,
"and soon they decided to follow
the three guys and their dog.
"While following them,
they met a man who had
a very annoying face,
"the kind of face that was
just begging to be hit.
In fact, it was the kind
of face the brothers hated."
Zenyatta: I must have hated
that face in a past life,
and a face like that
deserves a knuckle sandwich.
Mondatta: "Even though
he was a perfectly nice man,
big bro punched him anyway."
( Man groans )
( Gasps )
Mondatta: "Thus, the man
with the bad face ran away"...
( Man wails )
Mondatta:
"But fortunately for them,
"he dropped
a wallet full of money.
"’yay. We’re rich.
Whoopee!’ cried mondatta."
( Zenyatta laughs )
What a dumb-ass.
Mondatta: Yeah, thanks to that
smarmy-faced fool, we’re rich.
( Laughs )
Huh? Hey, brother, check it out.
- The new page is coming.
- Zenyatta: Oh.
Mondatta: "The brothers
continued their pursuit.
"The bad guys got in their car
and hurried over to the hospital
"to check on their friends
avdol and kakyoin.
"But they had no idea
zenyatta had made a bomb,
"placed it an orange,
and planted it in the car.
"Jotaro was blown
into a million pieces.
"His head was split in two,
and his blood
was splattered everywhere!"
L-l-l-look how clearly
the pictures
in the comic came in.
Zenyatta: I see!
♪
( Zenyatta humming a tune )
( Ticking )
( Mondatta laughing )
It’s true that my stand, thoth,
can only see the near future,
and most would see that
as a disadvantage, but--heh--
once the prediction has been
printed, it can’t be changed,
no matter what anybody does,
not ever.
Zenyatta: We’re gonna
blow jotaro to smithereens.
The bomb will detonate
three seconds after he sticks
his finger in to peel it.
It’s destiny.
( Chuckles )
This is the end.
There’s no way out.
Joseph: Hmm?
Polnareff: Who the hell
is in our car?!
Do you recognize this bozo?
- Joseph: What? Isn’t it jotaro?
- Polnareff: No.
Jotaro said he was
going straight to the hospital.
- Be careful.
- Zenyatta: Damn it.
Joseph: Don’t let him get away!
Mondatta:
You’ve gotta be kidding.
It’s joestar and polnareff.
Polnareff: Whoever you are,
come out this instant!
Joseph: What he said!
Out of the car!
( Both gasp )
Polnareff: Quit your stalling,
and get out of there already!
Joseph: Make it snappy.
Zenyatta: Hey, hey,
what’s the matter with you two?
It was me. Couldn’t you tell?
- Polnareff: Oh.
- Joseph: Oh,
so it was you, jotaro.
( Zenyatta chuckles )
My stand, khnum, gives me
the power of transformation.
I can alter my height, weight,
and scent however I see fit.
I even used my hair
to recreate this hat.
Polnareff: Wait. I don’t get it.
Last I heard,
you said you were going to head
straight for the hospital.
Zenyatta: Huh? I did?
Ah, the hospital.
I forgot something,
so I decided to come and get it.
Oh, that’s right.
I left my wallet in the car.
- Good grief.
- Joseph: Hmm.
Jotaro,
where’s your school uniform?
Zenyatta: Uh, uniform?
What’s he talking about?
What school uniform?
Polnareff:
Nothin’ personal, friend,
but that’s not really
a good look on you. Heh.
Zenyatta: Uh, ah, my outfit.
I mean uniform.
Well, it’s actually
at the dry cleaners.
I took it in for a wash,
but then I realized
I didn’t have any money.
Yeah, that’ll convince them.
I’m in the clear.
Polnareff: That so?
All right then.
You can go ahead and
hop in the car. Time to go.
Zenyatta: Huh?
Mondatta: Oh, no, not the car.
Then, that would mean.
Zenyatta: No, i-it can’t be.
If I get into the car
with this face,
that means the real jotaro won’t
be the one getting blown up.
Instead, it’ll be me!
Shit.
You know,
it’s a beautiful day out,
so I think i’ll go ahead
and walk--
polnareff: We don’t have time
to wait for you
to walk there, jotaro.
Things’ll go a lot faster
if you just get in the car
and ride over with us.
Mondatta: Brother, you have
to get out of there now!
( Wails )
Zenyatta: Crap, this is bad.
I’ve got to undo
my jotaro disguise
before it’s too late.
If I don’t,
i’ll be the one who gets
blown to bits instead!
That’s it.
I just need to throw it away.
I’ll covertly
get rid of this one
and put another one
in the car later
so it can blow up
the real jotaro,
thereby saving my ass.
I did it.
( Sighs ) What a relief.
I’m safe.
Polnareff: Hey,
what do you know? It’s iggy.
He’s chasing our car.
He’s got an orange in his mouth.
Did you steal that, iggy?
It’ll make a nice gift
for kakyoin and avdol.
Zenyatta: Hmm?
- ( Iggy grunts )
- Zenyatta: Wha--
yow!
Both: Come again?
Joseph: Everything okay?
Never thought i’d hear you
say something like that.
Zenyatta: Oh, really?
That’s weird. "Yow"?
You know, "yow."
Actually, I was pointing out
that there’s
a "cyow" over there.
Polnareff: A cow?
( Cow moos )
Polnareff: Man,
you sure are acting
pretty peculiar today, jotaro.
You’re usually a lot cooler.
I hate to say this,
but i’ve gotta wonder.
You’re not really a fake,
are you, jotaro?
( Zenyatta stammers )
Joseph: Hmm.
( Iggy grumbles )
♪
Zenyatta: G-good grief,
polnareff.
What the hell are you
even talking about, man?
By the way,
are we at the hospital yet?
( Chuckles )
Polnareff: Hey, jotaro,
i’m super bored,
so how about you show me
that trick again?
Zenyatta: Hmm. A trick?
Which one is that?
What’s he talking about?
Polnareff: The one
you taught me a while back.
You know, this one here.
Joseph: Hey, you’ve gotten a bit
better at that, polnareff.
( Polnareff chuckles )
Zenyatta: Oh, that’s the trick
you were talking about.
Thank goodness.
I know how to do that one.
It’s risky,
but I can pull it off.
Why didn’t you say so
from the beginning?
That’s an easy one.
Polnareff: All right.
In that case,
do the one
with five cigarettes, then.
( Zenyatta gasps )
F-five cigarettes?
Polnareff: Hurry it up already,
would you?
I wanna see the trick again.
Zenyatta: Why is this
happening to me?
Damn that jotaro, and damn
his stupid party tricks!
But if I don’t
at least try to do it,
they’ll really think
something is up.
They’re already becoming more
suspicious of me by the minute.
And polnareff,
loathsome idiot that he is,
is seconds away
from setting off the bomb.
All right, fine. Damn it.
I’ll do it!
( Grunts )
Have it your way.
Five cigarettes.
♪
( Joseph laughs )
Polnareff: That’s the way.
Now come on. Do the trick.
Zenyatta: All right,
it’s now or never.
I’m gonna do it.
I’m gonna do the trick, damn it.
Here goes nothing!
( Stammering ) Hot.
H-hot. Hot.
I did it!
Hot damn, I did it!
Both: Ah!
Zenyatta: There.
Did you see that? I did it!
A man can do anything
when his life is on the line.
Polnareff: Here.
Last time,
you did this super cool move
where you drank
a bottle of juice
without putting
the cigarettes out.
( Zenyatta stammering )
Polnareff: Come on. Drink up.
( Zenyatta screams )
Polnareff: Aw, you blew it!
Joseph: Jotaro,
are you all right? Oh, my god!
Zenyatta: Brother! Brother!
Please, little bro,
make that prediction
go away right now!
Tear up that page!
Mondatta: Sorry, big bro, but
the prediction can’t be changed.
Hurry, and go back
to your regular self.
If you can undo the disguise,
the real jotaro
will get blown up instead.
I believe in you, brother.
Polnareff: Jotaro, I know
we’ve said this already,
but you’re acting
really weird today.
Zenyatta: It’s nothing.
I just feel a little
under the weather is all.
Both: Hmm.
♪
Eh?
Zenyatta: Crap.
This couldn’t get any worse.
I know their type.
Since i’ve put them on guard,
they’re gonna interrogate me
and realize i’m an imposter.
If they figure me out,
they’ll kill me,
and if I don’t undo my disguise,
i’ll blow up
just like the prophecy said.
Ah?
That’s it.
I’ll just pretend i’m sick
and make them let me
out of the car
to relieve myself. Brilliant.
Polnareff: Jotaro,
I couldn’t help but notice
the way you’re
clasping your hands.
Aha! Are you aware
you’ve got your left thumb
on top of the others?!
Well, are you?!
- ( Zenyatta gasps )
- Polnareff: Hmph!
Zenyatta: Damn it.
I wasn’t prepared for this.
Does jotaro have a weird tic
that causes him
to clasp his hands
with his right thumb on top?
Who even notices
something like that?
What am I gonna do?
( Polnareff laughs )
That just proves
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that you were a woman
in a past life!
And since, unlike you, I always
put my right thumb on top,
it proves that I was a man
in my past life.
Joseph: Wow, now how about that?
I always put my left thumb
on top, as well.
Polnareff: Sorry, Mr. Joestar,
but that proves you, too,
were a woman in a past life.
Joseph: Says you.
How does it prove anything?
How do thumbs factor
into reincarnation?
That’s so stupid.
- ( Both laughing )
- ( Zenyatta groaning )
Now I really do feel sick.
These rabid lunatics
are driving me up the wall.
All right, i’ll tell them
i’ve got a stomachache.
Polnareff: Jotaro,
what do you say we find out
which one of us can eat
an orange the fastest?
Zenyatta: Say what?
- ( Polnareff humming )
- Zenyatta: Hey, maybe you--
stop it!
Don’t do that, you idiot!
Polnareff: Whoa there!
What the hell
are you doing, jotaro?
Joseph: What’s going on
with you today, jotaro?
Zenyatta:
Oh, it’s nothing, guys.
Joseph: But this
isn’t like you at all.
Zenyatta: I just
don’t think it’s good
for you to eat
that particular orange.
Polnareff:
What’s the problem with it?
Zenyatta: Well,
it’s obvious, isn’t it?
Who knows where the heck
iggy found that thing?
For all we know, he could have
dug it out of the gutter.
You should eat a different one.
Polnareff: Thanks for caring,
but it doesn’t look
bruised or dirty,
so I think i’ll be fine.
I’ll eat this one,
and you can have one of those.
I can’t wait to see the look
on your face when I win.
- Zenyatta: Ow! The pain!
- Both: Huh?!
Polnareff: Hey, what’s wrong?
Zenyatta: Please, stop the car.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Come on. Stop the car! Hurry!
Polnareff: Does your stomach
really hurt that bad?
( Zenyatta groans )
I can’t hold it anymore!
Let me out! Let me out!
I’ll go behind that rock!
Joseph: The hospital’s
right there. Just hang on.
Zenyatta: No, no,
go on ahead without me.
I’ll catch up
once i’m done. Ohh!
♪
( Panting )
Polnareff: Not so fast, jotaro.
( Both groan )
( Zenyatta gasping )
♪
( Both groan )
( Groaning )
♪
Polnareff: Take this. It’s--
zenyatta: Yes!
I did it!
I can’t believe I did it!
I actually managed to get out
of that metal deathtrap alive!
I’ll go behind that rock
and undo my disguise.
Polnareff:
He brought up a good point.
Who knows where iggy
found this orange?
For all we know, it could have
been lying in the gutter.
Do you wanna eat it?
Joseph: Nah. You can toss it.
Zenyatta: Success!
Now I can use khnum’s powers
to transform back to normal.
After that, they’ll get
what’s comin’ to ’em,
and the zenyatta mondatta
brothers will have won again.
( Laughs ) We win.
( Laughs )
Uh--( Gasps )
( Ticking )
Are you kidding me?!
( Gasping )
Polnareff: Huh?
Did you hear that sound?
Joseph: Just forget it.
It was probably construction.
( Sizzling )
Mondatta: Oh!
Big bro, are you okay?
( Gasping ) Speak to me.
Zenyatta: Hey, little bro.
I think we lost this battle bad,
really bad.
Mondatta: No, big brother.
No, no way.
Those wannabes haven’t beaten me
and my stand thoth yet.
I-i’ll destroy them all,
brother,
by myself, if I have to.
- ( Zenyatta gasps )
- ( Mondatta growls )
Zenyatta: No, don’t.
Don’t do this, brother.
These guys aren’t some rookies
you can push around. You’ll die.
Mondatta: I’ve already decided,
and I can beat them on my own.
I know I can.
Zenyatta:
You were always so shy.
You’ve really grown up,
little bro.
Mondatta:
I’m gonna kill ’em all.
What does the book of thoth
say next?
Huh? ( Gasps )
Man: This is them, all right!
They’re the ones who punched me
and purloined my wallet
while they were at it.
All right, men,
beat them to a bloody pulp,
and i’ll make sure
you’re rewarded handsomely.
( Men laugh )
Zenyatta: It’s him again!
Mondatta: I’m scared, brother!
This doesn’t look good for us!
"Despite his intense, yet
short-lived, burst of bravery,
"mondatta would have to wait
a while to avenge his brother.
"But try not to lose heart,
mondatta.
Life is full of wonderful ups
and terrible downs."
Polnareff: Huh?
Joseph: Well,
if it isn’t jotaro.
Jotaro: Hmm?
Hey, what took so long?
Polnareff: Forget that.
How’d you take a dump
- behind that rock so fast?
- Jotaro: Huh?
Joseph: I can’t believe
you got here before us.
You even found time
to go to the dry cleaners.
Jotaro: What the hell
are you two talking about?
- ( Siren blaring )
- Joseph: Hey,
it’s an ambulance.
Jotaro: Someone must be hurt.
Polnareff: Ah, man,
that’s unfortunate.
Jotaro: Hmm? Oranges, huh?
I was just getting thirsty.
Think i’ll take one.
Polnareff: Huh?
Joseph: What’s this?
Polnareff: That man’s clothes...
Jotaro: You recognize him?
Polnareff: Nope,
can’t say that I do.
Joseph: Right. Let’s go find out
how avdol and kakyoin are doing.
Mondatta: "And so the brothers
"eventually gave up
on their mission.
"The battle was over, and after
all the chaos and the pain,
jotaro and the others
were none the wiser."
Brothers: Ba-dum-tss.
♪
( Speaking and singing
in Japanese )