Narrator: Previously on
"jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
Roofer: I don’t think i’m
gonna be able to help you folks.
it’s been my job
to repair rooftops in Cairo
for around 40 years now,
and I can’t say
that i’ve ever seen
a place like this.
Joseph: And my daughter’s
condition is much worse.
at best, she has
three or four days left.
( Both gasp )
Joseph: I can almost feel it.
It’s like dio’s
right on top of us.
Avdol: We should get moving.
We’ll talk to everyone here
until we find him.
♪
( Polnareff moans )
It’s a real scorcher
out here today.
I haven’t had a shower
in almost two days.
It’s beginning to ruin
my je ne sais quoi.
Huh?
Uh...
Hmm.
Huh?
( Growls )
( Man grunts )
( Polnareff gasps ) Huh?
( Grunting )
What’s the big idea, asshole?!
You got some kind
of problem with me?!
Man: I got a problem
with where you’re sitting!
A cocky foreigner like you
has no business
sitting here, pretending to be
some kind of beggar!
don’t you have
a lick of common sense?!
who said
that you could sit here?!
Polnareff: Huh?
Man #2: Ah, you must be
a beggar from a foreign land.
I know this isn’t much,
but I hope it helps.
( Beggar gasps )
Polnareff: Thanks, but...
Beggar: How dare you?!
back off, pal!
this is my turf,
you poofy-haired blockhead!
polnareff: Huh?
What’s that supposed to--
avdol: Hey, polnareff!
Don’t just sit there
with your mouth agape.
Give that money to him
immediately.
- ( Beggar sighs )
- Polnareff: Huh?
Oh, I get what’s going on here.
He’s a beggar.
Avdol: You’ll have to forgive
my friend’s obliviousness.
He’s not accustomed
to the rules of this city.
polnareff:
Why didn’t you tell me
you were a beggar
in the first place?
beggar: It’s called
having a shtick, you numb-nut.
People around here
know me as a mute beggar.
Avdol: There’s something known
as a beggars association here.
Beggars have their own areas
where they’re paid to do nothing
but sit around and beg all day.
While it may seem strange to us,
the rules they’ve put in place
help keep everything
running smoothly.
- Polnareff: Get out.
- Beggar: Yes,
and that exchange from earlier
has hurt my pride.
- polnareff: Huh?
- Beggar: I wonder if i’d make
more money by disguising myself
as a foreign beggar.
The hobos, the are a-changin’.
Oh, by the way, I thought
I recognized you from somewhere.
if i’m not mistaken,
you’re avdol, the fortuneteller.
Way I hear it, you got spooked
and fled to Japan.
Apparently someone
was lookin’ to kill you.
Avdol: I’d rather discuss us
needing a favor from the one
who knows everything there is
to know about this area.
You’ll be well compensated.
Beggar: Hmm. Ah!
Avdol: It’s imperative
that we find this building
as quickly as possible.
We’re running out of time.
Beggar: Ah.
♪
I’ve done enough work
for one day.
You gents have my word
that i’ll find the mansion
in three hours.
Just sit tight.
Polnareff: Eh?
( Car engine rumbles )
By the way, did anyone
see where iggy ran off to?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Iggy snuffling )
( Dogs snarling )
( Dogs whimper )
( Iggy growls )
( Yawns )
( Flapping )
( Dogs growling, panting )
( Clang )
( Barking )
( Whoosh )
( Slam )
( Iggy gasps )
♪
- ( Gasps )
- ( Crunching )
( Iggy squeals )
- ( Helmet clatters )
- ( Gasps )
beggar:
That’s the place, all right.
Mission accomplished.
( Chuckles )
And it only took two hours.
If it exists in this city,
you can bet your ass
i’ll find it.
Huh? ( Gasping )
( Screams )
♪
narrator:
Iggy thought to himself...
Iggy: So that bird is
a stand user, same as me.
Given that it offed that guy
with a giant block of ice,
it must be
the guard around here.
it’ll kill anyone
who approaches the mansion,
which means
that bird’s next target
is probably gonna be me.
♪
Narrator: From early on,
the ancient Egyptians
recognized the prowess
of the noble falcon
soaring high
above the nile valley.
They trained the bird
as a hunting partner
and considered it
a symbol of horus,
guardian deity
of the royal family.
The falcon’s vision
is able to spot prey
from several kilometers away.
its oculus is forever
represented by the eye of horus,
an emblem of protection
and royal power.
The falcon soaring through
the air is called pet shop.
It is the wielder of the stand
horus, god of the sky.
Nervously, iggy thought...
Iggy: Damn it.
This is just my luck.
looks like
I stumbled on dio’s mansion.
Why’d I have to find this place
instead of one of the others?
what’s worse,
that falcon can use its stand
to shoot giant chunks of ice.
it’s like
a superpowered guard do--
actually, it’s more
like a guard bird.
♪
come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
I couldn’t care less
about this dio guy.
i got dragged here
against my will like some pet
and forced to be
one of the joestars’s allies.
like hell,
i’m gonna fight this thing.
All I want is a little r & r,
a girl of my own,
some place to settle down.
Fighting someone else’s battle
isn’t on my list
of things to do.
Besides, even if
I were to throw down
with tweety over there,
what would I get in return?
There’s no way i’m putting
my life on the line.
time to bring out
that old "dumb dog" routine.
That birdbrain will never
suspect i’m with those guys.
( Snorts )
♪
( Grunting )
( Babbles )
( Yelps )
those eyes.
That’s the thing about birds.
You can never tell
what they’re thinking.
I bet my stand could take him,
but then again,
there’s a reason i’m making
a fool out of myself here.
I’ve got nothin’ to do with
jotaro and those other guys.
Go back to your mansion,
you feathered freak.
( Car approaching )
Driver: Huh? A bird?
( Honks horn )
W-what’s with this bird?
why isn’t
the damn thing moving?!
No, it’s too late.
I’m gonna run it over!
( Iggy gasps )
Driver: I’ve never seen anything
like that bird in my life.
How could it fly under a car
so low to the ground?
It didn’t even try
to dodge out of the way.
it dove without
giving it a second thought.
( Iggy sighs )
Crazy bastard,
but it seems like the freak’s
lost interest in me for now.
Apparently it only
goes on the offensive
when people try to make
their way inside the mansion.
even so,
if jotaro and the others
ever end up finding this place,
they’ll have a hell of a time
trying to get in.
Oh, well.
That’s their problem
to deal with.
Boy: Buch! Tiny!
buch! Tiny!
Where’d you guys go?!
Hey, you haven’t seen
my dogs around, have you?
Their names are buch and tiny
if that helps at all.
Iggy: Get the hell
out of my face.
I’m a dog, pal. Even if I knew,
it’s not like I could answer.
What are you, stupid?
( Boy gasping )
Oh, no! That collar looks like--
I was right. It’s tiny’s!
I don’t understand.
Why’s it under this gate?
And why is there blood on it?
Iggy: Tiny and buch?
is he talking
about those big dogs?
Boy: Tiny! Buch!
( Iggy gasps )
What’s that kid thinking?
if he tries
going under the gate,
he’ll have to face the wrath
of that bird. It’ll murder him!
Boy: Tiny! Buch!
Are you there?
- ( Iggy gasps )
- Boy: Tiny! Buch!
( Iggy sighs )
Boy: Tiny! Buch!
Iggy: Don’t know why
i’m getting so worked up.
If some human kid
bites the big one,
it’s not my problem.
Survival of the fittest,
as they say.
- The stupid die first...
- Boy: Buch! Tiny!
Iggy: As do people
who act recklessly.
I’d rather stay out of this,
so goodbye, kid.
Boy: Tiny, buch, come out!
This isn’t funny!
I’m here to take you home!
- ( Squelch )
- ( Gasping )
♪
Holy sh-shit!
( Pet shop screeches )
( Boy screaming )
♪
Iggy: Good grief.
I have a soft spot
for kid dog-lovers.
Lucky for him.
Boy: Tiny! Buch!
( Groans )
( Iggy barking )
I didn’t wanna
get involved, but...
It’s up to me now!
( Gasps )
narrator: He had
finally revealed his stand,
confirming pet shop’s suspicions
about iggy’s
extraordinary canine abilities.
Iggy: Bring it, feather boy.
i can’t wait
to rip you to shreds.
Narrator: The falcon
is known for its ability
to dive at speeds
of over 300 kilometers per hour,
making it the fastest animal
on the planet.
Even at its trademark speed,
the falcon can spot its quarry
with pinpoint accuracy.
The prey, once discovered,
faces a violent death
by way of razor-sharp talons.
Iggy: Huh?
what the--
did he just smirk at me?
I could have sworn
I saw the corners
of its beak creep up.
But birds can’t smile,
can they?
( Gasps ) Wait.
What’s going on here?
The air, it’s getting colder.
Huh?
Hmm! Ice is coming
out of the ground!
I’m such an idiot!
I was so focused on the bird,
i didn’t realize
my feet were frozen over!
My stand’s feet froze, too!
Shit.
Icicles?!
( Pet shop screeches )
( Polnareff exhales )
( Sighs )
come on.
Give it to me straight, avdol.
Do you honestly believe
that guy has any chance
of finding dio’s mansion?
Avdol: I certainly hope so,
because if he can’t find it,
there’s no one left
in this city who can.
No one knows cairo’s
complex maze of streets
better than him.
Try and have some faith.
Polnareff: Faith is something
i’m quickly running out of.
we’ve been looking
around this godforsaken city
for three days with no luck.
I highly doubt some beggar
will find the mansion
in three hours.
Avdol: You’re starting to sound
like a broken record, polnareff.
You could at least
try to keep a level head.
joseph: Listen up.
We’re all on edge right now.
Until our friend gets back,
all we can do is try
talking to the locals.
Polnareff: Oh, brother.
And to make matters worse,
we haven’t seen iggy all day.
where the hell did
that stupid mutt run off to?
He better not be lost.
Joseph: For as long
as i’ve known him,
iggy’s always been
somewhat of a loner,
so i’m sure he’s
just wandering around somewhere,
killing time
before coming back home.
( Polnareff groans )
I used to think all dogs lit up
and wagged their tails
when they saw humans.
How’d we get stuck
with that little cynic?
♪
( Iggy panting )
I managed to get away
from it somehow.
( Winces )
its stand’s ice attack
took the skin right off my paws.
( Groans ) Damn it.
I knew I should have let that
human kid fix his own problems.
Its stand’s power
is nothing to sneeze at.
That was no ordinary ice,
and I bet he still
has a few tricks.
I’d better get out of here
while the getting’s good.
- ( Pet shop screeches )
- ( Iggy gasps )
- ( Shrieking )
- ( Pet shop warbles )
♪
Iggy: Talk about
holding a grudge.
( Moans )
( Pet shop warbles )
Narrator: Iggy disappeared,
but where could he have gone?
( Iggy sighs )
Damn it. That hurt.
the bastard
doesn’t hold anything back.
He’s strong for a dumb bird.
( Sighs )
this place reeks,
but it’ll have to do for now.
I have to keep quiet
and hide out down here
until he gives up.
( Stammers )
what is
this freaky bird’s deal?!
( Shrieks )
( Pet shop trills )
Iggy: Hey!
Surprise!
Thought you had me, didn’t you?
But what you "killed"
was my shape-shifting stand,
the fool!
( Pet shop clucks )
Iggy: Yeah! How do you like
them apples, featherbrain?
( Laughs )
Might wanna keep still.
Looks like you’re losing
a lot of blood there.
But before this
drags out any further,
you should probably know
I don’t give a rat’s ass
about you or your master dio.
What do you say
we call this a draw?
You got a few good hits in
with those ice missiles,
so we’re even, right?
( Pet shop spits )
Iggy: W-what the hell was that?
Who does this guy think he is,
Bruce Lee?
Hey, can’t you hear?!
I said i’ll stay away
from your boss’s mansion!
Let’s stop this, okay? Huh?
♪
( Gasps )
( Horus roars )
Iggy: That’s what
your stand looks like?
What am I gonna do now?
You stopped your wound
from bleeding by freezing it?
What the hell?! ( Yelps )
Blast it!
oh, no!
The exit’s blocked with ice,
and more’s coming this way!
Shit!
It’s starting to cover
the whole tunnel.
I gotta find a way out
of this deathtrap!
( Pet shop screeches )
( Iggy screams )
( Gasps ) No way!
It blocked off this exit, too!
( Yelling )
( Pet shop squawks )
iggy: Crap.
It’s got me in its crosshairs.
This bird’s insane!
this is more
than sheer determination.
this creep’s
a frickin’ killing machine,
and if it catches me,
it won’t just kill me.
It’ll eat me alive!
( Horus squawks )
( Iggy groans )
( Gasps ) What?!
( Grunts )
My paw!
( Pet shop trills )
Iggy: I can’t pry my paw loose!
( Pet shop warbles )
( Iggy screams )
♪