( Birds chirping )
( Knock on door )
Nurse: Rise and shine, sir.
Mr. Kakyoin, are you
feeling any better today?
Kakyoin: To be perfectly honest,
this new way of life
isn’t exactly agreeing with me.
I’m feeling a little on edge.
Nurse: And have you
had any discomfort?
Kakyoin: No,
I haven’t, actually.
The painkillers must be working.
Nurse: Good. Excellent news.
Doctor: We’re thrilled
that you’re feeling better.
Kakyoin: So, doctor,
about these,
how long will I
have to keep them on?
The thing is I can’t afford
to wait any longer.
( Doctor clears throat )
Look, kakyoin,
while your eyes will recover,
your condition is
nothing to be taken lightly.
You’ll be in our care
for quite some time,
so please be patient.
The fact of the matter
is we just don’t know
how long you’re
going to remain here.
- Just kidding!
- Kakyoin: Huh?
Doctor: It’s true your body
still needs time
to properly heal itself,
but for some strange reason,
doctors from
the speedwagon foundation
recently contacted us
out of the blue,
and they’ve asked
that we entrust
your medical care to them,
though I have little doubt
their state-of-the-art
medical treatments
will prove to be
more than effective.
But tell me, who are you
behind that schoolboy facade?
Surely you must know
that foundation is world-famous.
I can’t imagine
they’d want anything to do
with an average
high school student.
Kakyoin: Let’s just say
i’m fortunate
to have
a very dependable friend.
( Chuckles )
Thank you for everything,
Mr. Joestar.
I suppose we’ll be
seeing each other again
sooner than we thought.
Jotaro, polnareff, avdol, iggy,
just hang in there.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator:
Located in Southern Egypt
is the city of Luxor.
To the ancient Egyptians,
however,
it was the site of thebes,
and it is in this location,
on the west bank of the nile,
that the pharaohs of old
were laid to rest.
It is known
as the valley of the kings.
Avdol: Have you
heard of the tomb
of the great king tutankhamen?
It lies here
in the valley of the kings.
Polnareff: Wow, this place
is chock full of history.
Avdol: If what
i’ve heard is true,
some of the residents
of this area
still dig beneath their houses
in search of treasure
without permission
from the government.
Polnareff:
Think those ancient guys
left behind
any undiscovered treasure?
Avdol: Perhaps they did.
Jotaro: You guys see
where the old man ran off to?
Avdol: Oh, yes. To the bathroom,
and he took iggy,
since he can detect enemies.
Polnareff: Is that so?
Avdol: Do you need to go?
Polnareff: Hmm.
I might, if it’s
a normal bathroom.
- ( Joseph groans )
- ( Iggy groans )
( Joseph groaning )
Oh, my god!
The climate in this place
is so damn arid,
the crap dries up,
turns to dust, and blows away.
Which means
instead of using water,
this toilet
relies solely on wind.
And I don’t see
any toilet paper.
Hmm? Is that...
( Iggy groans )
Joseph: Exactly as I thought.
Some sort of sand basin.
So you wipe your ass...
- With sand?!
- ( Iggy groans )
Narrator: Desert sand
is as sterile as it gets.
Joseph: Oh, my god!
( Wails )
I think i’ll pull a polnareff
and wait ’til we
get back to the hotel.
What’s the point of a shack
if you’re going in a hole?
You might as well just do
your business behind a rock.
This thing is weird,
even for a place like Egypt.
Huh?
Eh? Eh? Eh?
- ( Iggy grunts )
- Joseph: Hmm.
This doesn’t make
the slightest bit of sense.
Who in their right mind
would think to put
an electrical outlet in a rock?
I wonder what it’s used for.
There’s no electricity
out here.
( Screams )
The damn thing electrocuted me!
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
is everything all right?
We should probably
get a move on.
( Joseph groans )
Huh? Oh, right.
- ( Sizzling )
- Just give me a second.
( Groans ) That scared
the living daylights out of me.
I can’t believe it’s still live.
I guess the cables must run
underground or something.
You can never tell
with this place.
It’s like traveling
through a fantasyland.
( Outlet humming )
♪
Narrator:
Card of the goddess bast.
Stand user: Mariah.
Mariah: Now how did
that old saying go again?
Curiosity killed the cat?
( Snaps fingers )
( Static buzzing )
Avdol: We could make it
to Cairo in two days,
but since all of us
are injured and exhausted,
why don’t we spend tonight
and tomorrow in Luxor
and use that time to recuperate?
- ( Hand clicking )
- Joseph: Hmm. Hmm.
Polnareff: Sounds good to me.
Ever since we got to Egypt,
the enemy stands have been
getting stronger and stronger.
We’ve been winning these battles
by the skin of our teeth.
Joseph: Hmm.
Polnareff: Hey, Mr. Joestar,
is something wrong?
Joseph: I’m fine.
My prosthetic hand
is acting funny. That’s all.
It’s nothing to worry about.
I probably just need
to oil the joints.
Polnareff:
Hey, there! Shopkeeper!
Can you please do something
about that radio? It’s busted.
Shopkeeper:
Man, that’s peculiar.
It was made in Japan,
and I just bought
the darn thing. ( Groans )
Polnareff: Well,
it’s just static now!
Turn it off!
Joseph: Huh?
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar?
Joseph: Hmm? Yeah, you’re right.
It’d probably be
in our best interest
to rest up
before heading to Cairo.
( Polnareff grunts )
Joseph: Remember,
we can’t let our guard down.
Okay, let’s find a hotel.
( Shopkeeper groans )
What’s going on?
Joseph:
Thanks for the drinks, mister.
Shopkeeper: Uh, come again!
♪
( Music playing )
Hey, look at that.
The radio’s working again.
( Man grunts )
- ( Humming )
- What the--
why’s the hammer
suddenly so heavy?
I can’t--huh?
♪
What the hell?
( Wailing )
Joseph: Hmm?
Man: Th-the nails!
Ohh! Oh, god, it hurts!
Polnareff: Hey, old man,
did you bang your finger
with the hammer?
You gotta be more careful.
You can’t just go
throwing hammers around.
It’s dangerous.
Jeez.
( Birds chirping )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
it’s time to wake up.
Mr. Joestar.
Polnareff: Hey,
hurry it up in there!
( Joseph groans )
Avdol: Polnareff
is going on and on
about the four of us finding
somewhere to eat breakfast.
Polnareff: Hurry,
and wake him up, avdol!
He’s got five minutes
before I come up there!
You know, I thought old people
were supposed to get up early!
Joseph: Damn smart aleck.
He has no respect
for his elders.
Tell him i’ll be down
in just a minute.
Avdol: Right.
Joseph: Well, that’s bizarre.
Why did my watch stop working?
( Avdol laughs )
You know, Mr. Joestar...
Joseph: Hmm?
Avdol: You toss and turn
in your sleep
quite a bit for a man your age.
You haven’t noticed yet,
but you’re facing the wrong way.
( Joseph sighs )
Avdol: You went to bed
facing south,
but woke up northward
like a compass.
Glad you still have
a youthful spirit.
I’ll be downstairs
when you’re ready.
Joseph: Hmm?
Hmm.
Something strange
has been going on
ever since yesterday afternoon,
and for some reason,
my hand is still acting up.
♪
Hmm?
- ( Wheels rolling )
- Huh?
Hmm?
( Yelps )
What is up
with this freaky chair?
The blasted thing’s
moving on its own.
( Grunts )
If I didn’t know any better,
i’d guess the floors
in this place were slanted.
For such a ritzy hotel,
it sure does seem
like it was cheaply made.
Woman: So where
should we go today?
Woman #2: Well, I had an amazing
time looking around karnak,
so i’d say something like that.
Joseph: Mm. ( Chuckles )
Woman #1: How about the valley
of the queens, instead?
- ( Metal humming )
- ( Shrieks )
What the hell do you think
you’re doing, you old pervert?!
- Joseph: Huh?
- Woman #1: Jackass!
Joseph: I don’t understand.
What the hell just happened?
♪
( Humming )
Woman #3: Ooh!
( Coos )
( Joseph groans )
Woman #3: I do appreciate
your forwardness,
but you need
to work on your approach,
you naughty, naughty man.
( Giggles )
But that said,
you’re just my t-y-p-e.
Mwah.
Joseph: Oh, my god!
( Gasping )
I was right!
Something’s wrong here,
really wrong,
and it’s been this way
ever since yesterday afternoon!
Ahh!
Wait. What the--
th-they’re stuck to my hand!
Hang on.
It’s all starting to make sense,
the reason
why all these metal objects
are suddenly attracted to me.
But it can’t be.
That’s impossible.
( Humming )
Yaah!
It looks like I was right!
My body’s turned into a magnet!
( Screams )
( Panting )
I think this insanity
might be the work of a stand.
But if that’s the case,
why can’t I see it?
How could these knives
and forks fly at me
if the stand isn’t nearby?
( Gasps )
There’s no way. Could this
really be a side effect
of the shock I took
from the socket
on that rock yesterday?
- ( Metal humming )
- Hmm?
( Grunts )
I can’t get out of it.
Oh, no. It didn’t
even cross my mind
that the escalator’s
made of steel.
This doesn’t look good.
The magnetic pull’s
getting stronger by the minute.
Hmm?
( Yells )
How the--
you there,
lady in the micro-miniskirt!
I need you to help me out!
Please, miss, i’m beggin’ you!
Not to be rude, but your chain’s
wrapped around my body,
and it’d be nice
if you’d get it off me
before i’m shredded to pieces!
There’s not much time,
so if you could push
the emergency stop button,
that’d be swell!
Come on, lady!
The chains
are pulling me tighter!
This thing’s gonna rip off
my hands and feet!
What’s the problem?!
Are you even listening?!
( Woman laughs )
Joseph: Hmm?
Enjoy the ride, Joseph joestar.
Joseph: What the hell?!
You can’t be serious!
If you know who I am,
that would make you
the stand user!
Joseph: So it’s you,
damn it all.
You were the stand user
all along!
( Metal humming )
Mariah: Once you’ve made contact
with the magnetic field
surrounding my stand, bast,
you’ve sealed your fate,
as there’s no escape
from its deadly power.
( Joseph wailing )
Please, let me out!
Someone stop
this infernal escalator!
( Grunts )
Hey, that’s it!
I’ll push
the emergency stop button
using my hermit purple!
That doesn’t make sense!
Where is it?!
The only reason that i’d have
this much trouble finding it
would be if it didn’t have one,
but that can’t be possible!
What escalator doesn’t have
a shut-off button?!
( Screaming )
It’s pulling me in!
Yah! My neck! My neck!
- Avdol: Hmm.
- ( Joseph screaming )
It’s gonna cut off my head!
I’m done for!
- ( Wails ) Save me!
- Avdol: Hmph.
( Clears throat )
Mr. Joestar, pay attention.
- Joseph: I’m gonna die!
- ( Avdol coughs )
Hello! Mr. Joestar!
- Joseph: Why decapitation?!
- ( Avdol coughing )
Joseph: Goodbye, cruel wor--uhh?
Avdol: The escalator
stopped some time ago.
I already pushed
the emergency stop button.
It’s on the side
instead of in the front.
Joseph: Uh,
everything is a-okay!
I just inspected this escalator,
and it’s in working order!
You’ll be happy to know
the emergency button works fine!
Hello, sir. You must be
the owner of this establishment.
If you don’t mind,
i’ll be needing your signature
right here.
Avdol: Hmm?
I’m lost, Mr. Joestar.
What happened?
Joseph: A stand.
An enemy stand
managed to tag me yesterday.
Now my body’s turned
into one big magnet.
- Avdol: Hmm?
- Joseph: You see?
The user turned me
into a magnet,
and now metal
is attracted to me.
Would you pull
this thing off of me?
It looks like the magnetic pull
is becoming stronger
the longer the stand’s power
remains in effect. Huh?
( Mariah giggles )
Joseph: That’s her!
That woman there
is the stand user!
We’ve gotta find
a way to stop her!
And I have to get rid of this
insane magnetic pull somehow,
or I won’t be able
to move my body at all!
Avdol: We should also get
jotaro and polnareff!
- ( Metal humming )
- Uh, what?!
( Groans ) It’s so heavy!
Joseph: Not again!
Avdol, there’s no time
to get the others!
Just look! She’s getting away!
( Mariah giggles )
Avdol: Move away, Mr. Joestar!
Just run after her!
Joseph: Right! On it!
I have to get
a good look at her face.
( Gasps )
But this is...
Avdol: Clever. She went
into the ladies’ room. Now what?
Joseph: Mm...
Guess i’m going in.
My life is on the line here,
so I guess I have to catch
this Vixen no matter what.
Avdol: But, Mr. Joestar,
you can’t!
( Birds chirping )
Jotaro: What’s the holdup?
Polnareff: That’s what
i’d like to know.
Avdol went inside to find him,
but he hasn’t come back either.
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
What if those two snuck off?
Jotaro: What?
Polnareff:
They’re probably having
an amazing breakfast
as we speak!
( Jotaro sighs )
It’s more likely he’s
taking his time in the bathroom,
but if they don’t show up
in the next five minutes,
we’ll go look for ’em.
Polnareff: Yeah, the bathroom.
Guess that makes sense.
You know, come to think of it,
the bathrooms in this hotel
are spotless.
♪
Avdol: So, Mr. Joestar,
now that we’re in here...
( Joseph grunts )
Avdol: It’s just as I expected.
We have a problem on our hands.
- Joseph: Shh.
- ( Avdol gasps )
Shh. Forgive me, but i--
I haven’t the foggiest clue
which stall she’s in.
Do you have a way to find her?
Well, for one,
she’s got amazing legs.
Avdol: Her legs?
Joseph: That’s right.
Just look for those legs.
Believe me when I say
you can’t miss ’em.
Avdol: So we
have to take a peek?
( Gasping )
No, she’s not in this one.
Nope.
No again.
Mr. Joestar,
I think I found her.
Come over here.
Are these her legs?
( Joseph grunts )
Eh? Huh?
( Women gasp )
( Both groan )
( Toilet flushing )
Woman #3: Oh, my. You’re that
handsome fellow from before.
You came all
the way here to find me?
You dirty boy, the heart wants
what the heart wants.
Mwah!
Joseph: Holy shit!
It’s--it’s the hag
from earlier,
from the second floor!
Avdol: This is bad!
We got the wrong person!
But I thought for sure those
were the legs of the stand user!
Joseph: How could you
screw that up?!
- Run, avdol!
- Avdol: What?!
( Women scream ) Pervs!
( Men yell )
I don’t deserve to be treated
like a peeping Tom!
Polnareff’s the one
who should be getting called
a dirty pervert!
Woman: Dirty old man!
Woman #2: Disgusting!
Woman #4: Perverts!
Woman #3: Oh, no!
He’s scrumptious.
( Mariah giggles )
Avdol: Look, there she is!
She’s headed that way!
Joseph: Damn it!
How did that harlot
get so far away?! After her!
I forgot to tell you.
Whatever you do,
it’s imperative that you refrain
from touching
any electrical outlets!
It doesn’t matter
where they are!
Stay away from them!
She manifests her stand
through the outlets!
The moment you touch one,
you’ll get zapped,
and the magnetism
will begin to take effect!
Avdol: Eh? I’m afraid
I already did, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: What?!
Where did it happen?!
Avdol: I touched one
when I pushed
the emergency stop button
on the escalator.
There was a socket
directly beside it.
If only I had known!
Joseph: Damn!
That conniving minx.
- ( Humming )
- Avdol: Excuse me, Mr. Joestar.
Would you mind
giving me some space?
I can’t run with you
stuck to me like this!
Joseph: I was about to say
the same to you, avdol!
Avdol: What are you
talking about, sir?
You’re the one
who’s running close to me!
- ( Crackling )
- ( Both grunt )
Joseph: If what I know
about magnets is true,
we’re being forced together!
Avdol: I cannot believe
she managed
to turn me
into a magnet as well.
Mr. Joestar, I really hate
saying this, but...
Joseph: Yeah, I know!
We’ve gotten ourselves
into a world of trouble.
( Mariah laughs )
Joseph: This is ridiculous!
Avdol: I’m at a complete loss.
( Mariah laughs )
Joseph: She’s so powerful!
( Mariah laughing )
♪