♪
Polnareff: Hmm?
Barber: You did say under
the chin, right, polnareff?
Polnareff: What the hell?!
( Barber slurps )
Remember me, you fool?
I’m the Anubis stand
you fought earlier.
( Polnareff gasps )
Merde! What do I do now?
Barber: Goodbye! I’m gonna
shave your jaw clean off!
( Screams )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Polnareff: Who--who the hell
are you, really?!
And what have you done
with the barber?!
♪
Wait. Could it possibly be that
the sword is actually the stand?
Could it be controlling
the barber?
So the guy at kom ombo
wasn’t a real stand user!
Barber: Polnareff!
Polnareff: But in the end,
it doesn’t matter.
I’m still
way out of your league, buddy.
( Barber chuckles )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Groans )
What?! How are you so strong?!
Barber: If you must know,
I took the Liberty
of learning chariot’s moves
during our last fight.
I won’t lose twice
to the same adversary.
Do you understand me?!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: That’s it.
You can do it.
( Iggy grunting )
Joseph: Ah, come on!
You can’t give up now.
You’ve almost got it!
( Laughs )
Oh?
( Iggy farts )
( Joseph groans )
( Avdol sighs )
Polnareff and jotaro,
they should have
returned by now.
( Polnareff gasping )
Jotaro: Polnareff,
what’s going on?
The barber’s a stand user?
Polnareff: Stay back, jotaro!
Th-the sword is the stand!
Trust me. It’s too dangerous
to try using star platinum’s
bare fists against this blade.
The sword’s sharp enough
to slice through them.
This barber
isn’t the stand user,
he’s just a puppet!
( Barber laughs )
Polnareff: And that’s
not even the worst part!
The stand’s even stronger
than it was before!
Bastard!
Barber: Whoa, there!
( Blade vibrating )
( Barber laughs )
Too much for you? ( Laughs )
I suppose I should be grateful
you’ve shown me
the limits of your defense.
Most kind of you. ( Laughs )
Now, then, let’s see
if you have what it takes
to survive my next attack,
shall we, polnareff?
( Shrieks )
Jotaro: Polnareff!
( Shrieking )
Polnareff: His powers keep
increasing with every strike!
I can’t keep parrying forever!
Sooner or later,
he’s gonna get me!
( Barber shrieks )
- Huh?
- Polnareff: Now!
Take this!
How in the...
Barber: In case you
haven’t realized the obvious,
I know all your moves.
It doesn’t matter
who my wielder is.
As long as i’ve done battle
with you at least once,
I never, ever,
never, ever, never, ever,
never, ever lose twice!
Polnareff: I’m not gonna
win this without my rapier.
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
Jotaro, help me out here!
Jotaro: Star platinum.
Barber: Hmm?
♪
( Yells )
Star platinum: Ora!
Polnareff: Think that
finished him off?
Jotaro: No.
That punch was shallow,
even though it took
just about everything I had.
- Man: Hey, Khan.
- Jotaro: Shit.
- Man: Are you all right?
- Jotaro: This guy’s strong.
It’s been quite a while now
since we’ve seen
a stand like this one.
It only relies on strength.
( Bystanders gasp )
Khan: Not bad, star platinum.
The rumors of your speed
were true.
But now that i’ve seen it,
I can easily defeat it.
Man: Hey, Khan,
what’s wrong with you?
Polnareff: Stay back!
Your friend is being controlled!
If you don’t wanna
get sliced to ribbons,
go back inside, and hide!
( Man yells )
Polnareff:
We’re in major trouble, jotaro.
The more we fight this stand,
the faster it gets,
and its next attack
will probably be
its fastest and strongest yet.
We have to be ready
for whatever this glorified
butter knife throws at us!
( Khan shrieks )
Jotaro: Move, polnareff!
I’m the one it’s really after!
Polnareff:
Get out of there, jotaro!
Khan: Die!
Star platinum: Ora!
Khan: Ah?!
What? With his bare hands?!
Star platinum: Ora!
♪
Khan: Amazing. For him
to take that great of a risk...
Now it’s become
abundantly clear.
The true source
of star platinum’s strength
isn’t its speed or precision.
It’s jotaro’s nerves of steel
and ability
to make quick decisions.
Yes.
Now I know it for sure.
( Jotaro panting )
Is he dead?
Polnareff:
Hold on a second, jotaro.
He’s just knocked out!
Whatever you do,
don’t touch that sword.
You snapped it in half,
but the stand’s powers
might still be lingering.
It controls anyone
who touches it while unsheathed.
Let’s get the blade back inside
without touching the hilt.
( Sighs )
( Sighs ) Now what?
If someone draws it again,
we’re done for.
This damn thing has already
learned all of our abilities.
I don’t think we’re gonna get
any second chances.
Jotaro: Why not
toss it into the river
to rust at the bottom
of the nile?
Polnareff: The nile, huh?
That sounds like
a great plan to me.
Officer: Hold it!
This is the police!
Polnareff: This is
perfect timing!
This guy needs a hospital!
Officer: I have multiple reports
of a brawl at a barber shop!
What are you doing
with that sword?!
Polnareff: Huh?
Officer: Hand this weapon over
immediately!
Polnareff:
Hey, stop it, would you?!
Don’t pull it out!
( Both grunting )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Anubis laughs )
( Polnareff gasping )
Jotaro: Polnareff!
♪
No, damn it.
( Polnareff growls )
Jotaro: His eyes, that stare...
Polnareff is being controlled
by the sword’s spell.
Officer: Hey, you there!
You drew the sword!
( Polnareff chuckles )
I drew the sword, did I?
Hmph. Officer, you should really
be more careful
with your accusations,
since you call yourself
a servant of the law.
Officer: Take it easy!
What are you doing?
Polnareff: I’m simply attacking
the culprit
who unsheathed the sword!
Jotaro: I don’t know who you are
or where you’re hiding,
but I think it’s safe to say
polnareff is under your control.
Come to think of it,
i’ve never had to fight
against polnareff before.
Polnareff: Hmm?
Jotaro: And I can’t pull punches
with chariot as an opponent.
If i’m not smart about this,
I could end up
killing polnareff.
( Polnareff chuckles )
As I said before, at this point,
i’ve already witnessed
star platinum’s
entire repertoire of moves,
and if i’ve done battle
with you once before,
then I will never lose again!
Star platinum: Ora!
- Polnareff: Hey, now.
- ( Jotaro growls )
( Polnareff laughing )
- En garde!
- Jotaro: His speed,
- it’s incredible!
- ( Polnareff laughing )
Jotaro: He’s getting
fast enough to outpace me!
I have to find a way
to stop that sword.
I’ll catch it again.
It sped up!
Polnareff: This time...
I’ll take your head!
Polnareff: Wha--
star platinum: Ora!
( Jotaro groaning )
His speed and power
are overwhelming.
Without a doubt,
this is the fastest stand
i’ve ever faced.
At the rate i’m going,
this won’t end well.
I have to fight polnareff
with everything i’ve got,
or i’m dead.
( Polnareff laughs )
So you head-butted the sword
after you realized
you couldn’t catch my blade.
Honestly I didn’t think you were
capable of something like that.
I almost had you.
But now...
I’ve acquired
that skill as well.
- ( Jotaro gasping )
- ( Polnareff chuckles )
Jotaro...
I can tell that you’re thinking
the only way to survive is
to kill your friend, polnareff.
( Chuckles )
Even if you wanted to,
it’s naive to think
it’d be that easy.
Take a close look, jotaro.
What i’m about to show you
will put an end to this
once and for all.
So, let’s see...
If you can beat this, jotaro!
Feast your eyes on
the silver chariot and Anubis
two-sword technique!
♪
( Silver chariot laughing )
( Star platinum yelling )
( Silver chariot shrieks )
( Laughing )
Jotaro: Damn it.
This extra sword,
coupled with
his accelerating speed,
even star platinum
won’t last long.
Polnareff: What’s the matter?
Are you feeling
a little tired, jotaro?!
( Silver chariot grunts )
Jotaro: I’ll stop him
before he kills me. Star finger!
Polnareff: Huh?
♪
( Silver chariot laughs )
My right arm is
as light as a feather now.
Polnareff: Interesting.
I guess that was an option.
( Jotaro gasps )
Polnareff: Didn’t see
that coming, did you?!
Round two! Armor release!
( Star platinum yelling )
Silver chariot: You fool!
Your ridiculous, "ora, ora,"
is no match for two swords
wielded
by two master swordsmen!
( Star platinum yelling )
Silver chariot:
Your stomach is wide open!
( Jotaro groans )
Silver chariot:
I’ve got you now!
- ( Jotaro gags )
- Polnareff: I did it!
I win!
Anubis: Master dio,
i’ve exterminated jotaro!
I, Anubis,
have finally put him down!
Victory is mine!
( Anubis laughs )
Just forget it.
You’re not going to be able
to pull out that blade.
Give up already! I’m not sure
your tiny brain has realized it,
but i’ve surpassed
star platinum.
And now the final thrust.
( Jotaro gags )
The final thrust?
Anubis: Yes, precisely!
Once I slice open your bowels,
master dio will rejoice!
Jotaro: Please, stop this.
Don’t drive the blade
any further.
It--it’ll be murder.
Anubis: Nice try, but you
won’t get any mercy from me!
I can’t wait to spill your guts!
( Laughs)
( Jotaro groans )
- ( Yells )
- ( Star platinum yells )
- Ora!
- ( Anubis squeals )
What the devil?!
You’re breaking me!
I have to pull free!
No! Stop!
Jotaro: Maybe i’m wrong,
but weren’t you saying
something about slicing me open?
( Anubis gagging )
( Screams )
Jotaro: I told you
it’d be murder,
but the murder I was talking
about was yours, friend.
You’re a pretty easy target
when the sword
isn’t moving around.
( Groans )
Damn it, what a pain in the ass.
This was the toughest opponent
i’ve faced.
That last attack took everything
I had in me and then some.
Luckily it was
just enough to defeat him
before he could learn it like
he did the rest of our attacks.
This is new.
I’ve never been so exhausted.
( Groans )
I have to find avdol
and the old man.
( Polnareff groaning )
W-what in the world
just happened?
( Jotaro panting )
( Polnareff gasps )
The sword didn’t possess me
like it did all
the other guys, did it?
Jotaro: Yeah, it did,
but it’s over now.
Polnareff: Forgive me.
Jotaro: Just get
the old man and avdol.
I’m too tired to walk.
Boy: Huh?
♪
Wow, it’s so shiny.
( Boy grunts )
( Spits )
Anubis: Now i’ve learned
that trick.
My original stand user
was the sword Smith
who forged me 500 years ago.
He may have perished
centuries ago,
but I survive as a stand
with no master.
Master dio liberated me
from the gloomy shadows
of a dusty museum.
And speaking of master dio,
his stand,
the world,
is far more powerful than I.
That’s why I pledged
my undying loyalty.
Jotaro, I swear on my life
I will murder you!
I know your strength,
your speed.
You won’t see it coming
until it’s too late to stop it!
I’ll stab you in the back!
Now die, jotaro!
What just happened?!
Son of a--i missed!
I was tripped by a dog?!
Where the hell
did that mutt come from?!
Polnareff: Hey, iggy,
what are you eating?
Wait a second.
Is that a nasty, old sucker?
Eating right off the ground
again, you filthy mutt.
( Anubis screams )
You’ve gotta be kidding!
It’s the nile river!
Aah! No,
this can’t be happening!
What did I do
to deserve this cruel fate?!
If I fall into the river,
i’m done for! I’ll rust away!
Somebody stop me!
Aah! Oh?!
Aha! I’m heading for a wall!
The wall will stop me!
Lucky me!
What the--shit!
I was so panicked
about falling into the water
that I accidentally phased
right through the wall!
I’m gonna fall in!
♪
( Gasps ) Yes, it’s a ship!
I’m saved!
If I wedge into those planks,
that guy’s curiosity
will make him pull me out,
and then i’ll take over
his pathetic mind!
Once i’m safely
back on dry land,
i’ll use his body
to take revenge on jotaro!
( Cow bellows )
Anubis: What?!
A cow is onboard?!
Stop thrashing around!
Hey, calm down!
Would you cool it,
you stupid cow?!
I know! I’ll take over
the cow’s mind!
Then it’ll be a cinch--
i’m not gonna make it in time!
Polnareff: Hey, over there!
That cow’s really rockin’
the boat, don’t you think?
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
Who gives a damn?
Just go and get the old man
and avdol, will you?
( Cow bellowing )
♪
( Anubis yells )
Help me!
( Sobs )
Hey! Yoo-hoo!
Oh, fishies, look down here!
Come on. Swim over to me!
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
Hey, Mr. Crab,
it’s a pleasure to meet you.
Would you mind doing me a favor
and taking me ashore?
I’ll give you something yummy.
Wait, Mr. Crab!
You just can’t leave me here!
I’ll be rusted through
in a couple of days.
Please, help me.
Don’t leave me here!
( Sobs )
I’m so alone!
♪
Polnareff: Stupid mutt.
What are you staring at?
There’s nothing to eat
over there, flea bag.
( Grunts, groans )
( Iggy farts )
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Why,
you stinkin’ little...
( Gags ) Merde!
What the hell
have you been eating?!
Joseph: Come on, polnareff.
To think all of that happened
without us.
Joseph: You fought
the Anubis stand, huh?
That must have
been rough, jotaro.
Jotaro: Yeah, was.
( Polnareff yelling )
Jotaro: That’s the last time
I ever go anywhere with him.
( Both grunt )
Joseph: Stop it already,
you stupid mutt!
- Get the hell off my face!
- ( Iggy snarling )
♪
Narrator: The average tourist
to Egypt is mostly unaware
of the country’s
rich ethnic diversity.
For example,
take this Egyptian man
wearing
the traditional jellabiya
or this Egyptian nubian,
and here is a bedouin
from egypt’s desert region.
This gentleman hails from India.
And as a random example,
here’s another Egyptian citizen.
♪
Man: Hey! That fox has
got some smokin’-hot legs
that are out of this world.
Boy: I can’t keep
my eyes off her.
Wow! Those puppies’ll
pull you right in, you know.
( Both sigh )
♪