Polnareff: Hey!
Something’s coming this way!
♪
I don’t know who you are,
but you’re
definitely not normal!
Joseph: Polnareff, stop it!
Polnareff: I’m gonna
make short work of you.
Jotaro: Another playing card?
Butler: Master joestar,
welcome to our abode.
We’ve been expecting you.
How rude of me.
I am the Butler of this mansion.
You may call me d’arby.
- ( Men gasp )
- Jotaro: D’arby, huh?
d’arby: Yes.
I am the younger d’arby.
It might interest you to know
the d’arby whom you defeated
upon your arrival was...
My older brother.
( Men gasp )
Polnareff: So there isn’t
just one filou
in the d’arby family!
Avdol: So I take it you’re here
to avenge
your brother’s defeat?
( D’arby scoffs )
( Men gasp )
D’arby: No, not at all.
Such a thing is beneath me.
I would have assumed my brother
would share his motto with you--
"it is the deceived,
not the deceiver,
who holds the blame."
I, too, live by this adage.
My brother lost,
so he is the wrongdoer.
I harbor no ill will
toward any of you.
My brother is my brother,
and I am me,
two different individuals.
You see, my brother and I
were born ten years apart,
and while I did look up to him
to a certain extent,
he and I are
of different generations.
My brother tried to win
via old-fashioned deception,
but this method is
only useful against those
who are outdated
or inexperienced.
Master dio realized
this sad truth as well,
which is why
he kept me by his side
as his personal Butler.
Hmm. Forgive me.
Is something the matter?
( Both gasp )
D’arby: Here is my offer to you.
If you wish to fight me,
then I invite you
to enter our manor.
Avdol: Stay on guard.
He’s even more conniving
than his brother.
jotaro:
There’s no time for games.
Take us to dio right now.
Joseph: Jotaro,
stay on your guard!
He’s up to something!
Narrator: D’arby younger.
his stand, hailing from
the Egyptian pantheon, is atum.
( Gas hisses )
( Jotaro grunts )
polnareff: Hey, guys,
he just brought out his stand.
Joseph: It’s been a while
since we’ve seen one.
Avdol: Indeed. His stand
is physically showing itself.
Atum: I’ll let you decide.
Who shall be my first opponent?
polnareff:
As if we’d listen to you.
Jotaro, take this weirdo down.
D’arby: Let’s see.
I’ll wager that star platinum’s
first attack will...
Atum: ...Be with his left arm.
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- ( All gasp )
Atum: Oh, and it’ll be a punch.
How much would you care to bet?
Polnareff: Forget this.
Which arm doesn’t matter.
One punch will finish it.
Get him!
Let him have it already,
jotaro!
Star platinum: Ora!
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- Joseph: What?
He was able to dodge it.
Polnareff: His speed is insane.
- Avdol: Impossible.
- ( Jotaro growls )
( D’arby laughs )
Well, that’s a bit of bad luck.
Regrettably, it appears
as though i’ve lost the bet.
Like my brother, I also enjoy
a round of gambling,
but luck is never on my side.
- ( Star platinum grunts )
- D’arby: Allow me to take you
to a wonderful world
to apologize.
Jotaro: What? A pit?
Avdol: Damn it!
It was all subterfuge.
Joseph: Jotaro!
He’s falling into the abyss!
We have to get him out of there!
( Both gasping )
D’arby: Have it your way.
The more the merrier,
and all that.
( Both yell )
polnareff:
Mr. Joestar, kakyoin, no!
Avdol: It’s too dangerous
for us to follow.
Joseph: Avdol, can you hear me?!
If you don’t hear from us
in ten minutes,
torch the mansion!
Do you understand me?!
Burn it to the ground, avdol!
Both: Mr. Joestar!
Joseph: Mm.
Jotaro: Mm.
( Waves lapping )
Joseph: Is this an illusion?
Are we still aboveground,
or did he pull us under?
Huh? ( Gasps )
- huh?
- ( Seabirds calling )
if this stuff
is really an illusion,
they’ve got water down.
This stuff feels so real.
What the hell is this guy
trying to accomplish here?
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- Joseph: Eh?
( D’arby chuckles )
Jotaro: Old man, kakyoin,
see if you can figure out
his ability.
his stand,
it knew without a doubt
that I would throw
a right-handed punch.
Do you know why?
Joseph: Hmm.
jotaro: If we
can’t figure it out soon,
we’re gonna lose. No doubt.
D’arby: Would you care
to wet your whistle?
They’re real, and I assure you
they’re not poisoned.
Cross my heart
and hope to die.
Joseph: Just answer this.
Are we inside the mansion?
D’arby: Yes, of course.
joseph:
Where in the mansion are we?
D’arby: I can’t tell you that.
Joseph: The basement?
D’arby: Perhaps.
Joseph: Hmm.
is this illusion
the work of a stand’s power?
D’arby: Yes, it is.
Joseph: Is all this
the doing of your stand?
D’arby: No, it isn’t.
Joseph: Is it dio’s stand?
Joseph: Whose stand, then?!
D’arby: I would rather
not reveal that.
Joseph: The speedwagon
foundation has reported
there are two to three
more stand users.
Is that accurate?
D’arby: I’d rather
not reveal that either.
( Joseph groans )
Well, you’re about as helpful
as a cramp in a relay race.
D’arby: If it means so much,
I could lie to you,
but unlike
my dearly defeated brother,
i’d prefer not to resort
to petty trickery.
( Jotaro scoffs )
Joseph: Let me make sure
i’ve got this straight.
you’re saying
if we don’t defeat you,
we won’t be able
to get back to the real world?
D’arby: Heh. Exactly right.
You’ve pieced it together,
good sir.
Kakyoin: That obnoxious,
gentlemanly demeanor
is beginning
to wear thin on my nerves.
Joseph: You seem
to be forgetting
that it’s three against one.
We’re short on time,
so you’ll have to deal with
all of us attacking at once.
D’arby: Come now, friends.
You should take a load off.
feast your eyes
on what I have to show you.
Say hello to my collection.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- Joseph: Your collection?
♪
( Dolls moaning, murmuring )
D’arby: Much like my brother,
i’m what you might call
a humble collector of sorts.
My, thinking about it,
all collectors must yearn
to share their treasures
for that moment of praise.
Jotaro: He’s out of his mind.
Kakyoin: Why dolls?
What could he possibly
be doing with these toys?
joseph:
I don’t think I wanna know.
remember,
this guy is d’arby’s brother,
so i’m guessing
those aren’t ordinary dolls.
( Doll creaking )
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Doll groans )
D-d’arby.
Talk to me. Please talk.
Why won’t you talk to me?
d’arby!
Talk to me.
( Dolls moaning, murmuring )
Doll #2: Help me.
- Doll #3: I’m trapped.
- ( D’arby chuckles )
Joseph: Oh, my god.
Kakyoin: They’re alive.
How is that even possible?
Jotaro: Bastard.
You took their souls.
d’arby: Obviously,
as making dolls is my hobby.
But of course
ordinary doll makers
cannot imbue their handiwork
with human souls.
I suppose I may be
giving too much away,
but that’s my stand’s ability.
comparatively,
my brother’s collection
of simple coins made of souls
is rather uninspired.
With my collection,
you can play dress up
and have actual chats.
let me show you.
This little showstopper...
- Sonia: D’arby. Oh, my...
- Is named Sonia.
She can wax poetic about
her passionate love stories.
- Sonia: D’arby.
- D’arby: Such exquisite skin.
Anyone would be
proud to own her.
Dr. Elliott is a serial killer
with a victim count of eight.
He’ll tell you all about
the patients he’s exterminated.
I made the glasses
and stethoscope myself.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
I’d like for you
to meet tatsuhiko.
this one’s
a game expert from Japan.
This brilliant young man
was a formidable opponent
with an I.Q. Of 190.
Let me tell you, it wasn’t easy
beating this little guy
and stealing his soul.
Joseph: You’re just as messed up
in the head as your brother.
Actually, you’re more sadistic
than your brother ever was.
i hate to see
what your parents were like.
Kakyoin: I’m out of Patience
with this sociopath’s
puppet show.
He makes me sick.
( D’arby grumbles )
by the way,
i’m fairly certain you learned
this when you fought my brother,
but the human soul can be
a rather mysterious entity.
the moment
a person admits defeat,
their inner spirit dies,
and the soul loses
almost all vitality.
At that moment, I have the power
to rip the soul from the body,
and that’s the fundamental
mechanism of our stands!
Joseph: I’ve heard enough!
Show and tell is over!
We’re gonna beat you
to a bloody pulp
and get the hell out of here!
D’arby: But first listen
to what I have to say.
Atum: Surely the fact
that you’re under my control
hasn’t escaped your notice.
( Men gasp )
D’arby: Jotaro, as I recall,
you were quite shocked
when I knew exactly which arm
you were going
to attack me with,
and from where i’m standing,
it seems you still
haven’t figured it out.
Atum: You were shaken
by my prowess,
and I was able to give your soul
a little love tap.
What do you think I did
when I touched your soul?
( Jotaro gasping )
Kakyoin: W-what the--
Joseph: The hell’d
you do to his arm?
D’arby: I’ve done nothing
but embed atum’s hand
inside jotaro’s soul.
I could crush your right arm
with a thought
and, in doing so,
make master dio very happy,
but if I did, I wouldn’t
be able to defend myself
against kakyoin and Joseph
and would most certainly perish.
Now, we wouldn’t want that
to happen, would we, gentlemen?
( Joseph growls )
So here’s a suggestion.
Everyone, let’s play a game
with our souls as collateral.
Joseph: What?
D’arby: If you defeat me,
i solemnly swear
to release jotaro’s arm.
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
so, according to you,
i’m already under your control.
Well, I have news
for you, d’arby.
You’re gonna regret picking
a fight with me and my friends.
Let’s end this!
D’arby: Yes, yes,
your righteous anger
is all well and good,
but i’d rather hear you
say the words,
"i’ll bet my soul on this game."
by the way,
I have another request,
- if you’d indulge me.
- jotaro: Eh?
- D’arby: Kakyoin...
- Kakyoin: Hmm?
D’arby: You shall be
my first opponent.
jotaro: Hey,
what are you talking about?
Your fight is with me, buddy,
so don’t try
and pass the buck to kakyoin.
d’arby: You and
Mr. Joestar are family,
but kakyoin is decidedly not.
i’d prefer kakyoin
not back out of our arrangement
and attack me with his stand
after i’ve taken
both of your souls,
due to lack
of familial attachment.
Joseph: I’m sick
of this arrogant prick.
He thinks this challenge
is gonna be a walk
in the park for him.
Kakyoin: Very well.
If that’s what you want,
then I will be your opponent.
- Joseph: Say what?
- Jotaro: Kakyoin.
kakyoin: It’s okay.
I’m really not too concerned.
I’ve probably played
more video games
than anyone else here.
i officially
accept your challenge
and choose "f-mega" as our game.
And i’ll wager my soul.
Nd i’ll wager my soul.
D’arby: Very good.
( Chuckles )
Joseph: Kakyoin, don’t!
Jotaro: There’s no need for you
to take this guy on first.
Kakyoin: I have to do this.
We still don’t have a grasp
on that spirit hand.
it could hinder
your game-playing ability.
D’arby, do I have your guarantee
that you’ll release jotaro
from your stand’s power
if you lose the game?
( D’arby scoffs )
- Kakyoin: Huh?
- Joseph: What?
♪
( Gasps )
Joseph: The TV, console, and
game cartridges are all good.
as far as I can tell,
this is just an ordinary setup.
D’arby: I keep
trying to tell you
that i’m not a cheater
like my brother.
If you’re ready, let’s begin.
Kakyoin: Let’s do it.
♪
Game: "F-mega"!
Select your car.
D’arby: Go ahead,
and select your vehicle.
Kakyoin: Right.
D’arby: So you’ve decided
to go with number 28.
I suppose i’ll be number 15,
as my birthday is January fifth.
( Kakyoin sighs )
D’arby: We can begin
at your leisure.
kakyoin:
Enough with the courtesy.
Start the game already.
Game: Race starts in...
Five...
( Engine revving )
( Kakyoin gasps )
He’s button mashing
the accelerator
at an incredible speed.
He’s going for a turbo start.
- Game: Three...
- Kakyoin: Damn.
I don’t have time
to try the same tactic.
He’ll take the lead.
What am I going to do now?
Game: One...
Start!
♪
( Tires screeching )
Kakyoin: What?
He just cut me off.
( D’arby chuckles )
As long as i’m in the lead,
he can’t beat me,
and i’ve made it
impossible for him to pass.
It’s unfortunate, I know,
but the simple truth is I never
make a mistake during a race.
Victory will be mine, kakyoin.
( Kakyoin grunts )
♪
D’arby: What the...
kakyoin, you’ve played
this game before, haven’t you?
Kakyoin: I’d rather
not reveal that.
joseph: Yes!
This is your chance, kakyoin.
Get your machine back on course,
and start kicking
this bastard’s ass!
( Players grunt )
D’arby: That technique,
one doesn’t simply get those
skills by playing video games.
Damn it all. I never could
have imagined that someone
as measured as kakyoin
would make such a bold move.
Joseph: Yeah, that’s the way
to do it, neck and neck!
jotaro: No.
Look carefully, old man.
Kakyoin’s at the edge.
When it comes to those turns,
he’s at a major disadvantage.
Kakyoin: 355 k.M.H.
Now it’s 358...
And now 360.
three seconds
until the first turn,
but there’s no way
I can make it going this fast.
I’m entering the turn
at full speed!
Two, one!
Joseph: You seeing this?
Those two are hitting the turns
the exact same way.
It’s too close to call.
d’arby:
You’ve intrigued me, kakyoin.
With your soul on the line,
you’ve conquered your fear
and become the picture
of unwavering resolve.
I dare say you’ll make a worthy
addition to my collection.
All that’s left
is for me to win.
Narrator: Kakyoin
thought to himself...
kakyoin: So i’ve
conquered my fears, have I?
( Laughs )
Why, thank you.
It’s been a long road.
six months ago,
I had the unfortunate experience
of meeting your master, dio.
I was terrified
when he implanted
one of his flesh buds
in my brain.
My memories of that day
are as clear as ever.
I remember the horror
I felt in my soul
as I faced that monster.
My legs wouldn’t move.
Every hair on my body
stood on end.
It’s like I was frozen.
That’s when I realized it.
i was helpless,
completely at his mercy.
The mere sight of dio
was enough to turn my own body
against itself.
My stomach was in knots.
I was so close to vomiting,
I could taste bile
in the back of my throat.
Dio gazed down at me,
and, as if tenderly calming
a frightened child, he said...
- Dio: Easy, kakyoin.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
Dio: There is nothing
for you to be afraid of.
Let’s be friends, shall we?
Kakyoin: I still curse myself.
I heard his words, and...
( Laughs )
and I felt all
of my anxiety melt away.
I was completely
and utterly relieved.
I thought, "I still
have a chance to live."
It was humiliating.
I’ll never forgive him
for what he did,
and i’ll never forgive myself
for submitting
to that bastard’s will.
My weakness will forever
be my greatest failure.
Jotaro saved me from that hell,
which is why i’ve come
on this journey.
I will never again allow myself
to be such a coward.
and that, d’arby,
is why i’m able to fight you,
even with my very soul
on the line.
Three, two, one!
joseph:
They’re neck and neck again,
rounding the third corner!
Kakyoin: That is why on this day
I vow that I, noriaki kakyoin,
will never be controlled
by my fears again.
My word is my bond.
Joseph: All right!
It’s the fifth corner!
They’re back in sync!
Look! They’re turning
at the same speed!
D’arby: Damn you, kakyoin.
Damn you.
Joseph: The sixth corner
is coming up fast.
D’arby: If i’m not mistaken,
the speed tunnel
comes right after turn six.
If you enter that tunnel,
you’re granted a boost
that can double your Max speed
to 850 k.M.H.
I have to make sure
I get to that tunnel.
Kakyoin: But the thing is,
the tunnel is
only wide enough for one car.
Joseph: This isn’t good.
If they try to enter the tunnel
side by side,
one of them is gonna crash.
It’s the sixth turn,
and they’re still neck and neck!
There it is!
I see the tunnel!
- ( Players grunt )
- Joseph: Kakyoin,
push him out of the way!
D’arby: Haven’t you
realized it yet, kakyoin?
You don’t have the power
to push me aside.
If you don’t believe me,
why not glance at your
handy-dandy power meter?
Kakyoin: Hmm?
( Gasps )
Joseph: Kakyoin, you have
less power than he does.
D’arby: You used up your power
when you spun around
and blocked me
back at the beginning
of the race.
That wasn’t the best move
on your part.
I bet you’re regretting
that decision now!
♪
so close.
Two seconds ’til the tunnel.
Joseph: You’re gonna crash!
You can let this fool
have the lead!
get behind him
to avoid crashing right now!
Kakyoin: I can’t do that. If he
makes it to the tunnel first,
my chances of winning
go to absolute zero.
D’arby: One second left
’til victory.
Joseph: Kakyoin!
My god! He’s got the car
up on two wheels!
d’arby: How absurd.
You’re riding the tunnel walls?
Joseph: Yes. You’ve got this
in the bag, kakyoin.
just hang on
a little bit further,
and victory will be ours.
Now push him aside!
D’arby: Quiet.
I’m concentrating.
- ( Joseph laughs )
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
Joseph: Watch out!
He’s slamming you!
Kakyoin: It makes no difference
to me if I lose some power.
my only concern
is getting around that turn
faster than kakyoin,
even if it’s only
by a hundredth of a second,
just one one-thousandth
of a millimeter ahead.
Game: No radar.
joseph: Hey,
what’s going on here?
Can’t see the cars!
Kakyoin: From here on out, we
have to get through the tunnel
- in almost absolute darkness.
- Joseph: What?
Kakyoin: The problem is my radar
will be completely useless,
and worse,
there are eight turns,
a land mine, and a Cannon attack
waiting to put us
through our paces up ahead.
This area will remain dark
until we make it out.
one mistake,
and i’ll slam into the wall.
But, fortunately for us,
i already know
exactly where each turn is.
D’arby knows, too.
( Engines racing )
Jotaro: The cars
are beginning to turn.
joseph:
What’s happening, jotaro?!
I can’t tell who’s ahead
or where they are
in that blasted tunnel!
- Kakyoin: Three...
- Joseph: Eh?
- D’arby: Two...
- Joseph: Huh?
Both: And one! Cannon attack!
( Joseph gasps )
Did you see that?
For a second there,
the blast lit up the cars.
jotaro: Yeah,
I could see that kakyoin
is running slightly behind.
( D’arby laughs )
Joseph: Here we go.
They’re about
to exit the tunnel!
( Groans ) Oh, damn it!
D’arby was able
to take the lead!
he’s ahead
by a full car length!
D’arby: Looks like I win.
♪