♪
Jotaro: It’s about time.
( Singing in Japanese )
( Helicopter blades thrumming )
Men: Hmm?
Polnareff: Hey,
do you hear that noise, too?
Joseph: They’ve arrived.
Polnareff: It’s a helicopter!
Kakyoin: Thanks for the update,
captain obvious.
Joseph: They’re here
from the speedwagon foundation,
and they’re looking
for somewhere to land.
Jotaro: Speedwagon foundation?
Correct me if i’m wrong,
but aren’t they the group
that’s looking after mom
back in Japan?
They’re old friends
of yours, right?
Joseph: Yep,
that’s them, all right.
Jotaro: So, what?
Are we taking a helicopter
from here on out?
Joseph: Not quite.
As much as i’d like to,
the guys working
for the foundation
aren’t stand users,
so we’d be putting them
in harm’s way
if we hitched a ride.
Kakyoin: Well, if they’re
not here to give us a ride,
what’s the occasion, then?
Joseph: They’ve brought us
our new ally.
( Polnareff and kakyoin gasp )
Polnareff: Tu rigoles! An ally?
Joseph: I have to warn you,
he’s a bit of a handful,
which is the primary reason
it took so long to fetch him.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar!
You aren’t seriously considering
taking him with us, are you?
His presence here
would only hold us back.
Kakyoin: So he
might actually harm us?
Avdol: Correct, so be careful.
Jotaro: Not so fast.
This new ally of ours,
are you saying that he’s
a stand user, too?
Joseph: Yes, that’s right,
and his stand is represented
by the card known as the fool.
Jotaro: The fool?
Polnareff: Wait. The fool?
( Laughs )
Sounds like a pretty stupid card
if you want my opinion.
Avdol: You should count your
blessings that he’s on our side.
- You can’t beat him.
- ( Polnareff growls )
I’d suggest watching your mouth
if you know what’s good
for you, avdol.
Avdol: It’s true, polnareff.
Now move your hand.
You’re hurting me.
Polnareff: Who died
and made you the boss?!
Kakyoin: Enough, you two.
The helicopter’s here.
( Wind blowing )
♪
( Men grunt )
Man: Mr. Joestar.
Good to see you.
Joseph: Thank you
for bringing him here.
Must have been rough.
Jotaro: So which one
of you is it?
Who’s the stand user?
Men: Hmm?
♪
Well, are you gonna
answer me or not?
Is it you?
Man: No, sir.
Neither of us is the user.
He’s actually in the back.
Jotaro: In the back, huh?
I don’t see anyone.
Man: No, he’s there.
Polnareff: Hey, hey, cut it out.
Come on. Quit joking around.
What’s the deal? Is the guy
really short or something?
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
Man #2: Hey, watch out!
Polnareff: Huh?
That’s weird.
What the hell is this stuff?
Man #2: Please, be careful!
It was a rough copter ride,
so he’s in a foul mood!
Joseph: Step away! I’ve already
told you this guy is trouble.
Avdol: Get back, polnareff.
You cannot beat him.
Polnareff: What’s the big deal?
All i’m doing
is asking where he is.
Huh? ( Gasps )
- ( Dog snarling )
- ( Polnareff screams )
- H-h-h-h-he’s...
- Kakyoin: A dog.
Jotaro: Don’t tell me
this dog is...
Joseph: Mm-hmm.
Yes, this dog possesses
the stand of the fool.
His name is iggy, and he’s crazy
about ripping chunks of hair
out of people’s heads.
To be honest with you,
i’m not sure where he’s from,
but avdol found him in New York
after none of the dogcatchers
could wrangle him,
and it’s thanks to avdol
that he’s not roaming
the streets now.
Oh, there’s something that I
probably should have mentioned.
When he’s in the middle
of ripping out someone’s hair,
he likes to, uh...
- ( Iggy farts )
- ( Polnareff gagging )
Joseph: Pass gas in their face.
It’s a disgusting habit,
really.
Polnareff: You little mutt!
You’re gonna pay for that!
Damn you!
Chariot!
( Iggy grunts )
♪
( The fool growling )
( Growls )
Polnareff: Holy cow!
Jotaro: So that thing
is the fool.
Kakyoin: When we
were in Singapore,
we fought an orangutan
stand user, but this is...
Polnareff: Who does
this stupid mutt think he is?!
Bastard. Don’t make me
turn you into dog meat!
( The fool growls )
Polnareff: What the hell?
It turned into sand!
I can’t cut him!
Damn it!
His stand has solidified
and grabbed hold of my rapier!
Kakyoin: Is that...
Avdol: Yes, the dog’s stand
is made entirely out of sand.
Jotaro: Hmm.
As simple as the design is,
it’s so powerful, i’m not sure
I could land a punch.
- ( Iggy growling )
- Polnareff: Guys!
What are you doing?! Help!
Get this dog off of me!
Kakyoin: I’m sorry, polnareff,
but if it’s all the same to you,
i’d like to keep my hair.
Polnareff: You monster!
( Wails )
Avdol: Did you happen to bring
his favorite snack with you?
Man #1: Of course I did.
He wouldn’t have come
with us otherwise.
Polnareff: For the love of god,
stop! Help me!
( Iggy grunts, barking )
♪
Avdol: The dog’s sense of smell
is simply incredible.
Kakyoin: And that is?
Avdol: It’s coffee-flavored
chewing gum,
and iggy will do
just about anything
to savor
this tasty little morsel.
Man #1: No, Mr. Avdol!
Quickly, hide the packet
before he--
avdol: Blast it!
He grabbed the whole thing!
Joseph: He can’t get enough
of his coffee-flavored gum,
as you can see.
People, on the other hand,
are a different story,
unfortunately.
Avdol: The least he can do
is take the wrapping off.
Kakyoin: How is a gum-obsessed,
feral dog supposed to help us?
Jotaro: Good grief.
Polnareff:
Damn that little menace!
He’s completely ruined
my picturesque hair!
Petit con!
Man #1: He’ll be distracted
while he’s chewing his gum.
Let’s get the supplies.
Here’s the food and water you’ll
be needing for your trip, sir.
Joseph: Oh, thank you.
Man #1: There are
medical supplies
and a change of clothes, too.
We also took the Liberty
of buying a new camera
to use with your stand.
Joseph: Yeah, I suppose
it’ll be a lot easier
than using a TV, right?
Oh, I know. Look sharp, men!
- Polnareff: Hmm?
- Kakyoin: Hmm?
Kakyoin: Fantastic.
This is a perfect memento.
( Jotaro chuckles )
( Polnareff screams )
Avdol! Hurry up, and give
the mutt the stupid gum!
Avdol: Now, why in the world
would I do that
when the two of you are already
such good friends, polnareff?
( Laughs )
Man #1: Well,
if that’s everything,
I think we’re going to be
heading back now, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: Answer this
before you leave.
It’s regarding
my daughter’s condition.
And I want you
to be straight with me.
How’s my baby girl holding up?
Man #1: Well, to be
perfectly frank with you, sir,
it’s not looking good right now.
She’s rapidly losing strength,
and nothing seems
to help her condition.
Our doctors
at the speedwagon foundation say
she has two weeks at best.
( Jotaro and avdol sigh )
Kakyoin: We’re all out of time.
Polnareff: This is bullshit.
Man #1: I also have
some other information, sir.
Joseph: Hmm?
Man #1: Our investigators
say that two days ago,
nine unidentified men and women
gathered in a building
believed to be dio’s hideout.
Apparently they came
and left together.
( Men gasp )
Joseph: Dio has rounded up
nine more people?!
Man #1: We have
no clue who they are.
The spy who reported this
was killed shortly after,
and the mansion where they met
has been vacated.
We’ve had no luck
in locating these individuals.
We thought about tailing them,
but since our spies
aren’t stand users,
we decided
it would be too dangerous.
Polnareff: So these people
are stand users?!
Kakyoin: Hold on.
Think about it for a minute.
That would be impossible.
Other than hol horse’s stand,
the emperor,
the only tarot card
that still remains is the world.
I’ve been suspecting
that one belongs to dio,
but now i’m not sure. Avdol?
Avdol: I--i don’t know.
I just can’t wrap
my head around this.
Nine more stand users?
Joseph: From what I can gather,
it seems that dio’s head
hasn’t been able to adjust
to his new body yet.
But that monster
would never run from us.
He’s far too conceited
for something like that.
He’ll do everything
within his power
to keep us out of Cairo.
Jotaro: Good freakin’ grief.
We have to take out nine
stand users in two weeks, huh?
Man, that is one hell
of a whirlwind tour.
Man #1: Have a safe trip,
Mr. Joestar.
We await your return.
Joseph: Thanks for your help.
Look after my Holly.
( Iggy grunts )
( Sniffing )
( Wind blowing )
♪
( Man sighs )
( Chuckles ) That mutt...
So it sniffed out the great
n’doul from that far away?
( Fly buzzing )
( Scoffs ) So close.
( Chuckles )
What do you know?
I almost caught it this time.
Just a bit more practice.
( Chuckles )
All of this
because of the tsetse fly.
If not for those insects,
joestar and his band of meddlers
would never have known
master dio was in Egypt.
( Iggy chewing )
( Polnareff growls )
Mr. Joestar, why are you
letting him get away with this?
It’s not fair
he gets to be in the back seat
while we’re stuck in the trunk!
And in case you didn’t know,
it’s not exactly spacious
back here.
I’m gonna need a chiropractor!
Joseph: Look,
I know it’s not ideal,
but you’ll just have to wait
until the gum
runs out of flavor.
When it does,
throw another stick of gum
into the trunk
to lure him back there.
Then you can all
switch seats with him.
Polnareff: All right, all right.
Calm down already, flea bag.
Damn, you’re annoying.
- ( Joseph gasps )
- ( All yell )
Polnareff: Whoa!
What the hell was that?!
Joseph: Hey, quickly,
look over there!
There! Do you see it?!
It’s the helicopter!
Kakyoin: The speedwagon
foundation helicopter went down.
I can’t believe
what i’m seeing.
♪
Avdol: There’s no sign
of an explosion or gunfire.
Kakyoin: It seems like it
just fell out of the sky
for no reason at all.
- Polnareff: Could it be...
- Joseph: Careful, men!
I’d bet my life it was
attacked by an enemy stand!
Jotaro: Over there,
it’s the pilot!
He’s already dead. ( Gasps )
Whatever happened to him,
it wasn’t pretty.
Joseph: Eh, the poor bastard.
Approach carefully.
Whatever did this
could still be hiding in there.
( Jotaro grunts )
( Gasps )
It’s water.
There’s no way all that water
is just from his mouth.
It must be flowing
from somewhere else.
It must be from his lungs.
And the fish would mean...
He drowned in the desert!
This is getting
weirder and weirder!
Joseph: What is going on?
Polnareff: H-hey!
We found
the other guy over here!
He’s alive!
( Man #2 wheezing )
Joseph: Hang on!
You have to talk to us!
Tell us what happened!
Man #2: Wa--
water.
Joseph: What?
Are you saying you need water?
Hurry, polnareff,
hand me the canteen!
Polnareff: Huh? Oh, yeah.
Joseph: Here.
You just hang in there.
Drink this.
Drink it slowly.
( Man #2 wheezing )
( Screams ) No!
- The water attacked us!
- Joseph: What?!
( Men gasping )
Joseph: Men, watch yourselves!
It’s a stand!
The enemy stand
is inside the canteen!
Eh, damn it all.
They were just
innocent bystanders.
What reason did it have
to kill them?
Avdol, did you see what kind
of stand we’re dealing with?
Avdol: I just saw
the shape of a hand,
but i’d wager it’s
still inside the canteen.
I don’t believe I saw it leave.
Who could the user be?
The foundation members
informed us
dio had a meeting
with nine men and women.
Is it possible that one of them
is the assassin?
Joseph: Hey, I need you
to find the stand user.
Yeah, I know.
I’m already on it. That said...
I don’t see anything around us,
let alone the stand user.
When we duked it out
with that sun stand,
he was hiding behind
a mirror, but this time...
The enemy
seems to be so far away
that we’ll never be able
to find him from here.
♪
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
slice up the canteen, would you?
( Polnareff gasps )
Why me? Besides,
didn’t you see
what happened to the pilot?
His entire head got sucked into
that tiny, little container!
Think about it! If I so much
as poke a hole in that thing--
( gulps ) No way.
Why don’t you
slice it up, kakyoin?
You’re closer anyhow!
You can just use
your emerald splash
and call it a day, can’t you?!
Kakyoin: Yes,
but I don’t want to.
( Polnareff groans )
Don’t make me do something
just because
you don’t want to do it!
What the hell, man?!
What’s going on with you?!
Kakyoin: I’ve said no,
and that’s final.
Polnareff: Well, like I said,
i’m not gonna attack
the damn thing, either!
Joseph: Hmm?
♪
Kakyoin: Th-that’s the...
Polnareff: K-kakyoin!
Joseph: It’s the water!
The stand left the canteen
disguised as water
and hid in the blood!
Avdol: No, that’s wrong!
The stand wasn’t disguising
itself as water at all!
I think the stand is the water!
Polnareff: No! It got kakyoin!
( Wails )
It clawed out kakyoin’s eyes!
Joseph: Polnareff, panicking
isn’t going to help anything!
Summon chariot for protection!
( Polnareff gasps )
Jotaro: Damn it.
It’ll get polnareff, too!
( Polnareff gasping )
( Watch alarm beeping )
( All gasp )
Joseph: This doesn’t
make any sense.
Why would it go after
the pilot’s corpse?
Jotaro: It wasn’t the corpse.
The target was the watch.
It attacked the watch
because of the alarm.
Avdol: That’s it! The stand
stalks its victims by sound!
Polnareff: You’re kidding.
( Gasps )
( Dripping echoes )
Joseph:
Get out of there, polnareff!
It’s coming after you now!
Hurry, and get to the car!
( Polnareff yells )
It’s so fast!
Joseph: Faster, polnareff!
( Polnareff yells )
I-it got me!
Joseph: Hermit purple!
Avdol: The stand
disappeared into the ground!
Joseph: I see now.
It detects sound through
vibrations in the ground,
and it moves through the earth,
so there’s no way to find it.
That puts us
at a major disadvantage.
Since we can’t see it,
the stand has the ability
to attack from above or below
at any moment it chooses.
To make things worse,
the stand user
could be kilometers away.
( Vibrations echo )
N’doul: So the prey has
sought refuge atop the car.
Seems they’ve realized n’doul
is using the power of sound
to hunt them down one by one.
( Chuckles ) No matter.
It won’t be long
before they’re all eliminated.
( Laughs )
♪
Polnareff: Hey,
how’s kakyoin doing?
Avdol: Not good.
From the looks of things
- he may have been blinded.
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Avdol: We have to get going.
He needs to see a doctor
as soon as possible.
Joseph: But if we try
to move from this spot,
that stand will attack us.
We can’t afford
careless mistakes.
( Iggy snoring )
♪
( Sniffing )
Joseph: What the hell?!
( Men yell )
( Iggy grunts )
N’doul: Hmm? That sound...
It’s the dog.
Interesting. It leapt out of
the car before I could attack.
It anticipated
what my stand was going to do.
Seems like this dog is
going to be quite the nuisance.
Jotaro: The tires
are in the water!
Shit! What now?!
The whole car’s
about to be pulled in!
Avdol: I can’t
hold him for long!
Joseph: Everyone,
we have to move to the back!
Polnareff: Hey,
you good-for-nothing mongrel!
Aren’t you supposed to be
helping us or something?!
N’doul: I see. That accursed dog
is too perceptive
for his own good.
It knows i’m four kilometers
west of joestar’s group.
What to do?
( Iggy groans )
N’doul: Perhaps I should do away
with the dog right now.
( Iggy yawns )
( Polnareff yells )
Yeah, sleep while
we fight to survive!
You’re a bastard.
You know that?
( Iggy snoring )
( N’doul laughs )
Never mind.
The dog is of no concern.
Joestar and the others can’t
control that mongrel, anyway.
The mutt’s harmless
if all it does is nap.
( Laughs )
Now for the kill.
Joseph: Son of a bitch!
The water’s sharp enough to
slash through our front tires!
Move to the other side
on the double!
If it’s trying to do
what I think it is,
then we’re gonna need
to hang on for our lives!
( All yell )
♪