♪
Hol horse: Shit,
it’s dark in here.
I can’t see a damn thing.
where the hell
is that bastard, anyway?
( Cloth rustles )
( Growls )
It’s the middle of the day,
and I still have to feel my way
around this hovel.
This had better be worth it.
Okay, if I remember correctly,
i’ll find dio over in that room.
( Gasps )
Ugh! Disgusting.
This little lady must be
one of dio’s leftovers.
Damn broads just throw
themselves at the guy,
like having their blood drank
is the latest bedroom craze.
The whole thing’s nutty
if you ask me,
though girls do tend
to go for the bad boys.
But forget about that.
i’ve never seen
so much gold in my life.
How’d he get all this?
Seems like this guy can have
and do just about anything.
♪
Hmm.
Dio: Hol horse...
( Hol horse gasping )
Dio: What is it?
Hol horse: It’s master dio.
( Panting )
Son of a bitch.
What is this?
Just lookin’ at him
is enough to send chills
down my spine.
Keep it together, hol horse.
Don’t let him spook you.
he’s nothin’
to lose your cool over.
yeah, he’s not even
that much stronger than you.
Dio: I’ll ask you again.
Did you want something,
hol horse?
Hol horse: Uh,
well, yes, actually.
there’s somethin’
I thought you oughta know.
i received intel
that two of the nine great gods,
mariah and alessi,
have been put out of commission.
Dio: And your point is?
( Hol horse gasps )
Well, there’s more.
We’ve got trouble comin’.
Turns out joestar and his gang
will arrive in Cairo tomorrow,
and only three
of the nine gods are left.
Dio: It seems you’ve
misunderstood my question.
i want to know
what you’re going to do,
- hol horse.
- Hol horse: Eh?!
Dio: You seem to have been
caught rather off guard.
I simply wish to know
when you’re going
kill them, hol horse.
while it’s true you’ve
pledged your allegiance to me,
you have yet to adequately
prove yourself in battle.
In this day and age,
any simpleton
can deliver information.
twice you’ve failed me,
and here you are crawling back.
( Hol horse gasping )
( Sizzles )
Dio: You couldn’t know this,
but my body once belonged
to a man by the name
of Jonathan joestar.
Jonathan was the grandfather
of Joseph joestar.
look closely.
Notice how the left finger
heals at a slower rate
than the right?
The left side of this body
is weak,
which proves that it doesn’t
completely belong to me yet
and that I am not yet immortal.
I am ill-equipped
to fight a battle
with joestar and his friends.
now then,
if there is nothing else,
run along, and destroy
my enemies on my behalf.
Failure will most assuredly
result in your untimely demise.
( Hol horse thinking) You’re
barkin’ up the wrong tree, hoss.
As if threats are
gonna make me roll over
and do whatever you want.
( Growls )
On your behalf, my ass.
I’m no fool.
I’m smart enough to throw in
with whoever’s strongest.
Everything i’ve said
has been lip service.
I’d never swear my loyalty
to you at the cost of my soul.
rat bastard,
you’re not so tough, are you?
You’re wide open.
Guess having another person’s
body attached to your head
has made you go soft.
This is perfect.
I don’t have to fight Joseph
and the other three,
not when i’ve got dio
in my crosshairs.
It’d be a hell of a lot easier
to blow his head to smithereens
right here and now.
♪
If I do, his treasure’s
mine for the takin’.
This’ll be a piece of cake.
He doesn’t know emperor’s
aimed point-blank at his skull.
I could finish him off,
and he’ll be none the wiser.
Just one pull of the trigger,
and this nightmare will be over.
After all, emperor was made
for close-combat carnage.
I can do this. I can do this.
Dio: Is there a problem?
You seem to be hesitating.
( Hol horse thinking)
Eat lead, shit-bag!
i’m about
to splatter your brains
all over the floor, Mr. Dio!
Dio: Are you positive you want
to go through with shooting me?
( Hol horse gasps )
Huh?
He’s gone!
( Dio chuckles )
( Hol horse gasps )
Dio: Fascinating.
As you prepared to fire,
your breathing was relaxed.
You didn’t even perspire.
You were composed.
Very impressive, hol horse.
( Squelch )
( Hol horse gasps )
This doesn’t make
a lick of sense.
I didn’t even see him move.
There’s no way in hell he
could have creeped up behind me
without breaking a single one
of those spider webs.
Fast or not, he shouldn’t have
been able to sneak up to my rear
without me noticing something.
Was that the power
of dio’s stand,
the power of the world?
Ill-equipped? Yeah, right.
I-I finally understand,
master dio.
I’ve got no choice but to pledge
my eternal loyalty to you.
Y-you’ve got me beat.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
crew member:
Ladies and gentlemen,
we sincerely hope you’ve enjoyed
today’s flight from aswan.
We’ll be arriving on schedule
at Cairo
international airport shortly.
♪
man: Whoops! Snooze,
you loose, buddy! ( Laughs )
man #2: I hate
to break it to you, cowboy,
but it looks like this
is our cab now. ( Laughs )
- No hard feelings?
- ( Hol horse growls )
Man #1: Huh? Don’t tell me
you’re gonna start
cryin’ like a baby! Hah!
( Screaming )
Man #2: Shit! What the hell?!
Hol horse: Giza, pronto.
The mena house hotel.
I’m gonna open up this suitcase
and let you out.
Unless you want
some grade-a pain,
I suggest you keep calm.
we clear?
Driver: Huh? Did you, uh,
say something just now, sir?
hol horse: If I did,
it sure the hell wasn’t to you.
Now shut up,
and drive the cab!
Driver: Ehh! Yes, sir.
( Mondatta grunting )
hol horse:
Cut it out. You know,
if you weren’t
makin’ such a damn racket,
I wouldn’t have had
to hogtie you
and put you on the plane
like a piece of luggage!
Don’t be a baby, mondatta.
your brother’s got
another month in the hospital
thanks to that bomb,
so you and I are partners.
now make sure
those big ears are listening,
’cause here’s
what we’re gonna do.
We’re gonna use your book of
premonitions and my assassin gun
to stamp out jotaro, Joseph,
and the rest of those s.O.B.S!
Got that, mondatta?!
I get that we haven’t
known each other long,
but from what i’ve gathered,
you’re afraid
of just about anyone that’s
not your brother, zenyatta.
But don’t you think
this is the perfect chance
to avenge the guy?
You don’t wanna be
a yellow-bellied coward
forever, right?
That’s no good.
I’m out of options, too.
We’ve got no choice
but to fight.
time for us
to get our revenge, mondatta.
I’m gonna let you loose now,
but you have to swear to me
you won’t carry on
with all
that infernal hollering, okay?
( Mondatta mutters )
Hol horse: See that, son?
I’m not so bad.
Now try and settle down, eh?
I don’t need you
gettin’ sick on me,
’cause believe it or not,
i’m on your side
in this whole mess,
so don’t you worry.
Just relax for now.
Huh?
Driver: Sir, why do you
have a puking kid?!
Hol horse: Shut up!
- ( Mondatta vomits )
- Hol horse: I see.
You got motion sickness
from being on the plane.
mondatta,
l-let’s be pals from here on.
How’s that sound?
( Mondatta vomiting )
"I’m mondatta.
"This is hol horse.
"he’s mean,
and I don’t like him!
"While mondatta was sleeping,
"hol horse tied him up
and stuffed him in a trunk.
"mondatta was taken
from his brother, zenyatta.
"He was sad.
"But even though mondatta
was scared out of his mind,
"he wanted to avenge
his brother,
"so he decided
to work up his courage
and become partners
with hol horse."
( Hol horse growls )
hmm?
( Mondatta gasping )
Hol horse: Oh, come on!
You won’t even get near me?
Well, I guess you’re tryin’,
which is all I can
ask for at this point.
And by the way, I gotta know.
does your stand
really predict the future,
or is that just
some cockamamie rumor?
If that was all
just a tall tale,
then I brought you here
for nothin’.
I mean, even with it,
your brother
got blown to high heaven.
( Mondatta gasping )
Hol horse: Which is it, kid?!
Are you a fraud?!
Hmm? How’d a new comic
appear on a blank page
from out of nowhere?
mondatta:
"While mondatta and hol horse
"were walking through
the outskirts of Cairo,
"they met a lady who was
as pretty as the day was long.
Then hol horse jump-kicked
the lady in the neck!"
Hol horse: Hmm?
Mondatta: "The pretty lady
"was so overjoyed
about the kick that,
"out of the blue,
she gave hol horse her jewels.
Yahoo! We’re rich!"
Hol horse: What the hell
- is this crap?!
- ( Mondatta gulps )
Hol horse: You must think
I was born last night!
you call this
a prediction, mondatta?!
There’s just no way!
This crap has to be
made up or somethin’.
Mondatta: I’m telling the truth.
My stand, thoth, you just
have to trust in its prophecies.
Th-th-they’re 100--
they’re 100% right every time.
Hol horse: They’re right 100%?
You tryin’ to pull
the wool over my eyes?!
There’s no way some lady’s
gonna give me her jewels
after jump-kickin’ her
in the neck.
You’d have to be off your rocker
to do somethin’ like that.
Hmm?
♪
( Both gasp )
Hol horse: Listen, mondatta.
I am proud to say
that i’m a gentleman
and a proper gentleman at that.
’cause of that, I got girls
all over the world.
I might tell a white lie
now and again,
but i’d never haul off
and hit one.
I respect all the ladies,
the beauties,
the plain ones,
and even the ugly ones.
There’s no way your prediction
will ever come to pass.
Come hell or high water, I swear
I will never hit a woman.
She could pay me every dime,
nickel, and quarter she had.
I still wouldn’t
put my hands on her.
Mondatta: It’s 100% true, yes.
( Hol horse growls )
♪
Hmph.
- ( Mondatta whimpers )
- Hol horse: See there?
Your fancy prediction was wrong.
- ( Mondatta whimpering )
- hol horse: Huh?
( Gasping )
( Mondatta grumbles )
( Hol horse yells )
( Woman shrieks )
( Man yelps )
Who the hell are you?!
♪
( Woman gasping )
Man: What in the--
th-there was
a scorpion in your shawl!
This thing’s sting
is a death sentence.
Woman: What?!
( Hol horse gasps )
Woman: You spotted
that wretched creature
before it had a chance
to crawl into my clothes.
Man: If you hadn’t killed it,
she would have
been stung for sure.
( Hol horse gasps )
( Mondatta chuckles )
Woman: You saved my life.
Oh, please, let me repay you.
Would my necklace be
a sufficient reward?
It’s yours.
( Hol horse laughs )
Boy, this is my lucky day.
Mondatta and I are
practically invincible.
We’ll be the unstoppable duo!
Roofer: I don’t think i’m
gonna be able to help you folks.
it’s been my job
to repair rooftops in Cairo
for around 40 years now,
and I can’t say
that i’ve ever seen
a place like this.
from the looks
of the building’s design,
the thing was built
over a hundred years ago,
give or take.
If I had to take a guess,
based on the picture,
i’d say you’d find it
somewhere south of here.
The buildings in Cairo
get older and older
the farther south you travel.
Polnareff: Huh?
Roofer: I’m sorry I don’t
have more to go on, Sonny.
polnareff:
No, don’t worry about it.
Sorry to bother.
( Grunts )
( Joseph sighs )
All right, understood.
Thanks for the update.
I decided to make
a call to Japan,
and my daughter’s condition
is much worse.
She’s lost virtually
all of her strength.
at best, she has
three or four days left.
( Both gasp )
( Jotaro sighs )
( Joseph sighs )
I can almost feel it.
It’s like dio’s
right on top of us.
I’d bet anything that he’s
hiding somewhere close by,
but where could he be,
and how do we find him?
Avdol: We should get moving.
We’ll talk to everyone here
until we find him.
joseph: Hmm.
We’ve come this far.
We have to keep going.
♪
hol horse:
Been a long time comin’,
but it’s time
for our grand reunion.
I’m getting sick of those faces.
I never thought they’d get so
close to master dio’s mansion,
but they’re on a collision
course for his backyard.
And by the way,
listen, mondatta!
( Mondatta yelps )
( Whimpering )
Hol horse: We need to chat
about your latest prediction.
You sure it’s 100% foolproof?
It’s more than a little wacky.
They’re not dumb enough
to fall for this.
( Mondatta whimpers )
B-but my premonitions--ow!
Hol horse: "My premonitions
are always 100% accurate."
Is that what you were gonna say?
Mondatta: Well, they are, yes.
Hol horse: Come on!
you really expect me
to buy this load of baloney?
I think you’ve lost
your touch, boy.
"’we found them!’
shouted hol horse.
"’joseph, jotaro,
polnareff, and avdol.
"Darn it,’ hol horse fumed.
"’they’re a hop,
skip, and a jump
"’away from master dio’s manor.
Those nosy buffoons’ll each
get a bullet between the eyes.’"
mondatta: "Hol horse’s mind
was full of violent thoughts.
"’you’re gonna pay
for my brother!’
"mondatta was beside himself
with anger.
"But despite the pair
wanting immediate payback,
hol horse couldn’t use his gun,
the emperor, in the market."
"’now, hol horse,’
mondatta instructed,
"’stick your fingers
all the way up polnareff’s nose,
"’and then we’ll win!
"’they’re out cold
from losing all that blood.
"’lucky you, hol horse.
this is your chance
to finish them off for good.’"
hol horse: Like hell
i’m gonna buy that!
This is your big premonition?
Sticking my calloused fingers
up polnareff’s
booger-infested nose?
The hell do you take me for?
Well, speak, mondatta!
The part about killing ’em
sounds good to me,
but the rest of it--
you’d better not be planning
anything funny, boy.
I mean, come on! Even if I was
supposed to stick my fingers
up polnareff’s nose,
i’d have to somehow get
close enough to him to do it.
instead of
all that skullduggery,
I think we should go
with the direct approach
and put a bullet in him
with emperor! What do you say?
Mondatta: Y-you’re not gonna
be able to fire a bullet, yes.
E-even though you tried
firing your stand,
fate wouldn’t let you, yes.
You have to trust me, yes.
I know from personal experience,
I-If you try to go
against the comic,
you’ll suffer the consequences.
It’s fate, I tell you.
it’s 100%
up to the whims of fate, yes.
Hol horse: Hang on!
Your brother followed the comic
and nearly died.
Mondatta: M-my brother
was trying to save himself,
but he foolishly
disguised himself as jotaro
without thinking, yes.
If he had trusted what he read
and not disguised himself,
then the real jotaro
would have been blown up, yes.
The premonition itself
was correct, yes.
( Hol horse groans )
Then what now?
Hmm?
Wait! Where did polnareff go?
hey, kid,
polnareff left the herd.
Find out where he went.
( Mondatta gasps )
Hol horse: Shit! It can’t be.
Polnareff: Don’t you move...
Unless you’d like to be lanced.
hol horse:
But how the hell did you...
( Gags )
Polnareff: Imbecile!
What exactly did you think
you were trying
to pull just now?
If you know what’s good for you,
keep your hands
where I can see them.
( Hol horse groaning )
polnareff: I thought
I noticed someone stalking us
like a desperate,
starving hyena,
and wouldn’t you know,
I was lucky enough
to stumble across
our old friend, hol horse.
it looks you’re
still trying to kill us,
which means you haven’t
learned your lesson yet.
Say, thanks for all
the fun back in India.
you’re very lucky
avdol survived our run-in,
’cause if he hadn’t,
you, my friend,
would already be dead.
( Hol horse grunting )
polnareff:
You here alone, hol horse?
No way. A coward like you
wouldn’t come by himself.
I’m sure he’s hiding out
nearby, right?
Well, where’s your partner?
Hol horse: Crap!
On the upside, though,
he hasn’t noticed mondatta yet.
I still have a chance.
( Gasps )
Shit!
He’s gonna see the book
and his fingers.
Polnareff: On your own, you’re
not much of a threat, hol horse,
but i’m well aware
that you have
a special talent
for picking allies.
If you’ve found someone
to work with like before,
that could make you
a dangerous obstacle.
tell me,
where did your partner go?
out with it.
Where is the other stand user?
Hol horse: Your fingers.
Mondatta, hide your fingers.
if he gets wise
to where you are, it’s all over.
Mondatta: You have to believe.
the reason
you’re in this situation
is because
you tried using your gun.
Trust me. Believe in fate.
If you believe
in the power of fate,
our victory is guaranteed, yes.
- Polnareff: Hmm?
- Hol horse: Huh?
Polnareff: I saw a hand
go under the box,
which means my hunch was right.
Avdol: What’s the word,
polnareff?
Did you find the guy
that was following us?
Hol horse: Oh, no, it’s avdol,
and he’s headed straight for us.
Mondatta: Believe, yes.
Put your faith in the book,
and stick your fingers
up polnareff’s nose, yes!
Hol horse: Are you serious?
Damn it.
- Joseph: Hmm?
- Avdol: Hmm?
( Hol horse gasps )
I’ve got no choice.
Fine. I’ll do it!
♪
Polnareff: You under the crate,
show yourself!
Hol horse: Now, while he’s
looking the other way!
polnareff: I know
you’re hiding under there!
What the hell?!
Hol horse: Hell, yeah!
( Polnareff gasping )
( Mondatta chuckles )
"’whoo-hoo!
Everyone bled so much,
"’they all passed out!
Lucky you, hol horse!
Now’s your chance
to finish them off!’"
hol horse: So when is
this so-called chance
supposed to get here,
and what do I do ’til then?
Polnareff: Excuse me, hol horse.
Uh, what the hell
are you doing?
hol horse:
You’re not the only one
who wants to know
the answer to that question.
I haven’t the foggiest idea
where to go from here.
What am I supposed to do?
avdol: Hey,
what’s the matter, polnareff?
( Hol horse gasps )
Avdol: He’s not answering back.
Jotaro: Something’s off.
Hol horse: Shit! What now?!
They’re on me
like white on rice!
Damn it! How the hell
do I make the rest of this
stupid prediction come true?
This is crazy.
What am I supposed to do?!
♪
( Singing and speaking
in Japanese )