Joseph: Jotaro, do you hear
what you’re saying right now?
( D’arby growls )
Jotaro: Of course I do.
finally starting
to lose your hearing, old man?
Obviously I just told him
my next pitch.
i’m gonna win
with a high, outside fastball.
( Joseph gasps )
But, jotaro, you--
jotaro: Will you believe me,
or will you doubt me instead?
( D’arby scoffs )
Not too bright, are you?
♪
My stand peers into your soul
the same way a thermal imager
detects an object’s radiation.
Say what you will,
your soul cannot lie.
Regardless of what it is,
by analyzing your soul,
I can see the answer
to any yes-or-no question.
Right or left? High or low?
Outside or inside?
Fastball or curveball?
My stand’s perception
is infallible.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Will your pitch be
a high, outside fastball?
Yes or no?
Jotaro: Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
D’arby: Well, jotaro’s
telling the truth, after all.
He’s really going to pitch
a high, outside fastball.
What’s he up to?
it’s true that he
beat my brother by bluffing,
but he’s a fool if he thinks
the same, tired tactic
will work with me.
- Jotaro: Here it comes.
- ( Joseph gasps )
D’arby: For your sake,
I hope you haven’t forgotten
that you’ll lose the game
if you fall 11 runs behind.
♪
Was that a curve?
Impossible.
I thought he was going
for a high, outside fastball.
- Joseph: Eh?
- ( Bat strikes ball )
Announcer: He hits,
but it’s a grounder.
The ball is thrown to first,
and out.
( D’arby gasps )
♪
T-there’s just no way.
Everything about him
said he was going to throw
a high, outside fastball.
his soul can’t lie.
No one’s can, not a zen master,
not even my brother, and he’s
the world’s greatest con man.
jotaro: Next up is
another high, outside fastball.
( D’arby gasps )
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
What the hell?
He’s telling the truth.
Jotaro, you have the gall
to cheat your way to victory?
Jotaro: I do! I do!
I do! I do! I do!
d’arby: What?
He actually is cheating.
announcer:
A low, inside forkball.
it’s a fly ball
heading for the pitcher.
Out.
D’arby: You must have cheated.
Admit it!
You bastard. You clearly
tampered with the console.
Jotaro: No! No! No! No! No! No!
D’arby: Wha--
he’s telling the truth?
( Panting )
( Joseph gasps )
D’arby: I know
you’re cheating me.
You have to be. Would you
just come clean already?
No response.
Damn it, that’s right.
I only have use of my power if I
ask him a yes-or-no question.
Jotaro: Judging from
your scared expression,
your power requires
a yes-or-no question.
It’s like your brother
used to say.
this is
just a dance of deception
where the loser cries first.
D’arby: A dance, eh? So this
is nothing but a game to you?
( Growls ) How dare you?
Are you taking me for a fool?
Have you any idea
who you’re speaking to?
Jotaro, pitch the ball!
I’ll figure out
your little trick
and take your soul
as my prize!
( Jotaro scoffs )
All right, let’s continue.
For my next pitch, i’ll throw
a high, outside fastball.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
D’arby: Once again, his soul
says he’s telling the truth.
He’s really going to pitch
a high, outside fastball.
I’ve had about as much of this
as I can take. This ends now.
I’ll figure out
how you’re cheating
if it’s the last thing I do.
♪
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
D’arby: So jotaro
hasn’t changed his mind.
he’s still dead set
on throwing that infernal pitch.
It’s coming.
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
D’arby: So far,
it’s still a fastball,
and his soul is saying, "yes."
It changed direction!
a forkball!
what?!
It’s a different pitch now!
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes!
umpire: Out.
That’s three outs. Change.
( Joseph sighs )
( D’arby panting )
I don’t get it.
Why can’t I figure out
how he’s cheating?
Jotaro’s soul kept saying
he’d throw a fastball,
but at the last second,
it curved into a forkball.
Th-this doesn’t make any sense!
How? How is this wretch
deceiving me?!
Jotaro: You’re gonna
lose this game, d’arby.
D’arby: Shut your mouth!
come on. Tell me why
you removed your stupid hat!
I’m more perceptive
than you think.
I know you’ve been cheating
ever since you took it off.
Now move. I want to check
your station and controller.
( Jotaro pats hat )
D’arby: There’s nothing here.
Damn you! How did you do it?!
It must have something to do
with that hat of yours.
Isn’t that right?
Jotaro: No! No! No! No!
( D’arby gasps )
There must be evidence
around here somewhere.
- Jotaro: No! No! No! No!
- D’arby: I get it.
You’re using star platinum
to cheat, aren’t you?
Jotaro: No! No! No! No!
D’arby: Just admit it!
You’re doing something!
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes!
yes! Yes! Yes!
( D’arby growls )
damn it.
Damn it! I can clearly
read jotaro’s thoughts,
which means my stand’s power
is still working as it should,
so how can his mind
say one thing,
but his body do another?
Joseph: Hey, jotaro,
are you seeing this?
Looks like he’s losing
his youthful glow.
He definitely doesn’t look like
a guy in his twenties anymore.
Jotaro: D’arby, it’s your turn
to pitch, so hurry.
We don’t have all day.
D’arby: It’s four to three.
with only
a one-point difference,
I might still have a chance.
I am a video game genius.
i can’t lose.
I can’t lose!
I’ve won every game
i’ve ever played.
I’m invincible.
A video game expert
is an expert at life.
do you think you can
shake my confidence so easily?
Announcer: Look at that.
Another home run.
That’s another run
for the jaguars, folks.
It’s five to three.
( D’arby groans )
( Doll exhales )
- ( D’arby gasps )
- Joseph: Eh?
( D’arby groans )
I-it can’t be.
I accidentally released
his soul from the doll!
Joseph: Look! His soul
has returned to his body.
He’s regaining consciousness.
( Kakyoin murmurs )
D’arby: N-no. I didn’t.
I never once admitted defeat.
It was an accident.
I didn’t mean to release
his soul from the doll.
Jotaro: But the thing is
you did release his soul.
You know what that means.
Your soul admitted defeat,
and it’s game over.
D’arby: Huh? Hold on.
This is joseph’s stand?
it was wrapped around
the controller the entire time.
Joseph: Huh? Whoops. I guess
I forgot to put this away.
D’arby: How could
something so stupid--
no. You mean it was Joseph?
He was the cheater all along?
damn it.
Jotaro was telling the truth.
he really
wasn’t controlling it.
It was you, Joseph joestar!
Joseph: Hmm?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Jotaro: That’s right. Good boy.
Too bad you’re not your brother,
’cause if you were,
you would have figured it out
a long time ago.
( D’arby gasping )
Jotaro: By the way, old man,
you’re pretty clever.
I didn’t expect you
to catch on to my idea
as quickly as you did.
joseph: Well,
of course I did, my boy.
I can read you like a book.
You are my grandson, after all.
( Chuckles )
Now up and at ’em, kakyoin.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- D’arby: Damn.
Joseph was controlling things
from behind.
Joseph: Before I forget...
What to do with you,
you button-mashing jerk?
D’arby: Oh, shit!
Please, mercy! I beg you!
I’ve already given you back
kakyoin’s soul, haven’t I?
It’s like they say,
"no harm, no foul."
We’re good. Right?
Right? Right?
Jotaro: You wanna know
whether i’ll forgive you?
Why don’t you just do what
you do best and read my mind?
No! No! No! No! No!
( D’arby whimpers )
Jotaro: Answer this. Will I
hit you with my right fist
or decide to deck you
with my left?
I’d love to know.
D’arby: Well,
since you’re asking,
you’ll use your right one?
Jotaro: No! No! No! No! No!
D’arby: Then your left?
D’arby: You’re not
gonna use both, are you?
Jotaro: Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
D’arby: Are you gonna do
the "ora! Ora!" Thing?!
Joseph: Yes, yes, yes!
oh, my god.
( Star platinum yelling )
Narrator: D’arby younger,
out of commission
- star platinum: Ora!
- ( D’arby screams )
( Joseph and kakyoin gasp )
Joseph: How about that?
We broke through
some sort of wall.
That’s our ticket out of here.
Jotaro. Kakyoin.
Jotaro: Good grief.
♪
Man: Forgive me
for disturbing you,
but, your excellence,
as i’m sure you’re aware,
joestar and his comrades
have just infiltrated the manor.
regrettably,
I must also inform you
that d’arby has been defeated.
( Clock ticking )
dio: Oh?
But d’arby was a genius.
how could one
as gifted as d’arby fail me?
come. I’d like
to hear your thoughts.
You may enter, cool ice.
♪
Cool ice: As you wish.
Dio: Always remember this.
Whatever the obstacle,
whatever the danger,
the joestars are prepared
to sacrifice their lives
in order to save their family.
Kakyoin and the other two--
( Sighs )
What were their names again?
Ah, yes, I believe
it’s avdol and polnareff.
they’re willing
to surrender their lives
for the eradication
of yours truly.
They believe fleeing from me
is somehow the same
as running from themselves.
Fools, one and all.
Nonetheless,
the fools find strength
in this misguided belief.
D’arby swore his undying
loyalty, but unfortunately
he was not prepared
to actually die on my behalf,
which is why,
at the edge of glory,
victory slipped
through his fingers.
For the rest of eternity,
d’arby will remain in ignorance.
Ice...
have a look
at the scar on my neck.
Jonathan joestar’s body
is still rejecting me,
but I need the blood
of one more soul
before this body
truly becomes mine,
and once that happens,
the wound will heal.
Ice, will you offer me
the crimson vigor
coursing through your veins?
Cool ice: Yes. It’d be an honor.
♪
What is mine is yours.
( Blood pouring )
( Body falls )
♪
Dio: Ah, you beheaded yourself.
Most splendid.
But, cool ice,
I cannot accept the blood
of such a loyal servant.
My wound shall be healed,
but it will be
with the blood of another.
For now, you must live,
so awaken, and be reborn.
Your steadfast resolve
shall secure your victory
over those who’d oppose me.
♪
Cool ice: I shall
not fail you, my lord.
dio: No weapon
can surpass one’s own body.
You are ready, cool ice.
Now go, and attend
to our unwanted guests.
Cool ice: I swear, lord dio,
I will not let you down.
You have my word.
I’ll destroy them all.
( Stand growling )
Dio: Well, I sincerely hope
that for your sake,
your next victim into the void
will be one of the joestars
and not my boudoir.
Avdol: The ten minutes
he gave us are up.
I know that Mr. Joestar ordered
us to set the mansion on fire,
but I say we go.
We have to find them.
Polnareff: Agreed.
Avdol: Polnareff,
before we proceed,
there’s something
I need to tell you.
listen well. If you
lose your way, get injured,
or can’t go on,
I won’t come to your rescue.
Make sure you understand that.
Same for you, iggy.
I know that might sound cruel,
but remember
the reason we’re here
is to defeat dio
once and for all.
And of course the same rules
must apply to me as well.
if i’m injured
or separated from you,
you have to promise
you won’t attempt to save me.
Above all else, you must think
of your own safety.
we can’t
let ourselves get killed
trying to save one another.
There’s too much at stake.
polnareff: Oui.
That’s how it goes, then.
♪
If we get out of this alive,
you’re treating me
to one hell of a meal.
- Avdol: I’ll treat you both.
- ( Iggy grunts )
Polnareff: All right, let’s go.
Do your thing, silver chariot!
( Metal rings )
( Both grunt )
♪
Polnareff: Hey, avdol,
what do we do now?
this place looks
like it goes on forever.
( Avdol sighs )
I know Mr. Joestar told us
to set the mansion on fire,
but setting
this immense labyrinth ablaze
would end up putting us
all in danger, so instead...
Magician’s red.
( Both gasp )
Avdol: These flames
detect life-forms.
They can sense anything alive,
detecting
even cutaneous respiration
and minute movements.
These flames can also sense
a stand’s energy,
so we’ll let them lead the way.
Polnareff: Any particular reason
there are six flames?
Avdol: There’s one
for each direction,
as well as for above and below.
If there is anything hidden
within 15 meters,
regardless of its size,
the flame
will detect its presence
and alert us immediately.
Mr. Joestar and the others
were pulled below us.
Let’s head down.
- ( Flames hissing )
- ( Gasps )
the flames
are picking up on something.
apparently it’s
in front of us to the left.
Polnareff: What is?!
Iggy: The fool!
♪
( Both gasp )
( Man shrieks )
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Iggy growls )
Polnareff: What the hell?!
Who’s this guy supposed to be?
( Avdol gasps ) Look.
Do you see what’s happening,
polnareff?
Polnareff: Huh? The maze,
it’s totally disappeared!
Avdol: I’m willing to bet
the power of this man’s stand
created the illusion
of the maze.
it dissipated
as soon as iggy slashed him.
( Iggy scoffs )
Narrator: His name, Billie Jean.
His fate, instant defeat.
Avdol: The mansion
is back to normal now,
so we averted
at least one potential crisis,
and the flames don’t seem
to be sensing any danger.
Hmm?
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
The flames don’t sense a thing,
and iggy hasn’t picked up
on anything either.
( Gasps )
my god,
what is that abomination?
Impossible! Neither my flames
nor iggy could sense it.
Where did it come from?!
Polnareff, iggy, you have
to get out of here now!
( Both gasp )
♪
( Avdol grunts )
Hey, where are you, avdol?!
The hell?
W-what was that thing?
where did it--
no, it can’t be.
Whose arms are--
h-hey, avdol, where did you go?!
Avdol, where are you?!
Avdol!
Come out, avdol!
( Stand growls )
polnareff:
W-what the hell is that thing?
Where did it come from?!
Weren’t avdol’s flames
supposed to be
able to sense anything?
Hey, iggy, couldn’t your nose
pick up on this thing?!
Answer me!
( Groans )
Avdol, where are you?!
Where the hell’d you go?!
Stand: Avdol...
( Growls )
Has been reduced
to nothingness.
- ( Polnareff sputters )
- ( Iggy pants )
Stand: Beyond my jaws
lies an endless void,
a dark dimension
which harbors things
even I do not fully comprehend.
Your ally is dead, but fret not,
as you will soon join him.
You were arrogant enough
to believe
you could defeat lord dio,
therefore you must be punished.
( Growling )
( Polnareff gasps )
Cool ice: One by one,
each of you shall fall in line
as I scatter
your atomic fragments
across the deepest recesses
of the void.
( Iggy gasps )
( Polnareff sputters )
No, you’re lying.
It’s impossible.
There’s no way you killed avdol.
How dare you lie to me?!
♪