Narrator: Previously
on "jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
Joseph: That’s her! That woman
there is the stand user!
( Mariah laughs )
- Woman: Ooh!
- ( Joseph groans )
Woman: I do appreciate
your forwardness,
but you need
to work on your approach,
you naughty, naughty man.
Mwah!
Joseph: Oh, my god!
I forgot to tell you.
Whatever you do,
it’s imperative that you refrain
from touching
any electrical outlets!
Avdol: Eh? I’m afraid
I already did, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: What?!
- ( Crackling )
- ( Both grunt )
Joseph: If what I know
about magnets is true,
we’re being forced together!
Avdol: Mr. Joestar, I really
hate saying this, but...
Joseph: Yeah, I know.
We’ve gotten ourselves
into a world of trouble.
( Mariah laughing )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Mariah chuckles )
Joseph: Hey! Wait a sec!
Damn it all.
( Both grunting )
Joseph: Look!
She’s getting away! After her!
- ( Humming )
- ( Both grunting )
Avdol: Blast it!
Now my body’s a magnet!
I can’t believe
we allowed ourselves
to play right into her hands!
Joseph: Calm down, avdol.
You getting hysterical
isn’t helping anything.
Focus on figuring out how
to overpower this blasted stand.
Damn it! Now where did
that woman run off to?!
Avdol: I don’t see her anywhere!
Joseph: Well, we can’t keep
rolling in the dirt forever!
Why don’t we try
slowly standing up?
- Avdol: Give it a go.
- ( Both grunting )
Boy: Huh?
Joseph: All right, we did it.
Now that we’re upright,
the next step is to try
pulling away from each other.
However, I think it’s going
to be easier said than done,
since the magnetic force
that’s currently
holding us together
has been doubled.
But for now,
let’s use that fence
to try getting out
of this predicament.
We can do it, avdol!
Get those stomach muscles ready,
and make sure you stay in sync!
Avdol: Ready when you are,
Mr. Joestar!
Both: One, two! One, two!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
- One, two!
- Boy: Uh...
Joseph: Eh?
Avdol: Mr. Joestar, this is one
of the most embarrassing things
i’ve ever done.
Joseph: What do you think
you’re looking at?!
Can’t you see that we’re
just practicing our dance moves?
Avdol: It’s true!
What a perfect day
for dancing outdoors!
Joseph: Now run along!
Get out of here, damn it!
♪
There we go!
Almost got it, avdol!
Both: And one, and two.
( Both grunt )
Joseph: We did it!
We made it,
and we’re still standing!
Avdol: Yes, a remarkable feat.
Joseph: Avdol, now that
we’ve gotten over here,
do you think
you can slide off me?
( Avdol grunts )
I think I might be able to.
Joseph: All right.
Here’s what we’re gonna do,
so listen carefully.
I’ll hang on to the fence
as tightly as I can
while you slide down.
Free yourself once you’ve
gotten to the tip of my foot.
Do you see how our faces
are stuck together
as opposed
to the other way around?
Well, it’s more
than likely a sign
that my feet and your head
should repel each other.
Avdol: Yes,
that makes a lot of sense.
( Grunting )
Joseph: That’s the way, avdol!
Just keep moving!
( Humming )
Avdol: Hmm. ( Shudders )
Joseph: Uh, hey, what’s
the matter with you, avdol?
Avdol: D-don’t you think
this position is a little--
this pose is highly suggestive,
Mr. Joestar.
If anyone were to see us,
they would be inclined
to think that--
Joseph: Oh, come off it!
No one’s looking at us!
Hurry up, and slide off my--
yaah!
Those little brats came back
and brought their friends!
Why don’t you take a hike?!
There’s nothing to see,
so knock it off
with the staring, would you?!
I said beat it,
you little ankle biters!
Get out of here! Take off!
Avdol, hurry up, and get off me
before this gets any worse.
Avdol: I’m trying
as hard as I can!
( Moans ) I can’t believe
this is happening to me!
The embarrassment!
Joseph: All right,
i’ll be the one to move!
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
please slow down!
( Grunts )
( Joseph laughs )
( Avdol laughs )
♪
- ( Gasps )
- ( Crackles )
( Joseph wails )
( Both groan )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
moving around like that makes it
- seem as though we’re--
- ( Woman squeals )
- ( Joseph gasps )
- ( Woman stammers )
Joseph: Oh, no!
It’s that old hag again!
Woman: I come back expecting
to find my handsome man,
and instead my eyes
are assaulted with this?!
How dare you toy
with the fragile gift
of a maiden’s heart,
you filthy cheater?!
Joseph: For the love of god,
hurry, avdol!
She getting closer, and I can
already feel the tears coming!
Woman: Dirty, rotten scoundrel!
- ( Yelling )
- ( Joseph grunting )
Help me! Oh, my god!
Avdol: Please calm down!
You’ve got it all wrong!
( Joseph yells )
Avdol: We did it!
We need to stay far apart
from each other!
Your magnetic pull is getting
more powerful by the second!
Woman: It serves you right,
you damned fool!
You and your boy toy,
go to hell!
( Men groan )
( Mariah laughs )
- ( Both gasp )
- Joseph: What the--
avdol: There she is!
We found her.
Joseph: Just look at her
having her morning cigarette.
Avdol, try going after her
from that side.
We can’t let her
get away from us this time.
She’s cunning,
so this may be a trap.
- ( Clang )
- ( Avdol groans )
- ( Humming )
- This can’t be!
Mr. Joestar,
it would appear as though
we’ve already fallen
right into her trap!
Joseph: Eh?
Hmm.
Ahh! They’re railroad tracks!
Avdol: And I don’t think
we’re going to be able
to get off that easily!
( Grunting )
( Both yell )
Joseph: Are you kidding me?!
Avdol: It would seem...
Both: That we’re
stuck together again!
( Mariah laughs )
( Joseph groans )
Son of a bi--eh?
( Clacking )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
something is coming.
Joseph: That sound--oh, no,
we have to get the hell
out of here as fast as we can!
Avdol, I need you
to use magician’s red
to burn through the tracks!
We need to get out of here!
Avdol: But, Mr. Joestar,
I don’t think that would be--
- ( train horn honking )
- Joseph: Eh?
♪
It’s here! There’s the train!
Hurry up, and melt those tracks!
Avdol: I tried telling you,
Mr. Joestar!
If I were to burn away
these tracks...
- ( Joseph yells )
- Avdol: The train would derail,
and innocent people would
go tumbling to their deaths!
( Mariah exhales )
( Laughs )
Joseph: Shit!
That damn woman
is pure, unadulterated evil!
( Groaning )
I’m almost positive my vines
would be able to hold her,
but at that distance,
she’s too far out of range
for them to even reach her,
so our best bet is me trying
to pull us free from the tracks
using that post as an anchor.
I-it’s no use!
The magnetic pull is even
stronger than it was before!
Mr. Joestar, it’s life or death!
You can’t stop pulling,
no matter what!
It’s coming!
You have to pull harder!
( Joseph yelling )
♪
That didn’t work!
Mariah: I win.
( Chuckles )
♪
( Mariah laughs )
I took care of them for you,
lord dio.
Now that that’s done,
i’m going to do away
with jotaro and polnareff.
Eh?
Joseph: Good thinking, avdol!
Only someone as clever as you
would burn the railroad tracks
and dig a trench underneath!
Avdol: You see, Mr. Joestar,
unlike that earlier incident,
Mohammed avdol does indeed
have a decent modicum of class.
Doing things this way
is a little more my style.
( Laughs )
Mariah: So you think
you’ve outsmarted me?
You...
Obnoxious pieces of shit!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
Joseph: Me, too! Hermit purple!
- ( Chuckles )
- ( Avdol grunts )
Joseph: Now we’ve got you.
Unfortunately for you,
young lady,
i’ve got to keep a grip
on your neck until you pass out,
so you can count
on being in the hospital
for at least a week or so.
I can’t just let you and your
magnetic power run free, can I?
( Mariah laughs )
♪
Joseph: Hmm?
( Both gasp )
Mariah: Are your imaginations
running wild?
Sorry to disappoint, boys,
but my breasts
aren’t getting larger.
( Laughs )
But there’s no need
to worry yourselves,
because your magnetism’s
growing even stronger.
And lucky for me I just happened
to stuff my bra with weapons.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
we have incoming!
( Joseph yells )
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Joseph groans )
( Mariah laughs )
Your magnetism
will keep intensifying,
well, at least until your bodies
are crushed to tiny pieces.
Avdol: She’s getting away again!
Joseph: No, I don’t think so.
It’s all part of her strategy.
She’s moving
farther away from us
in order to maintain
a safe distance.
Remember,
that woman’s a stand user,
so she needs to stay close
to her target.
If she gets too close to us,
we’ll be able to catch her,
but if she’s too far out
of range, her power won’t work.
This magnetism
is still just a stand.
The normal rules apply,
which means if she puts
too much distance between us,
the magnetism should weaken.
Avdol: So what should we do?
If we don’t get free,
the magnetic force
will just continue to intensify.
Should we keep running
until we’re out of range?
That might be our best bet.
Joseph: No way. We might be able
to get away from her powers
for a short amount of time,
but the stand
would still prevail.
I’ve run away
from fights before,
but i’ve only done so
when running was part
of the overall strategy.
No matter
how hopeless things look,
Joseph joestar
never throws in the towel.
The real showdown begins now!
Avdol: Hmm?
Joseph: I’ve drawn
a map of the town.
Here’s our current position, and
here’s where the woman’s going.
As long as she continues moving
down this road,
she’ll eventually loop around
and head back this way.
We’ll split up, and...
Right here is where
we’ll catch that witch.
It doesn’t matter
if she’s a woman or not.
When we catch her, she’s getting
a taste of my boot!
Let’s get going!
Man: Check it out.
Man #2: Oh, yeah.
Someone’s cut the rails.
Avdol: Good.
The locals are here.
I’m sure one of them
will have the foresight
to notify the authorities
about the tracks
before the next train arrives.
Joseph: Come on!
( Iggy yawns )
( Men panting )
Polnareff: Huh?
Something is definitely up.
Man: Hey! Did you hear
someone cut the rail line?!
Man #2: What about
all the trains?
Man #1: Luckily they’ve stopped
running, at least for now.
Polnareff: Someone actually cut
the rail line?
People nowadays sure
are sick, don’t you think?
Who in their right mind
would do something so terrible?
Major douche canoe.
( Sighs ) Jotaro,
you wanna know what I think?
Rotten people always get
what’s coming to ’em.
You Mark my words.
They’ll get theirs.
( Jotaro sighs )
♪
Man: I saved three months’
salary, all for this.
Will you marry me?
Woman: Oh, my!
- ( Metal humming )
- ( Clank )
- Both: Huh?
- Man: What the?
Wait! Where did the--
woman: The ring!
Mariah: Those morons
are getting closer to me,
but at this rate,
they’ll never catch me.
( Joseph grunts )
( Avdol grunts )
♪
Cyclist: Huh? ( Yelling )
( Joseph grunting )
Shopkeeper:
Almost there. Almost there.
Man: Hmm?
( Grunting )
( Yells )
( Joseph grunting )
( Mariah laughs )
I must say you’re looking
a little weighted down.
But don’t worry.
The wild-goose chase ends here.
( Joseph groans )
Interestingly enough,
it would seem that the two of us
are more familiar with this town
than you are.
You should take a look
behind you.
( Mariah gasps )
Avdol: You’re now
caught between us,
and there’s nowhere
for you to run.
It may have
taken a while to get here,
but the tables have turned.
♪
( Mariah laughing )
( Joseph growls )
( Avdol grunts ) Hmm?
( Metal humming )
Mariah: So you think
I have nowhere to go?
You boys truly haven’t
realized it yet, have you?
You only thought
you were hunting me,
when really I was luring you
here the entire time!
Look up, idiots!
Both: Huh?
♪
Joseph: High-voltage
power lines!
Avdol: Oh, no!
The power lines are--
( Mariah laughs )
That’s right.
Power lines
are extremely magnetic!
( Joseph groaning )
Mariah: I’m afraid you’re
going to fry this time, joestar!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Joseph groans )
Hermit purple!
( Groans )
Mariah: Avdol might be able
to defend himself for now
with his flames, but not you.
Time to die, joestar.
My stand, the goddess bast
is the perfect trap,
and it’s also far more powerful
than your hermit purple!
Hope you’ve said your prayers,
because it’s time to die!
( Joseph groaning )
Avdol: Vile woman.
My flames will burn you
and your evil alive!
- ( Metal humming )
- ( Mariah chuckles )
( Avdol gasps )
( Groaning )
My entire body is being pulled
in another direction!
I--i can’t resist!
( Groans )
My flames should be
strong enough
to melt the steel
without a problem,
but I can’t defend myself
from every attack,
and this weight is crushing me!
( Joseph groaning )
( Yelling )
I can’t hold it any longer!
Mariah: Joseph joestar, since
you’re going to die anyway,
I can confess that I find you
to be quite a catch.
It’s true that I only knew you
for a short time,
but you were
so clever and hilarious,
not to mention your experience
would make younger men
green with envy,
plus you’re very handsome.
I know that you and I
are decades apart,
but if i’m being
honest with myself,
you would have made
a splendid lover. ( Chuckles )
Joseph: Well, if that’s how
you truly feel about me,
then what do you say
you give me a hand?
Mariah: Hmm.
Joseph: I’ve seen the light
and realize that your stand
is way more powerful
than mine could ever hope to be!
I can’t hold it anymore!
Please! I’m begging you!
You have to turn off
the magnetism!
Well, I suppose I could...
( Joseph groaning )
Mariah: But, no,
I don’t think I will.
While you are
exceptionally handsome,
you’re nowhere near
as good-looking as lord dio.
Joseph: So you’re
saying that you refuse
to turn off the power
no matter what?
Mariah: Exactly right.
Now don’t you have
some dying to do?
Joseph: Even though
i’m groveling to you?
Mariah: I won’t say it again,
you idiot.
Joseph: If that’s
how you’re going to be,
then it’s your loss, young lady.
Mariah: What?!
♪
Mariah: Shit! Shit!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Avdol yells )
( Bones cracking )
( Mariah gags )
Joseph: Weren’t you
listening to us earlier?
You’ve been caught
between us the whole time.
Magnets are attracted
to each other, you know.
It’s too late
to do anything about it now,
but getting between us
was your biggest blunder.
Avdol: There’s no way
she can hear you, Mr. Joestar.
She’s already
lost consciousness.
All the metal and magnetic force
has crushed her,
and it’s very likely
that she’s broken more than
a few bones in the process.
( Squish )
( Metal clattering )
Joseph: Hmm.
( Both grunting )
( Crowd gasps )
Avdol: Hmm.
Joseph: Hmm.
All right,
why don’t we get that breakfast
we were talking about?
Avdol: Yes, a wonderful idea.
All this running around
has made me rather hungry.
Joseph: Is it really
only 9 A.M.?
Mariah: Damn,
you pieces of shit--
( sighs )
( Typewriter clacking )
Polnareff: Those two
are taking forever!
As long as they’ve
been in there,
you’d think they were
putting on makeup
and dressing for a gala.
( Iggy growls )
Jotaro: And it’s almost 9 A.M.
( Sighs )
Polnareff: Hmm.
Jotaro: They may have run into
an enemy on the way here.
Polnareff: You think we should
see where they ran off to?
Jotaro: I guess.
Ah, good grief.
Polnareff:
It’s time to go, iggy.
( Iggy groans )
( Barks )
Polnareff: Yeah, yeah,
I know you’re hungry.
You’re not the only one,
believe me.
( Iggy groans )
Man: Hmm.
♪
Josef and avdol
are in the middle
of doing battle with Mariah,
so I, alessi,
shall take on the great honor
of killing jotaro and polnareff.
( Laughing )
♪