Narrator: Ponder this.
What walks on four legs
in the morning,
two during midday,
and three in the evening?
so goes
the riddle of the sphinx,
the legendary guardian
of the pyramids.
The answer--man.
Travelers who answer
the riddle incorrectly
are devoured
by the ravenous sphinx.
Now 30,000 kilometers
from Japan, jotaro and crew
have finally reached
their destination, Cairo.
Avdol: Cairo is massive.
It’s in our best interest to
systematically search the city,
working our way
toward the center.
♪
Joseph: We’re finally here.
( Jotaro grunts )
( All grunt )
Narrator: Jotaro and the others
have reached Cairo.
However, before the team
can reach dio,
they must first
navigate their way
through the many sphinxes
that stand before them.
Bartender: Hmm.
Very nice to meet you gentlemen.
What’ll you have to drink?
Joseph: There’s something
we’d like to ask you.
My associates and I are trying
to locate this building.
Any idea where it is?
Narrator: Joseph and the others
were utterly exhausted.
They had been searching for
the building in the photograph
ever since
their arrival in Cairo.
Taken with joseph’s
psychic photography,
the image revealed
dio’s whereabouts.
Dio had recently moved
to a new hideout,
and the speedwagon foundation
couldn’t find him.
Where was dio hiding?
Failure to locate him
as soon as possible
would spell
certain doom for Holly.
Bartender: I’m sorry, stranger,
but this is a cafe.
You should order a drink
before asking questions.
Joseph: Then iced teas,
four of ’em.
Bartender: Hmm.
( Tea pouring )
( Slam )
Never seen the place.
( All sigh )
Polnareff: Hmm.
Joseph: Cairo is
a city of six million,
so there must be at least
two or three million buildings.
How are we gonna find him?
Avdol: We know he’s here.
there must be
someone who can help us.
( Jotaro grunts )
Man: This is the building, huh?
Man #2: This picture
doesn’t tell me anything.
man #3: Sorry, man,
but it doesn’t look familiar.
Joseph: I see.
Sorry to bother you.
let’s go.
We’ll try somewhere else.
( Jotaro grunts )
Man #4: I happen to know where
your little building is located.
( All gasp )
Man #4: To be honest with you,
i’m quite familiar with it.
( Chuckles )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: W-was that you?
Were you the one who said that?
Do you actually know
where the building is?
- Gambler: Yes.
- Joseph: Huh?
Gambler: The exact location
of the building in question
is information
readily available to me.
Joseph: Are you serious?
That’s incredible!
Avdol: What remarkable news!
Polnareff: Amazing!
What are the odds
that we would
stumble upon someone
who knows exactly
where the building is?
joseph: Well,
don’t keep us in suspense.
Where’s it located?
gambler: Are you really
expecting something for nothing?
joseph: Eh, yes,
you bring up a good point.
My apologies. £10 for your help?
Now, then, where is it?
( Gambler laughs )
Joseph: Hmm?
gambler: Thing is,
i’m something of a gambling man.
I’ve been known to be
a sucker for cheap thrills,
and some would even go
so far as to say i’m an addict.
however,
when all’s said and done,
gambling’s
how I make my living.
Tell me, any of you boys
like to gamble?
Joseph: I’m not sure
I fully understand
what you’re trying to get at.
Gambler: I thought
i’d laid it out plainly.
If you don’t like gambling,
then say so.
Joseph: For the last time,
i have no idea
where you’re going with this.
Gambler: Oh, all right.
What i’m asking is if you
and your friends would like
to play a little game.
win, and i’ll tell you
the location of your building.
It’s as simple as that.
Joseph: A bet? Look, friend,
i’m as lucky as the next guy,
but i’m afraid that we don’t
have time for poker right now.
If I throw in another £20,
will you tell us?
Gambler: No need to worry.
A bet can be anything,
after all.
It won’t take very long.
For example, take a look
at that wall over there.
Do you see that cat?
So two pieces of dried fish.
Question is, which of the two
will the cat eat first,
the right one or the left one?
I must say there’s something
thrilling about its simplicity.
Polnareff: Hey!
I’ve had just about enough
of your games,
so take the money, and tell us
what we wanna know, you bastard!
Joseph: Take it down
a notch, polnareff.
that’s not the way
you ask someone for a favor.
Polnareff: Fine! If it’ll make
you shut up, i’ll take the bet!
the cat’ll choose
the piece of fish on the right!
gambler: Okay.
Now it’s getting interesting.
I’ll be placing
my bet on the left.
Joseph: Polnareff...
Avdol: Say, jotaro,
are you getting
a strange feeling from him?
jotaro: I am.
He might be an enemy stand user,
that, or he could
just be a compulsive gambler.
Avdol: If he does anything
at all that seems suspicious,
you should immediately
attack him with star platinum.
Jotaro: Understood.
Polnareff: Let’s say I lose.
It’s fairly obvious
that i’ll owe you
a hefty amount of money,
so would £100 do?
Gambler: I’ve no use for money,
but what would you say
to giving me your soul?
That should do just fine.
( Chuckles )
Polnareff: Huh?!
Ugh! Now the bastard
thinks he’s a comedian.
I wish we could get
the hell out of here
- and away from this freak.
- Gambler: Well?
Polnareff: Yeah, yeah,
that’s fine with me.
We’ll do things your way.
( Gambler chuckles )
Ah, it appears the cat
has taken notice of the fish.
Polnareff: Like I thought.
Hah! He’s going after
the one on the right.
If I were a cat, i’d pick
the bigger piece of meat,
and lucky for me,
that’s the one on the right!
( Gasps )
( Gambler chuckles )
And there you have it.
Our feline friend took the left,
then the right, then ran.
I win this round, gentlemen.
Joseph: Boy, you’ve outdone
yourself this time, polnareff.
I hope you’re thrilled.
How exactly are we going
to get the information
on the building’s whereabouts
out of him now?
gambler: Well,
if there’s nothing else,
as per our agreement,
it’s time to pay up.
Polnareff: Huh? Pay? With what?
- Gambler: Your soul, of course.
- ( Polnareff gasps )
gambler:
Surely you didn’t forget
about our wager, polnareff.
I want your soul,
as i’m a stand user who
prides himself on stealing them.
I find that it’s far easier
to take a person’s soul
if they lose it in a bet,
which is when my stand’s power
activates and
collects what’s mine.
♪
Joseph: What the hell?!
My god, what’s happening?!
- Jotaro: Polnareff!
- Gambler: Now, now,
I wouldn’t be so quick
to lash out if I were you.
i know you
desperately want to kill me,
but if I die, polnareff
will meet the same end.
Avdol: Polnareff!
Joseph: No. No!
Avdol: H-he has no pulse.
He’s dead! Polnareff is dead!
Joseph: Polnareff!
♪
( Chip clinks )
Gambler: Have a look.
Polnareff’s soul
resides in this.
now lord dio has
one less meddlesome fool
to interfere with his plans,
and what a fool he was.
( Avdol growls )
Gambler: Please allow me
to introduce myself.
My name is d’arby, d-a-r-b-y.
There’s an apostrophe
after the "d."
narrator: Gambler,
stealer of defeated souls,
and user of the osiris stand.
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Avdol growls )
D’arby: I believe
you’ve had the pleasure
of meeting my cat.
Avdol: What is this,
you bastard?!
( Men grunt )
Avdol: You call that a bet?
how dare you,
you vile, cheating son of a--
d’arby: A cheater, you say?
Have you considered
polnareff lost
because he lacked insight
to consider
all the possibilities?
- ( Avdol growls )
- D’arby: Hear me out.
Gambling is nothing more
than a simple analogy
for man’s relationship
with his brethren,
a dance of deception
where the loser cries first.
Are you planning to kill me
with your own two hands, avdol?
Go right ahead,
if you don’t mind your friend’s
soul being lost forever.
the choice is
completely up to you.
avdol: Know this.
We’re not just going to let you
waltz out of here in one piece.
D’arby: Try to think back
to September 22, 1984,
at 11:15 P.M.
Remember what you were doing
during that time and date?
Avdol: What does
that even mean?!
D’arby: I remember it
quite clearly.
i was in California
gambling against an American
that went by the name
of Stephen moor.
He said the same thing
you just said a moment ago...
But now he’s singing
a more silent tune.
The chip below him
is his father,
and the one next to him
is his wife.
if you want
polnareff’s soul back,
you have no choice
but to continue our game.
How much is his life
worth to you?
( Joseph gasps )
Avdol: This man
is evil incarnate.
jotaro: So that’s it.
He wants to capture our souls.
D’arby: So what’s it gonna be?
you can leave
if you’re too scared to play.
I’ll hold polnareff here
for safekeeping. ( Chuckles )
Why don’t you fine gentlemen
have a drink
and think things over a bit?
Care for a piece of chocolate?
( Jotaro and avdol grunt )
( Joseph grunts )
D’arby: Hmm?
Avdol: What is this,
mr. Joestar?
what are you
trying to accomplish?
Joseph: I’m curious.
do you have any idea
what surface tension is, Barbie?
D’arby: My name’s d’arby.
You know it’s not Barbie.
and I assume you’re
referring to how the liquor
appears to almost overflow,
but stays in the glass.
So is there a point
to all this build-up?
We’re playing a game.
The rules are simple.
we take turns
dropping coins into the glass.
whoever makes
the liquor spill loses.
Jotaro: Old man...
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
you’re not going to...
Joseph: Exactly right!
I’m going to bet my soul!
D’arby: Okay.
Avdol: You’ve got to be kidding!
You can’t go through with it,
Mr. Joestar!
this man is
a good-for-nothing cheater!
Joseph: He won’t
cheat me this time
I decided on the rules myself,
so i’ll be fine.
Jotaro, you watch
for funny business.
D’arby: Okay.
Since you’re so determined,
i’ll accept your conditions.
However, before we begin,
would you mind if I inspect
the glass and coins?
Joseph: Sure. Have at it.
You have the right to ensure
that i’m playing
on the up and up.
D’arby: Hmm. Hmm.
Joseph: A question--
what guarantee do I have
that you’ll return
polnareff’s soul
if you lose the game?
D’arby: You’ve my word
as a gambler
that i’ll keep my promise.
If I lose, I assure you
that I will pay in full,
but I won’t lose.
Joseph: Well, in that case,
you can go first.
Go ahead, and drop a coin in.
Avdol: Please, stop!
Joseph: Just leave
everything to me.
The old coin-and-glass trick
is one of my specialties.
surface tension is
a surprisingly strong force.
There’s room for at least eight
or nine coins in the glass.
I just have to stay calm
and make sure my fingers
don’t shake.
D’arby: Is it all right
if I drop in more than one coin
at the same time?
Joseph: As long as they
all go in at once.
D’arby: Well, then...
Avdol: What? Five coins?!
Joseph: Hey, that’ll create
a wave on the surface.
D’arby: Quiet, please.
Take your hands off the table.
( All gasp )
♪
( All groan )
( D’arby gasps )
( Sighs )
( Chuckles )
It looks like it’s your turn.
Joseph: It takes nerves of steel
to put in five coins at once.
I think i’ll go with one coin.
It’s too close to call.
♪
Jotaro: Hmm?
Jotaro: Typical old man.
He’s squeezing a cotton ball
between his finger
and the coin
to leak liquid into the glass.
So that’s how he’s gonna
make the glass overflow.
and he told me
to watch for cheating?
Clever bastard. Not bad.
♪
( D’arby growls )
( Joseph laughs )
The glass has reached its limit.
one more coin,
and the booze will spill.
Victory is mine. Ha ha!
It’s like he said.
we’ll see
which dance partner cries first.
Ooh, man, that was a close one.
I thought it was
gonna spill for sure.
Well, it’s your turn.
Good luck, obi.
D’arby: It’s d’arby.
Don’t make me say it again.
I told you my name
is d’arby. Understand?
Not obi, not Barbie!
Joseph: Hmm? Apologies.
( Jotaro chuckles )
He’s screwing up his name
on purpose
to get him riled up
and throw off his game.
I gotta hand it to the old man.
He’s a natural.
Joseph: So what do
you say we keep playing?
I believe it’s your turn
to drop a coin in, d’arby.
( Teeth grinding )
( D’arby growls )
The shadow makes it difficult
to see from here.
I’ll lower the coin in from
the right side of the table.
joseph: Drop it in
from whatever angle you’d like.
What he doesn’t know
is the glass
is already at its limit
thanks to my little trick.
There’s no way the liquid
could take another coin.
Even the slightest touch
will cause it to spill over.
( Chuckles )
♪
- ( Avdol groans )
- ( Jotaro sighs )
D’arby: You’re probably thinking
the glass has reached its limit,
that dropping in another coin
would be impossible.
( Joseph gasps )
d’arby: Well,
you’d be wrong about that.
( Joseph groans )
( D’arby chuckles )
Joseph: There’s no way!
How the hell did he do that?!
Why didn’t it spill over?!
d’arby:
Your question’s confusing.
What do you mean,
why didn’t it spill?
You saw the result
with your own eyes.
Jotaro: As far as I know,
he didn’t do anything devious.
I was watching him
with star platinum.
It’s hard to believe, but he
dropped it in fair and square.
There’s no doubt.
Joseph: But how did he do it?
I’m positive I added
enough liquid to the glass
that one more coin
would make it spill.
I don’t get it. There’s no way
it shouldn’t have spilled.
What’s going on?
D’arby: Make your move.
It’s your turn, joestar.
Hurry it up already,
or are you trying to wait
until it evaporates?
( Joseph gasping )
No, no, this can’t be happening.
♪
( Avdol gasps )
Mr. Joestar!
d’arby:
Deep in his heart of hearts,
joestar had already
come to the realization
that he’d lost this game.
That’s why his soul
emerged so easily.
I, d’arby, have won this bet
like all the others.
Joseph: Polnareff,
i--i failed you.
Holly, i’m so sorry,
my beautiful girl,
but daddy’s let you down.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar!
Jotaro: Old man, no!
D’arby: Two down.
Now let’s continue
where we left off,
that is unless you two have
decided to abandon your friends
and slink away with your tails
between your legs.
Avdol: You bastard!
( D’arby groans )
You don’t get it, do you?
I keep trying to tell you
that if you take my life,
your friends will die with me.
- avdol: Damn you!
- Jotaro: Avdol, stand down!
bartender: Hey,
if you’re gonna cause trouble,
then i’m gonna have
to ask you to Lea--
jotaro: Shut your mouth,
and stay out of this!
Bartender: Right!
( Jotaro gasps )
( D’arby chuckles )
You’ve noticed it too late,
jotaro.
Avdol: Eh, what? Something’s
wrong with the glass?
Jotaro: This is the reason
the coin didn’t make
the booze spill over.
If you look at the bottom
of the glass,
you’ll see that there’s
a tiny bit of chocolate on it.
He must have found a way
to stick it on
when he was inspecting
the glass and coins
at the very beginning
of the game.
D’arby: Surely you know
the rules by now.
It doesn’t count as cheating if
you never get caught in the act.
Avdol: What? I don’t understand.
How could a piece of chocolate
allow him to drop in
an extra coin?
Jotaro: Well, at this point,
it’s melted,
but it used to be a solid chunk
stuck to the bottom
of the glass,
just enough
to slightly tilt the glass,
but not quite enough
for us to notice the change.
Once the chocolate
started to melt,
the glass came to be level
with the table.
With the glass leveled out,
the booze began to settle,
which made enough room
for another coin.
Avdol: W-what the hell?!
b-but that
doesn’t make any sense!
How could he have known
the chocolate would melt
right when he needed it to?
Jotaro: He influenced things
by using the sun.
It slipped my notice.
when he moved
to the right side of the table,
he allowed the sun to shine
directly onto the chocolate,
thereby melting it.
( D’arby chuckles )
( Avdol growls )
Jotaro: All right.
D’arby, get your cards,
’cause we’re playin’ my game.
Hope you’re ready
for some poker.
- D’arby: Eh?
- Avdol: Say what?!
Jotaro!
D’arby: Interesting.
you couldn’t
have possibly known this,
but poker is
my absolute favorite game.
Avdol: Are you
out of your mind?!
You’re playing poker with a man
who outsmarted Mr. Joestar.
It’s too dangerous!
Jotaro: Yeah, I know.
Even though he doesn’t use
physical strength,
he’s the most dangerous
stand user we’ve ever faced.
So now...
♪
There’s no turning back,
and we’re playing for keeps.
♪