- Polnareff: What is that?
- ( Iggy growls )
polnareff:
Weren’t avdol’s flames
supposed to be
able to sense anything?
Avdol, where are you?!
( Stand growls ) Avdol...
Has been reduced
to nothingness.
You were arrogant enough
to believe
you could defeat lord dio.
Allow me to demonstrate
just how wrong you were.
( Polnareff gasps )
Cool ice: You’ll fall
in line one by one
as I scatter
your atomic fragments
across the recesses of the void.
( Both gasp )
( Stand growls )
( Polnareff gasps )
It can’t be.
I don’t believe you.
Avdol’s not dead.
Don’t you lie to me!
Stand: W-what?!
I never would have imagined
polnareff’s stand
could attack this swiftly
from so far away.
An amazing feat, to be sure.
Silver chariot: Over here.
I want you to look at me
when I kill you.
( Polnareff yells )
♪
( Iggy yelps )
( Polnareff screams )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Rubble falling )
- men: Hmm?
- Joseph: All right,
now i’m sure
something fishy’s going on.
ever since
we escaped the mirage,
i’ve heard
the sounds of a battle.
Kakyoin: Blast it. Avdol
and polnareff are out there.
- Joseph: Hmm?
- Jotaro: Mm.
( Polnareff panting )
damn that guy.
I know I hit the bastard,
but it wasn’t
enough to kill him.
He just swallowed himself again
so he could hide in that abyss.
Damn that guy and his stand.
( Iggy whimpering )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Woman vocalizing )
Polnareff: Avdol,
how could you do that?
How could you break
the one rule you gave us?
avdol: Polnareff, iggy,
you have to get out of here now!
polnareff: You told us
we had to watch our own backs,
that you wouldn’t save us,
even if we were in danger.
You liar.
You’ve been meddling
in other people’s business
ever since the moment
we set foot in India.
Damn it, avdol!
Why couldn’t you
just leave me alone
and mind your own
freaking business?!
( Both gasp )
Polnareff: If I hadn’t ducked,
i’d be a dead man right now.
it’s like fate
is telling me to carry on.
This must be avdol’s way
of knocking some sense into me.
( Iggy growls )
♪
( The fool growls )
Polnareff: It’s way
too dangerous in here.
Let’s get moving!
( Iggy barks )
♪
Polnareff: Come on, iggy.
We have to make it upstairs!
Don’t fall behind!
( Gasps ) Look up ahead!
It’s the exit!
We’re almost there!
But I won’t just turn tail
and run away.
( Iggy gasps )
polnareff:
Avdol sacrificed himself for us,
and i’ll repay that debt,
no matter what!
He believed we had the power
to put an end to dio
once and for all.
I can’t betray his faith in us
by letting him down.
That is not an option.
I refuse to take the easy way
out like some common coward.
I’m gonna see this fight through
to the bitter end!
The only place i’m running to
is dio’s shadow den!
♪
( Iggy growls )
( Barks )
polnareff:
So up the stairs we go!
♪
Stand: I expected him
to dash out the door.
( Chuckles )
Pity.
Cool ice: Impressive.
He managed a hit.
it seems
polnareff’s mental fortitude
gives him the ability
to conquer his fears
in the face of imminent death.
You will soon be joining avdol.
Rest assured.
Your strength
pales in comparison
to the harbinger of death
that is my stand.
polnareff:
If what he says is true,
his stand’s jaws are the gateway
to an alternate dimension,
a dark, unimaginable abyss,
one that allows him
to move through our realm
without leaving
any trace of himself.
But how does he do it?
and how the heck
am I supposed to beat him?
- ( Iggy yelps )
- ( Polnareff gasps )
♪
No, no, no! He’s cut us off!
He’s nearby.
But where exactly?
Iggy, I need you
to watch my back,
and don’t worry.
I’ll do the same for you.
Okay, if he wants to reach us,
then he’s gonna have
to come out of that other realm.
This is good.
He has to come out
from the dark beyond
at some point.
When he does,
i’ll take my chance
and attack him
with everything i’ve got.
All right, come at me,
you demented pinball!
I’ll slice you in two!
Now i’m pissed off,
so my chariot’s even faster!
I may have lost avdol,
but it’ll be a cold day in hell
before I let you get away.
( Gasps ) Huh?
Eh?
What the hell?!
He--he was hiding under my foot?
Chario--
( groans )
( Wailing )
Aah! My foot!
Stand: Now you can’t run away.
- ( Polnareff groaning )
- Stand: I got your foot
so that you can’t hide anymore.
( The fool growls )
Polnareff: Eat silver.
Stand: I’ll pass.
( Silver chariot yelling )
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar,
a brawl’s under way.
Joseph: Avdol and polnareff.
sounds like
they came in after us
and wound up getting themselves
into a fight.
come on, you two!
We have to find them asap!
♪
Cool ice: You’ve managed to hide
amid the chaos, polnareff.
How futile. You couldn’t have
gone far with that injury,
which means you’re hiding
beneath the rubble.
- ( Stand growls )
- Cool ice: By now,
you must have realized
you’re helpless against me.
You shall meet your end
by my hand.
now then,
where could you be, polnareff?
Dio: That’s quite the ruckus,
cool ice.
( Cool ice gasps )
( Gasps ) L-lord dio.
♪
Please be careful, my lord.
i believe polnareff
and that four-legged rodent
are still hiding nearby.
Allow me to handle
the situation.
You mustn’t trouble yourself
with such nonsense, master.
( Iggy whines )
polnareff: A fake dio
made from the fool. We got him.
You’d think i’d feel guilty
about attacking from behind
like a coward,
and you’d be wrong,
because you pulled
the same shit on avdol.
This is the death you deserve.
Now, iggy! Crucify him.
♪
Crucify him!
Make him pay for what he did.
End his life in the same
merciless way he did avdol’s.
Send him straight to hell!
( Both gasp )
Polnareff: You’re kidding?!
He knows. But how?!
Cool ice: Because
the windows to my left
are letting in
the light from the sun.
Lord dio would never enter
this room during the day.
You’ll suffer a thousand deaths
for your deception.
Polnareff: Iggy.
( Iggy whimpers )
( Yelps )
cool ice:
I made a vow to lord dio
that I would kill
you interlopers.
He entrusted me
with that honor.
Lord dio’s a man of his word.
He would never descend to
the second floor for any reason.
Polnareff: No.
He’s gonna kill iggy.
He’s about to be
swallowed by the abyss!
Cool ice: Now die,
you filthy, pathetic dog.
Your incorrigible ruse forced me
to destroy lord dio’s likeness!
( Iggy yelps )
♪
( Polnareff gasps )
D-did he really just hit him?
He didn’t use the void.
Instead of killing iggy,
he went in for a punch!
cool ice:
Do you know what you’ve done?
I don’t care if it was a fake.
You forced me to destroy
a figure
in the form of lord dio,
and you must answer
for that crime.
Your life is mine now!
I will kick you to death!
( Growls )
( Iggy gags )
Cool ice: My dark abyss could
swallow you whole in an instant,
but a quick death
wouldn’t satiate my fury.
- ( Iggy gags )
- Cool ice: This whole mess,
it’s all your fault!
This is what happens
to those who anger me.
Have you learned
your lesson yet?!
How ’bout it? Is this better?
Tell me! Is it? Is it?! Is it?!
( Polnareff gasps )
Stop it! Leave him alone!
It’s like cool ice’s brain
has melted.
Is he really going bat-shit
because he destroyed
some pile of sand
that looked like dio?
from over here,
his soul is the murky abyss.
It’s a bottomless black hole
that obliterates any and every
thing that gets in its way.
Cool ice: I was warned
about the humans.
lord dio said
the resolve in their hearts
must never be underestimated.
But you, you’re just
a flea-bitten stray.
You’ve never known resolve,
and you certainly
know nothing of pride.
( Iggy chuckles )
( Cool ice gasps )
Yeah? Grin at this!
Polnareff: Leave him alone.
cool ice:
You like that? Do you?!
Polnareff: What did I say?
cool ice: Come on!
Your suffering’s just begun.
Polnareff: Cool ice!
You’re dealing with me now!
( Squelch )
( Cool ice sighs )
I’m ending this, polnareff.
( Silver chariot yelling )
Polnareff: Damn it.
He’s gone!
But more importantly, iggy,
our plan to trick cool ice
may have fallen through,
but your sand
might have just saved us.
Thanks to you, I think I found
a way to find the bastard.
♪
Yeah, that’s him, all right.
I can see him moving around.
Guess your stand power
is a double-edged sword.
when you move,
your stand has no choice
but to absorb
everything in your path.
So choke on a mouthful of this,
and get over here,
you piece of shit.
As soon as you come out
from behind your stand’s
putrid teeth to attack me,
i’ll turn the tables
and finish you off.
( Cool ice gags )
Polnareff: Bull’s-eye!
Yeah, eat that.
Well, would you look at that?
I found your weakness,
cool ice.
Any attempt to pinpoint my
location leaves you vulnerable,
which is probably
a tad inconvenient,
since you can’t see me
without emerging
from your dark dimension.
( Cool ice gagging )
Polnareff: It’s over.
Now suck on my sword
and burn in hell, fils de pute!
Hurry up, and die.
( Cool ice growls )
( Polnareff gagging )
( Cool ice growling )
Polnareff: W-what?
How are you still alive?
I skewered your throat
and brainstem.
Would you die, already?!
No way you’re getting out of it.
Hurry up, and die!
( Cool ice gasping )
Polnareff: Stop making me
repeat myself. Die!
( Gagging )
Cool ice: I cannot die.
My mission is far too important
to feel any pain.
I will not rest
until I kill you.
I’ll swallow iggy, the joestars,
and anyone else
who gets in my way.
Only after your deaths
will I allow myself to die.
( Polnareff shrieking )
( Screams )
Silver chariot: Bastard!
Cool ice: There’s a good boy.
You knew to withdraw your sword.
Silver chariot: I also know
that you’re about to die.
( Polnareff gasps )
Cool ice: This is the one,
the vile arm
you used to stab me.
( Polnareff screams )
( Grunting )
Knock it off!
Silver chariot: Damn it!
I had no choice
but to shove him away.
- no!
- ( Cream laughing )
silver chariot:
Y-you’re not going anywhere!
did I get him?
Ah, where’d he go now?
- ( Groans )
- ( Polnareff groans )
Shit. He got my leg.
I can’t move.
but I can’t think
about the pain right now.
I was so close.
I almost managed
to land a killing blow,
but he got away.
This guy is different,
fueled by pure vengeance.
And he’s not just nuts.
His devotion to dio
is all-consuming.
But I won’t let him
get the upper hand.
You said you couldn’t die yet?
Well, I can’t die
until I kill you!
Okay, here he comes.
Take this!
Shit, it’s no use.
His stand just obliterated
the tip of my sword,
though it probably wouldn’t
matter, even if it were intact.
It’s impossible to attack him
when he’s hidden in the abyss.
if I so much
as touch that thing,
it’ll swallow me whole.
( Silver chariot gasps )
Great, now he’s absorbing
the building at random. Merde!
Polnareff: That’s clever.
He knows full well
i’ll go after him
if he shows himself,
so he’s blindly attacking to
prevent me from fighting back.
He’s not messing around.
at this rate,
he’s gonna hit me for sure.
I should pull back chariot
and think of a plan.
Damn. This isn’t good.
Iggy’s not gonna last long
if he keeps losing blood.
From the state he’s in,
i’d say his broken ribs
must have punctured his lungs.
( Gasps )
And just when I thought
this couldn’t get any worse.
why the hell
is he devouring the walls?
Wait a second. I’m starting
to think I was all wrong.
This isn’t random.
It was all part of his plan
from the beginning.
He’s been drawing circles
around me,
and with every lap,
he’s getting closer and closer.
The odds are stacked against me,
but I have to do something.
He’s closing in.
He still doesn’t know
our location,
but with that rolling ball
of death hurtling toward us,
it doesn’t matter.
he’s got us
right where he wants us.
There’s no way i’m gonna be able
to dodge an attack from him
with this bum leg.
i-i’ve got to try
to escape through the floor.
I don’t have enough time
to tunnel through!
He’s coming straight for us!
Somehow, I dodged it.
Not out of the woods.
He’s closing in on me
like a needle
on an old record player.
i only have
about five more rounds
before he makes
his way back here
and finishes me off for good.
So, the million-dollar question
is how do I dodge
with this injured leg?
♪
If I had it my way,
i’d just pick option two,
but I can’t count on that.
They only entered the mansion
10 minutes before us.
As much as i’d love for them
to swoop in out of thin air
and save the day like
some American comic book hero,
wishful thinking’s
not gonna save me now.
There’s no point hoping
for an out-of-the-blue rescue.
For all I know,
the others might be
in the middle of a fight
themselves.
All right then.
Option one’s our only choice.
Okay, chariot,
I need you to pull me
out of the circle
as fast as you can.
( Grunting )
What are you doing?
Pull me faster, chariot!
I-it’s no use.
♪
Narrator: What do you know?
The answer ended up
being option three.
Life’s a bitch.
Polnareff: Silver chariot
is a finesse-oriented stand
that fights with a saber.
It simply doesn’t have the power
to pull my body weight,
especially when i’m injured.
I’m done for.
♪
You’re holding on by a thread.
Stay down, you stupid mutt.
if you keep moving or
try using your stand’s power,
your broken ribs will sink
deeper into your lungs
and kill you.
hey, you can drop
the tough guy act, you idiot.
The only thing
this will accomplish
is you dying
right along with me.
Just you wait. I’m the one
who’s gonna save you.
You have to live on
to tell Mr. Joestar
and the others
about this bastard.
You have to defeat him
in my stead.
Avdol might have saved me,
but you sure as hell better not!
if we all die here,
then what was the point of this?
- ( Iggy gasps )
- ( Polnareff grunting )
( Chorus vocalizing )
One more loop,
and its lights out.
So it’s number three.
Life can be a bitch sometimes.
We both wanted to win.
Guess he wanted it more.
( Iggy gasps )
Polnareff: Au revoir, iggy.
( Iggy squeals )
( Yelps )
( Clang echoes )
♪