Rrator: Previously on
"jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
♪♪
( Iggy yelps )
( Yells ) Blast it!
oh, no!
The exit’s blocked with ice,
and more’s coming this way!
Shit!
It’s starting to cover
the whole tunnel.
I gotta find a way out
of this deathtrap!
( Horus squawks )
( Iggy groans )
( Gasps ) What?!
( Grunts )
My paw!
( Pet shop trills )
Iggy: I can’t pry my paw loose!
( Pet shop warbles )
( Iggy screams )
♪
( Warbles )
( Singing in Japanese )
♪
Joseph: Hmm.
all right,
the sun is about to set.
Polnareff: Didn’t "shades"
say three hours?
Guess that cocky beggar
had a bit more trouble
finding dio’s mansion
than he thought.
Can’t say I was expecting
this to happen, though.
Right, avdol?
Avdol: I have a bad feeling.
Maybe it’s better if he doesn’t
find that accursed mansion.
- Joseph: Hmm?
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- Polnareff: Hmm?
- Avdol: You see,
maybe he hasn’t come back,
- because he did find it.
- ( Both grunt )
Polnareff: What are you saying?
Avdol: It didn’t occur to me
until a moment ago,
but a stand user is likely
to be guarding dio’s lair.
We may have put that beggar’s
life in grave danger,
if he hasn’t
already been killed.
Polnareff: What?
Are you serious?
♪
( Water flowing )
( Heavy breathing )
Iggy: Son of a--i barely
made it out of there,
and my--my leg is--
that ice caught my paw
like a bear trap.
i’d be dead
if I hadn’t gnawed it off.
I-I think i’m gonna
hide out here for a while.
If i’m down here long enough,
maybe birdbrain’ll go away.
After this is over,
the speedwagon foundation
can make me an artificial leg.
But i’m still pissed as hell.
Damn that bird.
you’re not
getting away with this!
I’m gonna make you suffer
for what you did to me.
Just you wait.
Wait. That sound.
Something out there
dove into the water.
♪
No way.
narrator:
Birds have the capacity
to dive under water.
Like humans and canines,
birds are reliant upon lungs
for respiration,
but the average bird
has five to six air sacs
stored away in its chest
and stomach regions.
It’s these pockets of air
that give birds
the ability to remain conscious
at altitudes
of 6,000 to 7,000 meters,
a feat completely impossible
for humans.
Even if it were to be strangled,
a bird can survive
for several minutes
thanks to its
internal air reserves.
With these advantages,
a bird can survive underwater
much longer than a dog.
( Iggy panting )
It sounds like something’s
headed straight for me.
But how? That’s impossible!
I don’t understand!
What could be coming
after me down here?
Wait a sec.
Could it be?
( Yells )
( Gasping )
( Pet shop warbles )
( Iggy gasps )
It’s that bird again.
But how can it survive
underwater like this?
( Panting )
that bastard.
Where’d it fly off to now?
( Growls )
( Gasps )
It’s closing in,
but what’s its plan?
More icicles? One, two, three.
Great. Three icicles
are coming this way.
( Yells )
( Pet shop squawks )
( Iggy growls )
Suck on that, you frickin’ coot!
( Pet shop squeals )
Iggy: Yes. I did it.
How do you like that?
( Panting )
( Breathing heavily )
The icicles are stopping
the wall from leaking,
but at the rate
they’re spreading,
they’re gonna cover everything!
No. What am I gonna do now?!
( Gasping )
I know what it’s doing.
It’s focusing on freezing
the water around me.
And it’s cut my air pipes.
i-i don’t think
it’s trying to suffocate me.
Its real plan
is to Bury me alive.
( Grunting )
It’s no use. It’s collapsing!
This bird is too powerful
for me to hold it off!
And what’s worse, i’m surrounded
by ice and freezing water!
Just my damn luck.
So much for finding
a decent hiding place
to lay low in for a while.
( Gasps )
No other choice.
I have to dig my way out.
Give me a break.
This stupid day has gone
from bad to horrifying
in the worst possible way!
First, I lose my leg,
and now some demon bird
wants me flattened
into a frozen dinner!
damn.
I can’t hold it off anymore.
I’m about to be crushed.
I need to dig myself
out of here now!
( Panting )
Huh?
What is that?
It looks like someone
dug a tunnel down here,
but why?
( Screams )
It’s the bird!
it’s getting ready
to shoot another ice missile.
♪
damn it. My stand
is being held by the ice.
I can’t defend myself,
and there’s nowhere
for me to escape!
( Gasps )
Wait. That’s it.
Either way you slice it,
it’s do-or-die time!
♪
I’ll let the dome break
and use the air pressure
to catapult me forward
like a speeding bullet!
( Yells )
( Pet shop squawks )
( Iggy gasps )
I got out of there alive.
That dumb bird
didn’t have to die,
but it left me no choice.
One of us had to go.
( Shuddering )
But it looks like this’ll
probably be the end for me.
I’ve been bleeding out
for a while now.
i hardly have
enough strength in my body
to keep myself afloat,
let alone make it back to shore,
which means i’m gonna drown.
Why is this happening?
I was supposed to live
a trouble-free life.
♪
Damn it. I messed up.
( Boy gasps )
Thank goodness I found you.
As soon as I saw
that little face
and those great big ears,
I knew it was you.
It’s that stupid bird’s fault
that you’re like this.
It attacked you
just like my dogs.
( Iggy gasps )
( Boy panting )
You’re gonna pull through this.
The bird’s gone, so there’s
nothing to worry about.
Try and hang on, all right?
Keep fighting.
I’ll patch you up right away.
Narrator: The bird: Pet shop!
Stand: Horus.
Status: Deceased.
( Birds chirping )
( Polnareff groans )
Damn that mangy mutt.
Where the hell
did he run off to?
he’s gotta stop
pulling stunts like this.
Joseph: I’m starting
to get worried.
He’s been gone for a while.
Polnareff: That lousy flea bag.
( Jotaro gasps ) Huh?
Joseph: Jotaro,
what’s the matter?
Avdol: There must be
someone following us again.
Jotaro: Not quite,
but I thought I heard a voice,
like someone’s
calling out to us.
- Polnareff: Hmm.
- Joseph: A voice?
Avdol: Hmm?
( Iggy whimpering )
Avdol: It’s iggy!
Joseph: Hmm?
Polnareff: Iggy!
Avdol: What on earth happened?!
Joseph: Look at that.
He’s got injuries
all over his body.
Polnareff: Hey, iggy’s missing
his front leg, too!
joseph: You think
he got run over by a car?
Avdol: He’s not the kind of dog
that gets into car accidents.
You were attacked by the enemy,
weren’t you?
Joseph: What’s this?
it looks as though
someone treated his wounds.
i have to say
they did a great job.
( Polnareff sighs )
Jotaro: But it wasn’t iggy
that I heard.
Whoever was calling out to us
was definitely human.
- Joseph: Huh?
- Polnareff: Huh?
Kakyoin: Iggy did have
a run-in with the enemy.
When we found him, he was
half-dead in the arms of a boy,
so the speedwagon foundation
doctors saw to his wounds.
They did the same...
For my eyes.
Polnareff: It’s you!
You’re finally back!
♪
( Kakyoin chuckles )
All: It’s kakyoin!
polnareff:
Good to see you, kakyoin!
- how’s it going?
- Avdol: Kakyoin, tell me,
how are your eyes treating you?
Kakyoin: I’m glad
you’re all safe.
Joseph: We missed you, pal.
( Laughs )
So they were able to treat you?
kakyoin: Yes.
I’m ready for action.
While it’s true
i’ll have a few scars,
my eyesight is back to normal.
Joseph: We’re all really glad
to hear that.
Kakyoin: Jotaro.
( Jotaro grunts )
( Iggy panting )
( Growls )
Joseph: Hmm?
Where do you think
you’re going, iggy?
Kakyoin: He may have
been quite indifferent
toward humans and stands
in the past,
but now it looks like he’s
trying to lead us somewhere.
I’m not aware of all the details
surrounding his encounter
with the enemy stand,
but judging from his resolve,
this is about revenge.
Joseph: Maybe, but that
still doesn’t explain
where he’s taking us.
Polnareff: Hang on, iggy!
wait for us!
Avdol: Hmm?
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
Joseph: I recognize that car.
It’s the same fancy ride
the beggar was driving.
C-could this wreckage
mean that he...
( Polnareff and kakyoin gasp )
Polnareff: But how?
What’s strong enough
to tear a hole through a car
like a piece of wet newspaper?
Avdol: It would seem as though
i was right
to be concerned about him.
He should have
never been involved.
Joseph: Is it possible
this is the handiwork
of the stand user
iggy fought earlier?
Avdol: All signs seem to point
to that being the case.
Joseph: Huh? Iggy!
Avdol: Hmm?
( Iggy growling )
( Gasping )
♪
polnareff:
What the hell’s going on?
all of a sudden,
i’m drenched in a cold sweat,
and there’s
this oppressive feeling of doom
roaming in the air.
( Jotaro grunts )
polnareff:
I don’t know about you guys,
but I am majorly creeped out.
where exactly
is iggy trying to take us?
Joseph: I know where he’s going.
this feeling,
it’s all too familiar to me.
this aura
is pure, unmitigated evil.
( Men grunt )
Avdol: It’s the mansion
from the picture.
Jotaro: We’ve arrived.
Polnareff: Iggy, you were
able to find it by yourself?
♪
( Men grunt )
( Iggy grunts )
narrator: What lay
before jotaro and the others
was something more sinister
than anything
they’d previously faced.
They would soon look upon
the source of their predicament
and the very embodiment of evil.
The path that had led them here
was long and arduous.
Foreign lands
shrouded in mystery
and treacherous
stand-using assassins
met them at every step.
each battle was
a struggle for survival
where the wrong move
would spell out certain death.
There were tears, laughter,
sadness, rage, and joy.
- The journey affected them all.
- ( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Now nearly
50 days have passed
since the team departed Japan
on their quest
to save the life
of jotaro’s mother Holly.
Everything led to this.
The time had come to defeat dio
and end the hundred-year curse
afflicting the joestar family.
Joseph was determined
to save his daughter Holly,
and nothing and no one
was going to stand in his way.
Kakyoin vowed
to remain resolute.
He would defeat dio
not only to save Holly,
but to overcome
his own weaknesses.
Avdol was steadfast
in his conviction,
considering it his personal duty
to root out evil
wherever it lurked.
Polnareff was determined
to make the tyrant dio suffer
for turning him into a puppet
and forcing him
to betray his own principles.
Iggy’s spirit was untamable.
He knew his life of turmoil
could be traced back
to a single man
and was intent on making sure
the bastard faced his wrath.
And so...
Jotaro: In other words,
if we beat the shit
out of dio in there,
this damn nightmare
will be over once and for all.
- ( Iggy growls )
- Joseph: That’s right,
and the scent of evil
confirms that he’s here.
He’s hiding inside the mansion
like the coward he is.
Avdol: It’s hard
to believe, but...
polnareff:
We’ve finally reached the end
of this hellacious journey.
Joseph: All right,
men, you ready?
( Men grunt )
♪
iggy: The gate’s open
as if they’re inviting us in.
This is totally different
from the situation yesterday.
( Joseph grunts )
( Men grunt )
♪
Joseph: Now that I think
about it, if I can sense dio,
then it stands to reason
that he has the ability
to sense us, too.
If we try to enter
the mansion guns blazing,
no doubt we’ll be playing
right into the enemy’s hands.
before we do anything,
we need to think of a strategy.
- ( Men gasp )
- Joseph: Careful!
The door is opening!
Everyone on guard!
( Creaking )
Joseph: Hmm? ( Grunts )
polnareff: Check it out.
What’s with this weird corridor?
It must go on forever.
This can’t be real, right?
It has to be some sort
of trick or illusion.
joseph: Listen.
Polnareff, no matter what,
don’t go through the door.
Dio’s probably got
a couple more stand users
waiting in the wings
to fight us.
- ( Both gasp )
- Polnareff: Hey!
Something’s coming this way!
♪
Wait. Is that guy floating?
Is he a stand user or what?
Man: Master joestar...
Welcome to our abode.
We’ve been expecting you, sir.
I am the resident Butler
of the mansion.
♪