( Joseph gasping )
Dio: Just as I thought,
joseph’s blood suits me well.
( Jotaro growls )
Dio: It’s like it was
meant to be mine
from the very beginning.
It’s far more intense than
anything i’ve ever felt before!
This sensation is
absolutely incredible!
( Laughing )
A century ago, this body
belonged to Jonathan joestar,
and now these hands have feasted
on the blood
of his grandson, Joseph!
but it was you, jotaro,
who so thoughtfully led me here.
your ancestor
must be rolling in his grave.
You joestars have
always been a nuisance,
so I think the time has come to
put you self-righteous cretins
in your proper place,
beneath my boot!
In the end, jotaro,
it would appear
that the joestars’s destiny
is to facilitate
my ascension to perfection!
( Laughing )
Jotaro: Why, you...
( Dio laughing )
( Jotaro gasps )
♪
Old man.
Joseph: You have to stay calm.
From here on, no matter what
dio does to me, keep your cool.
Focus. Tempting as it may be,
never allow yourself
to succumb to anger.
Don’t worry about my fate,
jotaro.
i’ve accepted
that it was meant to be.
Jotaro: Wait a sec.
That’s his soul? But how?
Joseph: Kakyoin deciphered
the mystery of dio’s stand,
and I imparted
that knowledge to you.
Had we attacked dio together
before learning his secret,
he would have been able
to easily kill all of us.
You now have the ability
to move while time is frozen,
but you only have
two or three seconds.
Make sure you use
that time wisely.
Remember what I told you,
jotaro.
You mustn’t lose your head.
If you lose control,
it’ll only backfire.
Keep your emotions in check
when you face off with dio.
Jotaro...
( Jotaro gasps )
joseph: It’s been
quite the journey, eh, my boy,
an unforgettable adventure.
Call me crazy.
( Chuckles )
But our time together
was a lot of fun,
more fun than i’ve had
in a long time.
Jotaro: That was real, right?
Dio: Hey!
What are you looking at,
jotaro?!
( Blood flowing )
♪
Jotaro: You bastard!
Dio: He’s been sucked dry.
( Laughing )
Jotaro: I know you said
to keep my emotions in check,
but screw that!
He just crossed the line!
There’s not a person
on the planet
who could stay calm
after seeing that!
Dio: This fight
has come to an end!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Ticking slows, stops )
( Music stops )
( Footsteps echoing )
( Singing in Japanese resumes )
( Star platinum yelling )
( The world yelling )
♪
the world!
Bring time to a halt!
( Yells )
One second, two seconds,
and three seconds.
Now four...
- ( Gasps )
- ( Stands yelling )
( Dio yells )
( Star platinum yelling )
Dio: Five seconds. Interesting.
Six seconds. My, my.
( Jotaro gasps )
Dio: This makes seven seconds.
My power grows exponentially!
I can stop time for even longer.
But as for you, jotaro,
you wasted the opportunity
you had to move.
gambling on getting me
two seconds before time resumed
was all for naught.
What a miscalculation.
( Chuckles )
I feel so marvelous,
I could serenade the world!
The moment i’ve dreamed of
for so long is finally upon us.
Eight seconds have passed.
I’ve been an immortal being
for an entire century...
- ( Squelching )
- But never in my wildest dreams
could I have imagined i’d feel
something this exhilarating!
( Laughs )
The blood of the joestars
courses through my veins!
- courses through my veins!
- Jotaro: Damn it.
Guess you were right,
after all, old man.
My stupid temper got me
in a shit-ton of trouble.
For christ’s sake.
No, this isn’t the end!
He still hasn’t faced
the full force of my rage!
Dio: Nine seconds total,
that’s how long
my power lasted just now.
Yes, perhaps nine seconds
is the new extent of my stand’s
extraordinary power.
Jotaro: You bastard.
( Dio yelling )
( Jotaro yells )
Dio: Now to unleash
all of my stand’s power!
Jotaro, weren’t you mumbling
something about being angry?!
is this
all the power you possess?!
( The world yelling )
Muda!
Dio: And now I shall administer
the killing blow!
here it is,
my final dance with time!
Nine more seconds,
that’s all you have left!
Prepare to die! The world!
( Ticking slows, stops )
( Chuckles )
One second.
( Jotaro gasps )
Dio: Two seconds.
Three seconds.
narrator:
Jotaro couldn’t figure out
why dio had suddenly vanished
amidst the standstill...
Dio: Four seconds.
Narrator: But he pushed
the thoughts out of his mind.
No matter what sinister plot
dio was hatching,
no matter what unholy attack
he attempted to unleash,
jotaro had
only two seconds to respond,
only two seconds to drive
star platinum’s fists into dio
once and for all!
Dio: Five seconds.
Jotaro: I’ve had just about
enough of this neon vampire.
The next time I see
that goddamn face of his,
i’m gonna freakin’ lose it
and beat him into the ground.
Dio: Six seconds.
Jotaro: That’s right, dio.
Come and get it.
- Dio: Seven seconds.
- ( Jotaro gasps )
Dio: I’m going
to roll all over you!
( Jotaro groans )
( Growls )
( Star platinum yelling )
Dio: It’s too late!
Time to die!
( The world yelling )
( Star platinum yelling )
Dio: Eight seconds!
( Yells )
I’ll obliterate you!
Jotaro: Ora!
♪
Dio: Nine seconds.
I did it.
It’s over.
The world has defeated
star platinum.
my stand is
more powerful than his.
I am immortal.
I am everlasting.
( Laughs )
Stand power!
now there is
incontrovertible proof
that no one on this miserable
planet is stronger than me.
You loathsome humans,
I shall rule over your pathetic
species until the end of time.
Now bow before my wisdom
and power!
Ten seconds!
( Laughs )
Would you look at that?
I can stop time for ten seconds!
All right, now that
i’ve defeated jotaro,
I should inspect
his lifeless body
and drink his blood,
that is, if there’s
any blood left to savor.
( Grunting )
This can’t be.
My body’s slowing down.
What’s happening?
n-no. It’s not
that i’m slowing down.
For some reason,
I can’t move at all!
I don’t get it.
This is impossible.
i’m frozen.
Jotaro: Hey, dio,
it’s been 11 seconds.
i guess that’s
your stand’s limit, huh?
Dio: Eh, what?!
Jotaro: I stopped time
at nine seconds,
and it’s a good thing I did.
It gave me a chance to escape.
Good grief, you idiot.
( Dio grunts )
Jotaro: Here’s the thing.
Since you’re frozen like that,
destroying you
will only take a second!
( Dio sputters )
Jotaro!
Dio: This is madness.
You can stop time, too?
curse you!
This whole act was a ruse
to waste my nine seconds,
wasn’t it, you bastard?
Jotaro: How does it feel, dio?
Tell me.
( Dio sputters )
Jotaro: How’s it feel
having your archenemy
tower behind you while you
stand frozen and helpless?
I suppose it’s a lot
like holding your breath
while underwater,
only someone’s out to get you,
and your air is running out
as you desperately swim
for your life.
And then after finally reaching
the surface and taking a breath,
you get pulled right back in.
Sound familiar?
But after everything
you’ve done, dio,
you’re not gonna get
any sympathy from me.
Star platinum: Ora!
( Dio groans )
Jotaro: Time is about
to start moving again.
( Dio gasping )
Jotaro: Compassion is something
you’re never gonna get from me.
I haven’t got any kindness
for your sorry undead ass,
though I gotta admit
you look pretty pathetic
writhing on the ground in agony.
As much as I want to,
killing you like this
would leave
a pretty bad taste in my mouth.
i wonder how long
it’ll take for you to heal.
Three seconds? Four, maybe?
The very moment
your legs are healed,
star platinum’s headed your way
to demolish you.
( Dio gasps )
Jotaro: If this were
the wild west,
the hero would say,
"it’s high noon.
"Now get off the ground,
and draw your piece, dio.
You’re getting one shot."
Dio: This insignificant whelp,
how dare he mock me?!
Though I shouldn’t be surprised.
Of course he would use
this opportunity
to make
such a human declaration.
( Laughs )
You think like a true mortal,
cursed with a fleeting life
destined for obscurity.
A bad taste in your mouth,
you say?
What, are you afraid
you’d regret killing me?
That reasoning is as pathetic
as your species.
Your foolish honor
will be your demise.
( Laughs )
That is where you and I differ.
My vision is clear, and my mind
is focused on a single goal.
i want to dominate,
nothing more, nothing less.
it’s the only thing
that will bring me fulfillment.
But how I go about doing that...
Doesn’t matter in the slightest!
There! How about a little blood
in your eyes?!
I win! Die!
Jotaro: Ora!
( Grunts )
( Dio chuckles )
( Gasps )
♪
( Yelling )
What the hell?!
It’s impossible!
I am the immortal dio!
( Gurgles )
I am dio!
Jotaro: When the sun comes up,
you’ll be nothing but dust.
You only made one mistake,
one that got you killed.
Dio, this whole thing might
have ended differently, but...
You went and pissed me off.
Was it worth it?
♪
( Sirens blaring )
Driver: This is speedwagon
foundation, car two.
We’re traveling northbound
on the al-nil expressway,
and we’ve retrieved
dio’s remains.
i repeat.
We’ve retrieved dio’s remains.
man: Dio’s body is
showing cellular activity.
He must be exposed
to sunlight immediately.
Proceed with extreme caution!
Driver: Roger.
Man: Noriaki kakyoin is dead.
his body
is being transported now.
Jean Pierre polnareff
is unconscious.
The medical staff
of car one has him.
Driver: Roger.
Man: Car two,
I have a question.
Why have you placed
the remains of dio
and Joseph joestar
in the same car?
jotaro:
Because it’s not over yet.
Dio borrowed something
from us...
Doctor: Eh?
Jotaro: And we need to take it
back from the bastard.
Doctor #2: I’m not following
your train of thought.
jotaro: I need you
to perform a blood transfusion
between the two bodies.
( Doctors gasp )
Doctor #1: That’s absurd!
You want us to transfuse
dio’s blood into Mr. Joestar?
Doctor #2: I see! You’re trying
to bring him back to life!
Jotaro: It hasn’t
been all that long
since dio drained his blood.
his upper half
was destroyed in the fight,
but we’ll take
as much as we can.
if we hurry,
I think we can make it.
( Driver gasps )
hey, car one,
did you catch all that? Over.
( Man gasps ) Roger.
Doctor #2: It’s impossible!
- He doesn’t even have a pulse.
- Doctor #1: Right!
not to mention
his heart has stopped,
which means
we couldn’t circulate his blood
- if we wanted to.
- Jotaro: Don’t give me that.
You could call everything we’ve
done on this journey impossible.
I’m tired of hearing words
like "impossible" or "futile."
They all mean nothing to us.
( Doctors stammer )
jotaro: You can do it
if his heart’s beating, right?
- Well, you’re in luck.
- doctors: Huh?
Jotaro: Thanks to dio, i’ve
already had a bit of practice
with stopping
and starting hearts.
Star platinum: Ora!
Doctor #1: I hear a pulse.
Doctor #2: Yes, you’re right!
His heart is beating!
Doctor #1: We have
to transfuse his blood
into Mr. Joestar quickly!
doctor #2: We might
just be able to pull this off!
♪
( Gasps ) Remarkable!
Take a look at his skin!
It’s completely regaining
all its color!
His skin is filling out!
( Steady beeping )
Doctor #1: My god!
Brain activity, too!
Doctor #2: I don’t believe it.
His vitals are stable as well!
( Joseph sighs )
- ( Doctors gasp )
- Doctor #2: His eyes!
He opened his eyes!
Doctor #1: We did it! He’s back!
( Jotaro gasps )
( Joseph sighs )
Jotaro: Old man?
( Joseph chuckles )
( Jotaro gasps )
( Doctors gasp )
( Joseph laughs )
You’re a damn fool, jotaro.
Jotaro: You have
got to be kidding!
Joseph: Hmm.
all you’ve done
is resurrect yours truly!
Jotaro: Bastard!
Joseph: Wait! Calm down, jotaro!
It was a joke!
I was just kidding!
There’s no need to get violent!
( Jotaro groans )
Joseph: I’m sorry!
I was just trying
to have some fun!
You have my word, it’s me!
I’m Joseph joestar! I was
born September 27th in 1920!
My wife’s name is Suzie q,
and I collect comics as a hobby!
Jotaro: I have
a question for you.
Who’s the leading actress
in "Tarzan, the ape man"?
Joseph: Bo Derek.
Jotaro: Okay,
now answer this one.
Who sang "eat it,"
the spoof of "beat it"?
Joseph: "Weird al" yankovic.
Jotaro: Good grief,
it has to be you.
Who else would know
pointless crap like that?
( Joseph sighs )
Driver: This is car two. Over!
it’s amazing!
Mr. Joestar is back with us!
he’s come back
from the brink of death!
It’s a miracle! Over!
Jotaro: Hear that?
We’ve taken back everything
you stole from us, dio.
♪
Joseph: It’s finally over.
Dio took something precious
from all of us.
for a hundred years,
he’s taken whatever he wanted.
His appetite for power
has been insatiable.
Jotaro: He’s taken far too much.
You realize that.
joseph: Yeah.
He’s taken things from us
that’ll we’ll never
be able to get back.
The losses that we’ve endured
on this journey
stretch as far
as the planet itself.
But thanks to their sacrifices,
we’re here to tell the tale
and carry on in their stead.
( Jotaro sighs )
Kakyoin, iggy, avdol...
It’s over.
( Overlapping chatter )
Announcer: Passengers
awaiting incoming flights,
please make your way
to the boarding gate.
Joseph: So you’re really going
back to France, polnareff?
This may be a bit forward,
but your family’s gone.
Why don’t you come back
with me to New York?
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar,
I know they’re gone,
but France is the only home
i’ve ever known.
It’s filled with memories.
It’s a place I must return to,
no matter where I go.
But if you ever need anything,
all you have to do is call,
and i’ll be there
in a heartbeat.
Joseph: We’re gonna
miss you, buddy.
Polnareff: It wasn’t easy,
that’s for damn sure,
but I had a hell of a time,
and i’m lucky to have been
on this adventure with you guys.
Jotaro: Hmm.
Joseph: Remember, we’re a team,
and that’s never gonna change.
announcer:
Calling all passengers
for France international
airlines, flight 92 to Paris.
Please proceed to gate 18.
Polnareff: A bientot,
you ornery bastard.
Live long and happy.
And you, his moody grandson,
you’d better not forget me.
Jotaro: We’ll meet again,
that is, of course,
if you don’t hate my guts
by then, stubborn jackass!
Joseph: We wouldn’t be able
to forget about you,
even if we wanted to, polnareff.
You be well.
Polnareff: Au revoir.
Joseph: Yeah.
Jotaro: See you later.
♪
( Holly sighs )
Suzie q: Holly!
How are you sitting up straight
all of a sudden?
Holly: I’m feeling much better.
i’m not sure
how to put it into words.
It’s as if we could
read each other’s minds.
- Suzie q: What?
- Holly: Mom,
I can feel that they’re
coming home to us!
( Suzie q gasps )
holly!
Holly: Papa and my jotaro!
( Gasps )
They’re coming home!
( Jet engine roars )
♪
Joseph: Hmm?
( Chuckles )
( Jotaro chuckles )
♪