( Star platinum yelling )
- ( Dio chuckles )
- ( Jotaro growls )
( Stands yelling )
♪
( Dio chuckles )
( Laughs )
It seems I was right about
the world’s speed and power
exceeding that
of star platinum,
so there’s nothing left to do
but bring this game to an end.
( Jotaro yells )
Dio: It should have
been done ages ago,
but i’ll finally be rid of
you joestars once and for all.
( Star platinum yelling )
Dio: Using the power
of my stand,
I will send you all
into oblivion!
now the world
will stop time itself!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Ticking slows, stops )
( Music stops )
( Footsteps echoing )
( Singing in Japanese resumes )
( Star platinum yelling )
( The world yelling )
♪
dio: Jotaro,
your exasperating family line
is just moments away
from being eradicated.
my hundred-year struggle
with the joestars ends with you.
Begone!
- ( Knuckle pops )
- ( Dio gasps )
( Gasps )
He moved his finger.
But how? What’s going on?
He shouldn’t be able to think,
let alone move.
Wait. There’s no way.
Is his power...
The same as the world’s?
( Sputters )
Jotaro: Your stand has a lot
in common with my star platinum.
Dio: Did he mean the world
and star platinum
are the same type of stand?
( Groans )
Damn it. ( Scoffs )
Can you see me right now?
Are you consciously moving,
or is it an involuntary twitch?
( Gasps )
Okay, time’s up.
Star platinum: ...Ora! Ora! Ora!
( Jotaro grunts )
Dio: Jotaro, could you see me?
♪
Must I repeat? I asked if you
could follow my movements!
Jotaro: See what?
You’re not making sense.
need to have
your eyes checked, dio?
Dio: Just you wait.
You can’t run forever.
seeing me isn’t
going to do you any good
when time is standing still!
if your stand does bear
similarities to mine, prove it!
i want to see
just how much we have in common!
Yes, it’s been six months
since I began to grasp
the art of stopping time.
To test the world’s
speed and power,
I commanded my servant
to take aim point-blank
right at my back.
And for a moment,
it looked as though time itself
had stood still.
I thought for sure
I was hallucinating.
it seemed like
the vision a boxer has
when his opponent’s punches
linger in midair.
That second felt
like an eternity.
but I wasn’t
simply imagining things.
my stand was
actually able to move
between the hovering bullets
that were suspended in time...
And it could grasp them.
Enyaba: Yes, lord dio.
You are well on your way
to being the master of time.
The next step
is willing yourself
to move through
the realm of frozen time.
it must happen
as naturally as breathing
or as nonchalantly
as snapping a pencil
betwixt your mighty fingers.
You must think of it
as completely ordinary.
The most important thing
is having faith in yourself.
It’s imperative that you find
the mental fortitude
to steel your mind.
( Dio sighs )
Enyaba: You are the one,
true ruler of this world!
controlling time
should be second nature to you!
( Laughs )
dio: Then one day,
I sensed the wheels of time
and the world interlock
at long last.
Like a ray of clarity dispersing
the shadows in my mind,
a revelation befell me.
I was dio, and my destiny
was to surpass
all living things,
including stand users!
I can stop time
for five seconds,
and the time limit
keeps extending by the day!
now, jotaro,
you’re about to experience
just how weak you are!
Time to make good
on my promise!
The world! Grind to a halt!
♪
- ( Joint pops )
- hmm?
( Sighs )
( Laughing )
I see you planted a magnet.
( Scoffs ) Must have been
when we were exchanging blows.
It looks like a wallet magnet
or one picked
from a pocket planner.
( Laughs )
I have to admit
you had me fooled.
You’re a clever boy indeed,
but...
If you have to resort
to inane tricks like that,
it only proves
that you can’t move
while time is standing still!
you’ve only postponed
the inevitable by a few seconds!
This is the end!
Die, jotaro!
♪
( Gasps )
What?!
How the--
he’s moving. What nerve.
Although, he can
only do it briefly.
the magnet wasn’t meant
to make me think he could move.
It was made to make me think
he couldn’t.
Damn it. It was a trap
designed to lure me in,
and I fell for it!
Enyaba: The key is believing
that your power
is completely ordinary.
Dio: Disgusting! To think
that my domain could be invaded,
and by the one of the joestars,
no less! It’s infuriating!
( Woman gasps )
( Screams )
Jotaro: I was able to move
for a second there.
That’s a good sign.
Even so, that’s not much.
it would only give me
enough time for a single punch.
♪
( Woman gasping )
Dio: You there, woman...
( Woman shrieks )
dio: How about
you make yourself useful
and fetch me my leg?
( Woman gasping )
Dio: Bring it here this instant!
Imagine you’re
a flight attendant
bringing caviar
to a passenger in first class
if it gets you here faster!
jotaro:
Well, that’s good to know.
Seems i’ll have
to blow your head off
to do any significant damage.
bastard,
you’ve already siphoned off
enough energy to heal yourself.
It’s like that gaping hole
I opened in your gut
was never even there.
( Dio scoffs )
( Chuckles )
Your eyes followed me
even while time was frozen,
which confirms that you
can see my movements.
Isn’t that right, jotaro?
Jotaro: Nervous yet, sweetheart?
dio: Not at all.
Kakyoin did you quite the favor.
Because of his brilliant mind,
he was able to correctly deduce
the world’s secret,
and because he passed
that knowledge along,
you figured out that I
could stop time at will
and worked until you learned
how to do it yourself.
Jotaro: Hmm?
Dio: Then again, you haven’t had
as much training as I have,
so i’m curious to know
exactly how long you can move
while time is frozen.
Two seconds? Or maybe three?
Or perhaps you can move
five seconds like me,
but you’re pretending you can’t
to gain some kind
of an advantage. Clever.
( Laughs )
Which is it?
Jotaro: This isn’t good.
I could probably move longer
if I was able
to get some practice in,
but as it stands,
the best I can do is a second.
Dio: If I was forced
to make a guess,
i’d say you could
only move for a second.
Be that as it may, you’ve still
managed to infiltrate my world.
Only a fool would risk
approaching you now.
And though i’m many things,
a fool wouldn’t be
considered one of them.
While it’s achingly clear
that my advantage over you
is overwhelming...
I’ve still devised
a way to execute you,
so regardless of how long
you can move in my world,
you’ll never escape
your demise!
Dio: You’re white as a sheet.
Do these bring back memories?
Do they remind you that you’re
going to die a death
even more horrific
than your pathetic grandfather?
Jotaro: Screw this bastard.
How the hell does he come up
with this kind of shit?
I need to be careful.
( Dio chuckles )
There is no escape.
The world!
( Ticking slows, stops )
Five seconds left.
♪
Do you think your star platinum
can deflect all of the knives
once time resumes?
If I were a betting man,
i’d give that plan
a one-in-a-million chance
of working.
Four seconds!
( Laughs )
It must be terrifying
to stare death in the face
and be helpless to stop it.
Only three seconds remain.
Star platinum: Ora!
Dio: You’re down to two seconds.
are you telling me
that’s the best you’ve got?
( Chuckles )
That’s just more evidence
of your ineptitude
in the presence
of one such as myself.
One second left to go.
Zero.
( Star platinum yelling )
( Jotaro gags )
Dio: It’s over.
But one can never
be too careful.
( Jotaro groans )
Now, to be perfectly honest,
i’m relieved
I was able to do away with you
so quickly, jotaro.
i have to say,
I never would have thought
that you’d have the power
to infiltrate my perfect world.
Now let’s see.
A fitting analogy
would be the automobile,
useful machines until the roads
become clogged with them all.
( Bystanders chattering )
Dio: Sorry, but the mantle
of master of time
is reserved for me alone.
( Woman screams )
♪
( Jotaro sighs )
Oh, good grief.
He throw enough knives,
or what?
I mean, he turned my favorite
uniform into Swiss cheese.
Well, i’m glad I decided
to stuff my clothes
with magazines.
I figured it was
only a matter of time
before he tried
throwing weapons,
but I didn’t expect that many.
My best bet right now
is to play possum
and wait for a chance
to take dio by surprise.
Since he can regenerate,
i’ve gotta bash his brains in,
or else he’ll never die.
Eh?
♪
dio: I believe i’ll do
one more check for good measure.
The joestars have a way
of coming back from the dead,
and there’s a chance jotaro
is putting on this death act.
I need to make sure
he’s gone for good.
I’ll use this...
to sever
that troublesome head of his!
It’s time for you to die...
Jotaro!
♪
Polnareff: The only one
dying here is you!
Re the one who’s gonna die!
Jotaro: Polnareff!
( Ticking slows, stops )
Time has stopped.
Let’s get a good look
at your face.
I see. It’s polnareff.
And now time will resume.
( Polnareff gagging )
Dio: What a shame, polnareff.
You were so close,
but dropped the ball.
If you’d lunged with more force
behind your attack,
you could have
eviscerated my brain
beyond the point
of regeneration.
Polnareff: You bastard.
It’s not over yet.
Dio: When will you all accept
that you cannot kill me?
You are nothing more than pawns
destined to be put in check.
Your death brings about the end
of the joestars’s
tragic Egyptian journey.
( Jotaro thinking )
damn it.
If I don’t do something,
polnareff’s as good as dead.
I was gonna keep up this act
until I had a chance
to catch him off guard
and crush his skull,
but saving polnareff
from this undead freak
is more important right now.
It’s not gonna be easy, though.
He won’t make the mistake
of crossing
into star platinum’s range,
so it’ll just end up like
the last time he trapped me.
whatever I do,
I can’t let him know i’m alive.
As long as he thinks i’m dead,
I have the element of surprise,
which gives me a chance
to get in close.
strange how things
end up coming full circle.
one minute,
i’m trying to will myself
to move through a world
of frozen time,
and the next,
i’m doing everything I can
to stay completely still.
Dio: Enjoy your journey
to the afterlife!
- ( Scrape )
- ( Dio gasps )
Damn you, jotaro.
Was he alive all along?
At the very least,
he seems to be coming to.
( Growls )
Officer: Hold it!
This is the police!
Officer #2: You try anything
funny, and we will shoot!
Slowly put your hands
in the air!
- ( Officer #1 gasps )
- ( Officer #2 yells )
Dio: Ah, what impeccable timing.
If you wouldn’t mind,
there’s somebody
i’d like for you to shoot.
Do you see that man
lying on the ground?
Shoot his leg or torso.
That’s right.
Line up the shot,
and let the bullet fly.
Hmm.
I thought I heard jotaro
make a sound a moment ago,
but I guess my mind
was playing tricks on me.
Jotaro: Could he be
any more demented?
He’s at least lost interest
in polnareff,
but now that
his attention’s back on me,
he’s even more suspicious.
He’s not gonna rest
until he’s sure i’m dead.
Things just got a lot harder.
Dio: I know. Why don’t we
check his breathing?
No luck. He’s not breathing.
But there’s no way
to hide his heartbeat.
( Jotaro gasping )
Shit, this hurts.
if I black out,
everything we’ve been through
will have been for nothing.
dying because I used
my own stand to stop my heart,
it’d be ironic
in a morbid kind of way.
( Dio sighs )
And sure enough,
there’s no heartbeat.
What do you know? I suppose
the thought of him being alive
was just a figment
of my imagination.
Though, stranger things
have happened,
so I should still probably
lop off his head to be sure.
( Chuckles )
That’s not a problem, is it?
( Heart beating rapidly )
What?!
( Gasps )
Star platinum: Ora!
Dio: I have to stop time again!
The world!
( Gags )
Jotaro: I gotta hand it to you.
You really put me
through hell back there.
You’re not stopping time
or leaving
with your skull intact, got it?!
Dio: No! This can’t
be happening to me!
Star platinum: Ora!
( Dio screams )
Jotaro: Took long enough.
I finally got to run my fist
straight through
his demented skull.
But that walking
cesspool of evil
lived at the bottom of the sea
for over a century.
i can’t be sure
that attack killed him.
It’s a bit too early
to take a victory lap.
( Dio gasping )
I will annihilate you.
( Gasps )
What the hell? I can’t move.
Jotaro, what did you do to me?
I don’t have control
over my legs.
I can’t even stand.
♪
Agh! My head!
The pain is unbearable.
I think i’m going to vomit.
This can’t be happening to me.
I’m the pinnacle of perfection!
He actually damaged my brain
and paralyzed my legs!
Shit, shit, shit.
I’ve gotta find
a way out of here.
( Groaning )
jotaro: I’ve doused you
with gasoline so you can’t hide.
normally,
I would hate to kick a guy
when he’s down on his luck,
but with you,
I don’t give a damn.
You killed my friends and
countless innocent bystanders,
so don’t expect any mercy.
( Dio laughing )
( Jotaro gasps )
( Dio yells )
Come forth, the world!
( Ticking slows, stops )
If I can...
Just make it a little farther.
( Chuckles )
And now time will flow as usual.
♪
Jotaro: While he had
his ear to the ground,
he was also listening
for any nearby cars.
Clever, but...
bastard’s not
getting away that easily!
( Tire thumping )
Dio: A-almost.
Keep going.
( Groans ) That’s it.
I’m almost there.
Jotaro: And where do
you think you’re going?
We’ve got unfinished business.
( Dio gasps )
Jotaro: It’s over, dio.
Time to accept it.
♪
Dio: The world! Freez--
star platinum: Ora!
( Yelling )
Ora!
( Dio screams )
( Jotaro grunts )
Dio: You fell for it, jotaro!
Now my victory
is all but assured!
Once again, my genius
has triumphed over you!
Doesn’t this street
look familiar?
( Jotaro gasps )
This street.
What have I done?
( Squelch )
You’ve failed.
This was my escape route
to your grandfather,
and now his blood is mine.
( Joseph groans )
Jotaro: Dio!
You’re dead!