narrator: Previously on
"jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
( Polnareff gasps )
Young polnareff: What the?!
Why am I a kid?!
Young silver chariot: Pami!
Woman: Little boy,
are you all right there?
I’ll clean those wounds up
and put some medicine on you.
( Polnareff groans )
( Alessi cackles )
( Polnareff wails )
That’s impossible!
Chariot, help!
Alessi: Yes! Yes!
- ( Polnareff groans )
- ( Silver chariot screams )
( Polnareff screams )
I’m not strong enough
to beat him like this.
- ( Gasps )
- Silver chariot: Pami!
Polnareff: I don’t see
that nice lady anywhere.
where’d she go?
She couldn’t have just vanished.
She was sitting
right behind me.
I didn’t even hear a scream.
What’d he do to her?
( Alessi laughs )
polnareff:
Where could she have gone?!
Alessi: Oh, polnareff...
( Polnareff gasping )
Alessi: As I recall, you said
the shampoo stings your eyes,
and since it looks like
you’ve got some in there...
Allow me to help you
wash it out!
Now this won’t take long.
( Polnareff gurgling )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Polnareff gurgling )
C’est mauvais!
Having pint-sized arms is
gonna wind up getting me killed!
If only these stupid arms of
mine were just a little longer,
i’d be able to poke his eyes out
and make a run for it.
alessi:
So, even in the face of death,
you thought to pull the plug!
However...
- ( Laughs )
- ( Polnareff gurgling )
( Alessi laughs ) With your hair
clogging the water’s only exit,
it’ll take even longer
for the tub to completely drain.
I’d say you have five,
maybe 10 minutes left.
you may as well
throw in the towel now.
You’re going down
for a permanent nap!
good night!
Horrid dreams, you little brat!
( Silver chariot gasping )
Alessi: Now die!
( Laughs ) How does it feel
knowing that you’re
utterly helpless, polnareff?
( Laughs )
( Bubbles popping )
( Polnareff sighs )
♪
Alessi: Hmm?
W-what the hell is that thing?
( Gasps ) It can’t be!
But from the shape and color,
it looks like--
there’s no way!
No one in their right mind
would think of doing something
so downright disgusting!
( Screams )
It’s undeniable!
The smell proves it!
Ugh! How foul!
You took a shit in the bathtub!
- ( Wailing )
- ( Polnareff gasping )
guess i’m
not so helpless after all,
you creepy, four-eyed asshole!
Alessi: How dare you
do something like that?!
Dear god! Isn’t there a shred
of human decency in your body?!
What kind of hero
would ever stoop
to doing something
so disturbing?!
You are a bad boy, very bad!
Polnareff: Shut up, and tell me
what you did to that nice lady!
I wanna know right now!
Where are you?
Where’d you go?!
Lady, answer me!
Hey, lady!
Alessi: Hmm.
( Laughs )
Come on. You that stupid?
What do you think I did?
Whoa, there!
It’d be wise for both of us
to watch where we step,
polnareff.
One wrong move,
and your lady friend
is likely to be
squashed underfoot.
Huh?
( Gasps )
( Weak crying )
Polnareff: He--he wouldn’t.
there’s no way.
This can’t be happening.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Fetus mewling )
Polnareff: No, it can’t be.
Alessi: Anyone who’s
unfortunate enough
to come into contact
with my stand
experiences time in reverse.
Luckily for you,
you saw me coming
and jumped away from my shadow
at the last second,
buying yourself a few more years
than your friend down there,
but she had the misfortune
of touching my shadow
for several seconds,
which is the reason
she became a fetus!
( Laughs )
She’s alive for the time being,
but, if i’m
being honest with you,
she won’t last long outside
the safety of her mother’s womb.
That’s what she gets!
She should have
never tried to help
a pathetic piece
of trash like you!
What a moron.
( Polnareff yells )
You are the worst kind
of person on this planet!
( Alessi laughs )
( Polnareff grunts )
Crap! You gotta be
kidding me. I just...
( Gasping )
( Alessi laughs ) Oops!
Looks like you touched it again,
which means you’re
going to get even younger.
this time,
you’ll probably regress
to a diminutive four-year-old
version of yourself.
Polnareff: Not again!
- ( Alessi chuckling )
- Polnareff: This isn’t good.
I have to hurry
and beat this guy,
or the nice lady will--
at this rate,
she only has a matter of minutes
before she dies!
I’ve gotta find a way
to defeat this alessi freak,
and i’ve gotta do it fast!
( Alessi chuckles )
Polnareff: She took me in
and fixed up all my wounds.
She was so caring.
I have to hurry!
There’s absolutely
no time to waste.
Alessi: Come here, little boy!
Come here! Come here!
( Cackles )
Get over here, will you?!
where exactly
do you think you’re going?
You’re not gonna get far
cradling a dying fetus!
Here’s a fun idea.
Let’s turn you into a fetus!
Polnareff: Damn it.
Not this again!
His dumb shadow
keeps touching me!
( Gasping )
oh, no!
I’m getting even smaller!
Alessi: Yahoo!
Oh, boy!
There’s no way in hell
i’m gonna lose now!
Judging from your appearance,
polnareff,
you’re what,
three years old now?
Before you know it,
your intellect will be that
of a three-year-old’s as well.
( Laughs )
( Growls )
( Polnareff whimpering )
( Pounding )
( Alessi laughs )
Locking the door won’t
do you any good, little one.
Polnareff: Made it.
Huh? Damn it. The stupid bars
are too close together!
Even a kid can’t slip through.
But I have to find
a way to get out of here,
or that freak show’s
gonna kill us both! Crap!
( Silver chariot whimpers )
Polnareff: I-I can’t cut them.
( Alessi laughs )
this is
just too good to be true.
I see that your chariot
has also become a toddler.
The bars are too tough
for its baby rapier.
I bet it’s gotten slower, too.
( Polnareff whimpering )
Alessi: Ready or not,
here I come.
( Babbling )
Oh, polnareff,
here comes alessi!
Huh?
H-he’s gone.
Huh? Where did he go?
That brat. He just vanished.
Or maybe the little spunk monkey
found a way to slither
through the bars in the window.
( Growls )
( Gasps )
Clever, polnareff. Very clever.
You’re trying to pull
a fast one, aren’t you?
You think if you
trick me into believing
you slipped through the window,
it’ll distract me.
You must be hiding somewhere,
waiting to get the drop on me.
( Laughs ) Not bad, runt.
Quite cunning indeed,
for a miserable little shit!
Polnareff, come out,
come out, wherever you are.
( Laughs )
You’re so puny now,
you could easily be hiding
in that drawer over there.
Yeah, he’s probably hiding
in the bucket or the drawer,
or maybe he’s actually hiding
in that Teddy bear by the wall.
( Snickers )
Oh, where could he be?
I’ve got a one-in-three chance.
And, if at all possible,
i’d like to get him
with one swing.
i’ll crack open his
infantile skull with this ax!
( Polnareff whimpering )
Alessi: I’ve decided
you’re tucking away
in that tattered,
old Teddy bear!
But my second guess is...
This grandfather clock,
the perfect hiding spot
for a coward!
( Groans )
I guess I was wrong.
Then maybe he’s...
Hiding in this rusty bucket!
But i--
( groans )
So you are in the bear!
( Gasping )
Then how about the drawer?!
Where is he?! Where is he?!
Where is he?!
H-he’s gone! But how?
There’s no way he could
have gotten out of here!
The walls, floor, and ceiling
are all stone.
Even if they were
one centimeter thick,
chariot couldn’t break through.
and those bars
are too narrow for him.
I saw it with my own eyes.
This is insane. Where is he?
Where did he go?
- ( Polnareff chuckles )
- alessi: Huh?
polnareff: So you were
outsmarted by a toddler, huh...
- Alessi: What the...
- Polnareff: Old man alessi.
( Alessi gasps )
( Polnareff laughing )
Alessi: What’s going on here?
The goldfish just disappeared.
Huh? ( Gasps )
( Shrieking )
( Alessi shrieking )
polnareff: I was hiding
in the fish tank the whole time
and used this mirror
for camouflage.
A kid could have
figured out my plan,
and you totally fell for it!
I was worried that something
so simple wasn’t gonna work,
but lucky for me, you’re just
as stupid as you are creepy!
It doesn’t matter if chariot’s
stuck in his two-year-old form.
He can still skewer
your face, dumb-ass!
( Laughs )
( Alessi groans )
( Shrieks )
Bad boy! Bad boy!
polnareff:
Hey, get your ass back here!
- Silver chariot: Pami!
- Polnareff: Hey, wait!
Until you break your stand’s
spell, i’m gonna keep attacking!
( Fetus whimpers )
Alessi: Bad boy! Bad boy!
You’re such a bad boy!
Polnareff: Of all the--
that jerk
jumped out the window!
Alessi: Bad boy.
What a horrible boy.
Eh?
♪
( Shrieks )
( Thinking )
Jotaro.
Crap. If he’s here,
then i’m done for.
How’d he find us?
Jotaro: Hmm.
( Alessi gasping )
♪
jotaro: Someone falling
from a window, covered in blood.
You don’t see that every day.
Alessi: Stay calm. Stay calm.
At times like this, the winner
is the one who stays calm.
Just think about it, alessi.
Jotaro must be looking for
the adult version of polnareff.
He has no clue who I am.
I’ll do what I always do,
play dumb until the last minute,
then attack him
when he least expects it.
( Groaning )
O-oh, no!
My boss is going to be so very
angry with me when he finds out!
There I was cleaning the window,
and I suddenly slipped
and fell through!
What am I going to do?
I am in so much trou--
polnareff: Hold it right there,
you frizzy-haired freak show!
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Hey, mister! Uh...
What was his name again?
Come on. What was it?
( Groans )
Alessi: Now’s my chance.
I was waiting for polnareff
to poke his annoying
little head out.
Gotcha now, jotaro!
( Polnareff gasps ) Mister,
watch out for his shadow!
Alessi: I did it!
I really did it.
I managed to touch
jotaro’s shadow!
Polnareff: Mister, no!
( Alessi laughs )
So, jotaro, how does it feel
to be placed
under the spell of my stand?
( Jotaro gasping )
This feeling...
This is...
Polnareff: This is bad.
He’s turning into a kid
just like I did!
alessi: Oh, jotaro,
I heard through the grapevine
that you’ve
only recently developed
your stand, star platinum,
and that means
you didn’t have the ability
to use your stand
when you were a kid,
so now you’re nothing
but ordinary!
( Laughing )
( Polnareff gasps ) Oh, no!
He’s been turned
into a little boy!
It looks like he can’t be
any older than a seven-year-old!
Alessi: Guess i’m the winner.
Hope you’re watching,
master dio,
’cause i’m about to kill jotaro.
You’d better give me
a good reward
for everything
i’ve gone through.
Now, jotaro, it’s time to die!
( Groans )
Polnareff: Whoa, what a hit.
he decked him
using only his little-kid fist!
♪
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
Don’t underestimate me
just ’cause i’m a kid.
( Alessi whimpering )
Jotaro: Ora! Ora!
( Yelling )
Ora!
alessi: What?!
You’re seriously telling me
that jotaro could kick ass
even as a little kid?!
Polnareff: I knew he was tough,
but he was that strong
as a kid? Badass!
( Alessi grunting )
- ( Groans )
- ( Birds tweeting )
( Crash )
( Muttering )
Huh?
( Groans )
( Chuckles )
- ( Footsteps )
- ( Gasping )
( Polnareff chuckles )
You got off easy, friend,
but I can fix that.
( Alessi whimpering )
( Silver chariot and
star platinum chuckle )
( Alessi shrieks )
( Star platinum yelling )
Alessi: Attaboy!
( Narrator reading )
♪
( Woman sighs )
( Gasping )
Was all of that a dream?
( Gasps )
this earring
belongs to that boy,
so it really did happen.
I don’t know why,
but for some reason,
I couldn’t move my body.
That’s right.
I may not have
been able to move,
but I remember everything.
That sweet little boy devoted
himself to protecting me
and risked his life
by fighting against a grown man.
He had such a brave
and heroic heart.
Oh, where did that boy go?
where--where did
my little knight run off to?
Where did you go?
Where are you?!
Polnareff: I’ve never met
such an amazing woman before,
so kind, so genuine.
That was a close one,
but thankfully
i’m back to my normal self.
I wonder if she’s okay.
- ( Footsteps )
- hmm?
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
Woman: Uh, uh,
I hate to bother you,
but you didn’t happen to see
a sweet, little boy
leave my house in something
of a hurry, did you?
He has silver hair.
come to think of it,
it looks exactly like yours.
( Polnareff gasping )
Woman: Pardon me for asking,
but have the two of us
met before?
- ( Gasps )
- Polnareff: No,
I didn’t see
a kid come through.
Sorry I couldn’t help you.
Let’s go, jotaro.
( Jotaro sighs )
Polnareff: Come on. Hurry up.
Woman: Uh, wa--please wait!
Could you be--
that earring you’re wearing...
Polnareff: The two of us
have never met before.
It’s not possible.
My friend and I are travelers,
so if you’ll excuse us,
there’s another town
we need to get to.
We’ll be going now.
Woman: It was only a dream.
Too bad.
( Polnareff groans )
Not a single word
from you, jotaro.
I don’t wanna hear it.
( Groans )
( Jotaro chuckles )
joseph: Oh!
Jotaro and polnareff!
where in the world
have you two slackers been?!
polnareff: Ah!
Mr. Joestar and avdol!
Joseph: How many times
have I told the two of you
not to go wandering off
on your own?
polnareff: Oh,
you’re in a position to talk!
You’re the ones
who just disappeared!
- Joseph: Eh?
- Avdol: Now, now.
why don’t we focus
on getting something to eat?
Polnareff: Huh? Hey, iggy!
where the hell
have you been all day long?!
( Iggy sighs )
♪
( Overlapping chatter )
Waiter: Can I take that for you?
( Joseph gulping )
Yeah, thanks a million.
Eh, it’s about time.
We’re finally getting
a bit of relief.
Avdol: It was quite
the late breakfast,
but I suppose
it couldn’t be helped.
Avdol: Yeah.
Joseph: Since we’ve
almost made it to Cairo,
I think it’s time we figured out
where dio is hiding out.
♪
Polnareff: Oh, we’re doin’ this?
Jotaro: Will it appear?
joseph: I’m not sure,
but given that we’re so close,
the results
should be more precise.
All right, here we go!
( Yells )
Waiter: Excuse me, sir.
Is there a problem over here?
Avdol: Everything’s fine.
Mind your own business.
Waiter: Uh, yes, sir.
Joseph: Hmm.
Jotaro: Old man, tell us.
what is it?
Joseph: Just a little longer.
I see something.
It’s getting clearer.
Huh?
Take a good look!
♪
There you have it, gentlemen,
our final destination!
( All grunt )
♪