Narrator: Previously on
"jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
♪
Polnareff: What the hell?!
Hol horse: Hell, yeah!
( Polnareff gasping )
Mondatta: "’now, hol horse,’
mondatta instructed,
"’stick your fingers all the way
up polnareff’s nose,
"’and then we’ll win!
"’they’re out cold
from losing all that blood.
"’lucky you, hol horse!
this is your chance
to finish them off for good!’"
hol horse: So when is
this so-called chance
supposed to get here,
and what do I do ’til then?
Polnareff: Excuse me, hol horse.
Uh, what the hell
are you doing?
hol horse:
You’re not the only one
who wants the answer
to that question.
avdol:
What’s the matter, polnareff?
Horse: Shit! What now?!
They’re on me
like white on rice!
Damn it! How the hell
do I make the rest of this
stupid prediction come true?
Joseph: Hey, polnareff, did you
find the person tailing us?
Avdol: Say something.
Polnareff: Avdol and the others,
they’ll be here soon.
( Mondatta gasps )
Hol horse: Damn it. How am I
gonna get out of this one?
Polnareff: Chario--
hol horse: Hold it right there.
( Polnareff sputters )
this is bad.
hol horse: I-i’m the--
the fastest quick draw around.
Now don’t move, or you’re dead.
joseph: Hey,
did you say something?
Polnareff?
( Hol horse groans )
Avdol: Polnareff!
( Hol horse gasping )
- avdol: Huh?
- Jotaro and Joseph: Hmm?
( Polnareff chuckles )
Avdol: Hang on.
You’ve been here
the entire time?
What’s wrong? Did you find
someone following us or not?
Polnareff: Well, uh...
Hol horse: This is getting
uglier by the second.
They’ve backed me into a corner.
according to
that fool comic book,
I was supposed
to get my big chance
after I stuck my fingers
up polnareff’s nose,
but everything has gone south,
and i’m about to be
in a whole world of trouble!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Avdol: Is everything
all right, polnareff?
Polnareff: Uh, of course.
hol horse: Well,
now i’ve really stepped in it.
If avdol finds me,
i’m as good as dead.
I think i’m gonna cry.
Had I known something
like this was gonna happen,
I would have just blown him away
from a distance.
( Growls ) Mondatta, this is
all your fault. You know that?
That fool polnareff’s sword
would have had nothing
on my gun. Damn it!
- Avdol: Polnareff?
- Hol horse: Hmm?
( Scraping )
You waiting for an invitation?
Tell ’em to scram,
because I swear to you,
polnareff,
if i’m found out,
i’m taking you down with me.
( Polnareff stammers )
i-i was wrong.
No one was tailing us.
guess it was
just my imagination.
( Hol horse sighs )
All: Hmm...
Avdol: I see, and is there
any particular reason
you’re nonchalantly standing
in the corner like that?
( Polnareff gasping )
( Emperor clicks )
hol horse:
Tell ’em that you wanted
to find a place to take a leak.
do it, or i’ll
put a bullet in your head.
Polnareff: Oh,
I had to take a whiz
and couldn’t find a toilet,
so what can you do?
- ( Laughs )
- Avdol: Are you serious?
joseph: Come on.
You were peeing in the street?
Even after all this time,
your lack of shame amazes me.
( Polnareff chuckles )
( Thinking )
For the love of--
stop jabbing that stupid gun
into my head!
Wait! I may have found
a way out of this.
I’ll give them a signal and
hope to god they figure it out.
( Gulps )
( Grunting )
- Avdol: Hmm?
- Jotaro: Huh?
Joseph: Hmm.
( Polnareff grunting )
♪
Men: Hmm?
Hol horse: Hmm? Shit.
Why’d they stop talking?
Polnareff: Well, as you can see,
there’s nothing strange
going on here,
so you can go on ahead.
Avdol: Hmm? All right.
( Polnareff thinking )
i was lying.
How are you not catching on?
My tongue. Look at my tongue.
He’s right behind me.
Please don’t leave.
joseph:
Are you sure you’re okay?
You’re making a creepy face.
Something wrong
with your tongue?
- ( Hol horse gasps )
- Avdol: No. That’s not it.
he’s trying to tell us
that there’s something behind--
- ( Gasps )
- Polnareff: Shut your mouth.
- Joseph: You mean...
- ( Mondatta scoffs )
Hol horse: Damn it, polnareff,
you lowdown, dirty, son of a--
you were cluing ’em in.
You’ve pissed me off
for the last time.
I’ve had just about
enough of you. Now die.
- ( Polnareff sneezes )
- Hol horse: What the--
( slow-motion sneeze )
( Slow-motion sneeze ) Huh?
( Avdol gasps )
What’s he doing here?
hol horse: W-why?
You idiot, you had to sneeze?
( Both gasp )
( Hol horse groans )
Polnareff: Everyone, watch out!
Hol horse is back,
and he’s got a friend
hiding under the crate,
so be careful!
Hol horse: Blast it!
This can’t be happening.
He sneezed, because I went and
jammed my fingers up his nose.
damn, damn.
If polnareff hadn’t sneezed,
at the very least, I could have
gotten rid of him for good.
I should have known better
than to team up
with the likes of you, mondatta.
Now they’re gonna kill me.
This is all happening because
of that blasted premonition.
( Gasps )
Now i’m doomed!
man: Hey, bro,
you seeing what i’m seeing?
It looks like that jackass
that picked a fight with us.
( Man #2 growls )
That’s him, all right.
I’ll never forget
the face of the bastard
that blew my ear off!
i’ll run him over
like a piece of roadkill!
♪
( Both gasp )
Avdol: What?!
( All yell )
Hol horse: Huh?
( Mondatta laughs )
( Rubble clattering )
Hol horse: S-seriously?
It all happened so fast,
they didn’t have a chance
to whip out their stands
and stop the truck
from running ’em down.
My fingers went up his nose,
and the prediction came true.
i can’t believe this!
I got all four of ’em at once!
Mondatta: It’s fate.
My premonitions
are always right.
However, it’s too soon
for you to finish them off.
We must wait for the next
prediction to be revealed, yes.
Hol horse: Okay!
They proclaimed.
"The chance to finish off
their enemies had arrived.
"But be careful, you two.
Don’t rush in. Hide and wait."
♪
( Hol horse gulps )
"’it’s still
too soon for us to move in.
"’three of ’em are knocked out,
but jotaro’s still awake.
He’s gonna get up
any second now.’"
( gasps )
- ( Glass tinkling )
- ( Jotaro groaning )
( Hol horse growls )
Jotaro wasn’t hit head-on
by the truck
like Joseph and the others were.
That was close.
If we’d tried
creeping up to him,
there’s a chance
he could have laid us out.
Great. He’s lookin’ for me,
probably wondering why I split
instead of blowin’
his head clear off
when I thought
he was down for the count.
we are gonna be able
to beat these yahoos, right?
We’ve made it this far,
after all.
i have to win,
no matter what it takes.
you got that?
Are you with me, mondatta?
Mondatta: Yeah.
Hol horse: We’re so close,
I can taste it!
Mondatta, it’s time to take
these guys out once and for all,
so what’s our next move?
You’ve proven that your comic’s
predictions are 100% accurate.
i was wrong,
but I believe in you now,
and i’ll do whatever I must.
Need me to stick my fingers
up something, I will.
Need me to eat crap, i’ll do it
without a second thought.
I have to win this fight,
no matter what.
Mondatta: Oh!
Th-th-th-th-th-there it is!
It’s here!
I-it finally appeared, yes!
- It’s the final prediction!
- Hol horse: What?
Mondatta: "The time has arrived.
"Hol horse’s next attack
will be his last.
"While waiting to strike,
hol horse came across
"two plumbers
repairing drainpipes.
"he saw
the perfect opportunity to win
"and paid them
to open one of the pipes.
"If hol horse were to fire
every last one of his bullets
into that pipe exactly as
the clock struck 12:00 noon..."
- ( Pipe rattles )
- ( Hol horse gasps )
Plumber: Hey, check that out.
Looks like there was a car
accident around the corner.
plumber #2:
Who cares about that?
let’s hurry
and finish this thing.
Here. Hold this pipe for me.
Plumber #1: Okay.
♪
( Hol horse gasps )
W-what’s exactly gonna happen
if I fire my gun
into that pipe, huh?
( Mondatta groans )
( Hol horse groaning )
come on!
Turn the damn page, would you?!
I know I fire my gun
into the pipe,
but what happens after that?
Mondatta: "Once they’re fired,
"the bullets go through the pipe
and out the other end.
Ka-boom! Hol horse’s bullets
hit their Mark
and fly straight
through jotaro’s skull,
right smack
in the middle of his forehead!"
Yes. Yes! ( Laughs )
It’s finally happening! Yes!
Our time’s come, yes!
I’ve been waiting for this
since my brother’s accident,
yes! ( Laughing )
hol horse:
That’s great, mondatta.
I mean, it looks great,
but hold on a sec.
Mondatta: Hmm?
hol horse:
Let’s make sure we give it
a thorough once-over so we
don’t get our bacon cooked. Huh?
W-what’s happening
on this page?
Hey, this is the prediction
from when your brother
tried to wipe out jotaro.
But in the end,
your brother was the one
who got himself blown up.
Mondatta: Yeah, but my brother
transformed himself into jotaro
without giving it any thought.
If he hadn’t, the prediction
would have come true, yes.
b-b-but that’s
not going to happen to us,
because you and I can’t
transform ourselves, yes.
Hol horse: Oh, yeah,
you’re right.
I don’t have changing powers,
so I couldn’t pretend
to be jotaro if I wanted to.
Wait! Then does that mean...
Mondatta: It does indeed, yes!
At last I can avenge
my brother, yes!
There’s absolutely no way to
misinterpret this prophecy, yes.
All you have to do is shoot
your bullets into this pipe,
and jotaro
will meet his maker, yes!
( Sighs )
( Hol horse laughs )
( Gasps )
Let’s back up a bit.
It gave us a specific time
to do it, right?
It’s gotta be done
by the stroke of noon.
Hmm.
Huh?! Hey!
Your magic prediction comic book
neglected to mention
we only have two minutes left
before 12:00.
( Grumbles )
Mondatta: D-don’t panic!
All you have to do is
aim your gun and fire, yes.
you have more
than enough time, yes.
Just believe in fate.
It’ll work itself out.
Hol horse: Yeah, I know. I know!
It’s 100%
I believe you.
I really do, but...
( Watch ticking )
We’re down to the wire,
and time’s against us.
I’ve gotta haul ass!
You there, worker guys,
listen up!
This is a matter
of life and death.
I need one of you to open
that pipe on the double!
- Plumber #2: Hmm?
- Plumber #1: Huh?
hol horse:
Just do it, all right?
Plumber #1: Hey, who exactly
do you think
you’re barking orders at?
Plumber #2: Who do think
you are, pal? Take a hike.
Hol horse: Open the pipe,
or you can die!
Mondatta: Hol horse, you should
know that ordinary people
don’t have the ability
to see your stand, yes.
Hol horse: Huh?
Plumbers: Huh?
Mondatta: According to
the premonition in the comic,
you’re supposed to pay
the workers, yes.
Hol horse: Huh? Pay them?
( Squeals )
Only a minute, ten seconds left
before showtime!
All right, all right,
sorry about the attitude.
I’ll pay you to open the pipe,
but you have to do it now!
Please.
Plumber #2: Now you’re
gonna pay us? Weirdo.
Why would you give us money
to open the pipe?
plumber #1:
Does it really matter?
Hand over what you got.
Hol horse: Yeah, okay.
( Gasps )
Oh, no. Where is--
plumber #1:
Yo, what’s the holdup, man?
( Hol horse yelps )
I’m flat broke!
oh, that’s right.
I left my wallet at the hotel!
Plumber #1: Huh?
plumber #2:
What’s with this guy?
Hol horse: Mondatta!
Remember the money
I gave to you
just in case
you ended up getting lost?
Well, I need you
to give it back to me,
so fork it over now, mondatta!
Mondatta: Right. Let’s see.
hol horse: Crap!
We’ve only got 40 seconds left.
Move your ass!
Mondatta: I-I don’t know
if this is enough,
but go ahead, and take it.
( Yelps )
( Hol horse shrieks )
plumber #2: Hey,
I think I saw one of ’em
roll behind the bricks.
They’re just coins, but there
are a lot of ’em. Nice.
plumber #1:
Must be at least £20.
Hey, man, watch your feet.
You’re steppin’ on one.
- Plumber #2: What’s that?
- ( Hol horse screams )
Pick the damn coins up later!
You can have ’em all, okay?
Woman: Here you go, boys.
It’s getting close to noon.
I made you boys some tea,
so take a load off,
and have some lunch.
plumber #2:
Oh, sounds good to me.
Hol horse: Listen, granny!
I found ’em first, so get lost!
plumber #1:
Thank you very much, ma’am.
Hol horse: Put ’em down!
I told you to hurry up
and open the pipe!
if you don’t,
i’ll crack your skulls!
( Plumbers whimper )
Plumber #1: There. It’s open.
Hol horse: Move it!
( Yells )
Now die, jotaro!
♪
i won!
Just like the prediction said,
I shot the cocky bastard
at the stroke of noon.
Go get him.
Jotaro: Old man, time to get up.
( Both grunt )
Joseph: Uh, I don’t think
there’s any permanent damage.
( Avdol groans )
I only have cuts and bruises.
But polnareff,
on the other hand...
Joseph: Hmm?
polnareff: Hey,
don’t mean to be a nuisance,
but could someone
get this damn thing off of me?
( Grunting )
Hol horse: I won.
This is really gonna happen.
jotaro is
right in front of that pipe.
♪
( Polnareff sniffles )
- ( Sneezes )
- Jotaro: Ugh!
Both: What?!
Jotaro: Watch it.
( Polnareff sputters )
Sorry about that, jotaro.
i don’t know
what hol horse was thinking,
but he decided
sticking his fingers up my nose
would be the perfect way
to spend the evening.
That guy is tres disgusting.
Man, my nose still itches.
So sorry again.
hol horse:
But how’s it possible?
My bullets missed!
( Mondatta gasping )
Hol horse: What the hell?!
were you trying
to pull one over on me?
What the hell is
going on around here?!
Mondatta: I have no idea, yes!
Like I said, m-my predictions
always come true! It’s fate!
I can’t believe it.
Not once since I
started using my stand
have my predictions
ever been wrong!
Hol horse: Well, clearly there’s
a first time for everything,
’cause they’re still alive.
Not a single bullet
hit its Mark.
It’s safe to say your prediction
was totally wrong.
( Growls ) Damn you!
Announcer: Thanks for joining us
for today’s broadcast.
Be sure to tune in next time.
Now for the 12:00 news.
Both: Huh?
( Hol horse yells )
What the hell?
There’s no way in hell
it’s just now noon.
( Gasps )
I know what happened.
M-my watch is...
My watch is fast!
And that means I ended up
firing off the bullets
before it was time,
but now it is noon.
- ( Bell chiming )
- What’s that mean for us, huh?
Tell me. What the hell’s
gonna happen to us
now that we’ve
gone off script?
Mondatta: No, it can’t be.
( Gasps )
Hol horse: But where
did we get off track?
It said the bullets would go
right through jotaro’s forehead
at the stroke of noon.
Mondatta: Hol horse,
the bullets are--
hol horse: Come on.
all I need to know
is what’s gonna happen next.
( Bullets whizzing )
( Gasps )
( Mondatta gasps )
( Hol horse screams )
( Glass shatters )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Polnareff: Hey, tell me
i’m not the only one
who heard
that ear-piercing scream.
Joseph: I’m not clear
on the details,
but there’s something fishy
going on here.
But the bigger concern
is this truck.
i think we’d
better get out of here
before the cops
start showing up.
Let’s move, men.
Polnareff: But before we go,
i wanna know
where hol horse ran off to.
jotaro: I don’t know.
He disappeared for some reason.
( Grunts )
( Groans )
Avdol: Hey, if you don’t
get away from that pipe,
you’re going to get soaking wet.
You should try
to be more careful.
Jotaro: Hmph.
( Siren blaring )
Officer: Is he dead?
officer #2:
No, but he’s critical.
I couldn’t even begin to tell
you what transpired here today.
They looked him over, and it
seems as though the bullet
went through his forehead
and out the top of his head.
one centimeter lower,
and he would have been a goner.
Whew. Gotta say
that is one lucky man.
( Siren blaring )
Mondatta: In the end, it seems
my prediction was right,
which means this was
hol horse’s fate all along.
Jotaro is really something else.
How lucky can one person be?
Both my brother and hol horse
were defeated by fate.
At this point, we stand users
are wasting our time.
Master dio’s the only one
who can defeat him.
You know what, zenyatta?
hol horse,
that big buffoon of a man,
taught me that revenge
is nothing more
than a massive joke,
so i’m going
to forget about jotaro.
I have a new path in life.
I’ll use my stand’s powers
to help as many people as I can.
I’ll use them to bring
happiness to everyone.
maybe people
will start to like us,
and just maybe
our future will be brighter.
♪
I’m tired of being afraid.
Today’s the last day
I spend under a box
cowering from everyone.
I learned a lot
from this battle,
more than I thought I could.
I’m coming home now, brother.
I’m coming home to aswan
to join you.
- ( Iggy yelps )
- ( Mondatta gasps ) Eh?
Oh, my gosh, I am so sorry!
I kicked it without thinking.
I didn’t mean to hit you.
Please forgive me.
Hold on. This dog...
He looks familiar.
I pretty sure i’ve seen him
before, but where?
( Iggy growling )
( Mondatta yells )
There’s no way!
- It can’t be!
- ( Iggy growling )
Mondatta: No!
polnareff: Hey,
now that I think about it,
where’d our dumb-ass dog go?
Joseph: You talking about iggy?
I’m sure he’s scrounging around
for food somewhere.
Avdol: I’ve said
from the beginning
he wouldn’t help us
when we needed him.
Mondatta: "He should have known
it wouldn’t be so simple.
"If people could change
that easily,
life wouldn’t be so hard."
"So as fate would have it,
"mondatta joined hol horse
in the hospital,
only now he was meeker
than ever before."
Ba-dum-tss.
♪
( Singing and speaking
in Japanese )