This is the incident report
that seems most likely
to be connected to these
White‐Clad attacks.
That's right.
It's from our first job.
Sister Iris and Maki had only
just joined up with the Eighth.
We were all new.
That kinda makes me curious.
How'd the Eighth start
in the first place?
Good question‐‐I never
got around to asking about
what things were
like before I joined.
[OBI]
Hmm.
It's a long story.
But it relates to the heart
of Company Eight,
so it's worth telling.
Lieutenant, tell 'em
how we got started.
[HINAWA]
Hm?
[OBI] You're the better
talker by far, so...
Yeah, that's an order.
It's crazy.
The reports of Infernal
breakouts just keep coming.
Makes me wonder.
Maybe instead of
investigating criminals,
we could be helping
out with all that.
Infernals are the Special
Fire Force's jurisdiction.
Don't get any ideas.
Sergeant Hinawa!
[MAKI]
I'll be going now, sir.
Haven't seen her around before.
She who I think?
Lieutenant General Oze's kid.
That was Private Maki Oze.
[TOJO] She's so thin.
Is she doin' okay?
Oze works twice as
hard as her peers,
and always does more than
she's asked to in training.
At this rate, she'll flesh out
those muscles in no time.
That's impressive for
a general's daughter.
Yeah, but she's
still her father's
sheltered little princess,
and he got her in.
She's far too soft‐hearted
for this line of work.
All the effort she's putting
in will amount to nothing.
Why're you always so critical?
If she's giving this her all,
then you should help her.
[HINAWA] Wasted effort
doesn't count as effort.
She may as well be slacking.
Oh, c'mon. She's a nice kid
who's doin' her best, okay?
You always go easy
on these rookies.
[thud]
Standard USP nine‐millimeter.
Except I got it baptized.
Thought I'd take a page
from the Fire Force.
Another case of wasted effort.
Is it though?
Between a baptized gun
and one that wasn't,
which would you want
to shoot you?
Probably the baptized
gun, right?
[HINAWA]
Hm?
How about it, Hinawa?
Go visit the church.
Get your gun baptized just
to see if it feels different.
I've got a hunch that
your point of view
might change a little bit.
Well, I don't believe in
your so‐called "sun god."
No ritual can alter what happens
when a gun is discharged.
Yeah. I thought you'd
say something like that.
You're the same as ever.
You're a truly
kind person, Tojo.
Why stick with someone like me?
Honestly, man?
It's because you
aren't anywhere near
as cold‐hearted as you think.
You just bussed my tray with
yours without a second thought.
[TOJO screaming]
Tojo.
I'm turning, Hina. Shoot me!
Hurry up. Please!
While I'm still conscious!
[TOJO]
You have to shoot me! Shoot!
[screams]
Which would you want
to shoot you?
Probably the baptized
gun, right?
[thud]
[HINAWA gasps]
[gasps]
[HINAWA]
Why couldn't I do it?
Even when he begged?
[INVENTORY KEEPER A]
You're here early, Sergeant.
Just stamped your papers.
The late lieutenant's gun
is now yours, as requested.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[FIRE FIGHTER A] The Blue
Stripes have arrived!
We'll help the civilians
and contain the fire
while they put the
Infernals to rest.
Reporting in!
I've command of on‐scene
fire suppression personnel.
Akitaru Obi.
So I've been told that there
were two Infernals here.
[OBI]
Yes.
There are two,
but they're in different
locations at the moment.
The more belligerent one
is currently running
around inside our cordon.
The other one's
been pretty docile.
It's just sitting
inside a store.
I'll pass on that second one.
Yeah, that's not gonna
net us many points.
Wait, "points?"
Thanks for filling me in.
You fire fighters
can pull back now.
We'll deal with the
feisty one first.
I doubt the low point
one's going anywhere.
[FIRE SOLDIERS chuckling]
I beg your pardon,
Mr. Fire Soldier,
but my husband is
patiently enduring
the intense heat
of those flames.
Please, end his suffering
as quickly as you can.
There's an order of
precedence we have to follow.
We'll decide which Infernals
get put out first.
C'mon.
Please! Wait just a moment!
[OBI]
Excuse me.
[growls]
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you've got a
lotta soldiers here.
Seems like you could
send a couple
to put her husband to
rest without much risk.
We are professionals.
We make judgment calls based
on standards of our own.
The point standard.
Yeah, that's right.
To keep up my soldier's spirits,
I give out points based
on how dangerous
the Infernals they kill are.
To keep up their spirits?
When your job involves
snuffing out human lives,
the goal shouldn't be
to have a good time.
[FLAIL] You're not the one
risking your life here.
Just hook up your hose
and put out what's left
when we're done.
I'm so sorry. I know it
hurts, but please hold on.
I can't help you,
so try to stay strong.
Pardon, ma'am.
With your permission,
I'd be willing to step in.
I can bring your husband's
suffering to an end.
Would that be all right?
[HINAWA]
What're you planning to do?
[gasps]
Who might you be?
Takehisa Hinawa.
Sergeant with the Armed Forces.
[OBI]
This is Blue Stripes territory.
If a soldier like you or
a fire fighter like me
cuts through that tape,
we'll be severely punished.
[HINAWA]
No punishment could compare
to what the Infernal in this
building is going through.
We both know that.
So, there's nothing
to second guess here.
[OBI]
Sergeant Hinawa.
Do you have any experience
with Infernals?
[HINAWA] I aimed my gun
at a friend the other day...
...as I was watching
him turn Infernal.
But I just couldn't shoot.
I wouldn't call myself
a man of faith
by any stretch of the word.
And yet... because my gun was
unbaptized, it just felt wrong.
He really did wait patiently.
Sergeant Hinawa.
I don't think this is about
whether you believe in God.
It's about wanting to do
as much as you can
for the human being whose
life you're about to end.
[OBI] That's why we pray for
them and baptize our weapons.
You ask me, those rituals
offer a type of salvation
to those who kill
Infernals, too.
Start the prayer for us.
[screams]
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is
the soul's release.
Ashes thou wert and art.
May thy soul return...
[OBI]
I want you to know,
you're a truly kind
person, Sergeant.
[inaudible]
What you did in there
took some courage.
No, you're the courageous one.
If I hadn't seen that
you were taking action,
I doubt I would've done a thing.
Making the choice to
take action on your own
isn't really as difficult
as you'd think.
Trusting yourself is something
that comes easy to most,
but to put your faith
in someone else,
and act on that faith,
despite the personal cost,
that takes courage.
You're like a hero,
Sergeant, or a knight.
If so, then that
makes you a king.
It's settled.
I'm gonna create a Special
Fire Force company.
Once I'm in a position to do it,
I'll fight to end
human combustion.
I refuse to sit back
and do nothing
while the world burns
down around me.
It might be a while,
but when it happens,
I'll need people like you.
Soldiers who cherish
life above all else.
Whenever that time arrives,
don't hesitate to
reach out to me.
[OBI] This is our very
own fire cathedral.
[HINAWA]
About as rundown as you'd expect
for a den of outcasts.
So, am I the only crewman
you've recruited, or what?
Yeah. So far.
See, gathering people
who I know I can trust
has been a pretty
difficult task.
[sighs]
I think I've got
a line on someone.
She served under me in the army.
Puts in a lot more effort
than anyone around her.
But she wasn't really
cut out to be a soldier.
She was way too compassionate,
always thinking of
others before herself.
I'd say that makes her a
perfect fit for the Eighth.
Wow.
Way to go, Maki.
Golly.
I just thought I was recruited
because I have basic
pyrokinetic powers
and I'm strong enough
to be a meat shield.
Did you really say those
nice things, Lieutenant?
[MAKI giggles]
[MAKI]
Oh, you're so sweet.
[MAKI giggles]
That was well told. Good job.
The heart of the Eighth
hasn't changed
since the day it
was established.
For the dying Infernal,
we offer our prayers
and a dignified end.
For the living, we seek
deliverance from the flames.
There's one thing we value
above all else: Life.
We should get back to
the subject at hand now.
This report is from right
after Iris and Maki joined.
It was a hot day.
Everyone was nervous, since
it was our first call out.
[HINAWA]
The man who had gone Infernal
was wearing these
odd white clothes.
Putting him to rest was simple,
but there were several
things that didn't add up.
Take the strange
red cross we found.
The man had no family,
but the company he
had worked for
was in an awfully big
hurry to retrieve it.
We looked up that company
and found out that it's
still in business today.
It's based in Asakusa.
Company Seven's jurisdiction.
[CITIZEN A]
What's up, Beni?
[VENDOR A]
Come on by, come on by!
We've got Hoppy for cheap...
[CITIZEN B]
How goes it, Waka?
[VENDOR A] And plenty of
motsuyaki and monja!
[WOMAN A]
Benimaru!
[WOMAN A] I made some
daifuku. Take it with you.
[BENIMARU]
Huh?
I told you before, you old bat,
I don't like sweets.
[BENIMARU]
She makes too much.
Ah. Hey, Beni!
It's been a few days!
How bad d'ya miss me?
I wanna see your sweet
ass at the bar tonight.
[KANTARO laughs]
[sighs] Lemme be.
The old bat made daifuku.
If you want some,
then help yourselves.
That crumbling old fossil
makes the best daifuku ever!
If that senile crone
forgets the recipe,
she may as well just die.
[BOTH laugh]
Hinata, Hikage,
you need to listen here.
[HINATA, HIKAGE]
Whoa, there, Waka.
We're not taking any
complaints right now.
You realize they learned
all that from you, right?
Not taking any
complaints right now.
Case in point.
This is amazing.
Nothin' tastes better than
an old fossil's last hurrah!
[HIKAGE laughs]
The old bat's swan
song is delicious!
Oh, these students have
surpassed their teacher.
[KONRO groans]
By the way, Waka,
looks like we got a
message from the people
over at Company Eight.
They wanna search
our jurisdiction.
Said something about looking
for that Evangelist.
Too much trouble.
Just ignore them.
Beg your pardon, but
we're already here.
Huh?
You've got some serious nerve,
barging in unannounced
like this.
[OBI] I heard that
Captain Shinmon Benimaru
hated formalities and red tape,
so I thought I'd skip
making an appointment.
Fine, if you're here then,
you're here. Whatever.
But I don't give a damn about
this investigation of yours.
Regardless of the reason,
I can't have you disrupting
things on my turf.
The Evangelist has been
creating Infernals
through artificial means.
And there's a chance
that the White‐Clad
will target the people
of this area next.
That's coming from the
Tokyo Empire, correct?
Well, I'm not a trusting soul,
and I've never seen one of
these so‐called "White‐Clad"
turn someone into an Infernal.
[BOTH scream]
I have no reason to believe
that it's actually happening.
You might not've
seen it, but I have!
[BENIMARU] I don't care
what some imperial lapdog
thinks they saw.
And I'm especially uninterested
in hearing tall tales
from a gullible puppy.
That's funny, 'cause
I'm not interested
in taking crap from
a do‐nothing skeptic.
Captain Shinmon, is that right?
I hear you're the strongest
soldier around.
From what I've been told,
it's because you're so tough
that your town's fire brigade
was brought into the Force.
Well, I'm a tough guy, too.
I'm gonna kick your ass and
make you see things my way.
"Fires and fistfights are
the flowers of Edo," huh?
[CREWMAN A]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Someone turned Infernal?
Why'd you have to go and
jinx us like that, Waka?
Damn it.
I better not see Company
Eight here when I get back.
[BENIMARU]
Must be that way.
Who is it?
That boistrous old man, Kantaro.
[inaudible]
He was nagging me about drinking
with him just a minute ago.
Our friend Kantaro from Block
Three has turned Infernal!
[7TH CREWMEN]
Seiya! Soiya! Seiya! Soiya!
Seiya! Soiya! Seiya!
What's he planning to do?
He loves a good festival,
so let's start!
[7TH CREWMEN cheering]
What the‐‐?!
Didn't know he could fly.
What kind of power does the
captain of the Seventh have?
[BENIMARU]
There you are, you old fart!
[7TH CREWMEN]
Waka!
So many houses.
At the end of the day,
homes can always be rebuilt.
But now that Kantaro has
become an Infernal,
his life is over and there's
nothing that can change that.
What's goin' on here?
Is he igniting those fires
and controlling the flames?
I think there must be a trick
to those matoi flags he uses.
There's no trick. He started
those fires himself.
Beni can wield both
second‐generation
and third‐generation powers.
He can create his own fires
and manipulate them
as he pleases.
Unlike any other, he's a
compound Fire Soldier.
Look at this, Kantaro!
The whole town is in shambles!
You're too old to be
raisin' this kind of hell,
and you know it.
[roars]
That being said,
you always did enjoy
making a scene, right?
Way to hang in there, friend.
Thanks, young man.
You helped me see him through,
all the way to the end.
So what do you think
of what you just saw?
Did Beni's way of putting
someone to rest
seem a bit rough to you?
Your Sister's prayers
are a gift to your dead.
We destroy our town
as a gift to ours.
Everybody in our world
lives in continuous fear
of the flames of
Infernalization.
We're all looking to our deaths.
As for the people here,
if we have to die,
there's no way we'd prefer
to go out than at his hands.
The hands of Shinmon Benimaru,
the Destroyer of Asakusa.
It's too sweet.