[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that
long, morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
Anybody home?
[SHINRA] This'll be a good
chance for me to see
how far I can go against
a company captain.
That said, I've got no chance
if I can't deal with
that weird power.
It ends for you here.
[SHINRA]
Huh?
[ANGELS]
'Cause the Fifth Angels Three...
...have come for thee!
[NUNS groaning]
[HIBANA]
All right, Iris.
Be a good girl and watch your
allies from the Eighth burn.
[IRIS]
Why are you doing this?
Maybe you should ask
that god of salvation
you're still pledged to.
There are just two ways
you can live in this world.
You can burn others
or you can be burnt.
Think of all our Sisters.
The way their bodies shriveled
as the flames consumed them.
[NUNS groaning]
It certainly is lucky that I'm
a third‐generation pyrokinetic.
I'll never be consumed
by cruel flames
because I decided to
become like them instead.
I'll give purpose to the
worthless gravel beneath me
by burning it to fuel
my rise to the top.
Because that's what
true happiness is.
Whatever you gain
from living like that
could never be called happiness!
Spout those empty
platitudes all you want.
You're just waiting
to burn. Ignorant fool!
[SHINRA]
Get away from the Sister.
[gasps]
You've got a hero to fight.
[HIBANA] He'll be the first
of your friends I burn.
Sit tight and watch.
You have to run, Shinra!
As strong as you are, you still
can't defeat Captain Hibana!
[SHINRA]
It's all right. I'll be fine.
This won't go like it
did the last time.
You fool.
It seems you have
a short memory.
A hunk of gravel like you
doesn't stand a chance
of harming me.
There's no way to
know until I try.
Shinra, no!
You really must be gravel.
So eager to lie beneath my feet.
My head's spinning. Damn.
Ah!
What have you... done to me?
It's called heat syncope.
[SHINRA]
What's that mean?
Simple.
Your body has been enveloped
by a miniature heatwave
created by me.
[SHINRA]
Huh?
[HIBANA] This causes your
blood vessels to dilate
and your blood pressure to drop,
which means less blood
flow to your poor brain.
And that causes vertigo.
After storming in here and
dubbing yourself a hero,
you ended up getting taken
out by a bit of heat.
It's quite amusing.
Vertigo?
That's all it is?
I see now. You're sayin' this
is all in my head, right?
[HIBANA]
Huh?
What do you mean,
"all in your head"?
Look at yourself,
you can barely even stand.
I feel short of breath,
dizzy, and weak,
but now I realize
it's only a delusion.
Looks like you're just
trying to grin and bear it.
But if you'd like to talk
about yourself and delusions,
why don't we start with
the ridiculous idea
that you're a hero?
Let's think this over.
I'm dizzy in my head,
so I'm dizzy for real.
Well, hey, guess what?
I'm a hero in my head, too!
[HIBANA]
This is absurd.
How are you even standing?
[SHINRA]
Compared to the drills
Lieutenant Hinawa
put me through,
this is a stroll
through the park.
Fine, then.
There's no sport in burning a
man who can't defend himself.
Come forth, Clematis.
I shall grant you a beautiful
death by my flowers.
Sister, after all
this time, you‐‐
Just shut your mouth and watch.
[gasps]
But‐‐
[SHINRA]
I might be wrong,
but I think you're the
who's delusional, Princess.
[HIBANA]
Say what?
[SHINRA] Don't worry.
It's your lucky day.
'Cause Smack‐that‐Princess‐to‐
Her‐Senses‐Man is here for ya!
And what delusion are you
planning to save me from?
Not sure, but you look
like you're in pain.
You know nothing about me!
[chuckles]
[HIBANA] So your dizziness
is all in your head, is it?
I think we'd find that
a lot more convincing
if you'd stop falling
all over yourself!
Damn it!
Honestly, how can you
call yourself a hero?
If you must close
your eyes to reality,
then I guess I'll have
to burn off your eyelids.
Sakura!
[HIBANA] That's a funny
dance you're doing.
Don't you enjoy
the flower petals?
Sister, you have to stop this!
You could ask your
God to make me stop.
Oh, wait.
Could it be that you've
realized your God isn't real?
And for the record,
neither are heroes.
No, that isn't true.
If you pray with all your heart,
you can find real comfort.
There are people who
have been saved by it!
[HIBANA] You know damn well
that isn't real salvation.
[IRIS]
Then are you saying that there's
no such thing as salvation?
[HIBANA]
Sure there is.
You outsmart others and exploit
them to your own ends
until you've risen so high
that when you look down
at the foolish masses below,
you see nothing but gravel.
Gravel. Impotent gravel.
And then, safe in the knowledge
that you're better than
the riff‐raff, you smile.
The only salvation
I need comes from
the wealth and status
I gain with power.
How so?
You prayed with us every day
back at the convent, remember?
All of us prayed. And what
did we get as our reward?
[bell tolling]
[HIBANA] The convent was
a refuge for us orphans.
[HIBANA] We were taught to
devote ourselves to God.
I was probably the only one who
didn't take it all seriously.
And then, that day...
[NUNS groaning]
[HIBANA] The other Sisters
started burning away.
Every last one of them,
except you and me.
They were all devout nuns,
who served God far better
than I ever cared to.
Don't you see? Kind‐hearted
devotion never pays.
The fact that I'm still alive
while those nuns are dead
proves that more than anything.
You can only get stronger
by pursuing selfish gain.
And if you're hoping
to find salvation
without getting stronger,
why, you may as well
ask God for the moon.
[HIBANA] Salvation is
reserved for humans.
So by what right does
gravel hope to claim it?
[SHINRA]
Princess Hibana.
You're a victim of
the flames, too, right?
[HIBANA] Our cardboard
hero, standing again.
I know how you feel,
at least a little bit.
All the sweetest things in my
life went up in flames as well.
[HIBANA]
You'll never know how I feel.
Sakura Blizzard.
[screaming]
This time, I'll make you stay
down like the gravel you are!
[SHINRA]
You will never keep me down.
But the heat syncope.
[SHINRA] I'll get up
as often as it takes.
Convinced I can win every time.
'Cause I have to help you.
Huh? Have you lost your mind?
What're you talking about?
[SHINRA] Listen,
I'm about to lay you out.
And that, along with
the rest of this...
...is for your own good!
Well, if all you want
is what's best for me,
then go ahead and burn already!
Lie down and let the flames
do what they do best!
Fire does more than burn people.
It offers us warmth
when we're freezing,
and when we're surrounded by
darkness, it lights the way.
There's no such thing as a
hero in this wretched world!
[SHINRA] It might be true
that there aren't any yet...
...but that's all the more
reason for me to become one!
You're gonna be okay.
Or else my name isn't... Smack‐
that‐Princess‐to‐Her‐Senses Man!
[NUNS gasping, chattering]
[SISTER A]
Look at that one!
Wow, all of them are so pretty.
That's really amazing,
Sister Hibana.
[HIBANA]
Heh! Thanks, Sister Clematis.
Look here.
[NUNS gasp]
If I put a droplet of sodium
solution onto one of them,
the flame will react.
Watch.
Wow. It looks so cool!
This one is copper.
[HIBANA] Sister Sakura,
this one's for you.
It's calcium this time.
[HIBANA] I also have potassium,
strontium, and a few others.
They're all so
wonderful to look at.
I know. Flames are incredibly
beautiful, don't you think?
[SISTER CLEMATIS]
Uh‐huh!
[SISTER SAKURA] Sister Hibana,
I wanna be like you someday.
You can make fire, plus
you're good at science stuff.
[gasps]
Hello, Iris!
Don't hide behind the corner.
Come out and have a closer look.
[gasps]
‐‐Oh, uh.
‐‐Careful.
They might be in
the shape of flowers,
but each is a burning flame.
They can hurt you.
[SISTER SUMIRE]
My goodness!
What's going on here,
Sister Hibana?
Are you playing with
your fire again?
Come along now, everyone.
Back to the chapel, all right?
[NUNS]
Okay. Thank you, Sister Sumire.
[SISTER SUMIRE]
As for you, Sister Hibana.
Your power is a gift
from the great Sol‐‐
it's not meant
to be played with.
What's more, if you were to
wield these flames carelessly,
they could become
very dangerous.
But I'm being very
careful with them,
so it shouldn't be an issue.
[SISTER SUMIRE] And there
you go, arguing again.
Back to the chapel with you.
[HIBANA]
Fine.
Sorry.
But, Sister Hibana? I, um...
You okay?
[IRIS]
It's just‐‐ Well, uh.
I'd, um... I'd like to see
those flowers again.
Pretty please.
Sure, I'll show them to you once
you get over your shyness, okay?
Wait, do you really mean it?
[HIBANA]
The smell of burning bodies.
The inhuman screams
of the dying.
Searing pain. Anguish.
Lives crumbling to ash.
[HIBANA] Flames are incredibly
beautiful, don't you think?
[HIBANA] As if something like
fire could ever be pretty.
Let's go.
If we don't, then we'll
only burn up beside them.
As if a power like mine
could've come from God.
Fire comes from hell itself,
so if I wield it,
I know what that makes me.
And a devil should
act like a devil.
[IRIS]
Hey, wait.
Where are you going, Sister?
[HIBANA]
Away.
[HIBANA] Don't let
yourself be burnt, Iris.
[HIBANA]
People. Flames.
Whatever I find, I'll exploit.
[HIBANA] That's just a
taste of my findings.
Meet my conditions
and you get the rest.
First, I want the
rank of captain.
Furthermore, I want
funding and a lab
from which I can carry
on my experiments.
Why do all this?
We children at the convent
didn't have any parents.
But we did have our big sister.
She was beautiful and clever,
and she had mastered fire.
And when I was lonely
but too scared to speak,
my hero called to me.
I didn't have anyone
like that, though.
All I had to prop myself
up were my flames,
and then I found out they
couldn't be trusted, either.
[HIBANA]
I don't have anything left now.
If ya want a hero,
there's one right here.
Just look to the skies
and cry out my name!
I'll come and save you anytime!
But that's ridiculous.
You're under no obligation
to help me at all,
especially not after
what I've done.
But I don't have to be obliged.
If you say you need me,
I come running.
'Cause that's what heroes do.
Whatever the case,
you defeated me.
So I don't intend to
fight you any longer.
[IRIS]
Mh‐hm. Mh‐hm.
What do you think? Did I
overcome my shyness a bit?
How is that even a question now?
I can't believe you waltzed
into my base all by yourself.
Of course I did. I wanted
to see your flowers again.
They're pretty.
I did make you a
promise, didn't I?
They're irises.
Yeah. How do you like them?
[IRIS]
I love you, Sister!
[gunshots]
[CREWMAN groaning]
[CREWMAN A] The guy in
glasses, he's a monster!
Looks like the Eighth Company
has more or less
completely routed us.
[SHINRA, IRIS]
Must've been the Lieutenant.
[HIBANA sighs]
[HIBANA] How am I gonna explain
this mess to the higher‐ups?
For that matter, what should
I tell this spilt gravel?
Think Captain Obi had a plan.
He was gonna try and set
everything up to look like
a nocturnal joint
training exercise.
But you flew in before he could
lay the groundwork
for that, right?
If you keep charging
ahead like that,
you're bound to screw
up eventually.
I think I've come up
with a good solution.
What if we smooth things over
with a fun little dinner party
between the Fifth and
Eighth Companies?
[SHINRA]
That seems a bit outlandish.
[HIBANA]
And yet, it just might work.
[SHINRA]
Uh. Huh?
There are times when
the most ridiculous ruses
are the ones people are
least likely to suspect.
I can tell everybody
that to test
the fighting strength
of Company Five,
I planned a surprise
attack drill,
asking Company Eight
to play the bad guys.
Shinra, would you mind rounding
up the rest of the Eighth
and filling them in
on the new situation?
You sure are being
cooperative now.
Well, yeah.
That's because I've
taken a liking to you.
[SHINRA]
Uh.
[grunts]
[OBI] Chief, I know
it's ahead of schedule,
but we've begun our
investigation of the Fifth.
There might be violence,
so make what
preparations you can.
Hinawa, you read me?
That's right.
Took time to set things up,
but I'm ready to give
you some backup.
Huh?
It's over?