[ANNOUNCER A] The Meteorological
Agency has issued a warning
for the Fourth District
of the Tokyo Empire's
northern area at 1300.
Record‐setting rain is expected
in a short period of time.
Any persons heading
into this area,
please exercise
care and caution.
If at all possible,
avoid the District until
the danger has passed.
[OPERATOR A] Switching all
monitors to trace mode.
Canceling standby mode.
Identity confirmed.
Synchronization of GIS
and tracking ID complete.
[OPERATOR B]
Error of indication 0.083,
within acceptable range.
[OPERATOR A] Fire Defense
Agency alarm control system
activation signal confirmed.
[OPERATOR B] Continuing to
monitor. Forwarding...
[OPERATOR A] Subject has
entered Akihabra District.
Don't forward it.
I'm enjoying the confusion.
[OPERATOR A]
Commencing alarm system hacking.
[OPERATOR C] Kanda Firefighters
requesting instructions.
Tell them to stand down.
Isn't Kanda under Company
Eight's jurisdiction?
[MEMBER A grunts]
Gravel doesn't get
to have opinions.
Besides, they asked a question.
It was only polite to
give them an answer.
[ringing]
New message from
Haijima Industries.
[MEMBER B]
Owie!
I'll worry about it later.
I don't take orders
from the main office.
I've got a research
subject to catch.
The Fifth is heading out.
I don't care if we have to
step on the Eighth's toes,
we will secure that Infernal.
[OPERATOR B] Object approaching
subject at high speed!
[MEMBER C]
Owie!
[OPERATOR A] From the Adolla
pattern, I believe it is
a third‐generation Fire
Soldier from the Eighth.
Gravel from the
Eighth's interfering?
That's all we have for now.
Today's Amaterasu
operational rate is normal.
This concludes our broadcast.
Have a pleasant day.
Látom.
No news on yesterday's incident.
Nothin' about the Rookie Games
snafu or this Joker guy.
Seems suspicious
not to mention it.
The Fire Force have
something to hide?
[SHINRA]
Captain Obi's the key.
If I stick with him,
I'll get closer to the truth
about human combustion,
and about the day
I lost Mom and Sho.
[knocking]
Sorry to interrupt,
but I've got the results.
The analysis on the
substance Joker used
to blow up the
training facility.
They examined its components.
The main one is Infernal ashes.
Those ashes...
belonged to an Infernal?
Turning the remains of the
dead into an explosive?
Sick bastard.
[IRIS sighs]
[IRIS]
The flames of the original sin.
[SHINRA] I meant to,
but I couldn't bring myself
to tell them about Sho.
Wake up!
Quit looking like you're
about to die of boredom.
It's making it hard
for me to work.
[phone ringing]
This is Arthur Boyle,
valiant knight and
lord of Camelot.
How can I help you?
I am so sorry about that.
Special Fire Force
Company Eight.
Ah, of course. Certainly.
[MAKI]
Yes.
A dog?
Right. I understand. Can you
please tell me the address?
[SHINRA]
Hey.
Yeah, what?
Why did you decide to
become a Fire Soldier?
Easy, 'cause I'm a knight.
[MAKI]
We'll be there right away.
All right, look alive, you two.
We've got a report of a
dog stuck up in a tree.
Think you brave soldiers
can help get him down?
Go and rescue a dog?
That kinda sounds like a job
for regular firefighters.
[MAKI] We get calls
mistaking Fire Soldiers
for firefighters all the time.
What's the big deal?
I mean, it's not like you guys
are making much headway here.
Go on. I'll take care of
the rest of this for you.
[gasps]
Oh, I'll do it.
Tell me where to go.
It oughta be easy.
I'll just fly up
and grab the mutt.
Yeah, so... that's
not exactly a dog.
So much as a dog‐faced human.
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Goodness.
[MAMORU‐KUN] Thank you
very much, young man.
[SHINRA]
What were you doing up a tree?
[MAMORU‐KUN] I was in the
shopping district for an event,
passing out balloons,
and some local college kids
"hip hip hoorayed" me.
[STUDENTS]
"Hooray."
Why would they do
something like that?
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Do you remember the killings
carried out by that firefighter?
[SHINRA]
Huh?
[MAMORU‐KUN]
The man's name was Miyamoto.
He killed four people
for the fun of it.
Folks have resented the
Fire Defense Agency
and firefighters themselves
since the murders.
Sometimes, they take their
aggression out on us like this.
So what ended up happening
to that firefighter?
[MAMORU‐KUN] His verdict is
scheduled to be announced today.
According to the scuttlebutt,
he'll be found not guilty
for psychiatric reasons.
Setsuo Miyamoto, this court
hereby finds you not guilty.
[PEOPLE shouting]
[MIYAMOTO] Whaddaya know.
I got away with it.
Pretty easily, too.
Makes sense.
This country'd be up a creek
if they convicted a
firefighter of murder.
[MIYAMOTO screaming]
[MIYAMOTO]
Somebody help!
Put me out! Put me out!
Get an extinguisher!
Throw a blanket! Oh, no. No!
[MIYAMOTO screaming]
[MIYAMOTO laughing]
[MIYAMOTO]
How the tables have turned.
I think I'll grab a flagpole
and make a big
human shish kebab!
[laughing]
[PEOPLE screaming]
Got a little question
for ya, Judge.
Who do you think you are to
decide what fate I deserve?
I don't understand. I just
declared you innocent.
[MIYAMOTO]
Ah, shut your mouth!
I'll do the judging
now, Your Honor!
[alarm blaring]
Captain Obi, listen!
About the Infernal in Taito
Ward, Ueno District‐‐
He still has a sense of self?
Hmm...
[HIBANA chuckles]
[HIBANA]
Fascinating.
I want him, whatever it takes.
[MEMBER A]
Owie!
To the control room, quickly!
[HINAWA]
Where are Shinra and Arthur?
[ANNOUNCER B]
An Infernal has appeared.
Emergency vehicles
are about to deploy.
We request that all
civilian motorists
pull to the side of the
road and clear a path
so they can safely pass.
An emergency dispatch?
[SHINRA gasps]
[SHINRA]
The Matchbox!
Shinra. Arthur. I know you
punks are around here.
Wandering the streets
without permission.
When we get back,
I am going to redefine
your understanding
of the word "punishment."
[BOTH whimper]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry! I just couldn't...
Hey, Maki? Is something
the matter?
[SHINRA]
Sorry, Mamoru,
but that's all the
help I can give you.
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Látom.
See ya soon, Arthur!
I'm going on ahead!
Hey. What do you
think you're doing?
I'm coming with you.
Hi‐ho, Silver!
No way. Are you
serious right now?
What's wrong with you?
Oh, whatever.
Oh, hey. It's you two.
Wait, this is a public road.
You shouldn't fly here.
Yeah.
I'll move higher soon, but could
you tell me about that Infernal?
[HINAWA]
It was a murder defendant.
He was being tried at
Ueno District Court.
He's attacking
bystanders as we speak.
You two hurry ahead and
help out at the scene, okay?
Yes, sir!
Saving lives should
be your top priority!
Understood!
[whimpering]
[LAWYER A]
I'm your lawyer, remember?!
I've been on your
side all this time!
"It's dangerous.
Civilians should evacuate."
I used to say that all
the time as a firefighter.
It was my pleasure,
saving you from that
sickening courthouse.
You could say I saved your life,
which would mean your
life belongs to me now.
[LAWYER A whimpers]
And if your life belongs to me,
then I get to do whatever
I want to with it, right?
[SHINRA]
Let go!
God save me.
What the hell's your‐‐?
[MIYAMOTO]
What the hell?
What the hell's your
problem, ya crazy punks?
Our mascot friend Mamoru
got hip‐hip‐hoorayed
into a tree because of you!
Yeah, right!
Wait, that's your beef?
[MIYAMOTO] You're Special
Fire Soldiers, right?
So when you murder someone,
you get praised for
"saving the day."
Must be nice.
Good, we made it in time.
Sputter Comet!
Sputter Comet, I'm so sorry.
[OBI]
How can he still speak?
He's fully transformed.
When someone has a strong
will and attachment to life,
some of their traits
can survive the change.
I've never seen it
go this far though.
[MIYAMOTO] I don't see
any way to escape this.
All right, fine! I surrender!
[SHINRA]
What?
If you're not just a gang
of self‐righteous murderers,
you'll let me off, won't you?
I was found "not
guilty" at my trial,
so you can't kill me.
It's against the law! Right?
[gunshot]
[HINAWA] You aren't wrong,
but I'm not so good‐natured
as to forgive scum like you.
You'll kill me even
if I don't fight.
Whelp, that settles it‐‐
you are just murderers!
[MIYAMOTO laughing]
This isn't good.
If you guys get to go
around killing Infernals,
then I'm gonna go
around killing humans!
[SHINRA]
What should we do?
[OBI]
Go on ahead, Shinra.
You're the only one fast
enough to catch up to him.
Yeah, but, sir, he's self‐aware,
so should I still‐‐?
The fact is, he's
no longer human.
But even so, I get how you feel.
If I may, sir.
Shinra.
Pay no attention to
the words it says.
Dispose of that thing.
On the double.
Right!
[SHINRA]
Dispose of. Put to rest.
This is still a sentient being.
[OBI]
Hinawa. I'm sorry.
[HINAWA]
It's fine.
That needed to be said,
but not by our shining light.
[SHINRA]
If I back down from this,
then more innocent people
are going to get hurt.
[SHINRA]
So I'll do it!
I'll put him to rest!
[CITIZENS chattering]
[CITIZEN A]
It's an Infernal!
This city's startin' to feel
like a great big box o' toys.
Who should I play with first?
[MIYAMOTO]
Hm?
Hm?!
Where do you get off
interrupting my good time, kid?
Do you have any idea
how many people I saved
in my firefighter days?
Now that I've turned Infernal,
it's only fitting
I should kill a few.
But you killed people as
a firefighter, too, right?
Guess basic math is too much
for a dumb grunt like you.
That isn't even close
to the number I saved.
Who the hell is this guy?
I don't understand.
How are you this strong?
[MIYAMOTO]
You're some kind of devil.
I'm no devil.
I'm a brave hero!
I believe I just observed
a second Adolla Burst
coming from that
rookie Fire Soldier.
That rookie's the more
valuable specimen.
But for now, let's
focus on capturing
that self‐aware Infernal alive.
Retrieve him at once!
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke
is the soul's release.
[MIYAMOTO]
No! Please! Don't do this!
Hold on a second!
The Sister isn't here
to pray for you,
so you'll have to settle for me.
Ashes thou wert and art.
Wait, please, no!
Don't kill me! I'm scared.
Can't you at least let
me meet my end
to the sound of a
Sister's prayer of peace!
Please!
Whatever, I guess that's fine.
The Sister and the others should
catch up with us before long.
Stay still and repent
till they get here.
'Kay. That's what I'll do.
[MIYAMOTO snarls]
I doubt a soul like
yours can be saved.
You aren't anyone's hero.
You're just a
half‐cocked wannabe!
Shut your mouth!
You've lied enough.
I'm putting you to rest.
I am the Captain of Special
Fire Force Company Five,
known as Princess Hibana.
The Fifth will handle
this Infernal's disposal.
What the hell did you put on me?
Let me go!
[HIBANA]
Take him away!
[CREWMAN A]
Ma'am!
Hold on! The Eighth is
already taking care of this.
Your help isn't needed,
so get out of here.
You miss the part
where I gave my rank?
Don't defy my orders.
You might be their captain,
but you aren't mine!
Damn you.
What did you do to me?
You pathetic lump of
Eighth Company gravel.
Don't you know that your place
is on the ground
beneath my feet?
The only sound I care
to hear from you
is the crunch, crunch,
crunch of my heels
being pressed into your back.
Now lick my shoe.
I get that you're tryin'
to put me in my place,
but isn't this
going a little far?
Do as you're told
and lick my shoe.
I'm trying to talk
to you seriously!
[chuckles]
[HIBANA]
Hold him down!
[ANGELS]
The Fifth Angels Three are here.
Ready for action.
[KISHIRI]
Out of the way! Move it!
Hey, you!
Fire Soldiers are supposed
to keep people safe.
Have you dirtbags at the
Fifth forgotten that?
C'mon, it's not like we
used the brat for kindling.
We'd have to dry him out first.
Don't even crack jokes
about burning children.
Not ever.
Oh?
I'm about to show you what
a Fire Soldier should be.
Come at me, Company Five!
You're up against
Shinra Kusakabe,
Second Class Fire
Soldier from the Eighth!
[HIBANA]
This should be fun.
[OBI]
What happened?
[HIBANA]
It's unusual for an Infernal
to be as lucid as this one.
Simply killing him
would be a waste.
Our research team
will make use of him.
You must know you're in
the Eighth's jurisdiction.
Yet it feels like you're
trying to call the shots.
[HIBANA] Legally,
this man has been deceased
since the moment he transformed.
You could extinguish him
and return him to ash,
but you'll agree that this
corpse would be easier
to study in its current state.
And the Eighth is
a newer company.
I'm told that you've yet
to recruit a science team.
This is quite the rare specimen.
If solving the mystery of human
combustion is a goal we share,
then you should
want this Infernal
to be researched by the Fifth.
Can I take that as a promise
that you'll share the results
of your research with us?
Oh, absolutely!
[OBI]
Very well.
I'll leave the Infernal
in your custody.
[KISHIRI]
Someone's scared.
Huh?
I hear you're a powerless
nobody, Captain.
So it's no wonder
you backed down.
The mayor of Loserville.
You better watch your
mouth, or else.
[SHINRA]
You wanna fight, punk?
Oh, dear me, I've pissed off
Captain Nobody's
Second‐Class lackies.
Shinra! Arthur! Break it up!
[SHINRA, ARTHUR,
KISHIRI shouting]
[KISHIRI grunts]
[BOTH]
Uhh.
[humming]
[grunts]
A quick warning.
If a brave little firefighter
should stick his nose
where it doesn't belong,
he'll run the risk of being
extinguished himself.
Well, thanks for the tip.
It sounds like I've been blowin'
smoke in somebody's face.
Thing is, my flame
is Company Eight's,
and it won't go out easy.
[chuckles]
[HIBANA] Special Fire Force
Company Five, we're leaving.