[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that long,
morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
Huh?
Sister.
[gasps] I, um‐‐
Crap, my bad.
[SHINRA]
Was she crying?
I really am sorry for intruding.
Oh, no. You're okay.
I'm not used to people
coming through this early.
Anyway, take care with
your training, Shinra.
Thanks, I'll do that.
[IRIS]
Well, see ya later.
[SHINRA
Hey. Uh, Sister?
Thought I'd ask:
Is something bothering you?
[SHINRA]
I'm happy to help if I can.
It's why I took this job.
Thank you for your concern.
[OBI] After the dust‐up you
had with them yesterday,
this is probl'y obvious, but
Company Five can't be trusted.
We're looking into
their affairs,
and it could come to blows.
That's impressive, sir.
Is this a new training regimen
you've come up with
or some kind of performance art?
Hinawa!
Recall that our primary
objective is to protect people
by fighting Infernals and
putting them to rest.
However, we can't
forget that the Eighth
has a hidden objective:
To investigate suspicious crew
members within other companies
and oppose the ones
guilty of misconduct.
It's just as the captain said...
[SHINRA]
I'm so distracted by his cap
that I can't hear
a word he's saying.
[HINAWA]
...Company Five lies squarely...
More of those wretched griffins.
Come to attack my
castle again, eh?
Someday you'll be rust
on Excalibur's blade.
[SHINRA] Do you even understand
how your blade works?
Yeah, how about you put a lid
on that knightly temper of yours
and leave those adorable
"griffins" alone?
There are wildlife protection
laws for a reason, ya know.
It's kinda funny hearing
you tell someone else
to control their temper.
You have a point.
Ninety percent of the time,
Maki's just as cool‐headed
as she is beautiful.
It's a real shame about
the other ten percent.
I'm trying, okay?
[SHINRA, IRIS gasp]
No idle chatter.
We're in the middle of an
important meeting here.
Shut your mouths and focus.
Hey, Lieutenant,
I know you're kidding,
but could you please not
point your gun at us?
[HINAWA] What the hell made
you think I was kidding?
[SHINRA screams]
Látom.
Somebody get a doctor!
My leg! It hurts!
Huh?
Less than it should, though.
No way. An airgun?
No. It's very real.
Lieutenant Hinawa is a
second‐generation Fire Soldier,
the same as I am.
So he can't create fires,
but he is able to control
them once they ignite.
He weakened the
gunpowder's explosion
so the bullet would hit you
with non‐lethal force.
Fire Soldiers are versatile.
Hard to predict.
Unlike the Infernals we fight,
humans use all sorts of tactics.
You should all keep
your wits about you
when you fight them.
Excepting Arthur, of course,
since he has none.
[ARTHUR chuckles]
Perhaps I'll get some
when I slay this dragon.
You've got quite the
imagination, don't you?
Your training begins now.
I'll drill you punks
into the floor.
You're way too
focused on my fists.
Study your opponent's
whole body!
Listen, Lieutenant.
The thing is,
someone in the Fifth
joked about burning civilians
and I can't let that slide.
What's the deal with
that captain of theirs?
[HINAWA] Princess Hibana is a
third‐generation Fire Soldier.
She started out as a
recruit from Haijima
and shot up the ranks
with astonishing speed.
It looks like she did this
through illegal
research on Infernals.
All while selling
off her findings.
And these findings,
do you think they might
have anything to do
with human combustion?
She at least discovered
something big enough
to turn a nobody into
a captain overnight.
Whatever that might be, I'm sure
she'll have it documented.
We'll search their base
through force if we must.
Your feet and Arthur's
plasma can help with that.
Forget the documents.
I'm in it just to smash them.
[MIYAMOTO screaming]
No more!
It hurts so bad.
I'm beggin' you, stop!
And why should I?
You're gravel! Just gravel!
[MIYAMOTO screaming]
[HIBANA] Stop whining
and shut your mouth.
I'm talking to your body.
If there's anything about
you I don't know yet,
it'll tell me soon.
Those who aren't me
are just gravel,
and that most certainly
goes for you.
So why don't you pave
the way to my happiness?
Repulsive dung.
You gotta stop!
Keep that up
and it'll come out!
What do I care if you scream?
Your pain's meaningless to me!
Because you're just dung
strewn with gravel,
and I'm a powerful,
beautiful princess!
[HIBANA laughing]
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is
the soul's release.
Ashes thou wert and art,
may thy soul return...
...to the great flame of fire.
Látom.
[SHINRA]
That smile was strained.
Of all people, I should know.
Maybe it has to do
with the Fifth.
Hey, quick question.
D you know if something's
going on with the Sister?
What's that?
The princess has named me
commander of the order?
Guess that dumb imagination of
yours runs 24/7, doesn't it?
So what's the deal? You think
the princess is in peril?
Will you please stop calling
the Sister a princess?
For real. You stopped with Maki.
That's because
Maki's an ogress‐‐
Hey, you guys awake?
[ARTHUR snores]
[MAKI]
Uh?
Good evening, Maki. What's up?
I was wondering if one of you
knew where Sister Iris was.
[SHINRA]
Huh?
Apologies.
[5TH SOLDIER A]
It's fine.
But what's a Sister doing
here at this hour?
[IRIS] I was actually hoping
to meet with your captain.
[5TH SOLDIER A]
Uh. Doesn't seem likely.
Say that Iris has
come to see her,
and I think her response
might surprise you.
Is there something you wanted,
my little Miss Have‐not?
[IRIS] I'm not sure what
exactly you're doing,
but from what I've heard,
it sounds really dangerous.
Furthermore, it's clear
that your research
is corrupt and blasphemous.
Are you defying the
great Sol on purpose?
Sister, please.
[HIBANA]
You've got some nerve
wearing that habit
in front of me!
[IRIS gasps]
Why? I don't understand!
The Sisters are used
by the Fire Force
as nothing more than
window‐dressing.
And you've devoted your
life to that nonsense?
Looks like you're just as
foolish as you've always been.
Don't you talk to me about
your "great god Sol."
You're praying to
the ghost of a dream.
There's no god in this country.
Hell. There's no god
in this whole world.
Although there are a
few devils like myself.
[IRIS]
Devils.
Using you as bait,
I'll lure the Eighth here
and grind them into dust.
No!
[alarm blaring]
[5TH SOLDIER B] What was that?
Some kind of mortar?
[5TH SOLDIER C]
Think it's human,
but they came from the sky.
Who the hell are you?
I'm a hero, of course.
But specifically, I'm part
of Company Eight.
You can call me Save‐Sister‐
Iris‐by‐Crushing‐the‐Fifth‐Man.
Pardon, Lieutenant!
But isn't what we're doing
kinda reckless and illegal?
We believe the Fifth
has been carrying out
some pretty shady
research at this facility,
so I doubt they'll file
any police reports.
[HINAWA] Use those devil
feet to find the Sister.
Maki and I'll handle
things here.
You're gonna take on all
these guys by yourselves?
Start tearing things up
inside as fast as you can.
That'll give us some
breathing room.
Go!
Yes, sir.
You go, too, Arthur.
We'll watch your back!
Just don't forget to watch
your own back, Lieutenant.
Here he comes!
[5TH SOLDIER C gasps]
[5TH SOLDIER D yells]
He's fast!
[ARTHUR]
Do not discount.
That was the flat side.
[5TH SOLDIER E yells]
We can't just watch! Get him!
You won't escape my discipline,
so don't you dare start running!
[FIRE FORCE SOLDIERS yelling]
[5TH SOLDIER G]
Run for it!
[MAKI]
Not that this is anything new,
but I feel like you show
more mercy to Infernals
than you do to people
sometimes, Lieutenant.
[HINAWA] I didn't join
the Special Fire Force,
I joined Captain Obi's
Company Eight.
I did it 'cause I wanted
to knock some heads,
and force certain idiots
to listen to reason.
You should start
knocking heads, too.
Knock 'em around
until someone gives up
that research data on
spontaneous combustion.
I left the Military and joined
up with the Special Fire Force
against my father's wishes
because I'd rather save
people than fight them.
So I'm not too keen on
man‐to‐man combat.
[HINAWA]
Didn't seem that way
when you hit that
rookie from the Fifth.
[MAKI] That was just a tap.
It doesn't count.
I have to admit, that Devil's
quick when he wants to be.
Wish I could see
which way he went.
Look at that.
The Devil's footprints.
[CONEHEAD chuckles]
I take it that you're
trying to follow
the Devil's footprints as well.
[ARTHUR] It's dangerous here.
Back to your farm, old man.
Lest your head be
damaged even worse.
[CONEHEAD] I can't allow
you to snoop around
my company's base.
I'll roast you alive.
Not you again.
[CONEHEAD]
By administering a special drug
I've been developing,
I've boosted this
Infernal's firepower.
I'm quite pleased to have had
such a fine specimen
to work with.
[ARTHUR]
We meet again, Manslayer.
By this sword, you'll soon...
By this very sword‐‐
This sword will soon...
[KISHIRI]
Those punks from the Eighth
are way too full of themselves.
[HINAWA]
What's that?
Crap. Stay back, Lieutenant!
[MAKI]
That was some real firepower.
'Course it is. Damn nobody.
[KISHIRI] I just blow
some flammable gas
into my oxygen‐free bubble gum,
send it over to my target,
and pop the bubble.
When the flammable gas
hits fresh oxygen...
...it goes boom.
And that's the magic behind
Toru Kishiri's Backdraft
Bubblish Gum!
Another. Another! Another!
Hey. Can you see where
they're coming from?
From inside that warehouse.
I believe the target's
just around the corner.
Though I can't be sure.
[HINAWA]
I can work with that.
Oh, gimme a break. What
the hell're you aiming at?
I use the sparks
they create on impact
to adjust each bullet's path.
Uh‐oh.
[screaming]
How pathetic.
You'd need way more than
that to stop our rookies.
Come on, let's persuade
these crewmen to tell us
where the documents are.
Right.
[ANGEL A]
Hold it!
The Fifth Angels Three are here.
‐‐Let's fight!
‐‐Attack!
[CONEHEAD] Have you made
your peace yet, boy?
The fact that I've found
you here all by yourself
tells me the Eighth
is as undermanned
as our intel suggested.
The Infernal I have
fortified through science
will soon reduce you to cinders.
He's a cutting‐edge weapon
that can condense his fire
into one small point,
then release it!
I don't wanna see
one trace of a body.
That isn't gonna be a problem.
'Cause thanks to that drug,
the fire inside my
body is surging now!
See for yourself!
I'm about ready to explode!
That was close.
What's goin' on here?
Tryin' to cook some
Knight Teriyaki?
But you don't have any armor,
and I don't have any sauce!
[ARTHUR] I alight upon
this scorched red Earth.
Clad in a raiment
of glorious gold!
[MIYAMOTO] Huh? Then I guess
I'll make tempura!
Come on, why even fight?
I'm a knight.
[static crackles]
[HIBANA]
Status report?
[5TH SOLDIER J] The Angels are
fighting Hinawa and Maki.
Arthur's up against
the Infernal.
No one's seen Obi yet,
but he should be near.
[HIBANA] Moths do love
their flames, don't they?
Burn the lot of them and
leave no trace behind.
The truth, the intrigue
behind spontaneous combustion,
it was found through
our research.
I won't let gravel
steal it from us.
Are you sure you're
a Fire Soldier?
'Cause you're not putting up
much of a fight right now.
What's wrong,
ya scared or somethin'?
[chuckles]
[MIYAMOTO] I can see through
your act, tough guy.
[yells]
You put on a cute show.
But beneath that false
confidence, you're crazy weak.
And stupid, too.
Damn. What's going on?
Why do I feel so
out of form today?
[CONEHEAD] It isn't a question
of whether you're "in form."
My Infernal's firepower is
simply too much for you.
[MIYAMOTO]
Of course a punk like you
would blame your weakness
on somethin' or another.
You're not havin' a bad day‐‐
you were never any
good to begin with!
You've made exactly the kind
of excuse I'd expect to hear
from a dumb phony like you!
Say what?
[CONEHEAD chuckles]
[CONEHEAD] It would seem
that this tenderfoot rookie
isn't even competent
enough to understand
how terribly outmatched he is.
[MIYAMOTO] And to hear him
blame it on his form is sad.
You can call yourself a
knight all you want, chump.
Fact is, you're just an idiot
who's all bark and no bite.
In truth, I'm more than a
knight. I'm a Knight King!
You tried to stick your nose
where it doesn't belong.
And now I'm about to reward you
with a quick, painful death!
Why? I don't get it.
My power's failed me completely.
[gasps]
Wait a sec. I'm definitely
right‐handed.
Why's Excalibur in my left hand?
[MIYAMOTO]
Huh?! How should I know?
You can ask whatever you find
waiting in the afterlife!
That was my Violet Flash.
That's better. I thought
I felt something strange.
What did I just witness?
He's absurdly strong!
5th Angels Three!
Three‐on‐Three!
Triple Grating Slasher
Version Two Point Three!
[yells]
[MAKI]
That's way too many...
...threes!
[HINAWA] For some reason,
I thought there were
just three Fifth Angels Three...
...but it looks like
we got all of them.
[ANGEL C whimpering]
Well, good.
I wonder how things are going
for Arthur and Shinra.
[HINAWA] While the two of them
dash around spreading havoc,
we can track down
those documents.
Here we go.