You are aware of what's
going on in the world?
The chaos that consumes it?
The planet is in shambles.
Space distorts in areas
where the flames rise,
carving up continents.
Maps are being redrawn,
and many countries that
once existed have fallen.
These days, there are few places
where you can live
a decent life‐‐
other than the Tokyo Empire.
And so, people gather here in
the relatively undamaged Tokyo,
where the Holy Sol Temple
and Haijima Industries have
developed Amaterasu,
the perpetual thermal
energy plant.
The empire is the beneficiary
of its vast energy,
and has made further
advancements of its own.
Can we get down to it,
or does this story keep going?
[MAN B]
Eh. Who can say?
Personally, I would very much
like for it to continue.
So how'd it go?
Used the stuff I had
you make for me.
The results were more
than satisfactory.
I did a little digging
into Special Fire Force
Company Eight.
I found out something
interesting.
Their captain, Akitaru Obi,
was decorated twice
in his firefighter days.
He was later stripped
of both medals.
Both times it was
because he defied orders
and put human lives first.
Oh, did he, now?
For better or worse,
seems the captain was
a model firefighter.
He's the cornerstone.
Company Eight was built
around that man's
magnetism and strength
of character.
They're a different breed
than the other companies.
It's fascinating.
Yeah! The Rookie Games are here!
[TAMAKI]
Tamaki Kotatsu.
Ready to kick some butt!
Huh? Wanna tell me what
you're starin' at, loser?
Nothing.
[MAKI gasps]
Wone Wone Nyine!
[SHINRA]
"Wone Wone" what?
[MAKI]
You don't know them?
They're the Fire Defense
Agency's mascots.
Wone Wone Nyine!
These are our mascots?
Even the old dude?
Oh. His name is Mamoru.
[SHINRA]
Whatever you say.
[MAKI] Initially the characters
were two dogs and a cat,
but for whatever reason,
the higher‐ups at
the Agency complained
about all of them being animals.
So they switched
things up a little
and made one of them an old man
who kinda looks like
a dog instead.
If you ask me, they'd be
better off with the two dogs.
Huh? But Mamoru is adorable!
Him?
[MAKI]
Mh‐hm. Mh‐hm.
Him?
[MAKI]
Mh‐hm. Mh‐hm.
[gasps]
No, it can't be.
Excuse me!
[BURNS]
Hm?
Uh.
Can I help you with something?
You one of the new recruits
here for the games?
Yes!
Fire Force Company Eight,
sir. Shinra Kusakabe.
Sorry. Mind if I ask
some questions?
It's about that
fire 12 years ago.
I'm afraid I haven't got
time to chat right now.
Good luck.
I just need a sec‐‐
Watch it!
Who exactly do you
think you are,
talking to my captain
like that, you jerk?
[yelps, whimpers]
Uh, my bad. I'm sorry.
Hey! What are you
smiling at creep?!
[TAMAKI gasps]
[TAMAKI squeals]
It's not fair!
Why does my lucky lecher
lure always flare up
at the worst possible moment?
If your objective
was to distract me,
then you succeeded in a big way.
This won't take long, Captain.
Can I just have a moment?
[ANNOUNCER A] The competition
is about to begin.
All competitors, please
put on your turnout gear
and gather in the
designated area.
I believe you said
your name was Shinra?
Do you have the slightest idea
how many fires break out
in any given year?
Sorry to disappoint,
but you can't expect me
to remember one
from 12 years ago.
The competition is beginning.
Go and get ready.
[SHINRA]
He's hiding something.
What is this?
[MAKI gasps]
[CREWMAN A]
Inside this building,
you'll find a
simulated fire scene.
Your objectives are as follows:
Overcome the obstacles within,
rescue any who require it,
and be the first one
to reach the crewman
who's posing as an Infernal.
So that's it.
We storm the castle.
Ready, rookies?
Begin!
[TAMAKI]
He that cocky?
[SHINRA] Too bad for
the rest of these clowns.
I can fly my way
straight to the top.
[TAMAKI yells]
He's playing dirty.
This is why I hate devils.
[TAMAKI]
Damn it!
Nekomata!
Appearing from the sky
is the mark of a true hero.
[SHINRA]
Well, here we go.
I've got more questions
for that captain.
I need to wrap this up and fast.
Hello? Are there any
survivors up here?
Hey there.
I took the liberty of
ensuring our conversation
wouldn't be interrupted.
I need your full attention.
Ya got that, Devil Foot?
Uh...
I have some info about the fire
that happened 12 years ago.
Would you like to hear it?
You what?
[MAN A chuckles]
[SHINRA]
How? Who the hell are you?
You are curious, right?
About the fire that
claimed the lives
of your mommy and
sweet baby brother?
About the day that you,
yourself, became a devil.
Wait, how do you
know about that?
The fire... and my family?
[thud]
[SHINRA]
Get away from those crewmen!
[MAN A]
Huh? Really?
You're more worried
about these two
than the mysteries of your past?
You Fire Soldiers...
I'll tell you what.
If these men are making
it hard for you to focus...
...then I guess
I'll have to kill them.
Don't you dare!
[chuckles]
Now, what do you know
about the fire? Tell me!
Oh, I'll tell you,
but only if you manage
to entertain me first.
Time to play. Let's see how
many moves you can last.
[SHINRA]
Ashes?
Huh?
Pity. That was
disappointingly easy.
[MAN A]
Guess I'll kill you.
[SHINRA]
He... He's gonna kill me.
Wow, that's a hell of
a face you're making.
You can smile even
at a time like this?
You're tougher than I thought.
You've earned a reward:
I'll tell you something about
what really happened
in that fire.
Here's hint number one:
Your little brother is alive.
My brother? Sho is still alive?
What are you saying?
They told me he burned
to death, bones and all.
Besides, if he is alive,
where has he been all this time?
He was a baby when it
happened‐‐only one year old!
It's starting to
sound like someone's
been hiding something,
doesn't it?
[SHINRA]
You expect me to believe that?
I saw that look.
What's the matter, kid,
you have someone in mind?
Even if that's really true,
how would you know about it?
And why would you go out
of your way to tell me?
What are you after?
Why did you come here?
I'm glad to see I've
finally secured
your undivided attention.
You show promise, and I'd
hate for it to go to waste.
From the way you're acting,
I'm guessing you've got
your own suspicions
about the noble Fire Force.
And who can blame you?
Your mother is dead.
You wanna know
the truth, don't you?
If you wanna know what happened,
you have to quit
playing the hero
with your Fire Soldier buddies
and come be a devil with me.
That's my choice, hero or devil?
Screw you!
I don't care who you
are or what you know,
you still assaulted
two Fire Soldiers.
So I'm gonna bring you in
after I kick your ass!
Well, you're no fun.
And I had such high hopes.
A flying kick? That
leaves you wide open.
[gasps]
A flying kick is the
mark of a true hero!
Now that was impressive.
Nice to see a devil's
firepower in action.
[TAMAKI]
Hmph.
[TAMAKI screams]
Ow! That's gonna leave a mark!
[TAMAKI] I'm sensing
something nasty up ahead.
Whatever it is,
it smells like danger.
[ARTHUR] I am not a
knight‐shaped seat cushion.
Kindly move.
[screams]
Hey! What were you doing
down there, sicko?!
I am not a knight‐shaped
punching bag, either.
Hey!
Watch out!
This dragged on too long‐‐
now we've got an audience.
"Infernal." Sorry to keep you.
Arthur!
A suspicious man has
infiltrated the games
and injured two crewmen.
Go report to the
captains outside!
Oh, yeah?
[chuckles]
Clearly you lie,
but I won't be duped.
What?
Victory is mine!
[yells] You stupid knight!
How's wavin' that sword
around like an idiot
gonna help you catch me?
Out of the way.
It's my turn now!
[yells]
Ha! Gotcha!
Hm?
This kinda seems like overkill
for the Rookie Games.
Like I told you before:
He's not part of the games.
Okay, Shinra, if you're really
that determined to be a hero,
then let's see if you can get
every person out of
this building alive.
[SHINRA]
Hm? More of that stuff?
What's that?
Ashes?
Well, catch ya later, Devil.
Remember, if you ever wanna
team up with the Joker,
I'll be happy to take you in.
[JOKER]
Good luck.
We have to get outta here!
It's gonna blow!
Arthur, the ceiling!
We'll go that way.
Who are you to give
orders to me?
You're no fair princess!
My cuts were too
perfectly executed
to bring the ceiling down.
[TAMAKI]
Move it!
We need a way out, right?
[TAMAKI yells]
Grab on, you two!
[SHINRA]
I'm saving 'em all!
[JOKER]
Hero or devil?
Shut up, you jerk!
Of course I'm a hero.
I'm a Fire Soldier!
[SHINRA]
Arthur! Cat Girl!
Ah! Help!
God save me.
[TAMAKI]
Captain Burns!
[BURNS]
She's okay.
Make sure those two
reach the ground safely.
Right!
[ARTHUR]
So what about me?
[BURNS]
Look down.
Don't you punk
out on us, Arthur!
Show us the Fighting
Spirit of the Eighth!
Not too sure what he means.
How am I supposed
to fall with spirit?
[ARTHUR]
Ow.
It's pretty lucky that
you're all so muscular.
Who are you calling a
doped‐up neanderthal?
[ARTHUR]
That's not what I said.
[sighs]
[FIREMAN A]
Is anyone hurt?
[FIREMAN B] We need to get
further back just in case.
No one else is in there, right?
[SHINRA]
Hm?
Thanks for takin' care
of my subordinate here.
But for the record, I could've
gotten out by myself.
That was impressive, Shinra.
You did well.
You're giving me more
credit than I deserve.
But thanks anyway.
Shinra, there you are!
Not too shabby. You saved
four more people!
Might have to get
you a cape soon.
I appreciate it, sir.
[BURNS]
Well, we'll be going now.
[BURNS] Tamaki, I'll need a
full report on what happened.
[TAMAKI]
Yes, sir!
That's a good
soldier you've got.
[grunts]
[OBI]
Hm?
[SHINRA] I ran into a
strange man in there.
Someone who could
control explosions
with some kind of powder.
What I saw from him was
a lot like what I saw
at that fire scene
the other day.
Also, he seemed
to know something.
Captain, I have to ask.
Is the Special Fire Force
hiding anything?
[OBI]
Look, Shinra‐‐
[SHINRA] Before you tell
me something else,
the Special Fire Force
really is fighting
for the good of everyone, right?
I joined up to keep
people safe, sir.
Tell me we're heroes.
Please tell me we're fighting
back the terror of the flame.
[OBI]
Yes, we are.
That said, the Special
Fire Force isn't exactly
one monolithic organization.
It was formed with personnel
from three factions:
The Holy Sol Temple,
the Tokyo Armed Forces,
and the Fire Defense Agency.
Fact is, most companies still
answer to one entity or another.
The influence of the Temple
is strong at the First.
The Second reports directly
to the Tokyo Armed Forces.
And at the Fifth Company,
the real power is held
by Haijima Industries.
[SHINRA] Haijima? How do
they play into this?
[OBI] All the equipment we Fire
Soldiers use is made by Haijima.
They're more than
just some corporation.
We need them to operate.
They have interests throughout
the nation, and lots of capital,
so they've become
our sole supplier.
It's true that each
company does its duty
to fight for the people
and put Infernals to rest,
while seeking the cause of
spontaneous human combustion.
However, the companies
see each other as rivals
and keep what knowledge
they gain to themselves.
Nothing is shared between them.
Not even information about the
truth behind human combustion.
I believe in this organization,
but some companies
may have their own
dubious motives.
Since I can't trust
all its members,
I'm forced to be suspicious
of the larger group.
Wait a second.
Does Company Eight have
its own motives, too?
Yeah, I suppose
you could say that.
A group within the agency
strong‐armed us into existence.
They wanted a team led by me.
One they could trust completely.
Our goal is to investigate
Companies One through Seven
so we can zero in on the truth.
[SHINRA]
What truth?
Somebody in the Special Fire
Force should already know
what's causing the
Infernals to appear.
If I can force them to reveal
it, I'll save some lives.
With your leave, sir, I'd be
honored to assist with that.
Thanks, Shinra.
I'm proud to call you a
member of Company Eight.