[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that long,
morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
They're giving this
everything they have,
and they're only kids!
I put my faith in you.
I believed you could
take the fall for me!
What the hell's
gotten into you?!
[TAMAKI]
I cared for you so much.
Lieutenant Rekka,
why are you doing this?
What do we know?
An Infernal was seen
walking the streets.
There's fire where it
turned. Let's find it.
[REKKA]
Tamaki! Can you keep up?
Uh, yes, sir!
Don't worry about me!
There's an Infernal
somewhere close.
Keep an eye out
and stick with us!
Understood, Lieutenant
Rekka. I'll do that!
[REKKA] There it is!
Leave this one to me!
Hold it, Rekka!
Don't rush to rushing in!
Start the prayer.
The flame is the soul's breath.
Ashes thou wert and art.
[LI, REKKA] May thy soul return
to the great flame of fire!
Látom.
You're way too reckless.
Why do you jump in like that?
I get to be reckless 'cause
I trust you to watch my back!
Well, when you charge ahead of
me, your back's all I can see.
My stars!
You can't just brush this off
with one of your
grinning star smiles.
My stars?
My stars!
[KARIM]
I don't care how flashily you...
[TAMAKI] They all rely on
each other. They're so cool!
I need you to die, Tamaki!
[TAMAKI] Somebody...
please just make him stop.
Help me, please.
Hey, there, Tamaki.
You all right?
[REKKA]
My stars!
Oh, no!
Lieutenant Hoshimiya, care to
explain what's going on here?
Don't interfere with my work!
Or you'll feel my Star Fist Jab!
It's all over, Lieutenant!
With the hero
"Catch‐the‐Dirtbag‐
Who's‐Been‐Turning‐
People‐Into‐Infernals" Man
on the scene,
there's nowhere to run!
Huh?
[REKKA growls]
I don't care if there's
nowhere to fall back to.
Because the only direction
I ever move is forward!
[SHINRA]
Then call me
"Keep‐That‐Murderer‐
From‐Moving‐at‐all" Man!
This is amazing.
He's holding his own
against Lieutenant Rekka;
they're fighting toe‐to‐toe.
I will not allow anyone to
interfere with our evangelism!
Shut up already.
Hot‐blooded son of a bitch.
This isn't too much trouble.
Just one more body
to burn, really.
[screeching]
It seems to be attracted
to your flames, Kusakabe.
I see. It must be trying
to go back to them.
Well, look at that!
It's my lucky day!
To think you were
here all this time.
The third person the
Evangelist is searching for.
[laughs]
[REKKA]
You have the undefiled flame.
The Adolla Burst!
What's an Adolla Burst?
[REKKA] It's what we who
serve under the Evangelist
have been seeking.
Something which can
only be possessed
by the offspring
of the great Sol.
The sacred flame
to lead mankind!
[REKKA] It is pure.
It is unadulterated fire.
I've lit Pilot Lights in
children for a long time,
hoping I would find
someone compatible,
and now that
someone's right here.
You put those bugs into kids.
Exactly how many people
have you turned into Infernals?
Why would I bother counting?
Such minor sacrifices are
nothing in the face of our goal.
I'm finished listening to you!
[SHINRA] If you think you
can get away with this,
you're wrong!
[TAMAKI gasps]
What are you doing
there, you sicko?
Uh. Sorry!
[SHINRA clears throat]
Okay. Cool. Let's do this.
Could you give back
my skirt first?
Huh?
Star Fist Jab!
Your flames are bright,
but they're not as hot as mine!
[TAMAKI screams]
Tamaki!
[REKKA]
My stars!
[smooch]
[TAMAKI whimpers]
[SHINRA]
Hm?
Sorry! It's not like that!
I got punched into you, okay?
[TAMAKI] Enough already.
Just fight him, will you?
Uh. Right.
[TAMAKI]
Please. Defeat him.
You can't let
Lieutenant Rekka win.
[SHINRA] Don't worry.
The hero always wins.
[REKKA]
Hmph.
[SHINRA] My firepower's either
as strong as Rekka's
or just a little bit weaker,
but that won't matter.
'Cause with my feet,
I have him beat hard
in terms of mobility.
And with all these
surfaces to jump on,
this building's the
perfect place to use it.
Here goes nothing.
[REKKA]
My stars!
The heat of my passionate
arms will burn all away.
Come at me, bro!
Don't let him beat you!
He's packing some real heat.
I barely touched him
and he burnt my knee.
[REKKA chuckles]
Too easy.
[growls] Star Fist Jab!
[yells]
Looks like ya missed me!
What's the matter?
You only know how to
fight at ground level,
but I can attack from anywhere!
[gasps]
[REKKA]
My stars.
[SHINRA yells]
[REKKA screams]
[CHILDREN crying]
Get behind the pillars, kids.
Sorry, but we don't know
for sure if it's safe yet.
Don't worry, I'm heading
towards you right now!
C'mon, Tak‐kun!
[REKKA gasping, choking]
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
[SHINRA] Yeah, but I
flew all the way here,
and then started
fighting right off.
I feel kinda lightheaded.
I think I used too much fire.
Sounds like you overheated.
Your flames use the oxygen
in your body as fuel,
and you've burned
through your reserves.
[REKKA growls]
You're finished,
Rekka Hoshimiya.
Just give yourself up.
I finally found a kid
who can serve as the
Pilot Light's host.
For the Evangelist's sake,
I can't let him go!
[screams]
Why have you been turning
children into Infernals?
How many accomplices
do you have?
And who's this
so‐called "Evangelist"?
We will seek out
compatible children
and create strong
new pyrokinetics.
We'll produce
countless Infernals
and return mankind to flame!
All is in accordance with
the will of the Evangelist!
What the hell are you after?
[REKKA] Behold the radiance
of the blazing star
ensconced in the heavens!
What greater end could we seek
than a return to
Sol's warm embrace?!
We will set all
human beings alight.
Engulf the earth in the
great flame of fire!
Let its imperfections
be burned away
by the flames of salvation!
We will turn this world
into a second sun!
No way. This is
all because you‐‐
Want this world
to be a new star!
Follow me. We're gonna
get out of here, okay?
[laughs]
I don't think so, kids!
I just wanted it to look
like you burned to death.
I wanted to take you
away to receive
the Evangelist's teachings!
Wait a sec... You take
kids from fires.
[growls, screams]
But in that case...
...you guys could've
taken my brother!
Burn, my Star Fists!
Burn with all my zeal!
Burn! Burn!
Stop that! You'll be consumed
by your own flames!
That's true, but I won't
be burned alone!
I'll reduce every last
person here to ash!
Látom!
[gasps] What the hell?
[KARIM]
Don't you remember?
You said you trusted me to watch
your back, so I did, Rekka.
[REKKA]
Karim! Don't interfere in this!
Stop that. You're not
gonna overpower my power.
You'll just make me
freeze you more.
That's what you think!
I'm about to vaporize
this dumb ice!
Fire!
I still can't believe
it was you.
I wasn't watching your back
so you could kill kids.
I came as soon as
I heard the report.
Karim, what's going on here?
I put Rekka on lockdown.
We can question, interrogate,
and grill him later.
What does this mean
for our company?
Spitting balls in a brainstorm.
I highly doubt this problem'll
be restricted to the First.
This is one of those
wide‐spread,
far‐reaching problems
that spreads far and wide.
What was that?
[gasps]
[SHINRA]
Rekka.
It looks like someone shot him.
[ARROW]
Direct hit.
Hoshimiya has been eliminated.
[MAN B] There are more
Fire Soldiers in there.
Thin their numbers.
[ARROW]
Acknowledged.
Again?!
It's a sniper!
Ya know where
they're shooting from?
[ARROW]
I missed.
It won't happen again.
Karim!
[LI grunts]
Shinra! Put up a smokescreen!
Right!
Tamaki!
Stay with the children,
keep them out of sight.
[TAMAKI]
Yes, sir!
[SHINRA yelling]
You saved me. I'm sorry.
Company One's lost enough today,
and you're our shield.
We can't let you fall here.
What good is a shield that
needs to be shielded?
I need to get everybody out
of this building safely.
Shinra! Can you get
eyes on the enemy?
Two targets on the roof of
a building southwest of us!
'Kay.
On Shinra's signal,
project your fire
as far southwest as
you can, Tamaki!
And do a zig‐zag,
zag‐ziggy kinda thing
to hide your position!
Yes, sir!
[ARROW]
I've lost all visuals.
Karim, tell me, what's
the point of this?
We're demonstrating that
we know their position
while constructing a barrier
to further obstruct
their view of us.
More importantly,
we're doing something
that they won't understand,
which means they'll try to guess
and psyche themselves out.
After all, snipers do like
to work from safety.
[MAN A]
It seems they know our location.
[ARROW] I can't get a good shot
through all that smoke and ice.
We've silenced Hoshimiya.
If we fight any more, we'll just
expose ourselves to danger.
Let's withdraw.
We should tell the
commander what happened.
Hey, looks like the
targets are on the move!
Should I go after them?
You're still overheated
from fighting
that fight against Rekka,
so you'd just get killed.
All we can do right now
is hunker down in our shell
like frightened turtles.
If we let them run
with the wrong idea,
then I'm sure they'll
run away from us.
They made a hell of a mess here.
All I could see of them
is that they wore white.
[SHINRA] There's a group that's
turning civilians Infernal
and setting fire to the
scenes of their crimes.
Among them are the kidnapped
children they gave powers.
One might be my brother.
At least I know who to go
after now: The Evangelist.
Well, Tamaki, are these all
the kids you brought here?
[TAMAKI]
Yes, sir.
Put this on.
[TAMAKI] Oh, thanks,
but I‐I couldn't possibly.
It's fine; just put it on.
[TAMAKI]
I appreciate it, sir.
Sorry, Tamaki.
But even though Rekka lied to
you, you need to be prepared.
I know. I lured these
children into danger.
I'll accept any
punishment I receive.
I appreciate your
helping us stop him.
Did he start out hot‐blooded
and become a son of a bitch?
Or was he a son of a bitch who
ended up becoming hot‐blooded?
I dunno. Rekka was
just Rekka to me.
It's hard to imagine
him keeping a secret.
Or hiding what he felt.
Company Eight's investigating
the other special
companies, right?
I bet you're after
the Evangelist, too.
I want him caught just
as much as you guys do.
Let's catch him together.
That sounds good to me.
[SHINRA]
Our training has been cancelled.
The First has a lot
of reports to write.
And a need to
re‐examine its past.
Rekka was killed.
Arthur ended up getting
lost while chasing him.
We had to file a missing
person's report.
[chuckles]
[SHINRA] I didn't realize how
much I missed the Eighth.
I wasn't gone long, but this
still feels like a homecoming.
The captain's
constant workouts...
The lieutenant's weird hats...
The mostly cool and
beautiful Maki...
[IRIS]
Here. I made you a cup of tea.
Excellent work, Shinra.
You've done our company proud.
Thanks a bunch, Sister.
[SHINRA]
The Sister's angelic smile...
[SHINRA] I only joined the
Eighth a little while ago,
but there's something about it.
I already feel so relaxed here.
Huh?!
[TAMAKI]
Hm?
Wha‐‐?! No way!
What are you doing
here, cat girl?
[TAMAKI]
Meow.
Tamaki here has been put on
suspension at the First for now,
on account of her role in
the Hoshimiya incident.
We'll be takin' her
in while that lasts.
I figure that with the
two of you together,
you'll have an easier time
writing your reports
on the incident.
Oh. I see, sir.
Huh?
Okay. Well, that being
the case, Tamaki...
Would you mind letting me
have your phone number?
What?!
Wait, why are you pretending
you'll need my number for work?
We're gonna be in the
same office all day.
Though, I guess...
...exchanging phone numbers
isn't the worst idea.
So you'll do it?
Well, that's a relief.
Juggernaut's really
been bugging me
to help him get it from you.
No way! And don't ask again!
[screaming]
[SHINRA] Another aggressor
had invaded my safe haven,
and just as I'd gotten
rid of Arthur, too.