[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that long,
morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others.
[OBI]
Death by fire.
[ARTHUR] So this is meant
to be my castle.
So what are the Rookie
Fire Soldier Games?
It's a competition where
all the Fire Force rookies
that joined this year get
to show off their abilities,
and it's comin' up pretty soon.
You're gonna represent
Company Eight
alongside our other new recruit,
who we're expecting later today.
Hang on. There's a
new recruit coming?
Indeed there is.
[SHINRA]
Hey, uh, Captain?
Will there be any Fire Soldiers
aside from us rookies
at this contest?
Well, yeah. Some of us'll
come and cheer you all on.
[SHINRA] There could be someone
from another company
who knows about that fire.
Oh, a devil.
Hoped I'd never see you
again, ya damn knight.
What're you doing here?
Thought I'd slay
some hell‐spawn.
Still with the big talk
and dumb pose.
I'll shove that sword up‐‐
Rise and shine, Sputter.
[SPUTTER]
Spu‐Sputter...
You really are
something else, Maki.
The way you control
flames is amazing.
That's sweet of
you to say, Iris.
But honestly, I'm just
a second‐generation.
If I were a third‐gen
like Shinra,
then I'd be able to
make fire on my own
without having to
use any starters.
[SPUTTER]
Sputter?
Sputter? Sputter...
[MAKI]
Careful, it's hot!
[SPUTTER]
Sputter.
We're finally gonna
settle the score for good.
Since you insist,
I'll have to show you the
difference in our power.
[MAKI]
Hang on. Who are you?
The realm knows me as Arthur
Boyle, the Knight King.
Might you be the princesses
of this castle?
[MAKI, IRIS]
Huh?
Who, me?
[IRIS] Oh, you must be our new
third‐generation Fire Soldier.
It's nice to have you on board.
[MAKI]
Shinra. Do you know this guy?
Uh‐huh. Met him at the academy.
I told him that knights
have jack on heroes,
so midway through training,
he tacked "king" onto that
made‐up title of his.
What a loser, right?
[MAKI]
Okay...
He pretends he's the
smooth, silent type,
but the truth is,
he's just dumb.
He's literally too idiotic
to come up with words.
And yet...
[MAKI, IRIS]
And yet what?
Girls still think he's
cool for some reason.
Ah. Yes, that.
[chuckles]
I've got way more drive,
but girls just don't care.
No one can resist
a true knight.
Wait.
Knight King.
Ladies love a king.
Well, for the record...
[SHINRA]
Huh?
I think that you're
plenty cool, Shinra.
[SHINRA]
Huh...?
Let's see that awkward
smile of yours, Devil.
Say that again.
What's going on?
[MAKI]
Lieutenant Hinawa!
We just met the new
recruit, Arthur.
It turns out that he and Shinra
went to the academy together.
[SPUTTER] Sputter? Sputter,
sputter. Sputter, sputter.
Sputter!
Fire Soldiers don't
play with fire.
Right. Got it.
[HINAWA]
So you're Arthur Boyle.
Sure am. Glad to work with you.
Come on, man. You heard her
call him lieutenant, right?
We all stand as equals
before the round table.
He needn't bow.
Says the lowest‐ranked
soldier in this crew.
Látom.
[HINAWA]
Whatever.
[chuckles]
[HINAWA]
The Rookie Games are coming up.
I wanna see what you've
got in advance.
That means seeing your
powers in action.
Now. Go take them
both on, Maki.
[MAKI]
Wait. Do you mean me?
Do you see anyone
else on this rooftop
who might go by your name?
No, I do not!
[HINAWA]
You lead off, Shinra.
Are we s'posed
to fight for real?
[MAKI]
You don't have to hold back.
Are you certain that
Maki can handle them?
Third generations are extra
powerful, aren't they?
It won't be an issue for her.
Maki started out
in the military.
She understands what it
takes to destroy a man.
Okay. I'm ready to
begin when you are.
[chuckles]
[MAKI growls]
[SHINRA yells]
Whoa, Shinra!
[screaming]
[chuckles]
I really thought I was dead.
Isn't she overdoing it a bit?
Shinra has the instincts
to be a good soldier,
but he's got one
glaring weakness.
Fact is, he needs to be shown
that his third‐gen powers
can only get him so far.
You won't beat me
the way you did him.
Excalibur!
It's still lit.
Looks like a plasma cutter.
Excalibur is stalwart.
You'll find it a lot tougher to
extinguish than Shinra's fire.
But what kind of noble
knight would I be
if I injured an
innocent princess?
It looks like chivalry's
dead after all.
A true knight oughtta kneel
when he speaks to a princess.
That's for your lack of respect
toward the lieutenant.
I see now.
You're an ogre disguised
as a princess.
How dare you call me a hideous,
man‐eating, gorilla cyclops!
Didn't say that!
Now I'm doubting you can
understand human speech, ogress.
It seems like he just keeps
throwing more fuel on the fire.
That's a third‐gen
pyrokinetic for you.
I'm not outta the running yet!
[growls]
Huh.
You know when you're in combat,
ya start to look
a little brutish.
[IRIS]
Not you too, Shinra.
[growls]
If I can't just snuff
your flames out...
[FLARE]
Flare. Flare...
What the‐‐? Hey, what'd
you do to my fire?
No. You got Excalibur, too?
You should change the
name to Ek‐sputter‐bur.
"Ek‐sputter‐bur"?
So we have a devil
and a knight.
Following the pattern Arthur
and Shinra established,
I guess I'd call Maki a witch.
[MAKI]
Sputter! Flare!
Now come forth!
Bo‐bo‐bo! Bo‐bo, Bo‐bo!
[SHINRA, ARTHUR]
Uh?
"Bo"?
[BOBOBO]
Boh.
Would the two of you
like to continue?
[BOBOBO]
Bo. Bo. Bo. Boh.
Think we're out of options.
If you're throwin' in the
towel, then that's that.
Well, it's pretty clear
that you wanna surrender,
so I'll concede.
[BOBOBO]
Bo!
Bo‐bo‐bo! Bo‐bo, Bo‐bo!
[SHINRA, ARTHUR] Is he tryin'
to eat faster than me?
Take the time to chew, will ya?
Refill please.
More extra‐firm noodles.
[ARTHUR, OBI, SHINRA]
Thank you for the food!
Wow, that was some
really tasty fare, Cap.
Arthur, watch your tone.
No worries, I'm glad
ya liked it.
The grub at that
place is top notch.
[SHINRA]
Captain Obi sure is laid back.
Is there anything that
can piss him off?
[SHINRA]
Huh?
Hm. Somethin' wrong, Shinra?
Uh. No. I'm doin' swell, sir.
Well, good for you.
[OBI] It isn't healthy to train
right after a big meal,
so there's no choice but to
knock out some office work.
[ARTHUR]
Why's it unhealthy?
[SHINRA] He's even getting
along with that idiot.
This thing's pretty impressive.
The Type Seven Firefighting Ax.
It's a durable melee
weapon that can also fire
a sacred spike from
the head at range.
I've no need for a fire ax.
Excalibur's the only
weapon I wield.
Right, your plasma cutter.
By heating your
flame into plasma
and emitting it from that
bladeless hilt of yours,
you create a super heated,
ultra‐dense sword.
Yeah, fair point.
You pyrokinetics might not
need tools like fire axes.
Every time I deploy, I've gotta
equip over 30 kilos of gear.
Then there's the issue
of maintaining it all.
It sure would be helpful
if we could hurry up
and hire an engineer.
Might take some pressure
off the Lieutenant.
For the record, I don't
actually mind this work.
[OBI]
Mh‐hm.
[alarm blaring]
Another Infernal in Taito‐ward,
Iriya District! Sir!
This one was reported to be
in a single‐family home.
Odds are, we'll be putting them
to rest in close quarters.
Shinra.
You'll be pretty limited
in how you can
maneuver with your feet.
Take the Type Seven.
All of you keep your weapons
hidden inside your coats.
Don't let them be
seen by civilians.
Things are a little
quiet, considering.
First Mama. Now Papa.
How come? Am I gonna be next?
[HINAWA] Apparently, her mother
turned Infernal as well.
Just two years ago.
[OBI] And now she's lost her
Dad, too. Tough break.
[IRIS]
Captain Obi, should I‐‐?
[OBI] No. Let's do this
as gently as we can.
[OBI] I hear there's been
a rash of strange incidents
at recent fire scenes,
so stay on your toes.
Company Eight, we're goin' in.
[COMPANY EIGHT]
Yes, sir!
[OBI]
Shinra. Arthur. C'mere a sec.
[OBI] I thought I told you two
to keep your weapons concealed.
Why should we, though?
There's no rule or regulation
that says it's required.
None of our teachers
mentioned it, either.
Excalibur is more than
a weapon to me.
It's my pride, so why
should I have to hide it?
As Fire Soldiers,
we all have our duty.
We must fight the Infernals
in order to put them to rest.
All Infernals were once human.
We can say we're
"putting them to rest,"
but in truth, we kill them.
[OBI] Among the ranks
of the Fire Soldiers,
there are some who think of
themselves as crusaders,
and relish every moment of
combat with the Infernals.
Thing is, that means ignoring
the torment of the bereaved.
The Infernal you put
to rest in battle
is prob'ly someone's dad.
Or wife.
[OBI] Never let the next
of kin see your weapons.
If you can't follow that rule,
I don't want you in my company.
Yes, sir.
[SHINRA]
He's right.
If I'm not there for
those left behind,
then I'm no one's hero.
[MAN humming]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
The flames transformed, but why?
Could it've been
the Infernal inside?
[OBI]
Those flames are sneering at us.
Infernals have no sense of self.
It's hard to believe one
of them could do this.
Making entry now.
[SHINRA, ARTHUR]
Right!
[OBI]
Infernal located.
[SHINRA]
He's just sitting there.
[OBI]
Hm?
Why do these things
have to happen?
[ARTHUR]
Captain.
Please let me be the
one to put him to rest.
Wait, let's think about this.
He is an Infernal, but he
hasn't attacked anyone.
Don't be a dumbass.
The man's burning alive.
It's hard to imagine the kind
of pain he's going through.
We need to put him
out of his misery.
Time's 1706. Put the
Infernal to rest, Arthur.
I will not allow you to
suffer any more pain
than you already have.
Sister. The prayer, please.
Right.
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is
the soul's release.
Ashes thou wert and art.
May thy soul return...
[ARTHUR]
...to the great flame of fire.
Látom.
[COMPANY EIGHT]
Was that painful?
Yeah. It was.
Well, hang on to that pain,
because the worst thing
this job can do to you
is make you numb to it all.
[MAKI]
Huh?
What was that?
Everyone out!
Before it caves in!
Aren't you coming, sir?
Crap, Captain, look out!
[OBI]
Don't know who did this,
but they must not
know me, either.
I train every day. They'd
need a lot more to crush me.
This damn prank of theirs
has gone way too far!
[MAN] Seems to me this
so‐called Special Fire Force
is only blowin' smoke.
Time to see how well those
clowns can take a joke.
[MAKI]
Captain, are you hurt?
No, I'm all right.
That didn't just
happen on its own.
You think we were attacked
by a third party?
I'm not sure yet.
If so, then they also
trashed a fire scene
that was still full of
memories for the bereaved.
And for that, they will pay.
For now, let's just head back.
Flames took my parents.
And next they're
gonna come for me.
Papa. Mama.
[OBI]
Mikako, right?
Your father fought bravely
to hold back the flame's fury,
and he won that fight.
I think both of your parents
were protecting you
from the flames.
They both gave their all to make
sure that you would be okay.
Believe in them.
In the love you felt.
Papa. Mama.
[MIKAKO crying]
[SHINRA] I'm sorry, sir.
I couldn't do anything.
[OBI] It's rare that we can
offer the bereaved much comfort.
And sometimes it
feels just as tough
as charging into
a sea of flames.
But it's still important we try.
[ARTHUR]
Go to sleep, Devil.
There's nothing to be seen,
'least not by the likes of you.
Stop wasting your time.
[ARTHUR] Sometimes closing your
eyes can help you to see.
[SHINRA]
What's that supposed to mean?
[ARTHUR] If you don't know,
then go to sleep, Devil.
[SHINRA]
Wait, is he‐‐?
Why?
[ARTHUR] Just showing some
compassion as a knight.
Wait.
Shut up. I meant Knight King.
[SHINRA]
Hey.
[ARTHUR]
What now?
[SHINRA] Don't talk to me
just 'cause you can't sleep.
[ARTHUR] Pfft. I won't kill
you if you fall asleep first.
Even if you're a devil.
Just be grateful I'm a noble
knight and go to sleep.
[SHINRA]
Wait.
[ARTHUR] King. I'm noble‐‐
I'm a noble Knight King.
[SHINRA] It's almost like
you're messing up on purpose.
[SHINRA]
I‐‐
We need to bring spontaneous
human combustion to an end,
and quickly.