[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that
long, morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
[MAN] Yes. I'm performing
your works as instructed.
There may be a few
minor obstacles,
but I'll overcome them.
Infernalization will
continue unimpeded.
Understood, Evangelist.
Látom.
[OBI] You compared the core
matter of two specimens,
Infernals A and B,
and found a difference
in their compositions.
Through chemical analysis,
you discovered the
DNA of a creature
that wasn't the victim
inside Infernal A's core.
And you think that this
DNA belonged to a bug.
I don't just think that,
it's the conclusion I reached
through careful research.
I've studied many other
Infernal cadavers,
and the specimens I suspected
of artificial ignition
all had the same
things in common.
Their cores had
been compromised,
pierced from without,
as if a creature had
forcefully made its way in.
[HIBANA]
An insect.
[SHINRA] It's been five days
since we joined the First.
[chuckles, snorts]
[snoring]
[SHINRA]
We'll be undercover for a month.
We have that long to
try and find a lead
on the source of these
artificial Infernals.
[grunts]
C'mon, Lieutenant Hinawa,
what're you doing
here this time?
Checking up on you.
Run into any problems yet?
Has Arthur been holding up okay?
I told you we were
doing fine yesterday,
do you have to come by
here every morning?
[giggles]
Goodness. If it isn't the
Lieutenant from the Eighth.
Morning. Good to see you.
[HINAWA]
Good morning.
He has a lotta concern
for his soldiers, huh?
[SISTER A]
Yeah, he really does.
Sir, to be honest, this
is getting embarrassing.
[HINAWA]
Hm? Don't really see why.
I wouldn't need to come
if you checked in
with the captain more.
Fine then, I'll do that.
Shoo! Shoo!
Oh, crap. Captain Hibana
came with him this time?
The two of us are openly
prowling their grounds
and they're completely
unperturbed.
I can say for a fact
that we'd never be
this open at Company Five.
We have too many of
Haijima's secrets to protect.
According to my investigation,
most artificial Infernals have
appeared at fire scenes,
or in secured zones that only
Fire Soldiers can enter.
Disturbing though it is,
it's likely that our culprit
is a Fire Soldier.
The bigger question is whether
they're a member of Company One.
So, tell me,
why'd you guys wanna become
Fire Soldiers, anyway?
You know, as a hero, I thought
I should protect mankind
from the Infernals and
human combustion.
It's only natural
that a brave knight
should fight on behalf
of the peasantry.
Dude. This job is
a chick magnet.
I joined 'cause I wanted
to impress the ladies.
You guys are so amazing.
I can barely control
my pyrokinesis at all.
Maybe it's 'cause I don't
have a sense of purpose
like you guys do.
You don't need some
grand objective.
As long as you end up
helping people out,
I think you've done enough.
Yeah. I suppose you're right.
Thank you, Shinra.
I feel better. Uh.
It's time for morning assembly!
So finish eating already!
All of you need to hurry back to
your appointed stations and‐‐
[gasps]
If you would excuse me,
ma'am, I need mayonnaise.
[SHINRA]
Whoa. Hey!
You're such a friggin' jerk!
Stay away from meow, will you?
I was just sitting still
and then you fell on me!
[bell ringing]
[SHINRA] Is that the morning
assembly bell?
That's the alarm! It means
an Infernal's appeared!
Juggernaut, find
Lieutenant Hoshimiya!
Kishiri, Lieutenant Li!
And you two from the Eighth
should report to
Lieutenant Flam!
[KARIM] This is another
mass combustion incident.
A total of five victims
have turned Infernal.
Nozaka Squad, get
civilians out of the area.
Matsuda Squad, spread out and
keep the rest of us informed.
The rest of us will search
for the Infernals.
Let's put them to rest quickly.
[FIRST MEMBERS]
Sir!
[SHINRA] Awesome. This Company's
a well‐oiled machine.
[KARIM]
You two stand by.
Go to Matsuda Squad
if you see something.
Please let us help you, sir!
Throwing in new recruits
would only cause confusion.
The best thing you can do is
just stay right here, ya hear?
[SHINRA chuckles]
Hey, you all right?
[SHINRA]
Huh?
What happened?
[VICTIM A screams]
That's our culprit. After 'em!
Shouldn't we stop
the Infernal first?
No, we'll have to leave him
to Company One for now.
[SHINRA]
You'll pay for this.
Fire Soldiers are supposed
to protect people!
You can't run faster
than I can fly!
[gasps]
[REKKA]
Shinra!
[KARIM]
What are you doing?
I thought I ordered
you to stay behind.
Answer me: What are you
two doing back here?
Talk or‐‐ Uh!
We don't get to visit Shinjuku
much. We kinda got lost.
[ARTHUR groaning]
We finished, Lieutenant Rekka.
All the Infernals have
been laid to rest.
[REKKA]
Got it. Good work, Tamaki.
'Kay. Let's head back.
Shinra, why'd you stop me?
Someone's been making Infernals
and the Lieutenants are
our top suspects, right?
Yeah, but we can't tell
friend from foe here,
so we need to wait.
If we'd acted then, we might've
been silenced for good.
So what do you think
we should do now?
That man was killed.
I know. I saw it
with my own eyes.
He pressed a bottle
containing an insect
against that civilian's back.
And right after that...
The man turned Infernal.
It's pure evil.
How can a Fire Soldier
justify doing this?
Talked to a nun who was
passing by earlier.
Only the Lieutenants wear the
robes you saw on the culprit.
So we should start by
investigating Karim and Rekka.
You talk like that'll be simple,
but they're both
formidable foes.
How's that matter?
Strong or not, they should
be held accountable.
Let's start by searching
Karim's room.
[ARTHUR]
You sure he's not in it?
Yeah. I asked Juggernaut
to make somethin' up
and keep him occupied.
[ARTHUR] Did you tell
Juggernaut about our mission?
No need. He seems to have
taken a liking to Tamaki.
So when I said I could get
her phone number for him,
he volunteered to help us out,
no questions asked.
But anyway, why are you
wearing that get‐up?
[ARTHUR]
I made a job change.
Went from knight to assassin.
[SHINRA] So after all that
insufferable "knight" talk,
you're‐‐
Still a knight.
What was that?
I call this a mini Excalibur.
Make 'em from a
sheet of plastic,
which means they all tend
to melt after one use.
[SHINRA]
You idiot!
This'll make it obvious that
someone broke in here!
[ARTHUR]
You don't sound like yourself.
Guess you lost your nerve
after Burns kicked your ass.
What'd you say?
If the mystery of
human combustion
could be solved cleanly,
then someone would've
done it by now.
[SHINRA] I'd be surprised
to see you solve anything.
[ARTHUR chuckles]
[gasps]
That vial!
[ARTHUR] So one of these
can turn someone Infernal?
That settles it.
Karim Flam is our culprit.
[ARTHUR, SHINRA gasp]
I left that buggy little
bug there as bait
to lure the two of you out.
Your behavior in that back alley
was suspicious earlier,
so I thought I'd test you.
[KARIM] So the Eighth trailed
the same trail I'm trailing.
Interesting.
What're you getting at?
Those insects.
I wanna catch the louse
who's spreading them, too.
So we're on the same side, then.
How do we know we can trust you?
[KARIM] You saw the
culprit at work, right?
Judging from the fact that I'm
one of your first suspects,
they must've been
in robes like mine.
[KARIM]
It wasn't me.
And there was just one
solitary single person there
who wore robes like mine.
[SHINRA]
Rekka Hoshimiya.
[KARIM]
Had a case two months ago
where a large group of kids
caught fire all at once.
I knew it couldn't be natural.
And then I found the insect,
left behind at the scene.
So he was targeting children?
[CHILD C] I got a five star
from the gacha machine.
Whoa, for real? You're lucky.
[TAMAKI]
Hey there, kids.
[BOTH]
Hm?
Fires sure are scary, huh?
You heard about how those kids
your age burned up, right?
Well, listen,
there's a way to make sure
the flames can never get you.
I can show you if you
come with me, 'kay?
What're you trying to do, Rekka?
[TAMAKI]
'Kay! Let's go!
Tamaki, thanks for
rounding everyone up.
I've finally found
a sacred prayer
that can make people immune
to Infernalization!
If I can save these kids
from the fear of flames,
then I can die with
a smile on my face!
That's great, Lieutenant.
I only wish I could
save more right now.
I'm such a failure. Damn it all!
Father, is it really true?
Can you actually protect my
kids from becoming Infernals?
'Course I can!
You kept it secret, right?
Can't have any squabbling.
One of my friends from
school got burned up.
It was really sad.
I'm scared that I'll be next,
but you're saying you
can keep me safe, right?
You got it, bud!
Don't be scared!
Now that you're here with me,
everything's gonna be fine!
We'll get stronger so we can
never be beaten by the flames!
[REKKA] Tamaki, would you
mind stepping outside?
I'd like to focus on the prayer.
[TAMAKI]
Huh?
[REKKA] You've been a great
help. Thanks for everything.
I would do anything for
you, Lieutenant Rekka,
but I was hoping you might
let me see the prayer, too.
Just so I can keep helping.
[REKKA]
My stars!
Thank you, Tamaki!
It's okay. You're really
making too much of it.
[REKKA] No, I'm not. I'm so
grateful for you, Tamaki!
I‐‐
[REKKA]
You deserve a rest!
[ALL gasp]
Now then, all of you
have been chosen.
You're going to help me find
a host for the Pilot Light.
Please. We've changed
our minds. Let us go!
[REKKA] You wanna let
your children's futures
go up in smoke?
Sounds like you've
failed as a mother.
[gasps]
[CHILD B]
What's wrong, Mommy?
[MOTHER A roars]
Return to the great
flame of fire.
[ARTHUR] You're about to
go look for Rekka, right?
We're coming with you.
[KARIM]
Company One'll sort this out.
Outsiders like you
should stay out of it.
[SHINRA]
With respect, sir,
we're currently assigned
to Karim Squad.
Then consider this an
order from your Lieutenant.
Do not come with me.
As if we have to
take orders from you.
We're both with Company
Eight, remember?
So, you two are my squad
'cause you're serving under me,
but you aren't my squad
'cause you're not under me.
Feel free to feel free, then.
[CHILDREN crying, whimpering]
Well, that one's a no‐go.
But it won't be a problem
as long as one of
you kids can do it.
C'mon, stop crying!
You can't beat the flames
if you're this weak.
You've gotta act
strong to get strong.
That is what you want, right?
Yeah! Let's beat the flames!
[coughing]
[TAMAKI] Lieutenant Rekka?
What's going on here?
[REKKA] I wanted you to
live and take the blame,
but I guess I should'a
squeezed harder.
[TAMAKI]
Huh? What do you mean, sir?
[REKKA]
Don't sweat it, Tamaki.
You don't need to understand.
You just need to be
brave. Like these kids.
[TAMAKI]
No. This can't be real.
Don't tell me... You're the one
who's been making Infernals?
I adored you, Lieutenant.
There was no one I
believed in more than y‐‐
[REKKA]
You still adore me, don't you?
Or is your heart so lukewarm
that'cha let your feelings
change at the drop of a hat?
[REKKA screams]
[REKKA]
I refuse to surrender!
No matter how many innocent
children have to be sacrificed,
I will never give up,
understand?!
I will keep creating Infernals
for the Evangelist,
till I finally find someone
who can host the Pilot Light!
[screaming]
[TAMAKI]
You were always this awkward,
strangely hot‐blooded, guy.
I thought it was so cool
how driven you were
and how nothing got you down.
But now I'm finding
out that you're just
a hot‐blooded son of a bitch!
[REKKA]
My stars!
Lie there and be quiet
like a good little girl.
You‐‐ You're a‐‐
Okay. It's your turn now.
Put me down!
I don't wanna.
‐‐Oh, no! Tak‐kun!
‐‐Lemme go!
[REKKA]
Here goes, Tak‐kun. Get ready.
He's gonna burn!
[REKKA]
Tak‐kun!
[screaming]
What was that sound?
Hang in there!
I know that it burns,
but you can take it!
This is wrong.
[REKKA]
Don't give up, Tak‐kun!
Fight! Fight for your life!
[gasps]
He didn't turn Infernal.
How can that be?
This means that he's compatible.
At long last, I pulled it off!
I found a host
for the Pilot Light!
That's great,
but it doesn't mean
the rest of you
are off the hook.
So let's take on the Pilot Light
and earn victory for tomorrow!
[ALL gasp]
If you've got a fighting
spirit, you'll be fine.
Rev yourself up and win! Fire!
Please just... stop.
Let 'em go.
Someone...
Someone make him...
Somebody come and help us!
[REKKA]
What was that, Tamaki?
[REKKA] And you were
such an outstanding,
obedient subordinate!
What the hell's
gotten into you?!
There are children watching!
How can you let them
see you like this?!
They're giving this
everything they have,
and they're only kids!
I put my faith in you, Tamaki.
I believed you could
take the fall for me!
[TAMAKI]
I cared for you so much.
[REKKA]
I trusted you!
I trusted you and no one else!
Now I'll have to change
the plan and kill you.
[TAMAKI] The hot‐blooded,
gentle lieutenant...
[REKKA] I'll make it look like
you burned yourself to death!
Damn it. This is hard
for me, too, you know!
I didn't want it to go this way!
[yells]
[REKKA] Do you see how
my fist weeps for you?
I'll be right beside you
all the way to the
end, okay, Tamaki?!
You said you would
do anything for me...
...so die in my place!
[TAMAKI]
Somebody...
[TAMAKI] I looked up to you.
More than anyone.
Help me, please.
Hey, Tamaki.
You all right?