[ANNOUNCER A] This train's next
stop is at Tabata Station.
Amaterasu is operating
at full efficiency.
We are running according
to schedule.
[yells]
[SAFETY OFFICER A]
Get away from the rail lines!
It isn't safe here.
There's a burning train
heading this way! Move!
[SAFETY OFFICER A]
This way! Move...
That looks like a serious fire.
[COMMUTER A]
Think it's an Infernal.
[COMMUTER B]
Another one?
[SAFETY OFFICER A]
...and form an orderly line!
[ANNOUNCER B]
...clear the platform at once!
Bet it hurts in there.
[SHINRA]
I can help you with that.
[OBI]
Special Fire Force! Make way!
All civilians
continue to evacuate.
This area's dangerous.
[SHINRA]
Uh.
You, too.
Don't just stand around here,
go and join the others.
Wait. Captain, I think‐‐
Hey, Lieutenant.
Care to join us?
Yes. Of course, sir.
[roars]
Commence the operation.
Note the time as O‐810.
[HINAWA, IRIS, MAKI]
Yes, sir!
[OBI] Sister, would you
begin the prayer, please?
On it.
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is
the soul's release.
[INFERNAL roars]
[OBI]
Pile bunker's prepped.
I'll bust the core myself!
[IRIS]
Ashes thou wert and art.
May thy soul return...
[OBI yells]
[OBI]
...to the great flame of fire.
Látom.
[OBI]
That was awesome.
What a cool team.
[gasps]
[IRIS gasps]
Well, that was close.
You aren't injured, are you?
Oh, no.
What was that?
[gasps]
So you're the one.
Yes! Forgive the late intro.
As of this morning,
I'll be your new
third‐generation Fire Soldier.
I'm Shinra Kusakabe.
It's an honor to meet you all.
[OBI]
Huh.
So these are the "Devil's
Footprints" I've heard about.
I thought Company
Eight was new,
so why's it quartered
in such an old dump?
Too bad.
Shinra, right? Follow me.
Sir!
[HINAWA]
An old dump, huh?
[SHINRA]
No! It's got character.
Reporting in, sir!
[OBI]
Ah. You made it.
I'm captain of the Special Fire
Force's Company Eight.
The name's Akitaru Obi.
You're greeting
a new team member.
Let's maybe get
off the pullup bar.
Can do.
Takehisa Hinawa.
Around this dump,
I'm second in command.
So hey, Shinra.
About your résumé photo...
Why are you smiling?
Sir! Apologies.
When I'm nervous, my face
compulsively tightens
in such a way that my
teeth are exposed.
Huh?
Uh, that is... I tend to
smile when I feel tense.
‐‐My face‐‐
‐‐[OBI] Hm?
[OBI]
Mm...
Hmm...
[chuckles]
[OBI laughing]
Sorry about that.
Just wanted to see
for myself. You get it.
I bet that cute little quirk
gets you in a lotta trouble.
True. It's caused a few
misunderstandings.
Man, your poker face
must be somethin' else!
[OBI laughing]
[SHINRA]
Did he call it cute?
Pretty sure he means creepy.
So tell me, Shinra,
why did you decide to join the
Fire Force in the first place?
Sir!
Honestly, I just
wanted to be a hero.
[OBI]
Heh.
Well, that's as fine
an ambition as any,
but don't forget
you're part of a team.
Cool‐headed co‐ordination
saves more lives than heroics.
A hero, huh?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but that's in stark contrast
with your nickname.
Everybody calls you a devil
due to an incident that took
place when you were young.
If you act like you talk,
you'll do fine.
But if you're just
some delinquent
who's trying to clean
up his reputation,
you may as well walk out now.
[MAKI]
Sister.
[IRIS]
Yes, Maki? What is it?
[MAKI] That new recruit
swept you off your feet
like you were a princess.
He came outta nowhere and saved
you from danger, so, uh...
Tell me, did you feel
like he might be the one?
[IRIS]
Hm?
[IRIS] Maki always act so fierce
and cool in the field.
But the fact is,
her head's stuffed with
flowers and sparkles.
Reporting in, sir!
[OBI]
Hm?
Hi, I'd like to thank you
for helping me earlier.
Yeah, sure.
I just did what any hero would.
[MAKI gasps]
Wow, he really is the one.
This is a time for love,
not war, Iris!
And I really don't think
you should stoop
to violence anyway.
I mean, you're a nun,
you silly goober.
[MAKI, IRIS whimpering]
[MAKI] I adjusted the
length of your pants
to accommodate that
ability of yours.
Do you think they're
gonna work for you?
Yeah. Thank you very‐‐
[MAKI]
Hm?
[SHINRA]
Why does she smell so good?
[OBI] Easy, Turbo. You look
like you wanna eat her.
Say what?
I already explained,
it's an involuntary‐‐
[BOTH]
Hm?
Well, I think it's just
about time, Captain.
Yeah. Everyone's here now,
so let's get started.
[OBI] All of us know about
spontaneous human combustion,
but no one, not even us here,
knows when it'll happen next,
or to whom.
And so, we all live in fear.
[OBI] One day, without
cause or warning,
people the world over
began catching fire.
These were the
first‐generation victims
of spontaneous human combustion.
They, and those like them
who've come since,
are called Infernals.
Having lost all sense of self,
they run rampant until they die.
Those deaths don't come easy.
To put an Infernal to rest,
you have to destroy its core
by striking where the
victim's heart was.
The Special Fire
Force's main duty
is to put Infernals to rest,
saving their souls and
human lives in the process.
But we all have
another objective.
That's to solve the mystery of
what causes human combustion.
And with luck, to stop it,
and put an end to the terror
of the flame for good.
As quickly as we can.
[SHINRA]
I wanna become a hero.
No. I have to become one.
Mother.
Hey, Mom! Guess what?
I'm gonna be a superhero!
I'll keep you and
Sho safe forever!
Well, that sure sounds cool.
[chuckles]
Devil!
[SHINRA'S GRANDMOTHER]
No, I won't "take him in"!
That boy is dangerous.
[GOVERNMENT AGENT A] Please,
ma'am. He's your grandson.
Don't say anything
you'll regret.
[SHINRA'S GRANDMOTHER]
I'll say what I know.
That is no grandson of mine.
Do you have any idea
what he's done?
And look at him.
Not a shred of remorse.
He's grinning like
the devil he is.
[SHINRA] I made a promise,
and I'll keep it.
[alarm blaring]
The alarm!
[MAKI] Shinra! Someone
just turned Infernal!
Be ready in 30 seconds!
On it!
Our Infernal is in Taito
ward, Torigoe District.
The fire's at a small factory.
The person who turned Infernal
is the factory manager's wife.
[OBI]
We'll work with Squad Four
of the Fire Defense
Agency's Ueno branch
and put her to rest.
[OBI] Get in the Matchbox!
Let's do this!
[ANNOUNCER A] Emergency vehicles
are about to deploy.
We request that all
civilian motorists
pull to the side of the
road and clear a path
so they can safely pass.
Special Fire Force Company
Eight, moving out.
Here comes your
chance to be a hero.
[chuckles]
[FIREFIGHTER A]
It's the Blue Stripes.
[FIREFIGHTER CAPTAIN A]
From what we've been seeing,
this Infernal is
especially aggressive.
We've been able to keep
the flames contained so far,
but as long as the
Infernal's active,
there's a risk that more build‐‐
Excuse me.
[MANAGER]
Please help my wife, Sister.
See that she's put to rest.
[IRIS] Infernals are lost
souls shrouded in flame.
We'll offer your wife mercy,
and a return to the embrace
of the great god Sol.
[OBI] Special Fire
Force Company Eight,
it's time we went in.
[COMPANY EIGHT]
Right!
Done! You like it?
Oh, yeah! I can keep
everybody safe now!
'Kay, so whaddaya think?
Do I look all super?
Yup. My little hero.
[laughs]
[OBI]
She's further in.
[MAKI] These flames,
they feel conscious,
like they're actively
trying to stop us.
[IRIS] This place
must've been important.
To the Infernal, I mean.
[SHINRA]
Mom. Sho!
[INFERNAL roars]
Hey, Shinra! You okay, bud?
Huh? I was just...
[OBI] You still wanna
be a hero, don't you?
Listen, Fire Soldiers don't
abandon their comrades.
When you fall behind, we all do.
The bright blue stripes
that ring our bodies
aren't just for show,
they're what bind
us all together.
In this hellscape
of smoke and flame,
trust in that bond.
The fear you feel
is a survival tool.
It helps to keep you alive.
Just don't let it
make you a coward.
Understood, sir.
Maki!
[MAKI]
Right! Clearing a path!
[OBI] The flames are
getting sucked in!
Shinra!
[COMPANY EIGHT]
[SHINRA'S MOTHER]
Shinra!
Don't look, honey.
You need to run away! Hurry!
[SHINRA]
Mom.
[PASSERBY A]
That's her eldest son Shinra.
They say he caused the fire.
[PASSERBY B] His younger brother
Sho was burnt completely.
They couldn't even
find his bones.
[PASSERBY A] I heard them say
that he's a third‐generation.
They can create fire at will.
[PASSERBY C]
How terrifying.
[SHINRA]
I can't run away from this.
It wasn't me.
[SHINRA]
When my home burned,
I saw someone, or something...
[SHINRA] Something other
than Mom, or Sho, or me.
[SHINRA]
And I'm gonna find out what.
[PASSERBY A] That smile
of his‐‐it's so creepy.
He's a psychopath.
A devil.
[SHINRA] Since that day,
I haven't truly smiled once.
[HINAWA]
Devil! Hey, Devil!
Wake up, you damn delinquent!
[SHINRA]
What's with this blue light?
[HINAWA] You know, with a
badass nickname like "Devil,"
I figured you'd be tougher.
Try to sit up.
I must've been out
for a while. How long?
You're fine. It was
like five seconds.
Now get up already.
We're gonna need
you in action soon.
[MAKI] How do you feel?
Can you fight?
Yeah.
[OBI]
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Time is 2110.
Commencing operation to
put Infernal to rest.
[COMPANY EIGHT]
Yes, sir!
[OBI] Shinra, Maki and I
will draw her attention,
then you can end this
with one good kick.
Right.
[OBI]
Let's do it!
[MAKI screams]
[OBI grunting]
[OBI] Thanks. Improved
Type Two Fire Ax thrust!
[SHINRA]
I made two promises.
That I'd be a hero, and
that I'd protect my family.
[SHINRA]
Mom. Sho. I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep
that last promise.
But I'll honor your memory
by becoming a hero.
[SHINRA]
Hope you're watching.
Here I go.
I refuse to be what
they say I am.
No matter what I have
to do, I will be a hero!
All set. Make me proud, hero!
[SHINRA]
Will do.
Sister! Start the prayer!
[IRIS]
Right.
Captain Obi!
[OBI] Good luck, Shinra!
Aim for the core!
[SHINRA'S GRANDMOTHER]
That boy is a devil!
[IRIS]
The flame is the soul's breath.
[PASSERBY B] Repulsive.
What a twisted smile.
[IRIS] The black smoke
is the soul's release.
Ashes thou wert and art.
May thy soul return...
I know you're in pain.
Just let go!
Oh, wow. The third generation's
as strong as they say.
...to the great flame of fire.
[IRIS]
Látom.
[MANAGER]
Sister, is‐is my wife...?
[IRIS]
Her soul is safe.
She's been returned
to the Great Fire.
Shinra put her to rest swiftly,
so she wouldn't suffer.
Thank you, Shinra. I'm grateful.
You set her free.
[CROWD cheering, applauding]
[OBI]
Feels pretty good, right?
You'll be receiving cheers
like these from now on.
[SHINRA'S MOTHER]
My little hero.
I'd say you've taken
a pretty big step
towards that goal of yours.