[PRIEST A] You needn't appear
in person, Your Excellency.
[PRIEST B]
It's essential that this crisis
needs to be addressed,
but let us‐‐
It's fine.
Assemble the eight
Company captains.
I'll speak with them.
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Goodness.
What the hell am I looking at?
[OBI yells]
Damn it, Shinra!
My locker has been
violated again!
Enough, already!
But, sir, I didn't do anything.
Shinra is very busy enjoying the
handmade lunch I just gave him.
Don't interrupt.
Guess this means you're
the one behind that mess.
Don't you have an entire company
you're s'posed to be
running right now?
Yes, but I thought I'd go
to the conference today
with you and Shinra.
Now, don't get the wrong idea.
I forgot I'd packed a lunch and
bought myself this sweet roll,
only to realize I had
more food than I needed.
I had no choice but
to give it to Shinra.
It isn't like I made it
for him specifically.
I'm not worrying about
lunch right now.
Shinra! Tell the captain
to cut this crap out.
Huh? How come? The lunch
is really good, sir.
Is it now? Glad you like it.
Damn it. She's playing dirty.
Help me out and I'll treat you
to all the ramen
you want sometime.
I do love ramen.
I'll come as well.
Go get yourself lost again.
What?
I want ramen, too!
She's coming! Run!
[TAMAKI screams]
[SHINRA]
Lucky, my butt.
[grumbles]
Hey. Do the two of
you want i‐‐? Er!
[MAKI, IRIS]
Oh! Wow!
Hinawa. She's playing with
fire inside the office.
I need to make sure we take
the best route to Central.
[SHINRA, ARTHUR,
TAMAKI shouting]
Just stay away from me,
you skirt‐snatching devil!
[SHINRA]
It fell off on its own!
[ARTHUR]
Begone, skirt devil!
There's a great bakery
not too far from here.
Yeah. We know. It's the best.
Maki and I go all the time.
Yeah, they just
updated their menu.
They've got more savories!
The cakes have always been
great, but now they have...
The place sure
has gotten lively.
[grunts]
You sure it's okay,
us two tagging along?
The topic of this conference
is the Evangelist
and the so‐called
White‐Clad organization.
You two are the best
sources of information
we have on the subject.
Do the captains have
conferences often?
Or is this something special?
[OBI]
It's rare.
This hasn't happened even once
since I took command
of the Eighth.
That should tell
you how seriously
the country's taking this.
[CHILD B screams]
[OBI]
Man‐made Infernals.
[ARROW] Direct hit.
Hoshimiya has been eliminated.
We should tell the
commander what happened.
[OBI]
The White‐Clad.
[laughs]
[REKKA] Behold the radiance
of the blazing star
ensconced in the heavens!
What greater end could we seek
than a return to
Sol's warm embrace?!
We will set all human
beings alight.
Engulf the Earth in the
great flame of fire!
Let its imperfections
be burned away
by the flames of salvation!
All is in accordance with
the will of the Evangelist!
[OBI]
Then there's this "Evangelist."
I have no doubt,
if we follow this trail,
we can end this Infernal
outbreak for good.
Oh, whoa! Is that
what I think it is?
Yeah. Of course.
Wait, have you never seen
it before? Cool, right?
That thermal plant was built
when the Solar calendar
was first put into place.
Our perpetual power
plant: Amaterasu.
Amaterasu provides electricity
for the entire Empire.
So it all comes from there?
Must have some crazy firepower.
Thanks again for everything
you did the other day.
[SHINRA] No. I should be
the one thanking you.
I'm Lieutenant Karim Flam.
Part of Company One.
Shinra told me all about
what happened with Rekka.
I want to find out
why Rekka betrayed us.
Towards that end, I want to work
with you guys at the Eighth.
I hear you're a capable
man, so thanks.
[GIOVANNI] I thought we shared
an allegiance to Haijima.
Was I mistaken?
What're you trying to say?
[GIOVANNI] You've been
spending quite a bit of time
with the Eighth.
[HIBANA]
Heh. You're being ridiculous.
The captains' conference
is about to start.
The Seventh is here,
and they don't normally
show up for anything.
Tells you how urgent this is.
That's their captain?
They say he's the strongest
soldier in the force. Crazy.
The hell are you
grinning at, snot face?
Waka.
Come on. Tent hands.
The time has come.
All Company captains, as well
as their guests, have arrived.
[RAFFLES III] Let's begin this
emergency conference at once.
I've spoken with the
general of the Tokyo Army
and the chief of the
Fire Defense Agency.
They told me of a group
acting in secret.
Threatening our nation's safety.
Indulging in blasphemy,
they would defile the
great Sol's blessings.
Brave captains of the
Special Fire Force,
I call on you to make these
blasphemers pay for their sins.
Would ya stop rambling
about your sun god?
What? Benimaru Shinmon!
You stand before
our great Emperor!
You should cease your insolence
and treat him with respect,
or face Gustav Honda's wrath!
Shut your mouth, Honda Gustav.
I don't like hearin' my
name said backwards.
He prefers his surname first?
[GIOVANNI] You must be
a proto‐nationalist.
Look, the Seventh is nothing
but a bunch of idiots
from the vigilante corps.
I don't recall swearing
any oaths to your god
or your empire.
We're gonna keep on
as we have been.
[GUSTAV] Hey! Come back!
We aren't finished talking yet!
Stop right there.
[door closes]
[RAFFLES III coughs]
As I was saying, I want all your
companies to work together
and defeat the Evangelist.
That will put us back on
the path to saving mankind
from the fear of the flames.
It sounds like they're
getting closer.
Not too shabby, Devilfoot.
He did it sooner than expected.
The boy has real potential.
Maybe I'll pay him
another visit soon.
Shinra Kusakabe.
[SHINRA]
Yes, sir!
[RAFFLES III] I understand
you possess an Adolla Burst.
Rekka Hoshimiya said that I did.
[SHINRA] Sir, what exactly
is an Adolla Burst?
[RAFFLES III] It is an unsullied
flame of absolute purity.
The primordial flame.
The spark from which Sol
fashioned the world we live in.
When you were coming here,
did you not see it?
[SHINRA]
Hm?
[RAFFLES III] Tokyo's perpetual
thermal energy plant.
Amaterasu provides power
for the whole Empire.
All that energy comes from
a flame, which, like yours,
is an Adolla Burst.
[GIOVANNI]
It seems that the Evangelist
wishes to obtain Adolla Bursts.
It's known that these are
flames of high purity.
But how they differ
from common flames
has yet to be explained
by science.
Unless the Evangelist found
the difference before we could.
[GIOVANNI] The Evangelist
will target Kusakabe.
Perhaps he should be secured.
Secured? Please
don't lock me up.
I joined the Force so
I could protect people.
I can look after
myself just fine.
There's no reason for companies
outside of the Eighth
to meddle in the
Eighth's affairs.
We should all focus our energy
on finding and hunting down
the White‐Clads.
The Third wants to use
Shinra as a specimen.
I guarantee Shinra's safety.
Company Eight will make sure
that he never gets captured.
The Adolla Burst is sacred,
and Sol has chosen
you to possess it,
so treat it with care.
Right.
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Goodness.
[OBI]
We're back.
[TAMAKI]
How've you guys been?
Not too bad.
I'll go make some tea.
[OBI] Felt like this tie
was gonna choke me.
[Pardon, sir, but didn't
Shinra go to Central with you?
[OBI]
Yeah.
But he wanted to
check out Amaterasu
and catch up with us later.
So, I'll cover for him
if we have to move
out before he's back.
With Tamaki 'n Arthur,
we're fine.
Heh. More work for me, eh?
[SHINRA] If the Evangelist
is planning to come to me,
that suits my purposes fine.
[JOKER]
Long time no see, Devilfoot.
[gasps]
How are ya?
[SHINRA]
You!
[JOKER] Adolla Bursts
are powerful things.
One serves as the power
source for the Amaterasu.
One was used to create
this very world.
Though I guess I should mention
it was also the cause of
this world's downfall.
Whoa, there. Calm down.
I'm not in the mood
for fisticuffs today.
Though if you insist on having
a 'bout, I'm up for it.
You don't actually think you'd
manage to get a lick in,
do ya, Devilfoot?
[JOKER chuckles]
I've graced you with my presence
'cause you earned a new clue.
Call it your reward for
finding the White‐Clad spy
and getting closer to the truth.
You're close already.
I came to turn suspicion
into certainty.
[SHINRA]
What are you saying?
[JOKER]
Keep pursuing that Evangelist
and you will find your brother.
The commander of the
Evangelist's Knights
of the Ashen Flame...
is Sho Kusakabe.
Your long‐lost brother.
So then, Sho is with the
Evangelist serving as a knight?
What do you mean?! Uh!
Joker!
[JOKER] Hell is a perfect
fit for a Devil.
[SHINRA]
Mom. Sho. I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep
that last promise.
[SHINRA]
Mom. Sho!
[SHINRA'S MOTHER wails]
[SHINRA]
I failed...
But there's still a
promise I can keep.
If what he says is true,
then soon, I'll have
to fight my brother.
I said I'd become a superhero.
I said I'd keep
Mom and Sho safe.
I was too weak to protect Mom,
but I'm strong now.
And that promise
binds me to Sho‐‐
every bit as much as
the blood we share.
So I won't break my
word. Not again.
The Fire Force has been ordered
to go after the Evangelist.
To start, we'll look for clues
in every fire report
we've filed.
This is only a fraction
of what we have.
Be fast, but thorough.
If it might relate to the
White‐Clad, call it out.
The Evangelist and
the White‐Clad group
have been forcefully turning
humans into Infernals
for unknown reasons.
We can't allow even one of
them to get away with it.
Go get started.
[sighs]
[BOTH]
Uh?
Hey, Shinra. Hurry up and
find us a lead already.
What's the matter?
All this heavy brain‐work
takin' its toll on ya?
Just keep goin'
till ya die, okay?
[wheezing]
Like watchin' a candle
in the wind. Sweet.
Let's take a little
break for now.
[SHINRA]
Aw.
But if Arthur goes any
longer, he's gonna die.
Let's keep pushing.
[stomach growls]
Sister Iris should get
back from consoling
the next of kin before too long.
Why don't we girls cook
something for everyone?
Sure, I'm down!
How's that sound
to you, Lieutenant?
Could go poorly. Prob'ly will.
I just ignore him when he's
rude. It's fine, let's go.
I bet Maki's a great cook.
[gasps]
[HINAWA]
What's this?
[MAKI, TAMAKI scream]
Crap! Maki!
[TAMAKI] Cut it out, Kusakabe!
Don't look at me!
How in the blue blazes did
you end up looking like that?
You put the apron
over your clothes!
Yeah, she's a bit
of an exception
when it comes to
the laws of physics.
[sighs]
[HINAWA] Maki, go get Tamaki
back in her uniform, okay?
I'll handle dinner.
[TAMAKI yells]
You're helping, Shinra.
Uh. Sure. Will do.
Are you okay?
[SHINRA]
Uh?
[HINAWA] If it's not
something you can tell me,
you should go to the captain.
Y'know, I'm really
fond of this company.
I know it can be difficult,
but I'd like you rookies
to be able to trust us.
[SHINRA]
Honestly, Lieutenant,
I think I like it at the
Eighth just as much as you.
As for the other thing,
I do trust you.
You and the captain.
So, thanks.
[HINAWA]
No problem.
Dinner's ready everyone!
It's all set in the dining room.
Yay!
[grunts]
So how do you think
Shinra's holding up?
We put a lot on his shoulders
in the investigations
of the Fifth and the First.
You haven't recruited
any pushovers, sir.
Shinra's gonna be all right.
No doubt in my mind.
[TAMAKI] Awesome!
You made this, Kusakabe?
Nah. Just helped out
the lieutenant.
[TAMAKI]
Uh...
[ALL]
Thank you for this meal!
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Thank you for this meal.
Take time to chew, will ya?
Thank goodness.
It looks like you're
feeling better.
We were talking about how
weird you'd been acting.
I thought maybe you had an
upset stomach or something.
But if you're eating that much,
you must be fine.
Listen, everyone,
I know it's sudden,
but I need to say something.
Truth is...
[SHINRA]
I told them.
About meeting Joker.
About my brother, Sho.
Company Eight felt like family,
and I decided to trust them.
It's quite the tale.
But all of this is coming
from Joker, right?
Do you think we can trust it?
Couldn't tell ya.
I dunno what to believe.
In that case...
[OBI]
Shinra.
[SHINRA]
Huh?
Tell me.
Do you want to believe that
your brother's still alive?
Because that's what matters.
Yes, sir, I do.
Understood.
Well, then, all of us'll
have to believe he is, too.
We still need to go
after the Evangelist.
But we'll form our strategy
around the premise
that Shinra's brother
is with him.
[SHINRA]
Thanks so much, sir.
[EVANGELIST FOLLOWERS] We will
set all lost souls alight.
Burn the earth beneath our feet,
and make this planet
a flaming sun.
A scorched throne worthy of god.
All is in accordance with
the will of the Evangelist.
Látom.