[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that long,
morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
Seems the Eighth and the Fifth
had a joint training session.
Quite the cover story.
It sounds like Obi's
finally making his move.
[HINAWA]
To grill is to pit one's skill
against the fury of the flames.
[MAMORU‐KUN ]
To grill is to pit one's skill
against the fury of th‐‐
[megaphone hums]
[OBI]
Uh. Ladies. Gentlemen.
Well, first of all,
we're glad to have you here
for our "job well done" party.
The Nighttime Joint Exercise
was a big success,
so thank you.
Uh, when I spoke to Captain‐‐
or I guess it's Princess
Hibana, there‐‐ Whatever.
Self‐satisfied punk.
[KISHIRI groans]
[HIBANA] Gravel does not
speak‐‐does not even breathe
without my permission!
Right, Shinra?
Owie.
[OBI] Uh... we do
appreciate you taking on
a smaller company like ours.
[HINAWA]
Enjoy.
Yeah. Sure.
[SPUTTER]
Sputter‐sput.
[FLARE]
Flare.
There we are.
‐‐[SPUTTER] Sputter, sputter.
‐‐[FLARE] Flare, flare.
[ANGEL A, ANGEL B]
OOh.
[DARK‐HAIRED ONE, ANGEL C]
Aww.
[IRIS gasps]
[SPUTTER]
Sputter!
Begone! You damn Will‐o‐Wisps!
Hey, what are you
doing that for?
The lieutenant said if you
tried to play with fire,
my duty would be
to snuff it out.
[MAKI]
We're here to enjoy ourselves!
[MAMORU‐KUN]
Látom.
[IRIS]
Huh?
[OBI groans]
[OBI]
Just to be sure,
are you saying we have the
full cooperation of the Fifth?
[HIBANA]
Not the whole Company's,
but I'll cooperate personally.
As I'm sure you realize,
the Fifth is aligned with
Haijima Industries.
As things stand, Company
Eight would be hard‐pressed
to confront that
corporation directly.
You planned to start
by destroying the Fifth
and exposing our
research, correct?
[OBI]
Yeah.
How did you come by your
intel on the Fifth anyway?
Were Iris' actions
a part of your plan?
That was all her, I promise.
That said, I did figure she'd be
an ace up my sleeve with you.
[grumbles]
[HIBANA] You answered
one question vaguely
and ignored the other.
Well, I doubt a meathead
ape like yourself
could understand
the Fifth's research.
You should be grateful
to have my help,
'cause you're certainly
going to need it.
[OBI]
Why the sudden change of heart?
[HIBANA]
I once went through something
that turned my faith
in flame to despair.
The more I learned of
this country, this world,
the deeper that
despair took root.
I told myself that
my growing cynicism
was making me stronger.
Smarter.
I thought that to face
this crummy world,
my only hope was to
fight evil with evil.
Then, when a self‐proclaimed
hero named Shinra beat me,
I remembered...
Justice can be gentle.
Flame can keep you warm.
He showed me that it's possible
to stand against evil
without allowing it
to taint who you are.
[OBI]
From the way you talk about him,
it almost sounds like
he's your hero.
[HIBANA]
Ew. No. It's nothing so trite.
No shame in admiring a
hero's courage, Princess.
Honestly, I think his
light'll guide us
out of this dark
prison of flame.
[HIBANA] So your mission is to
investigate the other companies
in order to solve the
mystery of the flames.
[OBI] Yeah. That's why we
came to steal your research.
I heard that you made
quite the discovery.
Something related to the
cause of human combustion.
Did I hear right?
Yeah. And it may help you
to see why I turned devil.
Someone out there is
deliberately creating Infernals.
That said, I'm not
suggesting every
spontaneous human
combustion case is murder,
but certain samples I studied
were very different
from the others.
I can explain in detail later.
[OBI] I can't believe
someone out there
is sick enough to do that.
Well, they won't
get away with it.
I will hunt them down.
[HIBANA] The nuns, my friends,
all burned to death.
If a human being was
responsible for their pain...
...then I swear by
St. John's wort
and the malice it symbolizes,
I'll do whatever it takes to
find them and burn them alive.
[OBI] Sounds like we're
both after the same mark.
[HIBANA]
Hpmh. I guess that's true.
Of course, this investigation of
yours will only get harder now.
Yeah? How do you mean?
[HIBANA]
The suspected manmade Infernals
all have something in common.
They were first sighted
near Shinjuku Ward.
But that's...
Company One's turf.
Pardon, Sister, but what are
you doing here at the Eighth?
[HIBANA]
Hmm?
[gasps]
I mostly came by to make sure
you've been maturing properly.
Hey! Stop it.
That's a dirty move.
That's rather rude.
I'll have you know I'm
quite clean right now.
You know that's not
what I meant, Sister!
[MAKI] It must be nice
for the two of you,
having such soft,
feminine figures.
Oh, come on.
I say those hard‐earned muscles
are beautiful in
their own right.
D'ya mean it?
That's kinda nice to hear.
Sister, you're planning
something dangerous, right?
Yes.
I'm working with your captain
to investigate Company One.
There's a chance
it leads to war.
[HIBANA] A surreptitious
investigation of the First
using the rookie training
reassignment system?
Not bad, Obi. That might work.
Yeah, "The rookie training
reassignment system
enables first‐year crew members
to broaden their experience
by getting temporarily assigned
to different companies."
I'm gonna use this to
send the two of you
to Company One as spies.
So we're going to
the First undercover?
Just me and Arthur?
Somebody in their jurisdiction‐‐
perhaps in their company‐‐
has potentially been turning
human beings into Infernals
through artificial means.
Try to come up with
any leads you can.
This could be the key
to cracking the mystery
of human combustion,
so be careful.
Best of luck.
I'm on it, Captain.
If someone really is causing
human combustion, they'll pay.
They may begin to
suspect something
if they're only assigned
recruits from the Eighth.
I'll send one of
my soldiers, too.
And I'll have a word with
some other companies.
So this is the Holy
Sol Obelisk, huh?
Think it's even taller
than I'd imagined.
I bet I could climb it.
Pretty lame if you ask me.
Company One's Grand
Cathedral is so sacred.
I don't feel like I'm worthy.
Who're these guys?
They're camouflage, okay?
You should try to
make nice with them.
Thank you for your help.
[BOTH]
Uh.
[SHINRA]
Hm?
So you're the newbie‐in‐
training rookie noobs.
Sheesh. I bet even
your crap is crap.
Are you crappy? You crap?
[growls]
Huh?
[KARIM]
"I bet even your crap is crap.
Are you crappy? You crap?"
[SHINRA] I feel like he's
trying to insult us,
but it sounds like he's
just talkin' about crap.
You bet your ass I know
an ass when I see one.
And your ass is an
ass like any other.
Get me?
What did you say?!
Calm down.
He's basically just telling
you that your ass is an ass.
Huh?
[ARTHUR grunts]
[KARIM] Captain Burns
is expecting you all.
Come with me.
[SHINRA]
Company One's Captain Burns.
He was at the fire,
12 years ago.
[SHINRA]
He knows something.
He'll be waiting
before the altar.
[SHINRA] If someone caused it
on purpose, I need to know.
Company One welcomes you.
I'm glad you recruits
could join us.
[SHINRA]
And I'm one step closer.
It's bad form, wearing those
uniforms in a Church.
Cut 'em some slack.
They didn't know.
I am Maki Oze!
First Class Fire Soldier.
Here from Company Eight.
I've brought the new
recruits in for training!
We're speaking as soldiers,
but we're still in
the Grand Cathedral.
Forgive me for asking,
but I would prefer for you to
tent hands rather than salute.
[gasps]
Of course, sir. My apologies.
I'll introduce
Lieutenant Karim Flam,
Lieutenant Rekka Hoshimiya,
and Lieutenant Huo Yan Li.
They'll be looking after you for
the duration of your training.
You're free to look
around the premises.
We want you to feel
at home here.
'Scuse me, Captain Burns,
I know this is sudden...
[BURNS]
Hm?
[SHINRA]
But I thought I'd ask.
To give you a chance to
assess our abilities,
why don't we start our training
with a quick sparring match?
[MAKI] Wait, Shinra.
Did you really just say that?
We read about all your abilities
in the paperwork
that came with you,
so there's no need for that.
That's all right.
Rekka, help me give
all of 'em a workout.
Huh? Do you mean it?
Calm down. We're in
the Grand Cathedral.
Ahem. Right.
[MAKI] What do you think
you're doing, Shinra?
[KISHIRI]
This is so lame.
[SHINRA]
Throwing a light jab.
If I manage to beat you,
there's something I'd
like to ask you about.
That's fine by me.
[OBI groans]
[OBI]
Hope those kids are okay.
There's nothing more
you can do to help them,
so there's no point worrying.
Well, be that as it may,
worrying is still a
captain's prerogative.
I can't work like this.
Hey, stop complaining.
Just get back to it.
[HINAWA] Why don't you "get
back" to your post at the Fifth?
[giggles]
[HIBANA] I hope Shinra doesn't
get too full of himself
because he beat me.
That Captain Burns is
a seasoned veteran.
Shinra!
You just got here and
you're already sparring
with Captain Burns?!
It isn't fair!
The captain hasn't even
sparred with me before!
[TAMAKI] If that twerp
hurts Lieutenant Rekka,
I'll cave his cocky face in!
[SHINRA]
I'm gonna do this, damn it!
I'll make him spill
everything he knows!
Is your friend all right?
He seems to be a
little aggravated.
I think he's just so
delighted to be at the First
that he can't contain himself.
Then he's a
high‐spirited crewman!
Sweet! I'm getting all fired up!
[chuckles]
So which of us should go first?
How 'bout we start
with the recruit
from the lowest‐numbered
company?
There's no need to hold back.
I want you to put your
full power on display.
[TAKERU]
The lowest‐numbered company...
Huh?! I have to go first?
[chuckles] Hey, I'm
Lieutenant Hoshimiya.
Seems the two of
us'll be sparring.
[TAKERU] I'm Second Class
Fire Soldier Takeru Noto.
My family owns a jahgaimo farm,
so I started getting
called "Jaga Noto."
And then that turned
into "Juggernaut."
I'm looking forward to
a heated match, okay?
[TAKERU]
No. No fire, please!
Ya think this guy's okay?
[TAKERU]
Oh, no. This is just awful.
Now there's fire coming from me!
Somebody put it out! Please!
That's what I like
to see, buddy!
Those flames symbolize
your burning passion!
[TAKERU]
That is not what this is!
I'm just scared! Really scared!
Ah! It's so hot!
You and I like it
hot, Juggernaut.
Keep on pushin'. Lemme see
the best flames you've got!
[BURNS] That enthusiasm's
always set to broil.
[LI]
Yeah. I'm a little worried.
[KARIM]
I'll deal with any stray shots.
[LI]
See that you do.
Good grief.
This nuisance really is an
annoying thorn in my side.
I'm simmering!
Oh, man, the Special Fire Force
has been waiting for talent
like yours, ya know?
[TAKERU]
Don't talk like that!
You're gonna get me stirred up.
I'm scared of fire!
I joined the Special Fire Force
because I wanted to get
my flames put out!
But you guys just
keep fanning them!
The heat you're puttin'
out is incredible!
Every last shot has the
force of a juggernaut!
Lieutenant Rekka!
[REKKA]
Nice one! Keep it up!
[laughs]
[growls]
[REKKA yells]
Ya dodged 'em all,
ya lazy slacker sloth.
It's all good,
'cause I've got you
backin' me up, Karim!
What the‐‐?
He stopped them.
But that much energy can't
have just been erased.
So he froze all that flame?
Damn it, Rekka!
That might'a burned
the Captain's uniform
if I hadn't been here!
[REKKA] But you were here!
And I totally believe in you!
Does the First really
have a Fire Soldier
who conjures frost
instead of flame?
[KARIM]
Hm?
I'm just a regular
second‐generation.
You really think I have
some kinda frost powers?
Then where'd that ice come from?
It's called Thermo‐
Acoustic Cooling.
It's a technique that allows me
to convert the heat energy
of flame into sound
by compressing it
in a specific way.
As that sound abrades the air,
it's converted into cold.
So you can take a fire's heat
and convert it into
sound to freeze it over?
I didn't even realize
that was possible!
[ARTHUR]
Huh?
[SHINRA] Someone in
or near the First
is artificially turning
people Infernal.
The culprit could be
one of these guys.
Or it could be all three.
Let's start the next.
I only fight when I see
an essential purpose.
You'll have to excuse me.
Yeah, so, uh,
I can only do the stuff
on my paperwork,
which means you should know what
I can do without me fighting.
That okay?
That leaves Company Eight.
You two fight as a team.
I'll take on both o' ya.
Why would the Captain agree
to waste his time on them?
Bring it on.
Chivalry dictates that
we take turns,
and since I'm gonna beat
him, you won't get one.
Have at thee.
[ARTHUR yells]
What are you planning
to do with that hand?
Fight me with all you have.
If you don't, this match
will be completely devoid
of any meaning.
Fine, but don't blame
me if you lose an arm.
You would need to wield a hotter
flame than that one to cut me.
Set your mind at ease.
"A hotter flame than that"?
What's hotter than
Arthur's Excalibur?
He can even use that blade
to cut through steel.
[ARTHUR]
At least I warned you!
[gasps]
Your sword kills
with one strike,
but what if it should fail you?
No way. Not even the ogress
could extinguish Excalibur.
What are you waiting for?
Don't ease up on him now!
That crewman packs some
impressive firepower, too.
Step back or you'll be killed.
Unreal.
A question for you:
Why join the Fire Force?
I lost both my mom and
my brother in a fire.
I joined the Force to solve the
mystery of human combustion
and make fires like that
a thing of the past.
To become a hero who
can save the world
from the terror of the flames!
You still have a long way to go.
Let me bid each of you
welcome to Company One.
You'll be here but
for a short time.
I suggest you work hard
and make the most of it.
Are you hurt, Captain?
That was amazing!
[TAMAKI grunts]
[screams]
[TAMAKI]
Ah?!
Ah...
Gotcha.
Your Lucky Lecher Lure is
no match for my reflexes.
We're good.
Thank you, Lieutenant Rekka.
I'm so sorry! You
always have to help me!
[footsteps]
You Company Eight
guys'll train under me.
You two never had a chance
against Captain Burns.
But you still did all right,
in a fairly decent way.
Of course we did.
Thank you for saying so, sir.
But whether your pace keeps
you apace of our pace,
or whether your pace gets
outpaced by our pace,
just try to hang in there, okay?
Thank you very much, sir!
[ARTHUR]
Huh?