[OBI] Causes of death
are many and varied.
Old age. Illness. Suicide.
But out of that long,
morbid list,
there's one end that people
fear above all others...
[PEOPLE chattering]
Tamaya!
Kagiya!
[OBI]
It really is a festival.
This must be a way of mourning
that's unique to Asakusa.
It's different from most
proto‐nationalist funerals.
Let's get these
repairs started quickly.
[7TH CREWMEN]
Right!
If I destroyed your house
during Kantaro's send‐off,
you're welcome to stay
at the guardhouse.
We'll look after you
until it's been fixed.
I don't think it'll
take too long.
Hey, Captain, would it
be all right with you
if I helped out with
repairs as well?
Good idea.
Doubt they'll talk to us while
they're dealing with this,
so we may as well help
speed things along.
[BENIMARU]
Huh? Hey!
[SHINRA]
Please let the Eighth help!
Thanks to my powers,
I can carry heavy loads
to high places no problem.
Let me get all this wreckage
outta the way for you.
You can leave the
welding work to me.
[7TH CREWMAN A]
Huh. Not bad.
Whoa.
[7TH CREWMEN gasp]
Think we'll have to get a
truck over here to move this.
[yells]
[7TH CREWMEN gasp]
Aw, why?
[7TH CREWMEN yelling]
[MAN]
I saw Company Eight's Matchbox
parked on Yagen
Street in Asakusa.
Why would the Eighth be in
the Seventh's jurisdiction?
[ARROW]
When the Eighth moved
to investigate Company
One's jurisdiction,
it was because of Rekka.
They may have caught
our scent here.
What does the
Evangelist command?
[ARROW]
We failed to kill them before,
so we're to finish the job now.
[ARROW] Prepare the traps.
The bugs, too.
[7TH CREWMAN D]
Today's work is done!
[7TH CREWMAN E]
Call it a day and rest up!
You honestly don't
have to do this, Waka.
[BENIMARU] I do, the youngsters
have been out there
working their butts
off rebuilding,
so this is the least I can do.
Well, thank you.
[KONRO gasps]
Does that hurt?
I'm fine. The cold
just surprised me.
You know, Konro, honestly,
I still think you're the one
who should've become captain.
Well, I don't. Company Seven
is a bunch of rowdy thugs.
I can't fight anymore,
which means I'd never
make it as their captain.
[BOTH giggle]
[HINATA]
Konro!
[HIKAGE]
Waka!
[SHINRA]
Hey, hold on!
Hello, girls. How goes it?
That damn twerp keeps
chasin' us around.
I think he's try'na eat us.
Yeah, it's pretty
friggin' screwed up.
[SHINRA] I was nice enough
to play tag with you
and this is my reward?
Didn't you like seeing
my spinning fire top?
Spinning fire top?
He shoots fire out of his feet,
and then he spins
around on his head!
It's really stupid.
[HINATA, HIKAGE]
Yay! Ha‐ha!
It's a cool dance move
called break‐dancing.
It's not stupid, it's
difficult and awesome.
Heh. Such a kid.
Thanks for the help.
I appreciate it.
I know what a handful these
runts can be, and you...
Call us runts again and
we'll smoosh you, Konro!
No sweat. I'm pretty good at
keeping children entertained.
[HINATA]
Treat us like kids again
and we'll smoosh you, Shinra!
Come on. I'll show you one
more spinning fire top.
[HIKAGE] Shut up! Don't tell
us what to do, you punk!
[HIKAGE yelps]
These Company Eight people,
they aren't a bad
bunch to be around.
I feel like they're
a different sort
than the other companies.
They remind me of us in a way.
I suppose so.
[KONRO] Why don't we help
with their investigation?
So is that what you would
do if you were our captain?
Waka, you weren't chosen
to be this company's captain
just because of your power.
Do you know why Company Eight
chose to help us today? 'Cause‐‐
Just give it a rest. I've heard
you say all this before.
Sorry, but I'm not cut
out for this crap.
I never should have
been made a leader.
Face forward, will ya, Konro?
I can't wrap your
bandage like this.
Think we will help 'em.
Company Eight is pretty
all right in my book.
[BOTH]
Ah! Waka!
Sorry about the intrusion, sir.
That? There's no
need to sweat it.
So, hey, about
Lieutenant Konro's body.
[BENIMARU] When a third
generation continues
to use their powers
after overheating,
their body starts to incinerate,
and their flesh becomes ash.
Tephrosis. This the first
you've heard of it?
They taught us about
it at the Academy.
Never saw it though.
Not in person.
When it happened, I...
[BENIMARU]
Shinra, I'd like to have
a few words with your captain.
Is he around?
Oh. Right. That's actually
why I came here.
Captain Obi sent me to
ask if you'd meet him.
He's across the way, over in
that back alley by the river.
[BOTH]
Yay!
What're you gonna do now?
The Eighth stayin' in town?
As long as you're around,
you could always stay with
us here at the station.
It's not something
we were planning on,
but since we helped
with all those repairs,
our relationship with
Company Seven
has improved quite a bit.
Quick question, Missy.
You wanna strip for us again?
That's not gonna happen!
Hopefully, they'll allow us
to start our investigation now.
Oh, yeah.
I was just with Captain
Shinmon, and last I saw,
he was heading off
to meet with Obi.
Think they'll end up
working something out.
We haven't found anything
but breadcrumbs yet.
But we're on the
White‐Clads' trail.
I know we had to leave her
'cause of all the
proto‐nationalists,
but I feel weird
without Iris around.
And I'm glad the Fifth's
holding things down for us,
but we need to start
this investigation ASAP.
The sooner we can get this
mess figured out, the better.
Hurry up and get
rid of all this.
We need to clear more space
for Shinra's new desk.
You can toss Obi's junk outside.
Uh. Hey, could you not?
Apologies, Captain,
but why are we doing all this?
[HIBANA]
They need to learn
not to boss Company Five around.
Shouldn't you have just
told them "no" then?
Látom.
Where does a worthless,
lowly piece of gravel like you
get off telling me
what I should do?
Yes, I'm nothing
but a lump of gravel.
Punish me till you're satisfied!
Owie! Owie! Oh!
Stomp even harder, please!
[OBI]
That went well, don't you think?
[BENIMARU]
Hm?
[HINAWA]
Yes, it did.
[OBI] We turned that
Kantaro guy Infernal,
and they're none the wiser.
[HINAWA]
That's true.
Let's turn as many
of these people
as we can into Infernals.
Agreed.
[gasps]
[7TH CREWMAN H]
A fire!
[SHINRA]
Maki!
We need to assess the situation.
Let's try to avoid
doing anything rash
until we've met up
with Captain Obi.
[OBI]
What's going on here?
Why is he attacking us?
[HINAWA] I told you not to eat
Company Seven's daifuku!
[growls] I only had one of them,
though. He's overreacting!
You're dead.
[OBI]
What did we do?
[BENIMARU]
Shut up!
No chance in hell are
you talking your way
out of this one.
You're the ones who turned
Kantaro into an Infernal.
[OBI]
Hm?
[OBI] Wait a second,
you think that was us?
Captain Shinmon, what
are you talking about?
No point playing dumb.
I saw you and heard you.
I know you plan to
bury my town in ash,
but you screwed up big time.
Because now that I know,
you've got no chance!
I don't know what you saw, sir,
but please calm down
so we can talk.
Screw that. There's
nothing to say.
Your Evangelist is made up.
My real enemy's here.
I saw your captain
and lieutenant
plotting to turn the people
of this town into Infernals.
And I will make them pay!
You're making a mistake!
I'll beat all of you to a pulp,
and then hang you out to dry.
[BENIMARU] I know exactly what
I saw. It was definitely them.
Captain, doesn't sound
like he's messing around.
Wait a minute, please!
We didn't come out here
to start a fight.
[BENIMARU] If that's the
story you're sticking to,
then beat me and
prove you're innocent.
Might makes right around here!
If you didn't wanna
start this fight,
then prove your point
by ending it.
You'd best get ready,
Company Eight.
You're about to face
Shinmon Benimaru.
Looks like we managed
to provoke him.
Yeah.
Then let's move
forward as planned.
Hinawa!
Leave it to me, sir.
Waka! The musclebound
idiot's running away!
[BENIMARU] Hiding behind
women and children now?
Guess he's a murderer
and a coward!
Everyone, stay back!
I'm a Fire Soldier
just like you.
Don't look down on me.
Ya think you blocked that?
Maki!
[MAKI screams]
[gunshots]
[BENIMARU] Fire that
peashooter all you want,
you'll never hit me.
[HINAWA] I wasn't
really expecting to.
That said, I'd like to see what
limits your strength might have.
Can you wield your second‐ and
third‐gen powers in tandem?
Let's find out! Get him!
[TAMAKI yells]
[ARTHUR yells]
You guys are finished.
Iai Chop, Form One...
...Fire Moon.
Is that the best
your company's got?
[BOTH gasp]
[footstep]
[BENIMARU]
Hm?
When you go after my
soldiers, you answer to me.
He was just suiting up?
[OBI] Let's settle this‐‐
captain to captain.
Why the hell would you turn an
innocent man into an Infernal?
[OBI] You won't listen
to a word I have to say.
So you may as well
shut up and bring it on!
[BENIMARU] You finally ready
to drop the act, you scum?
[BENIMARU]
Hm?
You're not putting
out my flames.
[OBI]
Put them out?
I'd love to if that
were possible...
...but I don't have any powers.
[BENIMARU]
You're kidding.
Then shouldn't you be
afraid of all this fire?
[OBI]
Damn right I am. It burns!
[BENIMARU] If you know how
terrifying flames can be,
then how could you
bring yourself
to turn Kantaro infernal?
[OBI] I'm telling you, there's
been some kind of mistake!
[BENIMARU]
There was no mistake.
I know what I saw!
Captain, no!
[OBI] I don't care if you're
second gen, third gen, or both.
I train every single day.
An extinguisher grenade?
[gasps]
[BENIMARU]
You gassed yourself, too?
[OBI]
And let that be a lesson to ya.
It's almost like you
don't know how to flinch.
I can't afford to
flinch right now.
Not when I'm carrying the
weight of Company Eight
on my shoulders.
What's the deal with
that muscle guy?
He doesn't have powers.
Then how did he
manage to hit Waka?
How did he do that? The
captain's really that strong?
Did you think he was a pushover?
That said, strong or not,
he shouldn't act so recklessly.
Captains Obi and Shinmon are
both charismatic figures.
Whatever paths they take,
others will follow.
We can't allow this fight
to continue for much longer.
Is there a way we
can make them stop?
It seems as though beating
him is the only way
to set the record straight.
Waka!
Let him have it!
What's all this
commotion about?
Apparently these Eighth
people are the ones
who turned Kantaro infernal.
Waka snapped and
started a fight!
[BOTH]
Munch!
That can't be right.
It's too absurd.
None of these things
you do add up.
When'll you start making sense?
So you won't go down to anything
less than my best stuff.
[grunts]
Guess I'll stop playing then.
What is he doing now?
[KONRO]
No!
Here goes. Iai Chop,
Form Seven: Sun Wheel.
Waka, hold on!
Don't try to stop me.
These people aren't
what they seem.
They turned Kantaro infernal
and they wanna do the same with
everyone else in this town.
What makes you think that?
I saw this one
and his lieutenant
plotting the whole thing out.
How many times do I have to tell
you that you've made a mistake?!
Enough talk.
Let me do this, Konro.
No. You need to calm down.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you using
your pyrokinesis?
[KONRO groaning]
Hinata! Hikage! Bring
me a cooling blanket!
Can do!
We're on the job!
Waka, as a favor to me,
would you at least hear out
what they have to say?
[sighs]
Okay.
When Waka thinks he saw you,
where were you two actually?
The captain and I
were both at the store
stocking up on a few essential
supplies that we'd run short on.
We informed Fire Soldier
Maki before we left.
Yeah. They told me.
Hold on. He didn't mention
anything about the store to me.
He told me to go and
ask Captain Shinmon
to meet him and the
lieutenant in that alley.
[BENIMARU]
That's right you did.
I agreed and then
headed Obi's way.
Only I don't remember
ever saying that.
The hell is this?
Tryin' to fool him, too?
I'll ask the store
clerk to confirm this.
[BENIMARU]
For Konro's sake,
I'm delaying your judgment.
Try to leave before
I say you can
and there will be violence.
Sorry about him.
Waka's always been
a stubborn one.
That's just as true now
as it's ever been.
Lieutenant Konro, not to pry,
but how did you
end up like this?
Bottom line, I wasn't
strong enough.
Was Captain Shinmon with you?
He seemed to have
regrets about it.
[KONRO]
None of this was his fault.
Waka didn't do anything wrong.
[KONRO]
I'll just tell you.
This was a while back,
before we were recognized
as a Fire Force Company.
‐‐[PEOPLE screaming]
‐‐[bell clanging]
[7TH CREWMAN I]
Everyone run to the river!
What the hell's going on?
How can this many
people have turned?
Why're they all going
Infernal tonight?
I'm as confused as you are.
Let's just focus on
evacuation for now.
Where's the Fire Force?
Don't you think they should've
gotten here a while ago?
Yeah, but we can't rely on them.
We'll do this ourselves.
[BENIMARU groaning]
[KONRO]
Beni!
[BENIMARU]
Damn it. I can't breathe.
Hard as I try, I just can't
seem to get any oxygen in.
[KONRO] You're at your
pyrokinetic limit.
Stay here. I'll be back.
Not a chance, dumbass.
We both know you're in
the same boat as me.
[BENIMARU]
What?
[KONRO]
What is that thing?
A demon!
[DEMON INFERNAL roars]
[KONRO] That Infernal...
it isn't like the others.
[KONRO]
Damn it.
[BENIMARU]
What are you doing?
Konro!
I'm sorry,
but with a rambunctious
little brat like you,
there was no other way
to get you to sit still.
[KONRO]
It's too soon, Beni.
I can't let your
fire go out yet.
[KONRO]
Rest up. I'll deal with this.