- ( theme music playing )
- ( tires squeal, engine revs )
- ( pop music playing )
- YOU DIDN'T HIT THAT CORNER
TIGHT ENOUGH, MAKO.
- ( gasps )
- I'D EXPECT A TIGHTER
LINE FROM YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE
BETTER THAN THAT.
YOU'RE OFF BY LIKE
FIVE INCHES.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- HMM?
HEY, LOOK.
SOMEONE'S COMING DOWN THE PASS.
MAKO'S SIL-EIGHTY!
SHE ROCKS THIS PASS.
- SO FREAKING COOL.
- NOTHING MOVES SWEETER
THAN USUI'S FASTEST.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE CALLED
"IMPACT BLUE."
- Sayuki:
OH, YOU SUCK TONIGHT!
THIS CRAP DRIVING'S
NOT LIKE YOU, MAKO.
CONCENTRATE. WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS, HUH?
Sayuki: SO THAT'S HOW
IT ALL WENT DOWN.
I WAS WONDERING.
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT YOU GOT DUMPED
BY IKETANI. YOU'RE SO WAY
OUT OF HIS LEAGUE ANYWAY.
- I KNOW.
YOU'VE SAID THAT BEFORE,
BUT STILL.
- IT'S COMING TOGETHER
FOR ME NOW.
NO WONDER YOU'VE BEEN
DRIVING LIKE A LOOSE CANNON.
YOU'RE THE TYPE OF PERSON
WHO'S DRIVING MIRRORS
EXACTLY HOW YOU'RE FEELING.
RACING WITH YOUR EMOTIONS,
THAT'S YOUR STYLE.
- Yuuichi:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO NOW?!
- ( gasps )
- BEING IN LOVE MEANS
YOU ACCEPT EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE OTHER PERSON
THE WAY THEY ARE. I MEAN,
THAT'S WHAT LOVE'S ALL ABOUT.
- ( stammers )
- YOU WON'T KNOW IF
SHE'S WAITING FOR YOU OR NOT
TILL YOU GO.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW
OR YOU'RE FIRED.
- ( groans )
-  MEET ME AT 8:00
AT THE KAMAMESHI BILLBOARD
WHERE WE MET.
I'LL BE THERE.
- Iketani:
BOSS IS RIGHT.  I'M SO STUPID.
SHE WAS ALWAYS
STRAIGHT UP WITH ME.
BUT I COULDN'T DO IT BACK.
I'M SUCH A JACKASS.
- MY FEET ARE KILLING ME.
I HATE HEELS.
- OH, PLEASE, PLEASE.
JUST ONE MORE CHANCE.
( gasps )
NO!  THERE'S AN ACCIDENT?
- ( crying )
I'M NEVER WEARING
HIGH HEELS AGAIN.
- ( engine starts )
- ( tires screech )
- I CAN'T FATHOM HOW ANYONE
WOULD WANT TO BREAK UP WITH YOU.
YOU'RE AWESOME.
AND HE LOOKED LIKE
HE WAS OVER THE MOON
CRAZY FOR YOU TOO.
BUT I GUESS THAT'S
GUYS FOR YOU.
MAYBE YOU TWO GOT
YOUR MEETING TIMES MIXED UP?
- I THOUGHT ABOUT THAT, SO I
STAYED THERE WAITING FOR HIM.
I WAS THERE FOREVER AFTER
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO MEET,
BUT NOTHING.
- AND THE JERK NEVER
EVEN BOTHERED TO CALL YOU?
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST CALL HIM?
- I COULDN'T BE THAT FORWARD.
YOU KNOW THAT.
BESIDES, AFTER WAITING THERE
FOR THREE EXTRA HOURS,
I WAS HUMILIATED.
AND THE FACT THAT
HE HASN'T EVEN BOTHERED
TO CALL ME AFTER THAT NIGHT?
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT MEANS
HE'S NOT INTERESTED.
- ( sighs )
SOUNDS LIKE YOU WERE
REALLY STOKED OVER THIS GUY.
THAT REALLY SUCKS.
STOKED ENOUGH THAT IT
JACKED WITH HOW YOU'RE
HANDLING YOURSELF
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
- YEAH.  AND I WAS READY TO
HAND IT ALL OVER TO HIM.
- HUH?  HAND WHAT?
- ME.
- ( coughing )
I CAN'T TELL IF YOU'RE
SOME NAIVE LITTLE GIRL
OR A WALKING SET OF
BRASS BALLS.
I REALLY CAN'T.
YOU GOTTA FILL ME IN.
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT THIS GUY ANYWAY?
- IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
HE'S SINCERE AND GENTLE.
HE WAS NEVER PUSHY.
WHENEVER WE STARTED
TALKING ABOUT CARS,
TIMES JUST SOARED BY.
WE MUST HAVE REALLY
GOTTEN INTO IT.
THAT WAS JUST PART OF
THE MAGIC, I GUESS.
- ( cellphone ringing )
- THIS IS SAYUKI.
SHINGO, LONG TIME NO TALK.
HOW'S THE BIG BAD WORLD
BEEN TREATING YOU LATELY?
- JUST FINE.
BUT THIS ISN'T A SOCIAL CALL.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT'S THE LAN-EVO SQUAD
DOING IN MYOGI?
- I'M WONDERING IF THE NEWS
HAD REACHED YOU YET.
LAN-EVO'S WITH TOCHIGI PLATES
SHOWED IN MYOGI
NOT TOO LONG AGO.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- I HEAR THE NIGHT KIDS
LOST THEIR ASSES TO THEM TOO.
COURSE IT WAS THAT IDIOT,
TAKESHI.
HAD TO LOSE TO THOSE SPEED
MONKEYS ON OUR HOME TURF.
- I KNOW WHO
THESE GUYS ARE.
A FELLOW NAMED KYOICHI SUDO
IS THEIR LEADER.
HE'S AN EXCELLENT RACER
WHO HAILS FROM
THE NIKKO IROHAZAKA COURSE.
- ( gasps )
- I KNOW YOU'RE HERE NOW,
KYOICHI.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS WHAT DO
YOU HAVE UP YOUR SLEEVE?
- WE SHOULD DO THIS
MORE OFTEN, SHINGO.
- YEAH.
- IF YOU DIDN'T
KNOW IT ALREADY,
THE NIGHT KIDS ARE
A JOKE AROUND HERE.
- WELL, THAT'S A HELL OF A NICE
WAY TO GREET AN OLD FRIEND.
TAKESHI, I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET SAYUKI.
WE GREW UP TOGETHER.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- Takeshi:
DAMN, SHE'S HOT.
- YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD IT
ALREADY THROUGH THE GRAPEVINE,
BUT TAKESHI'S THE ONE
WHO RACED 'EM.
- GLAD TO MEET YOU.
- CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
LOST TO THOSE DUDES
ON YOUR HOME TURF. HOW COULD
YOU DO SOMETHING SO STUPID?
- ( exhales )
Takeshi: I AM HERE
TO DEFEND GUNMA TONIGHT.
AND BEFORE I'M DONE,
YOU'RE GONNA FIND YOURSELF
BURIED DEEP AT THE BOTTOM
OF MYOGI VALLEY.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT?
Takeshi: I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
BUT WE STILL GOT
A LONG WAY TO GO
BEFORE THE FINISH LINE.
IF I DON'T STOP THESE GUYS...
THEN WHO THE HELL ELSE
IS GONNA BE ABLE TO?!
( gasps )
( grunts )
AAH!
- ( gasping )
- ( chuckles )
- THEY'RE A TEAM OF
LAN-EVO RACERS.
CALL THEMSELVES
"THE EMPERORS."
IT ALL WENT DOWN AFTER TAKESHI
HAD LOST TO THE RED SUNS
IN AN UPHILL RACE.
I DON'T THINK HE'D FULLY
GOTTEN OVER GETTING WHOOPED YET.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN FEELING
PRETTY OUT OF SYNC
TO FAIL TWICE LIKE THAT.
- WHATEVER.
- HE'S NOT THE MOST CONSISTENT
PERSON ON THE PLANET,
AND HE CERTAINLY
FOLDS UNDER PRESSURE.
- TELL YOU WHAT, SHINGO,
YOU DON'T YOU PUT
A FREAKING CORK IN IT?
- BUT NOBODY CAN DRIVE
A THREE-TWO LIKE HE CAN.
I GOTTA GIVE HIM THAT MUCH.
IN FACT, I'D SAY HE'S PROBABLY
THE BEST THREE-TWO RACER
WE GOT AROUND OUR REGION.
BUT EVEN HE COULDN'T
KEEP UP WITH THE FIRE
BURNING OFF THE BACK
OF THAT LAN-EVO,
WHICH LETS YOU KNOW
JUST HOW FAST THEY ARE.
THEY SAID TO
GIVE THEM A MONTH
AND THEY'D KNOCK OUT
ALL THE COMPETITION IN GUNMA.
SOONER OR LATER
THEY'LL BE HERE.
SO YOU BETTER
WATCH YOUR BACK, SAYUKI.
MYOGI'S CLOSE TO USUI.
IT WON'T TAKE MUCH
FOR THEM TO GET TO YOU.
- I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
- ( gasps )
- PEOPLE DON'T CALL US
IMPACT BLUE
BECAUSE WE SIT ON OUR ASSES
AND LET EVERY LOSER
WHO COMES THROUGH
ROLL OVER US.
- Takeshi:
MAN, THIS CHICK IS AGGRESSIVE.
- I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU.
GIVE YOU A LITTLE HEADS UP.
YOU'RE BETTER OFF
AVOIDING THESE GUYS.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BY NOW
TO TRUST WHAT I'M SAYING.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
GETTING AT WITH THAT, SHINGO?
YOU THINK WE'RE NOT GOOD
ENOUGH TO DEAL WITH THE JERKS,
IS THAT IT?
- I WOULDN'T SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT TO YOU.
YOU KNOW ME
BETTER THAN THAT.
- ( both gasp )
- Takeshi: BOUNCY.
- WE MIGHT JUST
BE CHICKS TO YOU,
BUT DON'T COUNT US OUT.
WE DON'T BACK DOWN
FROM ANYONE.
NEVER HAVE, NEVER WILL.
- ( stammers )
- YEAH, I BELIEVE YOU.
- IS THAT ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY TO ME?
GREAT, THEN I'M LEAVING.
- SHE CAN BE SUCH
A STUBBORN PAIN IN THE ASS.
DON'T YOU COME
CRYING TO ME, OKAY?
SO IN CASE YOU HADN'T
FIGURED IT OUT,
I BROUGHT YOU HERE
'CAUSE I WANTED HER TO KNOW
JUST HOW DANGEROUS
THE EMPERORS ARE.
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST
TRIED TO HELP OUT.
EARTH TO MORON,
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- DUDE.
SHE'S SO HOT.
- HMM?
- ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
DON'T ASK ME WHERE I HEARD IT,
BUT I KNOW THAT
A LAN-EVO TEAM
CALLED THE EMPERORS ARE PLANNING
TO PULL AN ATTACK ON GUNMA.
- A BUDDY OF MINE WAS TELLING
ME ABOUT THAT THE OTHER DAY.
IT SEEMS EVERYONE'S BEEN
TALKING ABOUT THEM LATELY.
- YEAH.  I HEARD SOME CRAP
ABOUT THEM CUTTING
THE NIGHT KIDS
STICKER IN HALF
AND PUTTING IT UPSIDE DOWN
ON ONE OF THEIR SPOILERS.
SOME KIND OF
VICTORY THING THEY DO.
- WHO WOULD PULL THAT?
- YOU REALLY THINK THEY'RE
GONNA COME UP HERE?
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
IF THEY SHOW UP, SAYUKI?
YOU GONNA TAKE 'EM ON?
- YOU KNOW, DUDE,
THAT'S A REALLY STUPID QUESTION.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY SO, MAKO?
- YEP.  ANY CHALLENGE
IS WORTH TAKING.
WE'RE THE FASTEST
USUI HAS TO OFFER.
THEY DON'T CALL US
IMPACT BLUE BECAUSE
WE DRAG AROUND THE CURVES.
- SO THAT'S WHERE WE STAND.
BUT WE NEED YOU GUYS
TO HELP US OUT, OKAY?
THE SECOND ANY ONE OF YOU
SEES THOSE LAN-EVOS,
CALL ME ON MY CELL AND TELL
ME EXACTLY WHERE THEY ARE
SO WE CAN TAKE THEM DOWN.
- ( cheering )
- IT'S BEEN TWO DAYS
AND WE HAVEN'T SEEN
OR HEARD A THING FROM
THE LAN-EVO GUYS.
MAYBE THEY'RE NOT
COMING HERE TO USUI.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST
WITH MYSELF.
THERE'S A BIG PART OF ME
THAT'LL FEEL A HUGE RELIEF
IF THEY DON'T.
I KNOW I HAVEN'T BEEN
AT THE TOP OF MY GAME LATELY.
AND IF I HAD TO SQUARE OFF
AGAINST THEM TONIGHT,
I'M SURE IT WOULDN'T BE
THE BEST RACE I'VE EVER RUN.
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
BUT I WANT TO CLEAR
THIS HAZE FROM MY MIND.
SOMEHOW.
I JUST WANT TO FORGET
ABOUT IKETANI.
I WANT THAT REJECTION
OUT OF MY MIND.
- COME ON!
- ( Mako screams )
SAYUKI, WHAT IS THIS?
DO YOU WANT TO TELL ME
JUST WHAT IN THE HELL
YOU'RE DOING IN MY BATHROOM?
- ARE YOU STUPID?
THIS ISN'T THE TIME
FOR YOU TO BE LOUNGING
IN THE FREAKING BATH.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I CAME TO PICK YOU UP.
WE'RE BLOWING THIS JOINT.
NOW MOVE YOUR ASS.
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- UP TO USUI PASS.
THE LAN-EVO JERKS
JUST ROLLED INTO TOWN.
- ( gasps )
- HURRY AND PUT ON SOME
UNDERWEAR FOR GOD SAKES.
- JUST GIVE ME A SECOND,
YOU FREAK!
- LAN-EVOS COMING UP
THE MOUNTAIN, GUYS.
- OH, MAN.
IT'S THE EMPERORS ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY ACTUALLY SHOWED UP.
- WE NEED TO CALL
SAYUKI AND MAKO NOW.
- YEAH.
- FOR REAL?
THE LAN-EVOS JUST SHOWED UP?
- SAME DAMN EMPEROR JAG-OFFS
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT EARLIER.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY
UP THERE RIGHT NOW,
AND I THOUGHT
YOU'D WANT TO KNOW.
- THANKS FOR THE HEADS UP.
- ( cellphone beeps )
- HEY, TAKESHI.
THE LAN-EVO SQUAD
JUST SHOWED UP IN USUI.
- YOU SCREWING WITH ME?
- I'M NOT.
NOW LET'S GO.
- YOU GOT IT.
- Rourke: ALL I SEE IS
A BUNCH OF DRIFT PUNKS
WITH DUMBASS LOOKS
ON THEIR FACES.
GUNMA DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
SUCH A KILLER PLACE
FOR REAL RACERS.
THIS IS AMATEUR HOUR.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
AND TELL KYOICHI
HE'S GOT AN EASY KILL WAITING.
- SURE.
HUH?
- HOW YOU FELLAS DOING?
IF YOU CAME
LOOKING FOR A RACE,
WE'LL TAKE THE CHALLENGE
'CAUSE OUR SIL-EIGHTY
IS THE FASTEST CAR YOU'LL
FIND ANYWHERE AROUND HERE.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, I GOT A QUESTION.
ANYTHING GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU AND THAT
SIL-EIGHTY CHICK?
I COULDN'T REALLY TELL
AT THE RESTAURANT.
- HMM.
ME AND SAYUKI, YOU SERIOUS?
NAH, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
THE TWO OF US HAVE BEEN FRIENDS
SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
WE LIVED NEAR EACH OTHER,
WENT TO THE SAME SCHOOLS,
THAT KIND OF STUFF, YOU KNOW.
WE'RE JUST REGULAR FRIENDS, MAN.
- THAT'S COOL.
- I KNOW.
OH, I JUST PUT IT TOGETHER.
YOU TOTALLY DIG
AGGRESSIVE CHICKS, DON'T YOU?
- UH-- WELL...
- FORGET HER. SHE'S A
STRONG-WILLED PAIN IN THE ASS
WHO'LL WALK ALL OVER YOU.
YEAH, SHE DOESN'T LISTEN TO
ANYTHING ANYONE ELSE HAS TO SAY.
DOES HER OWN THING.
EVEN IF THEY ARE
THE FASTEST IN USUI,
THEY DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THE LAN-EVOS.
SHE THINKS THEY'RE GONNA BE
EASY TO WHIP, BUT SHE'S WRONG.
EVEN I CAN ADMIT
THEIR DRIFT TECHNIQUE
IS AN AMAZING THING,
FOR FREAKING REAL.
THERE'S PROBABLY
NO ONE IN USUI
WHO COULD HOLD A CANDLE
TO THOSE CHICKS.
BUT WITH PURE SPEED RACING,
THEY GOT NO EXPERIENCE.
THAT KIND OF DRIVING
REQUIRES CONTROL
THAT'S SIMPLY
OUT OF THEIR REACH.
THEIR CONTROL'S GOOD, YEAH.
BUT IT'S NOT-- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST NOT CRISP ENOUGH.
THEY'LL BE OUTCLASSED
BY A SERIOUS FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
AND I'M NOT SAYING THEY'RE
SLOW BECAUSE THEY'RE CHICKS
OR ANYTHING
TOTALLY STUPID LIKE THAT.
I JUST KNOW THE FACTS
AS THEY STAND.
- OH, SO YOU'RE IN
A SIL-EIGHTY, HUH?
AND YOU'RE CHICKS TO BOOT.
THAT'S FUN.
LOOKS LIKE A GOOD TIME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLAY
A LITTLE ROUND-AND-ROUND?
- I DON'T THINK THAT'S
SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
KYOICHI WILL KICK YOUR ASS.
YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
WHY WE'RE HERE, MAN.
WE CAME UP HERE
TO SCOUT THE PLACE,
AND THAT'S ALL
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO DO.
- SHUT UP.  DON'T BE SUCH
A BUZZ-KILL, NANCY.
I MEAN WE CAME ALL THE WAY
UP HERE, DIDN'T WE?
SO BACK OFF.
I DON'T SEE THE DAMAGE IN US
HAVING A LITTLE FUN
WHILE WE'RE AT IT.
AS LONG AS I WIN.
- SURE, DUDE.
BUT WHAT IF THEY'RE GOOD
AND YOU ACTUALLY
LOSE TO THEM?
- DON'T INSULT ME.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD AND
EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO ME, REN.
HOW COULD MY BADASS EVO FOUR
LOSE TO A COUPLE OF
HAIRSPRAY SNORTING BIMBOS
LIKE THOSE TWO CHICKS?
- HEAR THAT, MAKO?
HE SCREWED UP NOW.
THAT'LL BE THE LAST
DUMB THING HE SAYS TODAY.
- PEOPLE WHO
INSULT WOMEN RACERS
JUST BECAUSE THEY'RE WOMEN
ARE THE WORST KIND OF JERKS.
SO THAT'S THE LAST STRAW.
WE'RE NOT GOING EASY ON YOU.
- ( engine starts, revs )
- Sayuki: HER EYES GOT
THAT SERIOUS LOOK IN THEM.
SHE'S FASTER THAN A HYDROPLANER
WHEN SHE LOOKS LIKE THAT.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHEN
HER EMOTIONS FUEL HER.
WE'RE GONNA RUN
A DOWNHILL RACE.
AND SINCE USUI'S
A NARROW COURSE,
WE'RE GONNA DO IT
CAT-AND-MOUSE STYLE.
I'M SURE YOU'RE
FAMILIAR WITH IT.
IF THE MOUSE GETS AWAY,
IT'S OVER.
IF NOT, WE KEEP SWITCHING
UNTIL SOMEONE WINS.
YOU COOL WITH THAT?
- THAT'LL WORK.
- JUST TELL ME WHICH
POSITION YOU WANT FIRST.
SINCE YOU'RE THE OUTSIDER,
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU THE CHOICE.
- YOU KNOW, I'LL FOLLOW YOU
ON THE FIRST RUN.
THAT WAY I CAN CHECK OUT WHAT
YOU'RE MADE OF FROM BEHIND.
- SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE
READY TO GET STARTED THEN.
AFTER WE EXIT THE FIRST TURN,
WE'LL KICK IT UP
TO FULL SPEED.
THAT'LL BE THE START
OF THE RACE.
THINK YOU'RE CAPABLE
OF REMEMBERING ALL OF THAT?
OR IS THAT TOO MUCH?
- I'M GOOD.  LET'S DO IT.
- HEY, YOU GONNA BE OKAY
DOING THIS ALONE?
- DIDN'T I JUST SAY
A SECOND AGO THAT I WAS GOOD?
I'M ONE OF THE TOP
RACERS ON OUR TEAM.
HE'LL, PAL, I'M EVEN
BETTER THAN YOU.
I'M MORE THAN POSITIVE
THAT MY EVO FOUR
IS GONNA WIPE THE ROAD
WITH SOME LAME-ASS SIL-EIGHTY
DRIVEN BY TWO CHICKS.
- ( engines revving )
- RIGHT.  LET'S GO.
- WE'VE GOT THIS IN THE BAG.
I'M NOT LOSING TO SOME GUY
WHO INSULTS FEMALE DRIVERS.
- YOU LOOK READY. YOU REALLY
THINK YOU'RE UP FOR THIS?
- WHENEVER YOU ARE, SAYUKI.
- HIT THE GAS.
- HUH.  SHOULD BE AN EASY WIN.
EVEN ON ITS WORST DAY,
HIS EVO FOUR
WOULD NEVER LOSE TO SOME
SPENT SIL-EIGHTY.
- I'M SURPRISED THEY'RE
REALLY GOING THROUGH WITH THIS.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
WOMEN CAN HAVE A HELL OF A LOT
MORE COURAGE THAN MEN DO.
- BUT CAN THEY
BEAT THE EMPERORS?
I MEAN, THOSE GUYS LAID WASTE
TO THE NIGHT KIDS
NOT TOO LONG AGO.
- THAT EVO FOUR IS AN
EXTREMELY HIGH-POWERED
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
ANYONE ELSE
WOULD HAVE RUN AWAY.
BUT IF SAYUKI AND MAKO
CAN'T WIN,
THEN I CAN'T THINK OF ANYBODY
WHO'S GOT THE SKILLS
OR THE CAR TO DO IT.
- RIGHT.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHO IT WAS
THAT NAMED THEM IMPACT BLUE,
BUT THEY CERTAINLY
DESERVED IT.
THEY'RE USUI'S FASTEST
BY A MILE.
- ALL WE CAN DO NOW
IS BELIEVE IN THEM.
BECAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE
WE BOTH HAVE FAITH
IN ONE CENTRAL THING:
THAT THE SIL-EIGHTY
IS THE BEST HERE.
- NOT BAD FOR A COUPLE
OF DUMB CHICKS,
BUT IT'S THEIR COURSE
SO THEY KNOW BETTER THAN ANYONE
HOW TO ATTACK IT.
- NO CARS AHEAD OF US, GIRL.
YOU CAN KICK IT OUT
AND DRIFT RIGHT ON
THROUGH THIS CORNER.
- ( chuckles )
MY EVO FOUR'S DRIFT
IS MORE POWERFUL THAN ANY
PIECE OF CRAP FR'S DRIFT
BY A LONG SHOT.
WHAT I GOT IS A HIGH-SPEED
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE DRIFT
WITH AN ENGINE
ALWAYS ON FULL BLAST.
- ( tires screech )
- ( gasps ) MAKO,
YOU'RE DOING GREAT, SISTER.
GRIP THE NEXT CORNER
AND HUG THE INNER WALL.
YOU'LL SKIP LIKE A STONE.
SO FAR WE'RE ABOUT EVEN.
I'M NOT SURE IF IT'S
THE EVO FOUR ITSELF,
OR THE DRIVER'S TECHNIQUE THAT'S
LETTING HIM KEEP UP WITH US.
- IT'S LIKE YOU WERE
SAYING EARLIER,
THE SWINGING DRIFT INVOLVES
SO MANY VARIABLES
YOU KIND OF HAVE TO BE
A MASTER OF ALL TRADES.
EVERYTHING DEPENDS ON
HOW YOU USE THE TIRES.
- YEAH.
- SO WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW THIS SIL-EIGHTY RACE?
HAS IT BEEN LIKE
YEARS OR WHAT?
- NO, IT'S BEEN
SINCE LAST SPRING.
- THEN MAYBE HER DRIVING STYLE'S
CHANGED A LITTLE BIT.
- HUH?
- I'VE EXPERIENCED IT TOO,
YOU KNOW.
AFTER A HORRIFYING LOSS,
EVEN THE BEST RACER
CAN REALLY CHANGE HIS TONE.
SOMETIMES FOR THE BETTER,
AND SOMETIMES FOR THE WORSE.
- YEAH.
- THERE ARE PLENTY OF
TALENTED RACERS IN THE WORLD.
LIKE AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
THAT'S AN FR RACER WHO
COULD BEAT THE PANTS
OFF A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
- BUT THAT EIGHT-SIX
IS AN EXCEPTION NOT THE RULE,
YOU KNOW THAT.
IT PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
BEEN A DIFFERENT STORY
IF THOSE GIRLS HAD
EVEN HAD A CHANCE
TO SEE THE EIGHT-SIX
RACE BEFORE, BUT THEY HAVEN'T.
THEY'RE BLIND TO WHAT
THEY'VE GOTTEN INTO.
- ( chuckles )
STUPID WOMEN DRIVERS.
JUST PLAIN DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
- Mako: I'M NOT LOSING
TO THIS CREEP NO MATTER WHAT.
- Sayuki: THIS IS UNREAL.
HER DRIVING IS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT NOW.
HER STEERING'S DEFINITELY
GOTTEN WAY BETTER.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN THE RACE
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX.
THAT HAD TO HAVE BEEN
WHAT TIGHTENED THE SCREWS
ON HER SKILLS.
SHE'S COMPLETELY OPENED
HER EYES AS A DRIVER
LIKE SHE'S NEVER
DONE BEFORE.
YOU CAN DO THIS, MAKO.
THIS RACE IS YOURS TO LOSE.
- ( tires screech )
- THAT EVO FOUR ISN'T AS SHARP
AT THE CORNERS AS WE ARE.
DUDE'S NOT AS GREAT
AS I THOUGHT HE'D BE.
10-TO-ONE SAYS HE'S
NOT THE GUY WHO BEAT
THE NIGHT KIDS IN MYOGI.
HAD TO BE SOMEONE ELSE.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
I'D HATE TO KEEP
LETTING HIM
STARE AT OUR ASS.
WE'RE FINISHING HIM OFF
AT THE NEXT CORNER.
THAT'S C-121.
I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING
YOU ALREADY KNOW,
BUT YOU'RE A HELL OF
A LOT FASTER
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS TONIGHT.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ENTERING THE CORNER
AT A MUCH HIGHER SPEED
THAN YOU'RE USED TO,
SO DON'T FORGET
TO ADJUST FOR THAT
WHEN WE GET THERE,
ALL RIGHT?
EXCELLENT.
NO CARS AHEAD.
TIME TO NAIL IT.  GO!
- ( grunts )
IF THOSE FREAKING CHICKS
CAN CLEAR THAT CORNER
THAT EASY,
THEN MY EVO FOUR
CAN DO IT NO SWEAT.
HERE I COME!
I'M GOING TOO WIDE.
I CAN'T STAY ON
THE SAME LINE.
I'M GONNA CRASH!
AAH!
- IT'S OVER, MAKO.
YOU BEAT HIM.
- DUDE, ARE YOU OKAY?
- HEY.  DO ME A FAVOR
AND DON'T TELL KYOICHI
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
IT'LL JUST BE BETWEEN US.
- UH...
- SAYUKI, WHAT'S UP? WHERE
THE HELL'S THE LAN-EVO SQUAD?
I THOUGHT THEY WERE HERE?
- AW, YOU'RE TOO LATE, SHINGO.
THE RACE IS ALREADY
SAID AND DONE.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE ALREADY FINISHED?
- THAT SUCKS.
BUT DON'T FEEL TOO
BAD ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, WE LOST ON
OUR OWN TURF TOO, YOU KNOW?
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, DUDE?
WE BEAT THEIR ASSES.
- ( both gasp )
- I SAID WE WHIPPED
THEIR TAILS, STUPID.
- Shingo and Takeshi:
THEY WON?!
- MAKO WAS REALLY
SHINING TONIGHT.
SHE'S A GENIUS
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
- CUT IT OUT.
- ( giggles )
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
SEE YOU AROUND, SHINGO.
- HEY, WAIT.  YOU KNOW,
WE CAME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
TO ROOT FOR YOU AND NOW
YOU'RE JUST GONNA RUN AWAY?
- ( engine starts )
- DUDE, THAT SIL-EIGHTY IS
GIVING OFF SOME SERIOUS VIBES,
I SWEAR.
THOSE CHICKS ARE
THE REAL DEAL.
- YOU ROCKED IT OUT
LAST NIGHT, MAKO.
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE THE GUY
DRIVING THE LAN-EVO LAST NIGHT
WASN'T REALLY THAT
GOOD OF A RACER.
- THAT'S A LOAD OF CRAP.
HE ACTUALLY HAD A PRETTY
TIGHT GRIP ON HIS STYLE.
IF WE RACED HIM BEFORE
HE RACED AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX,
IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
A CHALLENGE FOR YOU,
BUT IT TIMED OUT JUST RIGHT.
LESS ANGLED CORNERING
HAS BEEN OUR FOCUS
EVER SINCE OUR LOSS.
WE'RE GETTING BETTER.
AND YOU'VE PROVED THAT
WITH EVERY SINGLE TURN.
BUT AT C-121 WHEN WE
WENT IN FOR THE KILL,
YOU SLIPPED RIGHT BACK
INTO YOUR FLASHY,
DRAMATIC STYLE OF DRIFTING.
- I GUESS I ENTERED THAT CORNER
A LOT FASTER THAN I SHOULD HAVE.
IT'S SAD. I'M ALMOST
GETTING NERVOUS
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT NOW.
( chuckles )
- WELL, IT SURE AS HELL WASN'T
FUNNY LAST NIGHT, OKAY?
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
FREAKING DIE.
I GOTTA SAY, YOU'RE ONE HECK
OF AN EMOTIONAL RACER, MAKO.
YOU CHANGE INTO SOMEONE ELSE
WHEN YOU GET BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF THAT CAR.
- I FEEL THIS HUGE
SENSE OF RELIEF RIGHT NOW.
BUT I STILL HAVE
A LONG WAY TO GO.
LIKE I'M CHASING AFTER
SOMETHING THAT'S JUST
WAY BEYOND THAT BLUE SKY,
YOU KNOW?
SOMETHING INTANGIBLE.
I'M NOT GONNA NEED
A MAN FOR A LONG TIME.
JUST YOU WATCH ME, IKETANI.
BANG.
- ( Iketani sneezes )
- YOU CATCH A COLD
OR SOMETHING?
'CAUSE YOU SOUND LIKE
ABSOLUTE HELL.
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M COOL.
- YOU'RE KIND OF WOBBLING
AS WE GO AROUND THE CURVES.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.  DAMN.
YESTERDAY'S SNOW
HAS FROZEN SOLID,
AND IT'S MAKING ME
SLIDE ALL OVER THE ROAD.
GUESS MY STUDLESS TIRES
AREN'T REALLY
CUTTING THE MUSTARD
OUT HERE.
( gasps )
OH!
WHAT?
HOW'S THAT CAR DOING IT?
IT'S GOT STUDLESS TIRES TOO.
UNBELIEVABLE.
- Sayuki:
WHOA!  WATCH OUT!
WHOA!
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT!
AAH!
( screaming )
NOT AGAIN.
GO RIGHT, RIGHT!
NO!  NO!  CRAP.
OH, DAMN IT.
OH, WHY?
- SAYUKI, YOU COOL?
- THAT SUCKED!
THE SNOW'S FROZEN SOLID
LIKE A ROCK.
- SO YOU OKAY OR WHAT?
- HMM.
THIS IS FLIPPING ANNOYING.
WE STARTED SNOWBOARDING
AT THE SAME TIME,
AND HERE YOU ARE
MAKING IT LOOK LIKE
THE EASIEST THING
IN THE WORLD.
- ( chuckles )
- LOOK, I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT OTHER CHICKS DON'T HAVE
YOUR ATHLETIC TALENT.
IT MAKES ME WANT TO VOMIT.
OF COURSE IT WAS
THE EXACT SAME STORY
WHEN YOU FIRST STARTED
LEARNING HOW TO DRIFT.
YOUR INTUITION IS KILLER,
AND YOU LEARN HOW TO
DEVELOP IT SO DAMN QUICKLY.
( laughs )
IT'S SHINGO!
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
- OH, HEY.
WHAT'S UP, SAYUKI?
- LONG TIME NO SEE, MAN.
IT'S CRAZY TO RUN INTO YOU
ALL THE WAY UP ON THIS MOUNTAIN.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT
YOU WERE INTO SNOWBOARDING.
- YEAH.  I DIG IT.
IT'S MY THING.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
AGAIN, I HAD NO IDEA.
- ( Shingo and Sayuki chuckle )
- Shingo: COME ON, I KNOW
HOW TO SNOWBOARD.
PRETTY FREAKING GOOD TOO.
- Sayuki: AND IN GRADE SCHOOL,
SHINGO ALWAYS HAD A STREAM OF
SNOT POURING
FROM HIS NOSE.
IT WAS SICK!
- Shingo: SHUT UP.
- EVERYONE ALWAYS
MADE FUN OF HIM.
CALLED HIM DROOPY-NOSE SHINGO.
THAT'S ABOUT THE TIME
HE BROKE BAD
AND TURNED INTO A SLICK BOY
REBEL RACER, RIGHT?
- DON'T GO MAKING
STUFF UP, SAYUKI.
COME ON. I JUST HAD A BUTTLOAD
OF ALLERGIES WHEN I WAS A KID.
YOU KNOW THAT.
- ( chuckles )
SO MAKO, WANT TO GET OUT THERE
AND HIT THE SLOPES A BIT MORE?
- UH...
- GO ON, I DON'T MIND.
I THINK I'M GONNA STAY HERE
AND CATCH UP WITH SHINGO A BIT.
TALK ABOUT THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU GO UP
WITH HER, MIYAHARA?
IT'LL BE FUN.
- ( gasps )
- SURE.  I COULD GO
FOR ANOTHER RUN.
- YEAH.  I COULD
USE THE COMPANY.
- YOU GOT IT.
- ( people chattering )
- Shingo:
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK OF HIM?
- HE KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE A WHIMP,
BUT FOR A FRIEND OF YOURS,
I GOTTA SAY, HE SEEMS NORMAL.
ANY IDEA HOW
HIS DRIVING IS?
- HE'S ONE OF THE FASTER
DRIVERS THE NIGHT KIDS HAVE.
BUT OF COURSE, NOT AS FAST
AS A COUPLE CHICKS I KNOW
WHO DRIVE A RIDE
CALLED IMPACT BLUE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( sighs )
YOU KNOW,
SPEAKING OF FRIENDS,
YOURS IS TOO CUTE
NOT TO HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DIDN'T
TRY TO HOOK YOUR BUDDY SHINGO
UP WITH HER INSTEAD.
- OH GIVE ME A BREAK, SHINGO.
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL THAT
YOU'RE NOT GOOD ENOUGH FOR HER.
BY THE WAY, IF YOU LET
THE CAT OUT OF THE BAG
AND TELL EITHER OF THEM
THAT THIS WAS
A BLIND DATE SETUP,
SHE'LL KILL ME
AND THEN I'LL KILL YOU,
GOT IT?
- I'LL KEEP
MY MOUTH SHUT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, SAYUKI?
YOU GOT A SPECIAL GUY
ON THE SIDE THESE DAYS?
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
- TAKESHI WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
THE GUY'S DEVELOPED A CRUSH.
YOU INTERESTED IN SOME
NIGHT KID ACTION?
- UH...
- YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
SO HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN SNOWBOARDING?
- I JUST STARTED LAST YEAR.
- THAT'S REALLY AMAZING.
I DON'T KNOW MANY GIRLS
WHO CAN GO AS FAST AS YOU.
I MEAN, THIS KIND OF SNOW
IS MORE FOR THE SEASONED.
- WHAT CAN I SAY?
IT'S EXCITING FOR ME.
MORE SO THAN A LOT OF
OTHER STUFF.
WHEN I REALLY GET
INTO SOMETHING,
I TOTALLY FOCUS ON THAT THING
SO IT'S ALL I CAN SEE.
- HMM.
- SO TELL ME, MAKO,
YOU BEEN HAVING
ANY THOUGHTS ABOUT
SHINGO'S FOUR-EYED BUDDY?
- NO, NOT UNTIL
YOU BROUGHT HIM UP.
HE'S NICE.
JUST SEEMS KIND OF SERIOUS.
I GUESS THAT'S NOT
A BAD THING THOUGH.
- IS THAT ALL?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"IS THAT ALL?"
I JUST MET THE GUY. I DON'T
HAVE MUCH OF AN OPINION YET.
- Sayuki:
YEAH RIGHT.  I CAN TELL.
THEY'VE GOT SOME CHEMISTRY
BUBBLING BETWEEN
THE TWO OF THEM.
OH, I FORGOT TO TELL YOU,
I HEARD SOMETHING INTERESTING
THE OTHER DAY.
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI
OF THE RED SUNS
IS RECRUITING RACERS.
HE'S GATHERING TOGETHER
A NEW TEAM,
AND I HEAR THAT HE MAY
EVEN BE PUTTING
AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX ON IT.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE SOME KIND
OF SPECIAL TRAVELING TEAM
RUNNING AROUND
TO OTHER REGIONS.
- YOU'RE MESSING WITH ME.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
OF COURSE IT IS.
AND I REALLY ADMIRE
THE CONCEPT.
THE WHOLE IDEA OF
NEVER STAYING IN ONE PLACE
KEEPS THEM ALWAYS
MOVING FORWARD.
IT'S REALLY PROGRESSIVE
FOR DRIVERS.
- HMM.
- THEY'RE SO BADASS,
IT ALMOST MAKES ME
HATE THEM A LITTLE BIT.
THEY'VE GOT SOME
SERIOUS CHARISMA GOING ON.
( sighs )
I WISH I COULD SEE
TAKUMI AGAIN.
I WONDER IF HE'S BEEN DOING
WELL THESE PAST FEW WEEKS.
I BET YOU ANYTHING
HE'S LOOKING AS HOT AS EVER.
( chuckles ) THAT'S SOMETHING
I'M NEVER WRONG ABOUT.
- YEAH. YOU DO HAVE
GOOD TASTE IN MEN.
- OH, GIRL.
I'M REALLY HOPING TO GET
MY RACE ON SOON.
YOU KNOW THE ROAD
ON THE WAY HERE
ACTUALLY LOOKED
KIND OF NICE.
I THINK IT WOULD BE
A TOTAL BLAST
TO GIVE IT A RUN SOMETIME.
I DIDN'T SEE ANY SNOW
DOWN TOWARD THE BOTTOM.
- ( chuckles ) YOU KNOW, I WAS
THINKING THE EXACT SAME THING.
YOU WANT TO GO CHECK IT OUT
WHEN WE'RE FINISHED?
- THAT SOUNDS KILLER.
WE'RE JUST SUCKERS
FOR RACING.
- Keisuke: I'M SO BORED.
THE PASS IS
TOO SNOWY TO RACE.
- YOU KNOW KEISUKE,
THOSE WHO CAN CONQUER
THE PASS IN WINTER CAN DO IT
EASIER IN THE SUMMER.
- HUH?
- OUR PROJECT ISN'T
GONNA GET GEARED UP GO
UNTIL THIS SPRING
AT ITS EARLIEST.
WE'RE CERTAINLY NOT GONNA MAKE
ANY PROGRESS WHEN WE DO START
IF WE SIT ON OUR HANDS
ALL WINTER LONG COMPLAINING.
GET OUT ON THAT SNOWY ROAD
AND START DRIVING.
- WHAT?
- CLEAR YOUR MIND
OF EVERYTHING,
AND GET YOUR ASS
ON THAT FROZEN ROAD
DAY AND NIGHT
AND EVERY SECOND IN BETWEEN.
YOU'LL SEE THE EFFECTS
OF YOUR HARD WORK
IN THE SPRING WHEN
THE SNOW THAWS
AND YOU CHANGE BACK
TO HIGH-GRIP TIRES.
IT'LL BE A MASSIVE DIFFERENCE.
YOUR SENSES WILL BE SHARPER
THAN THEY'VE EVER BEEN,
AND YOUR DRIVING SKILLS
WILL BE DRAMATICALLY REFINED.
YOU'LL BE LIKE
A WHOLE NEW MAN.
LISTEN, KEISUKE.
WE'RE GONNA CREATE A NEW
UNBEATABLE RECORD AT EVERY PASS.
THAT'S HOW WE BUILD
OURSELVES AS LEGENDS.
ARE YOU COOL WITH THAT?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- UNDERSTAND,
THE SNOW'S NOT A HANDICAP.
IT'S YOUR BEST FRIEND.
A TRAINING PARTNER LIKE
YOU'VE NOT HAD.
RACERS DON'T GET
AN OFF SEASON, BROTHER.
- ( tires squeal )
- THESE STUDLESS TIRES,
THEY DON'T GRIP VERY WELL.
- BUT STILL, THIS IS REALLY
GOOD TRAINING FOR YOU.
LOOK, YOU SEE A CORNER,
YOU ATTACK IT.
THAT'S THE VERY INSTINCT
OF A RACER.
- WHOA.  CRAZY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYBODY THAT FAST.
- AND THAT WAS
A SIL-EIGHTY.
I MEAN, WHERE DID IT
EVEN COME FROM?
- MAN, THAT DRIVER'S
GOT SOME MAD SKILLS.
- HOW'S SHE HANDLING?
- THESE ARE ALL ONE PATTERN,
MID-SPEED CORNERS
WITH NO LIFE TO THEM.
IT'S FREAKING BORING.
I GUESS I'LL ALWAYS LIKE
USUI PASS THE BEST.
- ( cellphone ringing )
- Sayuki:
HELLO? OH HEY, SHINGO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT?
THOSE TWO HAVE BEEN
SEEING EACH OTHER?
SHE NEVER BOTHERED
TO TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- THEY ARE.  AND HE'S ALL
JAZZED UP ABOUT IT.
IN FACT, I THINK
THEY HAVE A DATE TODAY.
- NO KIDDING.
GREAT FOR THEM.
WELL, I HOPE THEY HAVE FUN.
YEAH?
YEAH, THAT'S NICE.
WELL, CHRISTMAS IS
COMING UP PRETTY SOON.
YEAH.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
- ( phone beeps )
- I WONDER IF ALL THOSE
YEARS WITHOUT A BOYFRIEND
ARE FINALLY GONNA COME
TO AN END FOR MAKO?
- I THINK THIS SW-20
IS A REALLY SWEET RIDE.
- A TWO-SEATER'S FUN,
BUT IT CAN KIND OF
CRAMP YOUR STYLE,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I THINK NEXT TIME,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO BUY
SOMETHING A WHOLE LOT MORE
PRACTICAL THAN THIS FOR SURE.
A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE SUV
MIGHT BE NICE.
- WHY?  THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE QUITTING RACING, DOES IT?
- I THINK SO, YEAH.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
ANY EXCUSES ABOUT IT,
BUT I THINK I'VE ALREADY
HAD MY FUN WITH RACING.
WHEN YOU'RE A BEGINNER,
YOU TRY YOUR HARDEST,
YOU GIVE IT YOUR ALL.
AND IT'S EXCITING
TO GO FROM NOTHING
TO A GUY THAT
PEOPLE ADMIRE.
BUT ONCE YOU REACH
A CERTAIN LEVEL,
AND YOU KIND OF
SEE YOUR LIMITS,
YOU STOP SETTING
GOALS FOR YOURSELF.
YOUR EAGERNESS SUBSIDES.
IT'S JUST NOT
WHAT IT USED TO BE.
- I GUESS THAT'S THE WAY
EVERYBODY SEEMS TO GROW
OUT OF IT SOONER OR LATER.
THAT'S HOW I DID.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE THAT
EVERYBODY'S GOALS
CAN JUST UP AND VANISH
FROM THEIR LIVES THAT EASILY.
- HUH?
- AWHILE BACK,
THERE WAS THIS TIME
WHEN I THOUGHT
AFTER THIS SUMMER
I WAS GONNA
QUIT RACING TOO.
BUT THEN I HAD
AN OPPORTUNITY
TO WATCH THIS REALLY
HIGH LEVEL RACER
AT THIS INTENSE COMPETITION.
AFTER THAT I REALIZED HOW MUCH
MORE THERE IS TO THE CRAFT.
- ( chuckles )
I DON'T THINK I TAKE RACING
AS SERIOUSLY AS YOU DO.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYING TO BE
A PRO OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- (  Mako gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- Miyahara: I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT'S A POSSIBILITY,
BUT I THINK IT'D BE COOL IF YOU
QUIT RACING ALONG WITH ME.
- RACING A PASS IS ONE OF
THE MOST DANGEROUS
THINGS IN THE WORLD.
I DON'T THINK IT HAS TO DO
WITH YOU BEING A GIRL.
IT'S JUST, I DON'T
WANT TO HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT YOU GETTING
INTO AN ACCIDENT.
I KNOW, NO ONE CAN
TAKE AWAY YOUR RIGHT
TO DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO DO.
THAT'S YOURS, OF COURSE.
BUT IF I WAS YOUR BOYFRIEND,
I WOULDN'T BE TOO CRAZY
ABOUT YOU KEEPING ON.
IT'D WORRY ME SO MUCH
TO LET YOU RUN OFF EVERY NIGHT
TO RACE SOME STRANGER WHO'S
GOT ONLY VICTORY IN HIS SIGHTS,
AND NO CARE AS TO
HOW HE GETS IT.
THERE'S SO MANY OTHER
FUN THINGS TO DO IN LIFE.
THINGS YOU COULD BE
DOING WITH ME.
I THINK IT MIGHT
SUIT YOU BETTER
TO PUT ON A FANCY DRESS AND
LET ME TAKE YOU OUT TO EAT.
YOU'RE TOO PRETTY
TO LET IT WASTE
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF A CAR.
- ( gasps )
- I'M SERIOUS ABOUT EVERYTHING
I SAID TO YOU, MAKO.
I'VE NEVER FELT
THIS WAY ABOUT ANYONE.
YOU'RE THE FIRST.
WILL YOU DO ME THE HONOR
OF BEING WITH ME?
- I...
I'M HONESTLY FLATTERED
THAT YOU FEEL THIS WAY.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
HOW I FEEL YET.
I MEAN, WE-- WE JUST MET.
WE HARDLY KNOW EACH OTHER.
AND ALL OF THIS,
IT JUST FEELS
KIND OF SUDDEN TO ME.
- THAT'S OKAY, MAKO.
I'M NOT ASKING FOR
AN ANSWER RIGHT NOW.
HOW ABOUT YOU LET ME
TAKE YOU OUT AGAIN
IN A WEEK OR SO.
SAY MAYBE ON CHRISTMAS EVE?
UNTIL THEN,
JUST GIVE IT SOME THOUGHT.
NO RUSH.
- ( humming "Jingle Bells" )
AAH!
- YOU'RE IN A GOOD
STINKIN' MOOD, DUMMY.
YOU GOT SOME BIG
PLANS FOR CHRISTMAS
YOU AIN'T TELLING US ABOUT?
- I DON'T HAVE ANY PLANS.
I SWEAR I DON'T.
- YOU DOING ANYTHING,
IKETANI?
- OF COURSE NOT.
SPENDING ANOTHER NIGHT ALONE
'CAUSE WE'RE THE LONELY DRIVERS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, ITSUKI?
- COURSE IT'S SAD.
LET ME GO.
- Yuuichi: WHAT A PATHETIC
BUNCH OF LOSERS.
- WHAT'S WITH
THE SERIOUS FACE, GIRL?
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING'S
CHIPPING AWAY AT YOUR MIND.
- I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
NOT EVEN TO YOU,
SORRY.
- THAT'S A BAD HABIT YOU GOT.
KEEPING EVERYTHING THAT
BOTHERS YOU TO YOURSELF
ALL THE TIME?
IT'LL TEAR YOU UP.
- I JUST HAVE
A LOT ON MY MIND.
I WOULDN'T EVEN
KNOW WHERE TO START.
MOSTLY I KEEP WONDERING WHY I
EVEN BOTHER WITH RACING ANYMORE.
- HMM?
- STOP STARING AT ME.
I KNOW THAT YOU AND I
USUALLY TRY TO AVOID
THIS KIND OF SERIOUS TALK.
- I WANT TO BE
A BETTER RACER, I DO.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
THAT'S ALL THAT DRIVES ME.
THAT PROBABLY SOUNDS PRETTY
STRANGE TO YOU, DOESN'T IT?
- NO, I DON'T THINK
IT SEEMS STRANGE AT ALL.
HANG ON, DID SOMEBODY SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU? WHO WAS IT?
HELL, I MEAN MAYBE YOU'RE
JUST TOO INNOCENT A GIRL.
TOO EASILY INFLUENCED
BY OTHERS, YOU KNOW?
THE TWO OF US,
I MEAN, WE ARE WHO WE ARE
NO MATTER WHAT
OTHER PEOPLE SAY.
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( car door opens )
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- EVERYTHING'S FINE.
BUT I'M SORRY TO HAVE TO
HAVE YOU COME OUT HERE
ON CHRISTMAS EVE
OF ALL NIGHTS.
- IT'S ALL GOOD.
REALLY JUST HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
- I WANT YOU
TO DO SOMETHING.
- WAIT.
I'M NOT RACING YOU.
YOU'D HAVE TO BE CRAZY TO THINK
I'D EVEN CONSIDER DOING THAT.
- WHICH IS WHY
I'M NOT ASKING.
I WANT YOU TO RIDE
NEXT TO ME
WHEN I GO ON A RUN.
- UH?
- ( engine revs )
- Mako: USUALLY IT'S SAYUKI
SITTING IN THE SEAT NEXT TO ME.
THIS FEELS WAY DIFFERENT.
LIKE I'M CHEATING.
RIGHT.
HOLD ONTO YOUR BOOTS.
- ( gasps )
- Miyahara:
DAMN, SHE'S GOOD.
I HAD NO IDEA SHE COULD
ROCK IT LIKE THIS.
YOU'RE WAY BETTER THAN
I THOUGHT YOU WERE, MAKO.
WE ONLY HAVE A HANDFUL OF NIGHT
KIDS WHO CAN DRIVE LIKE THAT,
AND YOU'D EVEN GIVE THEM
A RUN FOR THEIR MONEY.
WHO KNOWS, YOU MIGHT EVEN
BE BETTER THAN TAKESHI
AND SHINGO PUT TOGETHER.
( sighs )
DIDN'T TAKE ME LONG
TO FIGURE OUT
WHY YOU HAD ME
RIDE WITH YOU TONIGHT.
THAT WAS A SMART MOVE.
I'M GUESSING THIS WOULD BE
YOUR ANSWER TO MY QUESTION.
- YEAH, I'M SORRY.
BUT I THOUGHT ABOUT
IT PROBABLY MORE
THAN I'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT ANYTHING.
AT THE END OF THIS,
YOU MIGHT THINK
I'M JUST SOME DUMB GIRL,
BUT I CAN'T SHAKE
HOW BADLY I WANT TO RACE.
IT'S PART OF WHO I AM.
I'M A SIMPLE PERSON.
I WANT TO KEEP CHASING
AFTER THE OTHER CARS
IN FRONT OF ME THAT ARE
TRYING TO GET AWAY.
AND I WANT TO DO IT,
EVEN IF I CAN'T--
EVEN IF I CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH THEM, I DON'T CARE.
I JUST WANT TO
KEEP MOVING.
I'M SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS.
HOW YOU TREATED ME
SINCE WE'VE MET
HAS MADE ME FEEL
SO SPECIAL.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- BYE.
- ( car door opens, closes )
- ( engine starts )
- Miyahara:
I DON'T KNOW WHO THEY ARE,
BUT THE PEOPLE IN HER LIFE
THAT SHE CARES SO MUCH ABOUT
DON'T KNOW HOW GOOD
THEY GOT IT.
AND I COULDN'T BE
MORE JEALOUS OF THEM.
- ( pop music playing )
- WHY IS IT JUST
THE THREE OF US SITTING HERE?
WHERE THE HELL IS TAKUMI?
- MAYBE HE'S GOT
A BIG DATE TONIGHT.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- WHO CARES, GUYS?
LET HIM HAVE HIS FUN.
WHY DON'T WE JUST FOCUS
ON THE THREE OF US
HAVING A BLAST!
YEAH!  SWEET.
( laughing )
- ( both sigh )
- MERRY CHRISTMAS!
- ( theme song playing )