[OCULUS] Hang tight. This
should only take a second.
Isn't that just fascinating.
An arbiter with human emotions.
[DECIM] You know. I don't
believe people live
just so that they
can die someday.
I think it's because
they are alive
that they must die
at some point.
[CHIYUKI]
Hmm.
I believe that there is
a purpose to being alive.
[gasps]
And there's a purpose
to judgment, as well.
Judging is tricky.
Difficult to do right.
It goes hand-in-hand
with both life and death.
By its very nature, it must
be performed hand-in-hand
with human beings.
And because of that,
it requires human emotions.
[QUIN]
There you go. It's done.
[QUIN sighs]
It's lovely, isn't it?
Yeah, sure. At first
glance, anyway. But...
But this isn't all.
There are no lives
without darkness. None.
[QUIN]
You got that one right.
What? No way! Harada?
How are you here?
Didn't you go to
that void place?
Harada! Hello? Harada, wake up!
Huh. What's with him?
[GINTI] That's just a shell.
His soul hasn't come back yet.
Whoa, his soul's missing? Um.
So, how do you get it
to come back, then?
Not easily.
You need a soul to cast
into the void in its place.
Seriously? And if his
soul doesn't come back?
What then?
--[clatter]
--[gasps]
You get stuck with this.
Oh, wow.
I have to choose a soul
to send into the void.
Mine should be
good enough, right?
[GINTI]
Hm?
I don't see why I
can't take his place!
[grunts] You little idiot.
Do you have any clue
what the void is like?
No, how would I?
[growls]
[GINTI]
Unfathomably reckless moron!
It's in the name:
a space containing nothing.
It's a graveyard for souls.
Your mind is all that remains.
Terror. Regret. Despair.
The sensation of falling
forever while feeling
only the worst emotions.
That's the kind of
place the void is.
There's no way!
You're making that up!
No, I'm not.
But I've got someone else
who can take his place.
Harada or this guy.
The choice is up to you.
Who gets the void?
[MAYU]
What?
[DECIM] Chiyuki, please.
If you don't mind.
I need you to fill in
the blanks for me.
I don't understand
what you want me to say.
Start with this.
[MAYU] I don't get it.
Why do I have to choose?
[GINTI] Human behavior
is so predictable.
You're all a bunch of idiots.
Huh?
[GINTI] You all seem to
forget that someday
you're gonna die.
Until suddenly, you come
face-to-face with death.
Then you start clinging to life.
That's why, up to now,
I've never had so much
as a second thought
about my judgments.
[gasps]
[GINTI]
Hm.
When you've made a decision,
press this button.
So, who is this guy, anyway?
[GINTI] Is that something
you need to know?
What?
To cast Harada into the void,
what kind of person
would it take?
[gasps] I don't know,
but I would never do it.
Then it sounds like
you've got your answer.
[MAYU sighs]
[gasps]
[door clicks]
[DECIM]
You look very lovely in that.
[footsteps]
If you'll come this way, please.
Welcome to Quindecim.
Have a seat.
My name is Decim.
A pleasure to meet you.
I will be your bartender
while you're here.
I'm sorry. Is
something the matter?
I'm confused. What am
I doing here?
I'm supposed to be dead.
[DECIM grunts]
[DECIM] You can remember
that you're dead, then?
Yes, but...
What I don't remember
is how it happened.
[DECIM gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Please. Tell me.
[NONA]
Oh, really? That's unusual.
[DECIM] Obviously, I was
unable to prompt her
to play a game.
It sounds like the
information bureau screwed up.
Don't worry, all right?
I'll deal with her.
Deal with her? How do you mean?
We'll erase her memories
and start her judgment over.
Not too difficult.
Let's go ahead and
bring her with us.
Certainly, ma'am. I'm on it.
If it's not an imposition,
I'd actually like to
handle her judgment.
Why's that?
I'm not really sure.
Huh?
[NONA]
Hm.
Well, if you want to, go ahead,
but I think I'll
leave her here awhile.
[DECIM]
Hm?
[NONA]
As an assistant of sorts.
Here we go.
[piano plays]
[gasps]
[applause]
[CHIYUKI pants]
[DECIM] You loved to skate
more than anything, didn't you?
[CHIYUKI]
Mm-hmm.
I sustained a
serious leg injury.
[CHIYUKI]
They ran some tests.
Before long, they told me that
I would never skate again.
Everyone cried for me.
They were all so sympathetic.
But me? I didn't feel anything.
No matter what anyone said,
nothing got through to me.
But, I couldn't
tell anybody that.
[door scrapes]
It's time to eat.
Come on, dear.
Aren't you hungry?
[CHIYUKI'S MOM sighs]
[footsteps]
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
Hm. This is the trophy you won
in the first
competition you entered.
You know, Chiyuki.
Watching you skate was
always one of the highlights
of my life, but what
made me happiest
was watching you grow up.
Seeing you become a good woman.
I'm not, though.
What?
[sobs] I'm not a good woman.
[gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Just go, okay?
Okay.
[CHIYUKI sobbing]
[door scrapes]
[CHIYUKI] The fact that
I couldn't skate anymore
wasn't what was hard for me.
There were lots of
other things in my life
that were more important.
Like my family and friends.
I had lots of
friends from skating.
I didn't really
know what was wrong.
I was just so
confused at the time.
But now, I think I know.
These people I'd
been so close to.
They were, in a very
real sense, strangers.
I mean, they weren't me.
It sounds so obvious, right?
But somehow I'd never
realized it before.
And suddenly, everything
started to seem hollow.
I just felt like...
"I'm nothing. I'm nobody."
I couldn't get those
thoughts out of my head.
They festered, and I started
hating myself. Till finally...
[CHIYUKI]
I took my own life.
[CHIYUKI] People can't know
each other perfectly.
And to hope for that
kind of understanding...
It's wrong. I didn't realize
that until I was dead.
Until too late.
Life is so cruel.
[DECIM gasps]
[DECIM] From my understanding,
when humans are happy,
they smile. And when they
are sad, they shed tears.
Chiyuki, may I ask you
what emotion you are
feeling right now?
Well, obviously I'm
feeling sad, right?
And if I told you I
wanted to understand that,
you would say
that's wrong of me?
Huh?
Because it's true.
Regardless of
whether it's possible,
I wish I could know you better.
[DECIM] I've never been
part of the living world.
Nor have I experienced death.
I'm afraid I don't know the
correct way to express this,
but I am glad I got to meet you.
It's truly been my pleasure.
[gasps]
Uh--
Listen, Decim.
Certainly. I'm listening.
[sighs] Nothing, never mind.
[CHIYUKI]
My last drink at Quindecim.
So, what's this one called?
[DECIM] A "memento mori."
Apparently it means
"Remember that you must die."
[CHIYUKI]
"Do not forget that you
are certain to die someday,
and, as such, you have all
the more reason to live now."
I believe that is how the
phrase should be interpreted.
"Live now"? A little late.
Shall we?
Cheers, Decim.
Wow that's delicious!
[DECIM]
I am terribly sorry for this.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Oh.
So where are we going now?
[GINTI] You're headed for the
place where Harada's soul is.
And he's really going to
wake up? You promise me?
[GINTI]
Yeah.
Something I've been wondering.
Who exactly is Harada
to you, anyway?
Don't you get it? He's my life.
[GINTI]
Oh, really?
So what would your life be,
then, if Harada wasn't around?
What's that mean?
Are you making fun of me?
I want an answer.
What's your life's meaning?
[MAYU]
I've got no clue, okay?
Why does there have
to be any meaning?
Oh, perfect. Someone
else who has no idea.
[MAYU]
Well, what about you, huh?
What?
Why do you do this?
Do you have some
meaningful reason?
No, I don't need a
reason. I'm an arbiter.
This is what I do.
Then you arbiters have
my pity. All of you.
[GINTI]
Pity?
I decided for myself
how I was going to live.
Maybe it wasn't a life others
would be super proud of,
but I devoted it to him
because I wanted to.
If you ask me, there is
some meaning in that.
[GINTI]
Wouldn't that be nice?
And that's that.
[gasps] Wait! What's happening?
No! He lied! Harada!
I'm so sorry!
[MAYU]
Harada.
[phone ringing]
Hello, there.
Information bureau.
[DECIM]
I have a favor to ask.
Oh?
[DECIM] Do you think I
could have you send me
[QUIN]
It's happening.
I'm just about to
forward them along.
[NONA] All right, good.
Thank you, Quin.
[elevator dings]
[gasps]
And where are you going?
What's it matter
to you, old man?
[OCULUS] I hope you enjoyed
yourself. Looked like fun.
Sorry?
[OCULUS]
You've been bad, Nona.
[QUIN] The last episode:
"Suicide Tour."