[giggles] Let's play again
sometime, all right?
Yeah! Sometime soon, okay?
[GIRL]
See ya later!
[DECIM]
I'm sorry, sir. Excuse me.
[SHIGERU grunts]
[SHIGERU]
What the--?
[DECIM]
I hope your sleep was restful.
What is this place?
I will be happy to explain
that in just a moment.
If you'll step this way, please.
[WOMAN B]
How are you?
Oh. I'm fine, th-thanks...
What is it? Is something wrong?
Uh-- I'm sorry.
I'm kind of out of it.
[DECIM]
All right.
We shall begin now.
Allow us to welcome you.
It's a pleasure to have you
here at the Quindecim.
My name is Decim, and
I'll be your bartender.
Now then. I have a question.
I hope you do not find
it too impertinent.
Do you remember anything just
prior to your arrival here?
Well, no.
I had been asleep when I
realized what was happening.
The last thing I can remember...
...is riding alone at
the back of the bus
on the way home from college.
Thank you for indulging me.
How about you?
No. I don't remember
anything, either.
Very good, thank you. Moving on.
I will now explain some details
about your current situation.
This is important.
Please pay close attention.
Number one!
First: I cannot provide
you with any information
regarding your present location.
Number two!
However, now that you are here,
we shall ask you to play a game.
What? A-A game?
[WOMAN]
Number three!
As to game selection--
That will be decided
upon by roulette.
[SHIGERU, WOMAN B gasp]
Number four...
You'll find the stakes
of the game are very high.
Your lives, in fact.
[SHIGERU]
Whoa, hold on!
And number five.
Don't worry, this is
the final point.
Until the game is completed,
you cannot leave.
[SHIGERU]
I don't think it's coming.
[WOMAN B]
No, neither do I.
[SHIGERU] What's with
this game stuff, huh?
Doesn't make a lot
of sense to me.
Huh?
Yeah.
Hey, is something the matter?
[WOMAN B]
Well, it's just that...
I can't remember anything.
Yeah, I understand.
Neither can I.
No, what I mean is, I don't
remember anything at all.
Really, nothing. I don't
even know who I am.
It's like I've forgotten
everything about myself,
including my name.
It's so weird.
You remember some
things though, right?
Like your name?
A few things, yeah.
I know my name is Shigeru Miura.
[WOMAN B]
Oh, okay.
I'm scared. I don't
know what to do.
If it helps at all,
I believe you will recall
your name following the game.
Who are you, anyway?
How can you just promise
something like that?
Sorry. I'm afraid I cannot
answer that question.
[WOMAN B] I have to say,
having no idea who I am
is really pretty terrifying.
If it actually will
help me remember,
then I'd like to play the game.
Except that... I'm guessing
I can't play it alone.
All right, I'll do it.
I'll play your game.
Great! Thank you so much!
Now, if I could just have you
press this button, please.
The roulette will begin.
[game music plays]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH gasp]
[WOMAN] The rules are the
same as for regular bowling,
with some exceptions.
For example, you will
only be allowed to bowl
one ball per frame.
You will take turns in this
manner until the game is over.
Of course, as you might expect,
whoever knocks over
the most pins will win.
The balls you will use
have already been selected.
You'll find them on your left.
As you can see, they
have representations
of each of your hearts inside.
Ugh.
What are you saying?
[WOMAN] The pink is yours.
You're bowling with her heart.
And the blue is your ball.
Think of that as his
heart inside of it.
[DECIM] Very well.
The game will now begin.
[heartbeat thumping]
[SHIGERU gasps]
[SHIGERU yelps]
What is it? What's wrong?
The ball just throbbed!
Huh?
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
We did forget to
mention one thing.
You're linked to your
respective balls.
They register your pulses.
Also their temperature is the
same as that of your bodies.
[gasps]
[DECIM] You should know
that you will not
feel any actual pain.
I hope that helps.
There's no wiggle room, here?
We absolutely have to use these?
[DECIM]
That is the rule, yes.
[gasps]
[SHIGERU]
So, this is her heartbeat, huh?
I wonder if she's nervous.
It feels like it's
going a little fast.
[SHIGERU] And this is
the heat of her body.
She feels so warm inside.
[SHIGERU gasps]
[SHIGERU] Stop it, you
creep! Snap out of it!
Aw, damn, a split!
[scoreboard chimes]
[yelps]
A-Are you okay?
Oh, sorry! I'm fine!
It's just more life-like
than I expected.
[gasps]
[SHIGERU] She's gonna be
able to tell how you feel.
Just calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
[WOMAN B]
It's beating on the fast side.
I wonder if he's
a little nervous.
Of course, how could he not be?
Given the circumstances.
I got five.
Wow, you're good at this, huh?
Nice throw. And
your form is great.
[WOMAN B] It is? Really?
That's nice of you to say.
[gasps]
You're looking at
me kind of funny.
Is everything okay?
It's your turn.
Oh, right, sorry.
[SHIGERU]
That girl I used to play with
back when I was a little kid.
What was her name again?
We were still pretty young
when she moved away.
Nah, it couldn't be.
Aw! That was a horrible throw!
[giggles] You'll do
better next time.
Thanks! I hope you're right.
A relaxed and friendly game.
It's nice to have those
once in a while.
[DECIM]
Hm?
[WOMAN]
Hm. What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Just that you're getting
quite used to this.
And I appreciate your help in
explaining the rules, as well.
Sure thing. Don't mention it.
[SHIGERU] It's been awhile since
I've had such a good time.
Yeah, who knew
something like bowling
could be so much fun, right?
Especially when you don't
remember how you got here,
or who you are.
Whoops! I'm a jerk. Sorry!
No! I really am enjoying myself!
[SHIGERU]
Um, maybe this is weird,
but I'd like to make a side bet.
A what?
[SHIGERU] You know,
a wager, just between us.
If I win, you go
on a date with me.
[gasps]
Aw, too bad.
It shouldn't interfere
with our business.
No... That isn't what I mean.
The whole "already dead"
thing. I feel bad for them.
Oh, I see.
[WOMAN B] I didn't expect that!
My heart's racing now.
I'm not the only one.
Look at Shigeru's heart.
It's embarrassing in
a good way, somehow.
But why does all of
this feel so familiar?
And so good, for that matter.
[WOMAN B gasps]
[SHIGERU] Whoa! A strike!
Another great throw.
You must have some
bowling experience.
Still, I'm determined
to beat you!
Hey, everything okay?
[gasps] Oh, I'm fine. Sorry.
I guess I got distracted.
[WOMAN B] I think that was
a fraction of a memory.
If so, then I've met
Shigeru somewhere before.
[WOMAN B]
It's no use. I can't remember.
[giggles] Bye, Shigeru!
Let's play again
sometime, all right?
Yeah! Sometime soon, okay?
Bye, Chisato!
[WOMAN B gasps]
Whoa! A Double!
[WOMAN B]
Hey, Shigeru.
Huh?
I remember my name.
I'm Chisato! That's it!
Chisato Miyazaki!
Remember? We used to play
together at the park!
It was you, me, and Mai!
[gasps] I knew it!
You're Chisato. You're the
one who moved away!
I can't believe it!
Long time no see!
Ah, the beginning of the end.
How very cryptic.
Would you care to explain?
No.
Sorry. I don't accept that.
Tell me what you meant!
All right. I will.
What? You mean that
actually worked?
But, you must promise
not to raise your voice.
[WOMAN]
Huh?!
[WOMAN muffled grunting]
Yes.
Given that, those two may not
have the fairytale ending
you're hoping for.
[WOMAN muffled grunting]
But keep in mind,
regardless of what
the outcome is,
we must be prepared
to accept it.
[CHISATO]
So, here's the plan. Next,
I predict I'm going to
throw a gutter ball.
[SHIGERU]
If she throws her turn,
that will basically
ensure our date together.
but I still wanna get
the highest score I can.
Come on! Strike!
[gasps]
[YOUNG MAN 3B] Hey, man,
why did we have to come
all the way to
this place, anyway?
Just trust me, okay?
One of the girls who
works here is totally hot.
Look. Over there.
[YOUNG MAN 3B]
Huh? You mean her?
[SHIGERU]
Yeah.
Hey, isn't she the girl who--?
Yeah, I think she is.
Think she's what?
[YOUNG MAN 3A]
Oh, right, you went to
a different high school, so...
So? What is it?
[YOUNG MAN 3B]
That girl over there...
[gasps]
[SHIGERU gasps]
[CHISATO]
You did it! Amazing!
[CHISATO] What is it? What's
wrong? Did you hurt your back?
Hey, are you okay?
[SHIGERU pants]
Will you answer me?
I'm messin' with ya. I win!
[giggles] That's not funny!
[SHIGERU, CHISATO laugh]
[CHISATO]
Okay, this is the last frame.
One gutter ball coming right up.
[gasps]
[CHISATO] It's beating like
crazy. I wonder what's going on.
[CHISATO]
Hm.
[gasps]
[CHISATO] I'm Chisato!
That's it! Chisato Miyazaki!
Remember? We used to play
together at the park!
It was you, me, and Mai!
[SHIGERU] It really stinks
that Chisato had to move.
[MAI]
Yeah. Sure does.
But I'm not going
anywhere, not ever!
[tires squeal]
My name, it's not...
Very good. The game
is officially over.
Which makes you the
winner, Mr. Miura.
Our congratulations.
[SHIGERU]
Please tell me the truth.
Are we both already dead?
[DECIM]
Yes.
I'm afraid you have both
left the land of the living.
Following their deaths,
people are judged
and sent to either
Heaven or to Hell.
For the purpose of that ruling--
You can stop there.
[BOTH gasp]
[SHIGERU]
You don't have to explain.
I remember everything now.
As you wish, then.
We can forgo the remainder
of the explanation.
[WOMAN B] Shigeru, listen--
I need to tell you--
[SHIGERU] Hold on. I still have
a date to claim, don't I?
[BOTH gasp]
What?
It's hard to believe
that we're really dead,
but at least now we have
the chance to talk.
Since our conversation
got cut short earlier.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Dead or not, we can still
spend time together.
So, if it's all right.
I'd like to be with you,
right up until the last moment.
[DECIM grunts]
[SHIGERU]
So. Like I said.
I think I still have
a date to claim.
[gasps] I would like that, too,
but I have to tell you--
[SHIGERU]
I know.
[gasps]
Don't worry about it, okay?
I know everything.
It's all right.
I've always wanted to...
If you'll have me, I'd love to.
Let's spend whatever moments
together that we can.
What do you say?
Can we have some
time for a date?
Please, just a little time!
Very well. That can be done.
I trust that five minutes
will be long enough?
What? Of course it's
not long enough!
[DECIM] Very sorry.
I was making a little joke.
I hope you'll enjoy yourselves.
Right until the last moment.
[BOTH]
Thank you so much. We will!
Just so you know,
that wasn't funny.
[SHIGERU]
I've enjoyed this.
Yeah, so have I.
Thanks, Shigeru.
It's been amazing.
I don't know why I'm crying.
I actually am happy!
I know, so am I.
I'm so glad we died!
[BOTH laugh]
Yeah, me, too!
All right, then.
Yep.
[DECIM] She doesn't
realize it yet, but...
She is not Chisato.
Important parts of her
memory are still missing.
Her operation, for example.
[WOMAN muffled grunting]
Thank you for playing.
Best of luck on your journey.
[DOCTOR 3A]
You're completely sure
you wanna go through with this?
[MAI]
Yes.
There's somebody, well, I've
always had feelings for him.
But, in all this time,
he's never shown
any real interest in me,
and we just keep
growing further
and further apart.
I'm ready.
I feel like it's time to
take control of my life.
I'm tired of being scared.
I want more than this.
[SHIGERU]
So? What is it?
[YOUNG MAN 3B]
That girl over there.
Her name is Mai Takada.
You were friends
as kids, weren't you?
She left school and
had plastic surgery.
[gasps]
It really stinks that
Chisato had to move.
Yeah. Sure does. But I'm
not going anywhere!
Let's stay together forever!
I love you, Shigeru!
I always will!
[WOMAN]
Reunited with a childhood friend
after dying, huh?
Hey, does the current Mai
even look like Chisato?
[DECIM]
Sorry. That I don't know.
[WOMAN]
Hmm.
It's very true, what they say.
Life is a great mystery.
Huh?
People all lead separate lives.
Spinning their own individual
tales as they go along.
Yet they become intertwined
somehow, tangled up,
and nobody knows how
they are going to end.
True enough, You never
know until you die,
and for that matter, you may not
even know after you die.
But, then again,
that's what makes
it interesting, right?
That was very impressive.
[chuckles]
[QUIN]
Episode Four: "Death Arcade."