There was this guy who had been
giving her a lot of trouble.
A stalker, you know?
I even told the police about it.
But they didn't do anything.
I can't let him...
just get away with it.
[TATSUMI] Revenge, huh?
I know something about that.
It's what I'm after, too.
It is?
I'm sure this isn't
the kinda thing
that you'd expect to
hear from a detective.
But when I get outta here...
...somebody is going to die.
[WOMAN panting]
It wasn't just one of them?
They're both killers?
Your wife was murdered?
I'm so sorry!
Yeah. My attention was
always somewhere else,
I guess. Sorta comes with the
territory of being a detective.
That doesn't excuse it.
I should've protected her.
I will protect you.
I promise, whatever it takes.
So you're looking
for revenge, too.
[TATSUMI]
Yeah.
What're you planning
to do to the bastard
when you find him?
Well, honestly,
I wouldn't mind
torturing him, but...
I think I can settle
for killing him, instead.
I admire your honesty.
And I agree.
His death would make
the world a better place.
Some people need to be put down.
That's what they're like?
The memories of the dead?
Confusing? A bunch of
scenes jumbled together.
They can be hard
to make sense of.
Thus, they are insufficient.
You can't get a full picture
of someone just from memories.
So, you're a detective
who endorses murder?
[TATSUMI]
It's taking out society's trash.
Most of the cases we handle
in the investigative division
are so vile, they'd shock
the crap outta ya.
You ask me, these perps can
barely be considered human.
I'm not sayin' this
as a detective.
I'm sayin' it as
one human to another.
Killing this guy--it's just
the right thing to do.
I...
[gasps]
[WOMAN] Come on, Decim.
You should stop it.
This is how it's done.
They must expose their souls,
the darkness within.
And then I pass
judgment upon them.
That's my job. That's what
it is to be an arbiter.
[SHIMADA groans]
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
[SHIMADA, MAN 9A grunting]
[MAN 9A, SHIMADA grunting]
[SHIMADA yells]
[panting]
[SHIMADA gasps]
What's wrong, kid?
What the hell are you
doing with that thing?
[SHIMADA] I don't understand.
I-I already killed the man.
I stabbed him!
I did it with this!
I killed him.
I want them to die for
what they did to me.
Them? There was more than one?
There was a man.
He just watched.
I think they were friends.
One guy is dead,
but it's not over.
There was another bastard there.
The darkness of the soul.
Do you happen to know
what the most primitive
emotion human beings
experience is?
Fear, my dear.
This is crazy.
[TATSUMI groans]
Are you okay?
[sputters, groans]
[MAN 9B]
No! Please! Don't kill me!
[MAN 9B whimpers]
[MAN 9B screams]
[TATSUMI panting]
Yumi. I killed him. It's over.
[YUMI echoing]
Thank you.
[SHIMADA]
Hey, Tatsumi! Can you hear me?
Please get up!
There's something really
wrong with him! What should we--
[DECIM] If you would please
continue playing the game.
Seriously? But he's--!
[DECIM]
The score is currently tied.
Each of you has four points.
If you'll look at the next puck,
you'll notice that it's yours.
If you score a goal,
the points will be doubled.
You will reach the
stipulated score.
And, thus, you will be
declared the winner.
Of an air hockey game?
Who cares about that right now?
Tatsumi needs help!
Don't you get it?
[DECIM]
Before we began, I spoke about
the stakes of the game.
Your lives, remember?
[SHIMADA] Come on! This is
starting to get ridiculous!
Just find him some help!
I think you'll find
that won't be necessary.
Huh?
Tatsumi, you're all right!
Thank god! I don't know what
I would've done if you...
You're all right, aren't you?
Yeah, kid, I'm fine.
Let's just keep playing, okay?
[SHIMADA]
Uh-- What are you talking about?
The game doesn't matter
anymore! I forfeit!
[TATSUMI] Like you said
before, your revenge
isn't complete yet.
Well, no, but if it means
putting you through
this, then...
[TATSUMI]
Don't wuss out on me now.
Huh?
[grunts]
Don't you get it, Shimada?
You have to finish this guy,
or else he'll just do it again.
I know that. But I can't
keep torturing you.
Think about the bastard.
About squeezing the
life out of him.
I don't know, I...
[TATSUMI] Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
You do, don't ya, kid?
All right then. Let's do this.
[TATSUMI]
Okay, ready?
[SHIMADA]
Mm...
[TATSUMI]
I'm counting on you, here.
You're not gonna let
me down, are ya, kid?
Huh?
You're just like me.
You want the same thing I do.
I respect you for that.
Okay.
Hit the damn puck.
I'm not sure.
You're not gonna
let the people who
attacked your sister get
off like that, are you?
Why don't you get it?
The problem is I don't
wanna hurt you
in order to take my revenge!
Nothing comes free
in this world.
To get what you want,
you gotta make sacrifices.
Huh?
[TATSUMI]
If you're not even willing
to cause me a little pain,
how do you think you're
gonna get your revenge?
You probably just lucked
out with the first one.
Let's get on with it.
I don't mind being
your sacrifice.
Not if it gets you the
vengeance you deserve.
Now come on and settle
the score for your sister!
[growls] Damn it!
Ah!
[groans]
[door creaks]
[thud]
[TATSUMI gasps]
[TATSUMI] What the hell?
Hold on. Does this mean...?
[DECIM]
The game is complete.
Mr. Shimada wins, six to four.
Our congratulations to you.
That's it.
[TATSUMI]
Shimada...
[TATSUMI] So... You're Sae
Shimada's older brother?
Huh? Hold on!
You know my sister?
Hey, what're you... doing?
[TATSUMI]
So, tell me. Is this it?
Is this knife the weapon
I was killed with?
Yes, it is.
What?
Allow me to explain.
Following their deaths,
people are sent
to either Heaven or to Hell.
You see, this is the
tribunal of the soul.
[TATSUMI] Tribunal of
the soul? Quite a name.
It is. And I'm the
designated arbiter.
I am terribly sorry for
the necessary deception.
So we're here to be judged.
Yeah, very funny.
So, is the joke over now?
You are joking, right?
[DECIM] Interesting.
You still cannot remember?
See, Shimada, you've
forgotten something
pretty important. I'm
guessing you don't remember
doing this, huh?
It coming back yet?
You stabbed me.
[gasps]
[SHIMADA panting]
[SHIMADA wretches]
[SHIMADA]
One down, one to go.
--[door creaks]
--[SHIMADA gasps]
--[thud]
--[SHIMADA grunts]
[TATSUMI groans]
[growling, yelling]
[SHIMADA panting, growling]
It's over, Sae.
I did it. I got 'em both.
[SHIMADA whimpers]
[TATSUMI]
I gotta say.
I wish you'd at least have used
a different knife to do it.
The worst part about
all this is knowing
that that bastard's blood
got inside my body.
That bothers me a lot more
than getting killed does.
I still don't get it.
What were you doing?
I mean, you're a detective.
[TATSUMI]
When you get down to it,
I'm a lot like you.
What was your term?
An arbiter, was it? I like that.
[gasps]
I pay attention to people
who seem like scum,
and I figure out
what they're up to.
You sister's attacker--he was
one of the scumbags.
[TATSUMI] That's why I had
been keeping an eye on him.
[gasps] You mean you were
there the whole time?
You just watched it happen?
[TATSUMI]
Yeah.
Of course. I had to watch.
Just hold still, bitch!
--[MAN 9A] Don't move!
--No!
[SAE] There was a man.
He just watched.
I think they were friends.
[SHIMADA gasps]
But why?
Why the hell didn't you
stop him, you bastard?
How could you stand
there and do nothing?
Why didn't you even try
to help my sister?
You could have saved
her, couldn't you?
[TATSUMI]
But if I had stopped him,
I couldn't have killed him.
[gasps]
[SHIMADA]
Couldn't have killed him? What?
Call it meating out punishment.
Hah, no, no, no. Passing
judgment. That's better.
You can't judge a criminal
unless there's
a victim, can you?
[WOMAN]
God. Just stop it!
Then, you needed a victim,
and that's what my sister was.
[TATSUMI]
See? You're starting to get it.
[SHIMADA growls]
What the hell is wrong with you?
Please, make it stop!
[SHIMADA grunting]
I know it isn't easy,
but I thought you got it.
Are you kidding me?
You could have saved my sister!
I had to see it
through to the end
to get the whole story.
How else was I supposed to
accurately judge the guy?
For all I knew, he was
actually a killer.
That's your argument?
--What kind of a monster are--
--[TATSUMI] Back the hell off!
[gasps]
[TATSUMI]
If I'd've stopped him that time,
he would have done
it again anyway.
You don't have any idea
how many other women
the sick freak was
already stalking.
Sure, I could have
saved your sister,
but what then, huh?
It would just mean
that another girl
would have been assaulted.
[grunts]
[TATSUMI] At least your
sister's still alive, right?
And you've finished taking
your revenge, too.
I mean, let's not forget,
you did kill me.
Don't get greedy.
That should be revenge
enough for anyone.
[SHIMADA whimpers]
You will pay for this.
How would you like to
exact that payment?
Isn't that enough?
I can't pass judgment.
I need more information.
Huh?
I wanna kill him.
[DECIM]
Very well. That can be arranged.
[gasps] Come back here!
Stop! What are you planning?
[DECIM] Words alone will
not suffice in this case.
I must observe actions, as well.
I have to see it through to
the end to judge accurately.
[gasps]
Don't do this.
So, killing me once
wasn't enough for you, huh?
That will, of course,
be impossible.
The deceased cannot be
killed a second time.
However, one can still inflict
excruciating pain upon them.
That's unfortunate.
[WOMAN]
No, stop!
[SHIMADA gasps]
Don't do it. How can
you call this judgment?
Don't you see that you're just
doing the same thing as him?
[DECIM]
How so?
Everyone has to
live with the sins
they've committed.
Everyone bears some hatred.
You just inflame it.
How's that accurate judgment?
I just wish I could understand
why you're doing this!
Because it's my job.
I must draw out the darkness
that lurks in his so--
[WOMAN]
What do you know about darkness?
You've never been part
of the living world.
You've never lost anyone.
You know nothing about grief!
Actually, I believe
I do understand.
And it's not just grief, either.
There are as many emotions
as there are people.
The fragility of someone who
lets their anger rule them.
The strength of someone
who can overcome fear
in the name of love. Be honest.
Those aren't things you can
ever hope to comprehend.
So tell me, then.
How can you pass
judgment on them?
[gasps] But-But I am...
[WOMAN] I mean really,
what is it you do?
Bring out the worst in people,
then sit back, saying,
"Ah yes, indeed,"
an impassive observer.
No. That isn't what I do.
Once in while you send
them off with a hug,
and then you pretend
like you care.
You're just putting on an act!
[DECIM grunts]
This whole thing. It's
just a screwed up mess.
Whatever you wanna call it,
this isn't judgment!
People can't be characterized.
You can't fit us into
neat little boxes.
Anybody can turn brutal,
given the right circumstances.
It's a fine line when
you think about it,
and one that was
easier for me to cross
than it would've
been for others.
I changed after I got revenge
on the filthy bastard
who killed my wife.
Turns out, sorrow and anger
could only last for so long.
I became shockingly
dispassionate.
[TATSUMI] I heard my
wife's voice thanking me
for what I did.
So I decided that
my new job would be
exacting vengeance
for helpless victims.
My wife was the sacrifice
that made that possible.
I have to say, being a detective
made the whole thing
a lot easier.
I had no shortage of
filthy criminal bastards
to choose from.
How could y--
[SHIMADA]
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Wait! Don't!
Just do it, kid.
[SHIMADA grunts]
Like I've said,
sometimes sacrifices
have to be made.
That's the way it is.
A hard lesson to learn,
but I'm tryin' to teach you.
Shut up! That's enough!
Please, calm down!
You are being judged here,
but Heaven and Hell are a lie.
The truth is there's
reincarnation or the void.
If you're reincarnated,
you may be able to see
your sister again
in some other form.
That man is watching
what you do.
He's the one who ultimately
decides what happens.
Is she telling the truth?
Is this part of the judgment?
[WOMAN]
Please, control your anger.
Don't you wanna be
with your sister again?
[growls]
If you're cast into the void,
that won't even
be a possibility!
[SHIMADA grunts]
[SHIMADA grunting]
[SHIMADA whimpers]
[TATSUMI] Please! That's
just wishful thinking.
If you can't protect
somebody, then, hey,
all you can do is
kill the other guy.
The world's a cruel,
screwed up place,
and we have to accept it.
You can't change
that, nobody can.
The only thing you
can do is fight back!
[whimpers] You see, Sae.
I'm gonna do it right this time.
I'm gonna protect you.
[footsteps]
[WOMAN]
You don't get it!
People aren't as complex as
you seem to think they are.
They're really pretty simple.
They get sad and angry
over simple things.
Can you understand that?
People are simple creatures!
The littlest things
send them spinning,
and they live never knowing
when they're going to fall.
That's what being human is!
[QUIN]
Episode Ten: "Story Teller."