Huh? Okay, where am I?
Ooh! Maybe it's a
haunted house? Cool!
[MAYU laughs] Where are you,
ghosts? Come out and play!
Ghosts, ghosts, ghosts!
You're here to stay,
so come out and play!
Huh?
[GINTI]
Hey.
[gasps] You talking to me?
You see anybody
else around here?
Just sit over there.
Since you asked nicely.
[footsteps, rustling]
Are you a collector?
Don't touch those!
[grunts]
Took your sweet
time gettin' here.
I'm gonna make the
spiel quick, so listen up.
You ready?
[MAYU]
What spiel?
In a bit, I'm gonna
have you play a game
against that dude over there.
[MAYU]
What do you mean "play a game"?
What's going on? I don't get
the point of this. Do you?
[MAYU gasps]
[MAYU]
No way.
Hey, um.
I could be totally wrong
about this, but you look like
Harada from Cross Heart Attack.
Guilty.
[MAYU]
No! Freaking! Way!
[MAYU giggles]
I am your biggest fan!
I don't know what I'm doing
here, but I don't care!
Oh, nice to meet you, too.
I would be so honored
if you'd shake my hand!
I'm Mayu Arita.
Sure. No problem.
[MAYU squeals]
[HARADA]
What is that?
And you're the one who
brought us together!
Thank you! Uh, so,
who are you, anyway?
Name's Ginti.
[MAYU] Huh? That's
kind of a weird name.
Are you C.H.A.'s
manager or something?
[GINTI]
This is gonna be a long shift.
Listen, just press this.
That'll pick what game you play.
Playing a game with Harada?
I'm so totally in! Oh, do you
mind if I press the button?
Well, apparently we
can't leave here
till we play this
game. So, go ahead.
Here we go!
[MAYU gasps]
Ooh...
[game music plays]
Um, so, what's that?
Never heard of it.
All right, follow me.
Aw, what a cute little kitty!
[HARADA]
You comin'?
Oh! Yeah!
[MAYU] I wonder what this
place is. Do you know?
[HARADA]
No clue.
[MAYU]
So, no shows today, huh?
[HARADA] Nope. I guess
it must be my day off.
Only, I can't seem to
remember how I got here.
What about you?
No, I got nothin'!
Looks like you're
taking it pretty well.
[MAYU]
I'm here, chatting with Harada.
Nothing's gonna
ruin that for me.
[HARADA]
Right...
Ooh! That's huge!
[GINTI grunts]
[MAYU] I've got no idea
how to play this.
Well, gimme a sec. I'll explain.
Take your socks off
and stand on the edge.
All right.
The spinner is gonna
give you your instructions.
[MAYU]
What spinner?
This thing up here. It spins.
[MAYU] The kitty's the
one who controls it?
[GINTI]
Memine! Call her by her name.
[MAYU]
Okay.
Now, back to the instructions.
Just do what the
spinner tells you to.
Place the selected body part
on the selected circle.
If you fall or if you
touch the mat beyond
what's specified,
then, you lose.
That's it, those are the rules.
Everybody got it?
Yeah, that sounds
simple enough to me.
[game dings]
[SPINNER VOICE]
Player one, left hand to blue.
[GINTI]
Ladies first, I guess.
You mean we're
starting already?
That's the idea.
[MAYU] You're really
grouchy, you know that?
And my name's Mayu, by the way.
You could try using it.
Don't really care what
your name is, honey.
--Just start playing.
--[MAYU] Ugh!
[MAYU] What is this guy's
problem? He's a real ass.
[gasps]
[MAYU] Good, he wasn't
watching. Calm down, Mayu!
[game dings]
[SPINNER VOICE] Player two,
right foot to yellow.
[game dings]
[SPINNER VOICE] Player one,
right hand to blue.
You get the idea.
Have a grand old time.
Sounds easy enough.
[game dings]
Player two, left hand to blue.
Aw, yeah!
[gasps]
Uh...
[MAYU humming]
[MAYU] I guess you can't
expect a guy not to look.
And considering who it is, it's
not like I'm gonna complain!
Is there something wrong, Mayu?
It's your turn to move.
[MAYU] Gah! He said it!
He said my name!
I can officially die happy now!
[SPINNER VOICE]
Player two, right hand to red.
[game dings]
[HARADA sighs] I guess
I have to play this game,
but I wish the girl
was a little cuter.
[SPINNER VOICE] Player one,
right hand to yellow.
[HARADA]
She's just too obvious.
[laughs]
[HARADA] I just wanna get out
of here so I can see Lisa.
[door clicks]
[SPINNER VOICE]
Player one, right foot to blue.
[MAYU grunts]
Whew! Almost fell!
[SPINNER VOICE]
Player two, left foot to yellow.
Left foot to yellow.
How's that gonna work?
[HARADA]
Hm.
[HARADA grunts]
[gasps]
--[HARADA grunts]
--[game dings]
Amazing!
No wonder they call you
C.H.A.'s dance prince!
--[SPINNER VOICE] Player one,
--It was nothing.
--left hand to red.
[MAYU]
Oh! He is just too cool!
And I'm close enough to
smell his sweat! Yummy!
[yawns]
[MAYU giggles]
[MAYU] Ah! This is bliss!
If only I could stop time!
I wish this game could
go on forever and ever!
Okay. I'm getting tired.
My arms can't take much more.
[MAYU]
And I have to pee.
Hey. Can you hear me?
Yeah? What do you want?
I need to take a little break.
[GINTI]
Why's that?
[MAYU growls]
You get one, so why can't we?
I'm tired, okay? And I
need to use the restroom.
Too bad.
Come on! What is your problem?
It isn't just me. Harada
wants a break, too.
I could use one.
It's not gonna happen,
so quit bothering me.
And there's one more
thing I forgot to say.
There'll be consequences
for the loser.
Potentially fatal consequences.
Is that supposed to be
a joke or something?
'Cause it's not very funny.
[GINTI] A cruel joke, I guess
you could call it. See this?
What is it?
You think I'm just
kidding around?
Let me prove I'm serious.
What?
[gasps]
[cackling]
Ew, creepy!
[MAYU] That's it! What the
hell is going on here?
This is the beginning
of the actual game.
Hope you two kids
have a lovely time.
Well, what are
you waiting for?
It says left hand, red.
Let's get to it.
Fine!
What?
What happened?
[BOTH gasp]
Hot!
This is a prank, right?
It burns! Ow!
You can stop it now!
[MAYU]
Come on! Turn it off!
[GINTI] This is the most
fun I've had all day.
Why would I stop it?
I can't wait to see who's
gonna lose their balance first.
--[MAYU groaning]
--Hot! Hot!
[MAYU]
Quick! It's left hand green!
[HARADA gasps]
[yelps]
That feels nice!
Huh?
[screams]
You can just turn around!
[GINTI] You really think
anybody's interested
in whatever you've
got under there?
[growls] What did you say to me?
[screaming]
[MAYU] This wind's too strong.
I can't take a breath.
Quick! It's your move!
[MAYU]
Oh, right. Blue.
Well, player two, move your
right foot to yellow.
[BOTH panting]
You should really
focus on the game,
unless you wanna die.
[panting]
Freezing!
Right foot yellow.
That's not good.
[HARADA]
It'll be close.
D-D-Do you think
you can do it?
[gasps]
[HARADA] It's frozen?
No way! That isn't fair!
That's the kinda
thing that happens
when you dilly-dally.
[HARADA grunting]
Damn it!
[panting]
[MAYU] This is it.
We're gonna die here.
Although, this could
be a "Titanic" moment!
Wouldn't that be romantic?
These poses are
kinda awkward, though.
[grunting]
--[panting]
--[crackling]
[HARADA grunting]
Can he do it?
You should never doubt
the dance prince!
[HARADA yells]
[FANGIRLS chanting]
C.H.A.! C.H.A.! C.H.A.! C.H.A.!
[MAYU]
Harada...
Harada!
[GIRLS cheer]
[laughs]
I can't believe we did it!
You were amazing!
I thought we were gonna die!
[panting] It was nothin'!
--Huh? What now?
--[HARADA] Not again!
[gasps]
[MAYU]
Oh, god! No way!
[HARADA, MAYU scream]
Stunning view, isn't it?
You psycho! Get us out of here!
[GINTI]
No, I don't think I will.
This may come as a surprise,
but I don't actually care
what happens to you.
This is my favorite part
of the whole thing.
Welcome to the
sudden death round.
The game's about to end. Just as
soon as one of you falls.
[GINTI] There. Took a while,
but we've finally
reached the entertaining
part. Pathetic humans.
[HARADA]
When one of us... falls?
[MAYU]
Oh, god.
[HARADA]
Falls or... gets pushed.
[MAYU]
What do I do?
[panting]
[MAYU]
I can't.
[HARADA whimpering]
[HARADA]
It's either her or me.
[MAYU] It's... hopeless.
I can't hold it anymore!
[MAYU] I can't pee myself
in front of Harada.
I'd rather...
[MAYU]
It's over. I quit.
It's been amazing.
I got to play a game,
one-on-one, with Harada.
What more could a girl ask for?
I'm so happy. This is
a dream come true.
Ever since that first concert,
I've been your biggest fan.
I went to your shows
and bought your posters.
I even sent you fan mail.
A lot of fan mail.
Whenever things got tough,
or I was having a bad day,
I would listen to your songs,
and they would cheer me up.
Well, anyway. I guess what
I'm saying is, thanks.
Thanks, Harada, for
always being there.
[MAYU]
Without you and your music,
there were times I
couldn't have kept going.
[MAYU] I know people always
called you a womanizer.
But I never cared
about any of that.
I was your fan, no matter what!
They just didn't understand.
You treat fans like they're
special. That's how you are.
[gasps]
How could you?
Breaking up with me like I
never meant anything to you!
Hey, I said I'm sorry, Kana.
[laughs]
[HARADA] Kana, oh my god.
I didn't want this to happen.
No, my fans deserve better.
If I can ask one thing,
please don't forget me.
Good luck with C.H.A. and your
dancing and everything.
You'll be great!
Well, goodbye.
[HARADA gasps]
[HARADA]
No! Not this again!
What are you doing?
[HARADA]
I can't let you do this.
We'll find some way
out. Right, Mayu?
Without you, I'd be nothing!
Huh?
[HARADA]
My fans make me who I am.
They make me a success!
It's because of them that
I've come so far in my life.
It's because of you, Mayu!
How could I forget
something as basic as that?
It won't happen again!
[MAYU] You... You really
mean that! Wow.
[grunts]
I can't let it end like this.
I can't do it! Promise me!
Say you'll come to one
of my concerts again!
Yeah!
[HARADA] Do you promise?
I want you to promise!
[MAYU]
Yes! I promise you I will!
Thank you for that.
Sure.
No!
[gasps]
[MAYU]
What an awesome show!
Harada was so amazing!
C.H.A.! C.H.A.! C--
H--
No way!
[screams]
Huh?
Huh?!
[HARADA] Damn it. Damn it!
How could this happen?
Another woman gone
because of me!
[LISA]
Wake up, Harada.
Are you awake?
I wanted to let you know
I'm leaving. Goodbye.
It's early. You have
to leave already?
[door clicks]
[ticking]
--[yells]
--[explosion]
[HARADA]
No way...
[bell chimes]
[GINTI] Sacrificing yourself.
Didn't expect that one.
Is it all coming
back to you now?
In case you're confused,
the gist of it is you're de--
[MAYU]
Oh, just shut it!
'Scuse me?
[MAYU growling]
Alive or dead, whatever,
I just need a change of clothes!
I couldn't hold it anymore!
I need a shower!
Well, this is interesting.
You heard the part about
being dead, right?
Are we certain
this one's human?
[HARADA]
How can I be dead?
Hey, you, no touching.
Oh, Kana! I'm sorry!
[GINTI]
I said, don't touch it!
Sorry for the delay.
[MAYU]
Hm?
Who the hell are you?
[MAYU] Ugh! I told you!
My name is Mayu!
[GINTI]
Ah! Moron! What did you do?
Pick it up!
Wow, I didn't
recognize you at all!
Huh?
You look a whole lot
cuter this way.
Really? I do?
Yeah, you're totally my type!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
[GINTI grunting]
[MAYU]
You mean it?
--[HARADA] Yeah!
--[MAYU] Oh!
What's with them? Stupid humans.
[HARADA]
We're already dead, you know!
[MAYU]
Oh yeah, that's right!
[meowing]
[gasps]
[yawns]
Are you ready?
Let's get going!
Yay!
[laughing]
C.H.A.! C.H.A.!
My girl, Mayu!
This one's for you!
What do you say we kick it
off with our debut single?
Yay!
[CLAVIS]
[WOMAN, DECIM]
Yay.
[grunting]
Sit back and enjoy the show!
[MAYU, HARADA]
It's Cross! Heart! Attack!
[QUIN]
Episode Seven: "Alcohol Poison."