[QUIN] Hello, there.
Information bureau.
I have a favor to ask.
[QUIN]
Oh?
[DECIM] Do you think I
could have you send me
some memories, please?
Yes. Thank you very much.
[DECIM gasps]
[elevator dings]
[gasps]
And where are you going?
What's it matter
to you, old man?
[OCULUS] I hope you enjoyed
yourself. Looked like fun.
Sorry?
You've been bad, Nona.
[grunts]
[NONA]
No way are you sneaking a peek.
What you've been up
to isn't gonna fly.
Arbiters have to be dummies,
that's how it works.
Do they? Or is that
just to suit you?
Why don't you tell me
what you're after here.
[NONA]
You want to know?
[OCULUS]
Mm.
[NONA] Well, the fact
is, we can change.
[OCULUS] I take it you're
talking about arbiters
who possess human emotions?
Yeah, that's right.
Come on, don't you see?
We aren't just hollow dummies!
Ah.
[laughs]
[OCULUS] That's so ridiculous,
it's making my flower shrivel.
We're all just dummies, Nona,
and that includes me.
[NONA gasps]
[OCULUS]
Do you understand it yet?
Have you figured out
what we are?
What we're made of?
The souls of those
cast into the void.
Don't even get me
started on our location.
We are what we are.
As long as our fundamental
essence stays the same,
this nonsense you're trying
to pull won't change anything.
Face it, my dear.
The arbiters will behave
as they always have.
[NONA]
That isn't true!
[OCULUS]
Go ahead.
Ah.
You'll see the truth
of things soon enough.
[elevator dings]
Thank you for waiting. Huh?
Please take us to the
lowest level, Clavis.
Uh. Really? Are you sure?
I am sure, thank you.
[CLAVIS]
And you're taking her with you?
[DECIM]
That is correct.
Okay.
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
Chiyuki? Chiyuki.
[CHIYUKI grunts]
[gasps] What? This looks
like my room. But how?
Impossible. There's no way I--
--[CHIYUKI yelps]
--[thud]
[CHIYUKI]
Ow.
[gasps]
[door scrapes]
You woke sooner than
I was expecting.
[DECIM] May I ask what
it is you're doing?
No.
[DECIM]
Oh, look. I remember these.
They're the dolls your
mother made, right?
[CHIYUKI]
Mm-hmm.
[DECIM]
She's quite talented.
[CHIYUKI]
Huh? How do you figure?
They don't look
anything like the book.
That's okay. I
treasured them anyway.
This has been so strange.
I was starting to
think it was a dream.
I'm afraid this is reality.
It all happened.
Three months have passed
since your death.
Would you like me
to give you a hand?
[CHIYUKI] That's okay.
I can walk on my own.
It's empty.
[gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Mama!
[CHIYUKI gasps]
Read me the book again!
[CHIYUKI'S MOM] You really
like "Chavvot," don't you?
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[door clicks]
[gasps]
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
Well, I'm home.
That's my mom.
[gasps] Oh, god, Mom!
Hello, Chiyuki. I'm home again.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[DECIM] She is neither
able to see nor hear us.
We can't touch people
in the living world.
We cannot converse with them.
We can't make contact
of any kind.
[CHIYUKI] You could've
told me all that sooner.
[DECIM]
I am terribly sorry.
Why bring me here, anyway?
If you would please take this.
[gasps]
What's going on?
This is why I brought you here.
It wasn't just to give you
a glimpse of your old life.
[CHIYUKI]
Huh?
Did you know 7,000
people die every hour?
That's approximately
two per second.
While it lasts, life is
riddled with unfairness.
There are those who
live fulfilling lives.
And there are those who pass
away sooner than they should.
[gasps]
[DECIM]
Please listen closely.
I have a bargain to offer you.
In exchange for the
life of one person,
I can bring you back
to life, right now.
[gasps]
[DECIM]
Simply press this button.
If you do that, all of your
memories of Quindecim
will be erased, and you
will return to your life.
You must choose
quickly, however.
Little time remains.
What will your decision be?
[CHIYUKI] My life for someone
else's? That's the deal?
Yes.
It's possible that it will be
one of my friends
or family who dies.
[DECIM]
Yes.
However, do consider
the world's population.
It's currently more
than 7,000,000,000,
which makes that
highly improbable.
Your mother, your
father, your friends.
Everybody who knows
you will have
any and all memories
of your death erased.
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
You know, Chiyuki.
Watching you skate was always
one of the highlights of
my life, but what made me
happiest was watching
you grow up.
Seeing you become a good woman.
[sobs] I'm not a good woman.
[gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Just go, okay?
[CHIYUKI] The fact that
I couldn't skate anymore
wasn't what was hard for me.
People can't know
each other perfectly.
And to hope for that
kind of understanding.
It's wrong.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[CHIYUKI'S MOM] Here.
It was always your favorite.
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
You know, it's funny.
I just can't seem
to stop making extra.
Oh, Chiyuki. I'm so sorry.
I had no idea. I couldn't
tell what you were feeling.
--I was so blind.
--[CHIYUKI gasps]
[CHIYUKI'S MOM]
I've failed as a mother.
I'm sorry!
What kind of mother
can't even tell
what her own
daughter is feeling?
It's not true!
Mom, it's not true!
I miss you so much!
[gasps] Mom!
I accept. Give me my life back.
I have to tell my mom
it wasn't her fault!
I have to say sorry.
People have an
instinctive desire
to understand each other, right?
Maybe that's not so bad.
Or maybe it is, I don't know.
But it's still what I want.
So, yes.
[CHIYUKI]
I'm getting a second chance.
Let someone else die
and I can live.
[CHIYUKI] I have to, right?
It's the only choice I can make.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
You know, you're
actually right for once.
Yeah, I'm in love
with somebody else.
Like I said. I think I still
have a date to claim.
I've always wanted to.
Why couldn't I just
give her that?
She was always so good to me.
I'll do anything you want.
Please just send me
back to my children.
[TATSUMI]
I heard my wife's voice
thanking me for what I did.
So I decided that
my new job would be
exacting vengeance
for helpless victims.
[CHIYUKI]
Please, control your anger.
Don't you wanna be
with your sister again?
[SHIMADA grunting]
[SACHIKO]
It may be over now,
but at least I know
that I lived a full life.
[CHIYUKI]
I can't. I can't press it.
I don't understand.
It isn't right. Everybody
matters to somebody.
[DECIM] But whoever ended
up dying in your place
most likely wouldn't
matter to you.
[CHIYUKI]
I'm not an idiot. I know that!
I know it, but even if they
aren't important to me,
there's someone out there
they are important to.
Someone who cherishes them.
[gasps]
[CHIYUKI]
Somebody like my mom.
[DECIM gasps]
But, god. If only
I could talk to her!
[DECIM grunts]
[CHIYUKI sobbing]
Mom...
[CHIYUKI] I'm so sorry
for not valuing my life.
I'm so sorry for not
thinking of you.
For doing something so selfish.
For causing you
so much grief. Sorry!
And for not giving
you the chance
to say goodbye.
I'm so, so sorry!
[gasps]
[sobbing]
[grunts, pants]
[DECIM panting]
[CHIYUKI]
Here!
You press it!
[DECIM gasps]
Now! Press it!
[gasps]
[DECIM sobs]
[CHIYUKI]
Decim?
[DECIM]
I am terribly sorry.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[yells]
[CHIYUKI]
What's going on?
[DECIM]
None of it was true.
I am so sorry for deceiving you.
[CHIYUKI]
But why?
[DECIM grunts] I am sorry for
putting you through all of this.
You mean it was all
part of my judgment?
[DECIM grunts]
[gasps]
It hurts so much. This feeling.
This is sorrow, isn't it?
I think so.
Hurting you hurt me.
I just wanted to know you
better. To understand you.
[gasps]
[DECIM]
Chiyuki. I am truly sorry.
But this was the only way.
I had to know. I'm sorry.
[DECIM] I am an arbiter,
and arbiters judge.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
[CHIYUKI]
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
[CHIYUKI]
You don't have to apologize.
But after what I did...
It's okay, I understand.
[gasps]
[sobs]
[NONA]
Decim.
You've destroyed
that poor boy, Nona.
I just had him
conduct a judgment
together with a human.
Things change as
arbiters come closer
to being human. Judgment
becomes more difficult to pass,
and it is accompanied
by suffering.
One thing's clear.
Humans can't judge humans.
If you know that,
then what was the point
of this doomed experiment?
Judging humans is
difficult, true.
But that doesn't make
it right to assign
any random judgment to them.
There needs to be a change.
That was the point
of what I did.
[OCULUS] So your goal is
to make arbiters suffer?
Care to explain the
reasoning behind that?
[NONA] A judgment ought to be
accompanied by suffering,
or what's its purpose?
[OCULUS]
Its purpose?
[NONA]
To suffer, yet stand firm.
That's what it is to live.
It's what gives life meaning.
The meaning of life?
That's what this is about?
It's a concept. It's
only relevant to those
who are able to die. And the
funny thing about dying--
You can't do it
unless you're alive.
Even if the arbiters
become more human,
it doesn't change the fact
that they're just dummies.
You're wrong. It is relevant.
We live in the present.
[CHIYUKI]
What is this place, anyway?
[DECIM] This is where the
dummies are disposed of
after their judgment is
complete and their souls
have been removed.
Under normal circumstances,
no one is permitted
to come in here.
So, this is where I'll end up?
[DECIM]
No.
Oh, good. Thanks for that.
After they die,
some humans try to live
all the more in the present.
Those who led fulfilling
lives are the kind of--
[CHIYUKI] The kind of people
you respect, right?
[DECIM]
Yes.
[CHIYUKI]
Heard that a million times.
[DECIM]
Really? That many?
[CHIYUKI]
Heh. Forget about it.
[DECIM] I am terribly sorry
to have kept you waiting.
Eh, no worries.
You're stealing my
material, though.
What?
[CLAVIS]
Forget it.
Hello there.
Good to see you.
All right, folks.
Where're we headed?
[OCULUS]
Nona.
You have become quite
fascinated with life and death,
haven't you?
[DECIM]
Miss Chiyuki.
[CHIYUKI]
Hmm?
[DECIM]
Was it worth it? Being alive?
[gasps]
Mm.
[DECIM]
That is wonderful to hear.
That's my goal now.
To be the kind of
arbiter who can help
all his guests feel that way.
I am glad I succeeded with you.
Yeah.
Some advice, though.
Might do something
about your face.
[DECIM]
Huh?
You do know how to
smile, don't you?
[DECIM]
Er, is it like this?
[sighs] Baby steps, I guess.
I am terribly sorry I failed.
[CHIYUKI] You'll get it
before long, don't worry.
Well, this is it, huh?
[DECIM] Yes. Best of luck
on your journey.
Goodbye, then.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
[DECIM]
Farewell.
[CLAVIS]
Hey, where'd Memine go?
[GINTI]
I dunno.
Huh?
She doesn't come around
anymore, that's all.
[grunts]
[GINTI]
What're you doing?
Pour me a drink, bartender!
Why? What exactly is
going on with you today?
[CLAVIS] Please, like you
actually care, Ginti.
[GINTI]
Tch, whatever.
[CASTRA]
Oh, yeah? Your boy did it?
[NONA]
Mm-hmm.
This sounds like a
real game-changer.
There are so many
arbiters. What do we do?
Should we retain the
memories of death again
and forward them on?
Nah. Let's just see
what happens for a bit.
We don't have to do anything.
Old flower-head's been
watching her like a hawk.
You know that, right?
Yeah? What is she thinking?
[QUIN] We just need
to behave ourselves.
Number One:
Arbiters cannot stop
making judgments,
for this task is
more than their job.
It is the entire reason
for their existence.
Number Two:
Arbiters cannot
experience death,
for that would taint
their judgments.
It would make them too
close to being human.
Number Three:
Arbiters cannot feel emotions,
for doing so is not
in their natures.
It is impossible for a
dummy to have feelings.
[OCULUS] Number Four:
Arbiters may not work
hand-in-hand with life,
for doing so would ruin them.
It is an unacceptable
collaboration.
[elevator dings]
[WOMAN 12A, MAN 12A gasp]
Weird. What is this place?
Right this way, please.
Welcome to Quindecim.
Have a seat.