[DECIM grunts]
Where am I?
Who am I?
For the moment,
you don't have a name,
but I can tell you
that you are an arbiter.
What do you mean by "arbiter"?
An arbiter is someone who
judges people's souls
and sends them either for
reincarnation or into the void.
I'm to act as a
judge assessing souls?
The souls of humans?
An arbiter of souls.
[NONA]
Number One: Arbiters cannot stop
making judgments, for this
task is more than their job.
It is the entire reason
for their existence.
Number Two: Arbiters
cannot experience death,
for that would taint
their judgments.
It would make them too
close to being human.
Number Three: Arbiters
cannot feel emotions,
for doing so is not
in their natures.
It is impossible for a
dummy to have feelings.
Out with it. What are
you doing here?
Whatever you wanna call it,
this isn't judgment!
[DECIM] I have come to believe
that the way in which
we arrive at our judgments
is fundamentally flawed.
[NONA]
Is it? How so?
The method that we employ:
using extreme conditions
in order to reveal
the darkness within the soul.
What if we are creating
that darkness rather than
just uncovering it?
[NONA grunts]
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but I have true respect
for people who have
lived a fulfilling life.
So, I cannot judge them.
[NONA] I see. So, what
are we to do about her?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[NONA] Decim. Her term
is coming to an end.
The time has passed quickly.
[NONA] Do you think you
can judge her now?
Perhaps it would be easier
for you if I did it.
No, ma'am, but thank you.
[NONA]
Very well.
Then you judge her
and make the decision.
Will she be reincarnated or...
...will she be cast out
into the void?
However, creating the
right conditions--
What all do you know about
her? Is it insufficient?
If I'm correct, most of her
memories were erased.
They were.
Shall I have Quin send along
her compilation for you?
No. I should be all right.
Given your new doubts,
will you judge her
without seeing the
darkness within her soul?
In all honesty. I don't
think her true nature--
You really think you
know her true nature?
Even if you did, you might not
be able to understand it.
[DECIM gasps]
[NONA]
Go back to your post now.
I'm going to send you
a special guest.
Whatever you do, judge her.
You are still an
arbiter, are you not?
[footsteps]
[WOMAN]
Hm?
[DECIM] Pardon me. A guest
will be arriving shortly.
[WOMAN]
Could you handle it?
[gasps]
[DECIM] I can tell that
you are out of sorts.
You have become aware
that you are human?
There is something
else you should know.
Human souls cannot remain here.
If they should exceed
the period of judgment,
they become dummies,
like those you've seen.
The time has come.
I cannot wait any
longer to judge you.
Still judging. After all that's
happened, nothing's changed?
I am an arbiter. What
other choice do I have?
[WOMAN]
What will you do to judge me?
I do not yet know.
[WOMAN gasps]
I have refrained from
accepting the memories
of our next guest.
Nor do I have any idea which
game is going to be selected.
Our next guest, you said?
Somebody else is coming, then?
Right this way, ma'am.
Welcome to Quindecim.
Please have a seat.
[SACHIKO] You're saying
that I can't leave here
unless I play this
game of yours?
Correct. I'm terribly sorry.
[SACHIKO] I suppose I have
nothing else to do.
What about you?
Yeah, I've got plenty of time.
And when we're
finished with that,
you'll let us out of here?
Yes. I promise you I will.
Well, that settles that, then.
And what shall we be playing?
[SACHIKO gasps]
Oh, my.
What is it?
It's just... I think I've
seen that somewhere before.
Huh?
But, for the life of me,
I can't seem to think of
where it would have been.
[SACHIKO] Hmm? Is something
the matter, dear?
[WOMAN]
No, it's nothing, I'm sorry.
[game music plays]
Oh. It knows I'm here, I guess.
No, the card game--
Yes, I assumed as much.
Forgive an old lady
a joke, won't you?
[DECIM] I will be joining you
for the game, as well.
[SACHIKO] Two isn't enough
for Old Maid, after all.
[DECIM] First, if you will
please remove any pairs of cards
from your hand and lay
them down on the table.
Whoever is holding the joker
at the end of the game
is the loser.
[SACHIKO] And these are just
regular playing cards
that we're using?
Yes, although you
may find their design
a bit different than normal.
Oh?
[gasps]
Oh, my!
Isn't that something?
Well, you wouldn't
know it, as my drawings
aren't very popular, but I
work as an illustrator.
This is one of my characters.
[DECIM] The designs on these
cards are, in fact, relevant.
They show scenes that
relate to the players.
By dealing them, I have
distributed them about.
My goodness. These are
really something, aren't they?
Oh! Hello, Grandpa.
This makes me so happy.
Thank you very much
for saying so.
[SACHIKO] Oh, no, young man!
I should be thanking you.
I haven't even introduced
myself. I'm Uemura Sachiko.
And it's a pleasure meeting you.
[DECIM] My name is Decim.
I am the bartender here.
I'm sorry. I don't actually
know what my name is.
Oh?
Let's start, okay?
[WOMAN]
I don't know my own name.
With that done, the
game will now begin.
I haven't played cards
in such a long time.
I'm having so much fun!
[GINTI]
Say what?
What do you mean
"The point of judging"?
[DECIM] Well. What is the
purpose of what we do?
Why is it that
we pass judgments?
What the hell are
you talking about?
Are you a freaking idiot, man?
There isn't a point.
We're here to judge,
so we judge.
That's all! Finis!
The End! You get it now?
But is that a good
enough reason, though?
[GINTI]
It's not good, and it's not bad.
All there is, is the
outcome of the judgments.
Quit snoring!
You sound like a cow!
What's with you? You're
acting like a human.
Humans think dying's
something that happens
to someone else. So,
at the moment of death,
they start desperately
looking for meaning.
But there is no
meaning to living.
The fact of the matter is,
they live in order to die.
So stop thinking about
the meaning of life,
or of your judgments!
[SACHIKO]
Hm.
[WOMAN]
It's your turn.
I am terribly sorry.
[DECIM]
Things are moving right along.
They are.
[gasps]
[QUIN] Yeah? He's got
doubts about judging now?
[NONA]
Mm-hmm.
[QUIN]
Oh, that's all well and good.
Different from implanting
human emotions, though, right?
Yeah, well, at this point,
I think all we can have Decim do
is draw on all of his judgments.
[QUIN]
So? Why did you come here?
You have her
memories from before
they were condensed and
compiled. Give me all of them.
Huh?
[SACHIKO]
Ooh! Another pair for me!
Huh?
My, it's almost
like magic, isn't it?
I'm sorry. Is
something the matter?
No, don't trouble yourself.
Looks like my victory, eh?
Congratulations on the win.
Thank you very much, dear.
[DECIM]
Hm?
[SACHIKO]
I'm going to ask you a question,
and I want the truth,
all right? Be honest, now.
Is this the afterlife?
Oh--
[gasps]
Yes.
I thought as much.
[WOMAN]
What are you doing?
It does not matter.
Huh?
To summarize, following death,
people's souls arrive here.
It is my job to pass
judgment upon them.
I am what's called an arbiter.
Ah.
[DECIM] When did you first
realize this was the afterlife?
Only a moment ago.
Do you see this boy here?
His name is Miu,
but this drawing of him
doesn't actually exist.
[DECIM, WOMAN gasp]
[SACHIKO] He was going to
appear in my next feature,
but I haven't drawn him yet.
As a character, he
exists only in my mind.
But here he is, just as I
imagined him! What a surprise!
That's what tipped me off.
This couldn't possibly be
the world I've always known.
Sorry, but you don't
seem very troubled.
I might feel different
about the whole situation
if I could remember dying.
[laughs] Ah, the joys
of getting old!
No one who comes
here remembers dying.
It has nothing to do
with your age.
If you'd like to know how
you passed, I could tell you.
[SACHIKO]
That's okay.
Huh?
To be honest, I suspect
I'm better off not knowing.
Thank you for this, though.
My time in this place has
been like a wonderful dream.
[gasps] Oh, really? Playing
the game, you mean?
Yes, dear, that's right.
My husband and I weren't
able to start a family
of our own. So the
characters I created
became like my children.
I never imagined I would
see them again like this.
It's been a delightful surprise.
My work wasn't always
easy, but I'm glad
I got the chance
to come face-to-face
with my illustrations.
So, you see, I'm happy I
played that game of yours.
It may be over now,
but at least I know
that I lived a full life.
That is a wonderful
thing to hear.
A full life.
Shall we continue on
with the game, then?
Ugh!
What are you gonna do
with her memories, anyway?
[NONA]
Just get them, okay?
[QUIN] It's not like
I'm made of time, here.
Do you know how many
people die every second?
Seems like there's
a lot in here.
[QUIN] Actually, it's not that
much. She died pretty early.
Don't concern yourself with
arbiter memory capacity
this time around. I want
you to recompile these.
Uh...
Here, for your trouble.
Uh-- Ah!
Ha!
[gasps]
[SACHIKO] Oh, my. I
recognize those drawings.
That one's Chavvot, isn't it?
[DECIM]
Chavvot?
[SACHIKO] Yes, it's the name
of a little girl character
in the children's
book, "Chavvot."
By any chance, was that
one of your works?
No, not mine.
I've just read the book
before, that's all.
Can you tell us what
the story is about?
[SACHIKO]
Well, let me see.
It's about this little
boy named Jimmy
who falls in love with Chavvot.
But he can't tell her because
she's unable to hear.
So Jimmy wishes on a star.
He asks that someday,
Chavvot will know
how he feels about her.
Intriguing.
[SACHIKO]
Think about it.
When you want to express
your feelings to someone,
how would you usually do it, eh?
[DECIM]
Well, uh... I...
Using words?
Exactly, my dear.
That's what most people think,
and I believe that's why
the author wrote it
so Chavvot was deaf.
[WOMAN, DECIM gasp]
We don't always realize it,
but there are so many
other ways of expressing our
emotions besides using words.
Here's an example. Take a look.
[DECIM]
A smile?
Yes. A smile is universal.
Wherever you're from,
it means you're happy.
Just like a frown shows
everyone you're unhappy.
It really is wondrous, isn't it?
A language that
everybody speaks!
--[GIRL] Mama!
--[gasps]
Mama! Read me the book again!
You really like
"Chavvot," don't you?
Yep! That okay?
Well, of course!
Mama likes "Chavvot," too.
Okay, good!
What part do you like most?
Her smile really is
terrific, isn't it?
You're right. That's my
favorite part too, Chi!
I'm pretty sure...
my name is Chiyuki.
[gasps]
[SACHIKO]
Oh! You remember your name now?
Yes. I don't know what
could have changed,
but I do!
And what a beautiful
name it is, my dear.
It's sweet of you to say so.
[CHIYUKI whimpers]
I remember Mom.
What is it? Is something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
In that case, I
believe it's my turn.
[DECIM]
I'm out of cards.
Which means, that this game
is now officially over.
[elevator dings]
Are you coming, too, Chiyuki?
Not yet. I'm going to
stay a little longer.
Ah. Take care of yourself.
Thanks.
And you're quite sure
that it's all right
if I take these
with me, young man?
[DECIM]
Yes. You're welcome to them.
[SACHIKO] Thank you
so much. I was thinking.
[gasps]
You know how, in
Old Maid, the person
who gets left with the joker
in their hand is the loser?
I've always found that rule
to be a rather strange one.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Just look at most
other card games.
The joker's usually
a trump card.
Having it left at the end
seems prudent to me.
Yes.
Well, my dears.
It's been lovely.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for playing.
Best of luck on your journey.
[CHIYUKI]
So, out with it.
I wanna know how it happened.
I suppose that we really
can't do it this way, can we?
[CLAVIS]
Here I am, Oculus, sir.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Clavis! There's my boy.
I'm happy to help, sir.
What can I do for you?
[OCULUS]
Cruel-hearted Nona seems to be
avoiding me for
some reason. Tell me.
You play billiards, don't ya?
No, I'm sorry sir, but I can't.
I'm only jokin'.
[OCULUS] Hang tight. This
should only take a second.
Isn't that just fascinating.
An arbiter with human emotions.
Sorry about that.
What?
We're all done here.
You can go now.
Oh, all right. Thank you.
I'll get going, then.
[OCULUS]
How utterly pointless.
[DECIM] You know. I don't
believe people live
just so that they
can die someday.
I think it's because
they are alive
that they must die
at some point.
[CHIYUKI]
Hmm.
I believe that there is
a purpose to being alive.
[gasps]
And there's a purpose
to judgment, as well.
Judging is tricky.
Difficult to do right.
It goes hand-in-hand
with both life and death.
By its very nature, it must
be performed hand-in-hand
with human beings.
And because of that, it
requires human emotions.
[CHIYUKI gasps]
Chiyuki, please.
Sorry?
If you don't mind.
I need you to fill in
the blanks for me.
What?
Huh.
[QUIN]
Episode 11: "Memento Mori."