[OCULUS]
Number One:
Arbiters cannot stop
making judgments,
for this task is
more than their job.
It's the entire reason
for their existence.
Number Two:
Arbiters cannot
experience death,
for that would taint
their judgments.
It would make them too
close to being human.
Number Three:
Arbiters cannot feel emotions,
for doing so is not
in their natures.
It's impossible for a dummy
to have feelings, after all.
[WOMAN gasps]
[sighs] That same dream,
over and over.
[yawns]
[NOVEM]
Not being able to judge someone?
[GINTI] Yeah, that's
right. Ever happened?
No.
Never to me.
Uh...
What is it?
Nothing. Just forget
about it, okay?
Tch.
[growls]
[train horn blows]
[WOMAN sighs]
Huh?
[WOMAN]
What's that?
All the other books around
here are about booze.
This one's different.
[WOMAN gasps]
Wow, Quin. Looking pretty beat.
Yeah, and it's
all thanks to you.
[WOMAN gasps]
Just like the guests.
I'm dead, too.
[WOMAN gasps]
Good morning. I hope
you slept well.
I'll have a warm meal
ready for us to eat shortly.
[WOMAN]
Decim. Whose is this?
Sorry, but I do not know that.
Listen, I...
[WOMAN]
I was wondering...
Huh?
Oh, never mind.
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
[DECIM]
Now that I think about it.
It's possible that
Quin left it here.
Huh? Who's Quin?
Quindecim's former arbiter.
I guess you haven't met her yet.
The former you?
[elevator dings]
Sorry if you've
been waiting long.
Please step in.
Thank you, Clavis.
So, where are we
headed to today?
We're going to the Quindecim.
All righty.
Starting tomorrow, you will
officially be Decim.
I am at your disposal, ma'am.
[GINTI] The 15th floor,
is it? Pretty low, huh?
Haven't I told you that has
nothing to do with anything?
But you're all the
way up on the 90th.
Yeah, of course I am.
I'm in charge of this
whole tower, after all.
[CLAVIS chuckles]
Hey, Chuckles. What are
you laughin' about?
Last I checked, you're
on the 20th floor.
That's not much of
a difference, is it?
[GINTI]
Nobody asked you!
Let me introduce the
two of you. This is Quin.
It's nice to meet you.
Which one of them is
going to be Decim?
This white-haired one.
Do you like to drink?
Uh...
See that?
That's my liquor, and I'm
giving every last drop to you!
That's right, I'm finally
done being an arbiter!
What a freakin' relief!
[laughs] I'm not cut out
for this crap, ya know?
Looks like I've been transferred
to the information bureau,
but they provide
all the booze there,
so you're welcome to mine.
Oh, and one more thing.
[GINTI grunts] Doesn't know
how to shut up, does she?
Don't be such a jerk about it.
She just likes to talk.
Now, take these.
Time for the fun part.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
[NONA]
Tomorrow, that'll be you boys.
You'll be the arbiters.
Consider this your final exam.
By pressing the buttons
on those babies,
you can make the balls miss,
which will in turn,
create an extreme condition.
[GINTI]
Got it.
[DECIM]
Right.
Thank you for playing.
Best of luck on your journey.
[QUIN]
Glasses up, everyone! Cheers!
Wow! That's amazing!
You've got some serious
martini-making skills, man.
I feel much better about
entrusting my bar to you
after tasting this.
Good on ya!
That's kind of you
to say, thank you.
He's absolutely a
perfect fit to take over
as arbiter here,
don't you think?
He can certainly make
a drink, I'll give you that.
[QUIN]
Fill me up!
[DECIM]
Of course. Right away.
[NONA]
So, why didn't you ever use it?
I'm sorry. Use what?
My sincerest apologies.
I completely forgot.
[GINTI, NONA, QUIN]
Huh?
Perhaps it sounds odd,
but I was distracted
while watching them
play the game.
I couldn't help but wonder
what they were thinking.
What are you even talking about?
Humans are complete
and utter idiots.
You know that, right?
Who gives a crap
what they're thinkin'?
It's not like it
actually matters to us.
We create extreme
conditions then sit back
and enjoy while they make
fools of themselves.
I disagree. I don't
see them as foolish.
Really?
That is correct. You see,
I have respect for people
who have lived a
fulfilling life.
[QUIN] Well, this one's
a little different.
[gasps]
[GINTI] Man, you're a
real idiot. Seriously!
If you ask me, you're--
Be quiet for a second, okay?
So, just by looking at
them, could you guess
what they were thinking?
No. I wasn't able
to do that, ma'am.
[NONA] Well, of course
you weren't able to.
You don't have the
experience for it.
Which is why I
told you to create
an extreme condition, by doing
so, you force the darkness
they harbor inside their
souls out into the light,
making it easier to judge them.
All right.
[NONA] The darkness of the soul
can take on many forms.
It can manifest as
the fear of death
or as a desperate
thirst for life.
Think of it as
foolish if you like.
Or respect it. Either way,
it's entirely up to you.
Every arbiter is different.
There should be more
than one way to judge.
At least in my opinion.
[clapping]
Well, anyway!
It looks like it's time
for my going away speech.
I do have one or two words
of wisdom to pass on.
As an old, experienced arbiter.
It doesn't matter what
it is, but make something
that you can treasure.
[GINTI]
Tch...
Right. Thank you for the advice.
[WOMAN] Oh, yeah?
Something you can treasure?
Yes.
Well, do you have something?
I can show you
if you would like.
[DECIM]
Well, what do you think?
Uh...
[WOMAN]
These are what he treasures?
Really? How am I supposed
to respond to this?
I gotta say something, but what?
[WOMAN]
So, um, do you enjoy this, then?
[DECIM]
Sorry?
[WOMAN] I mean, this
is your hobby, right?
[DECIM]
Hobby?
[WOMAN]
It's not?
You mean my work for
Nona? No, it isn't.
[WOMAN] But it is something
you treasure, right?
Yes.
[WOMAN]
Huh.
[DECIM] If you want, there
are more I could show you.
[WOMAN]
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm!
[QUIN]
Glasses up, everyone. Cheers!
Ah!
[NONA]
Not doin' so well, are you?
And we know whose fault that is.
You mean me?
You're the one who said
I was better suited
to the information bureau.
It's why I let Decim take over.
What you didn't
tell me was how busy
things are in information.
Even being an
arbiter was better.
Condensing dead
peoples' memories
isn't as easy as it sounds.
[NONA]
Yeah. I know.
[QUIN] "I know"? What do
you mean, "I know"?
You've never done it before.
People are dying
too fast. Way too fast.
The rate is 7,000 an hour
now, did you know that?
Which works out to 116 a minute,
or roughly, two per second.
"Okay, you're dead."
That's what it's like!
At that pace, it's impossible
to do our best work.
Yeah, I know.
Saying "I know"
over and over again
isn't very helpful. So, what's
the situation over there?
Not too great
right now, honestly.
[QUIN]
He is still new at it.
He doesn't even have any doubts
about judging yet, does he?
I can see it on your
face that I'm right.
I'm sure if
everything went well,
he could be a fascinating
arbiter someday,
but that is a lot to hope for.
I mean, come on.
Implanting human emotions
inside an arbiter?
Kinda crazy.
"Number Three:
Arbiters can't feel emotions,
for it's not in their natures.
A dummy can't have
feelings, after all."
Make sure old flower-head
doesn't find out.
[NONA]
Don't worry. It'll be all right.
[DECIM]
We're fairly busy.
Every day, many guests
come to receive
our judgments, correct?
[WOMAN]
Yeah.
And with each guest
comes a slew of memories.
Eventually, arbiters'
minds fill with them.
As you can imagine, that
poses an obstacle for us.
So, to address the issue,
arbiters are set up
to periodically forget the
accumulated guest memories.
After judgment,
guests no longer need
corporeal form, and their bodies
return to being dummies.
Normally, those dummies
are disposed of,
but I claim some
of them instead.
[WOMAN]
Why do that?
[DECIM] We're talking about
people who lived a full life.
I don't like that they end up
as if they never were.
It seems wrong to me somehow.
[gasps] Then all
those dummies--?
[DECIM] Yes. That's right.
They were all my guests.
All have visited Quindecim.
I chose to make dummies of them
so they would not be forgotten.
[gasps]
A pretty revolting
hobby, isn't it?
[WOMAN]
No, it turns out it's not.
Hey.
Why don't you let me
make it this time?
I don't know.
It'll be okay. Go on,
I've got this covered.
[DECIM sighs]
[GINTI]
I've had enough of this!
I'm sick of having
you here interfering
with my judgments!
Interfering? I'm not
doing anything.
'Cause of you,
everything around here's
turned upside down.
What do mean? How else
is it supposed to be?
[GINTI]
Not like this.
[MAYU] Force people to risk
their lives on stupid games
and things are gonna get crazy.
'Cause all humans are
complete idiots, right?
[MAYU sighs]
No, it's not that.
People generally look
out for number one,
that's just how it is.
If that's true,
then what's your story?
Say what now?
I don't really know what
you're getting at, sorry.
Why are none of you
people ever capable
of understanding your
own motivations?
[GINTI] I should just
drop you into the void.
Yeah? And what
was a void, again?
[GINTI grunts]
[MEMINE purrs]
[GINTI] Cozying up to her?
Traitorous feline!
[GINTI] Just being around
you gives me a headache.
[MAYU] Ah! Watch where you
put those hands, Mister!
[screams]
[MAYU] Jeez! That hurt!
What was that for, anyway?
[GINTI] She needs to get
out of here. Quickly.
[QUIN groans] There really is
something special about alcohol
from the living world,
isn't there?
So, why do you spend so mucha
your time and attention
on Decim, anyway?
A fair question.
The thing is, I think it's good
for there to be more than one
method of judging people,
but so many people die each day.
And we have to find a way
to judge them all somehow.
This is it. We work on
auto pilot. Mechanically,
no questions asked.
Then afterwards, what happens?
We forget everything about
the people we judged.
Because if we didn't,
we couldn't continue on
being arbiters.
We're not human. We are dummies.
We never live and we never die.
And yet we're built to look
exactly like those we judge.
Doesn't it seem strange
and kind of unfair?
We don't even know the first
thing about death or dying.
Yet we're the ones
who judge the dead.
Besides all that, I'm curious.
I'd like to see an arbiter
who has human emotions,
who can make human judgments.
[WOMAN]
Well, eat up.
[DECIM]
Thank you for cooking.
So, tell me some stories
about guests you've seen.
What were they like,
these people?
Let's say, the woman
playing the piano.
You remember her, right?
[DECIM]
No.
What?
What has been forgotten
stays forgotten.
It is just a hobby, then.
Aren't you even going to say
"it's good" or something?
I am terribly sorry.
The food is good.
How convincing.
Can't you muster
some enthusiasm?
[DECIM] Once again, I beg your
pardon. It is very delicious.
[WOMAN]
Uh...
[sighs]
Ah-ha, finally awake,
are we? Good morning.
[yells]
You know, you're adorable
even while you're sleeping.
I'm afraid poor Quin over there
can't say the same thing.
I've told you not to come
in here without asking!
Plus, watching me
sleep is creepy!
I had no choice but
to seek you out.
You haven't been spending
any time with me lately.
Wounds me to my core!
Go bother somebody else.
I told you, I'm busy.
[OCULUS]
You stickin' to that story?
'Cause you certainly don't
look busy to me. Unless...
...there's something you're
hiding from me, Nona?
Go away. Stupid geezer.
Aw, you're so mean!
Hello.
[OCULUS] And what do we
have here? "Chavvot," huh?
[NONA]
Oh, that?
Looks like a picture book
from the living world.
[NONA] I liked it, so I
sent for it, that's all.
[OCULUS]
Hmm?
[OCULUS] Come by every once
in a while, I'm beggin' ya.
It's not fair of you
to deny me a rematch.
Okay, fine. I will.
[NONA]
Maybe I botched this.
I'm sorry for asking so much.
Eh, It's okay. I like you.
You're always
bringing me goodies.
There, that one will do.
[CASTRA]
No. Do you see that?
They're both marked, actually.
Gimme a sec. I'll retag them.
[NONA]
I said that they'll do.
[CASTRA] You want them
to go to your boy, right?
Sorry, I can't. They have to
be sent to a special arbiter.
I'll bring you even
better goodies next time,
I promise!
All right. You better.
[CASTRA]
So, Nona, feeling the pressure?
Well, there was never
all that much time
to begin with.
[QUIN]
Episode Eight: "Death Rally."