--[glasses clinking]
--[water running]
Hm?
[DECIM]
This is odd.
What is it?
If you can wait for
just a moment, please.
I must verify this.
[phone ringing]
Nona here.
Ma'am, it appears we
have a guest arriving
in the bar shortly who
has killed someone.
[WOMAN gasps]
What?
[NONA] Oh, yeah? Well,
you'll have to handle it.
The others are up
to their eyeballs.
[DECIM] But, ma'am, I have
no experience with this.
[NONA] Don't over-think it.
Killers are still people, right?
I'm sure it'll be
pretty standard.
As you say, ma'am.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
We're doing this?
[DECIM] Yes. She said the
others are all occupied.
[elevators rattling]
[elevator dings]
[WOMAN]
So, which one is it?
[DECIM]
Which one is what?
One of them is a
murderer, right?
[DECIM]
It seems they have arrived.
Right this way, please.
Have a seat, and
welcome to Quindecim.
My name is Decim, and I
will be your bartender.
Hi. Nice to meet ya.
Now then, you may find
this a strange question,
but I'm afraid that
I do have to ask it.
Do you remember anything
from just prior to
your arrival here?
Huh... Well, actually,
now that you mention it.
I don't remember
much of anything.
I'm pretty sure I was
on my way somewhere.
But that's really about it.
Thank you for indulging me.
And if I may ask you the same?
Let me think.
It seems I was headed
someplace, as well.
But I don't remember where.
Very good. Thank you
for answering.
[TATSUMI] Never mind that.
What is this place?
All right.
I will now explain a
number of things about
your current situation.
This is rather important, so
please do pay close attention.
We're supposed to risk
our lives on a game?
Why don't we split up
and look for an exit?
[SHIMADA] Sounds good. I'll
start in that direction, okay?
Go for it.
No good. It's just a bathroom.
--[TATSUMI] Hm?
--[piano playing]
[sighs]
[clatters]
Huh?
[zipping]
[SHIMADA]
What's in here?
[SHIMADA gasps]
Shit! A bloody knife?
Why's that in there?
[knocking]
[SHIMADA]
Uh, yes?
Oh, you taking
a leak? I'm sorry.
[SHIMADA]
Oh, no!
I mean, I'm done here.
It's no problem.
Well, I struck out.
How 'bout you?
[SHIMADA]
No luck here.
[TATSUMI] There really aren't
any exits, are there?
No.
As I tried to explain, you will
not be able to leave here
until the game is completed.
You sure about that?
Do you really wanna screw
around with a detective?
What?
[TATSUMI]
This is false imprisonment.
Section 2-20 of
the criminal code.
Keeping us here like this
is illegal, pal. You get that?
[TATSUMI]
Got nothin' to say, huh?
What if we don't play your game?
I would sincerely
recommend that you do.
[SHIMADA gasps]
[gasps]
What...?
[yelps]
[TATSUMI] If we don't play
the game, we end up like that?
I'm terribly sorry
for being vague.
But I'm afraid I cannot
say more than I have.
Well, kid? What do ya think?
[SHIMADA]
What, me? I-I'm really scared.
Where are we? Are those
people murderers?
[TATSUMI]
No, I don't think so.
What?
[TATSUMI] Just call it
an occupational hazard.
When I look a guy in the eyes,
I can usually judge
what kinda person he is.
His aren't the eyes of a killer,
but they don't look like
the eyes of a liar, either.
[SHIMADA] Oh, good. I mean,
that's a relief, right?
[TATSUMI]
Hm?
Glad you're here, detective.
It's reassuring, you know?
Ah, knock off the
"detective" business.
You can just call me Tatsumi.
[SHIMADA] Okay, Tatsumi it is,
and my name is Shimada,
by the way.
Okay.
Well, Shimada, think you
could work with me?
Huh?
[WOMAN] If I could have you
press this button, please.
The roulette will begin.
We'll play your
screwed up little game,
but you should know,
this won't be the last time
you're gonna hear from me.
Yes, sir. Understood.
[game music plays]
[WOMAN] The rules are
the same as they are
for regular air hockey.
You'll use the paddles to
hit the puck back and forth,
trying to score on the
other player's goal.
For each goal that you score,
you will win one point.
Whoever reaches a total
of six points first
will be declared the
winner of the game.
[WOMAN] However. The pucks
are a little unusual.
They are inscribed
with various images,
corresponding to your
respective bodies.
Ugh! What the hell was that?
[WOMAN]
The red pucks are for Shimada,
while the blue pucks
are for Tatsumi.
Attempt to score using
a puck of your own color.
If you do, you will
earn double points.
[WOMAN] Conversely, if your
goal is scored upon,
then you will lose one point.
Very well, then.
If you're ready, the
game will now begin.
[sighs] Here goes nothing.
[TATSUMI]
Yep.
Two for you.
[TATSUMI]
All right. My turn now.
[gasps]
[SAE sobbing]
It's okay. Don't cry, Sae.
You still have me.
I'll look out for you now
that Mom and Dad can't.
[SAE]
But...
I will protect you.
I promise, whatever it takes.
[TATSUMI]
Somthin' wrong?
Huh? Oh, nothing. Just
thinking about old times.
Hmm?
[SHIMADA] I remembered that
my sister and I played this
a long time ago.
We lost our parents when
we were pretty young.
Money was always tight.
So we tried to drag out the
game by keeping a rally going.
[TATSUMI]
Oh?
Unfortunately, the time
ran out on us. That's right.
We didn't know the thing
had a time limit on it.
Not exactly a good surprise.
My sister was inconsolable.
It took me forever to
get her to stop crying.
What about now? You still play?
No, we don't.
My sister is actually
in high school now,
and since I started
working, I'm so busy.
[TATSUMI]
How old are you, Shimada?
I'm 22 now.
I started working right after
I graduated from high school.
I get it. Sounds like you
put your sister first.
Pardon me, are you
perhaps not feeling well?
It's not that.
It's the remote. I don't
want you to use it.
I know that it bothers you.
As it happens, it's actually
broken at the moment.
[DECIM] Are you especially
worried this time
because of the killing?
Just imagine what could happen.
Things get out of hand
even when normal people
go through this.
Maybe, but killers
are still people.
How are you supposed to
make a legitimate judgment?
Killer or innocent,
there is no one
who cannot be judged.
Whatever happens,
I will judge them.
[sighs]
It's one wacky thing after
another in this place, isn't it?
I wish I knew what the
deal was with this game.
[SHIMADA]
Huh? You don't know anything?
When you asked me to
cooperate, I assumed you did.
How can I explain this to you?
Tell me something.
What do you think's the
hardest part about what I do?
Uh... I don't know.
The long hours?
Or somethin' like that.
[TATSUMI] It's not the
time or physical stress.
The cases my division handles
are the serious ones.
We see some real heavy
emotions on a daily basis.
Real heavy emotions,
huh? Like what?
Well, for example,
there's the grief
of the victim's family
after their loved one
has been murdered.
That's always rough.
I'm telling ya, it takes
a lot out of you to confront
that kind of emotion.
Earlier, I talked
about judging people
by their eyes, but something
is off about that guy.
As far as I can tell,
he doesn't feel anything.
I've never met anybody
like that before,
to be honest.
Can't figure him out.
All right, kid.
Back to the game.
Wait! Can you explain something?
Why are we even playing at all?
'Cause if we keep going,
we might actually
find something out.
Something like what?
[TATSUMI] About the game,
maybe. About the guy.
But I'm not interested in that.
Not in the game,
or the white-haired guy.
I said that I would cooperate
because I thought you were
gonna get us outta here.
Yeah. I get it.
Just hang in there a
little longer for me.
I'm not like you, though.
You don't seem to get
frightened by anything.
[TATSUMI]
I get scared sometimes.
But right now, it doesn't matter
whether we're afraid or not.
Till we end this game,
one way or another,
we're not gettin' out
of this damn place.
[SHIMADA]
Fine. Let's do it.
Congratulations.
[SAE] That means a lot
from my big brother.
Look at you. You sure
have grown up, huh?
[laughs] Don't start
crying on me!
I promise, I'll do my best.
[TATSUMI]
What's wrong?
Uh, just daydreaming.
Here we go.
[TATSUMI gasps]
--[door clicks]
--[TATSUMI] Hey, I'm home.
[TATSUMI]
Hello? Yumi? Are you here?
[TATSUMI gasps]
[SHIMADA]
W-What's goin' on?
[TATSUMI]
No, how could I have forgotten
something like... that?
You're so pale. What's wrong?
Hey! Tatsumi?
[TATSUMI] I have a headache.
Give me a sec, okay?
[DECIM]
They're going more slowly
than I thought they would.
What?
Maybe the shock from
their deaths is greater.
Their memories seem
to be buried more deeply
than other guests'.
And we can't tamper
with what memories
they do recall, can we?
So, what are you going to do?
[DECIM]
Hm.
[WOMAN]
You could let me see them.
The guests' memories, I mean.
I'll put in a request
about that later.
[YUMI]
Here you go, honey.
What's that?
You are a stereotypical
detective, aren't you?
[YUMI chuckles]
My poor husband!
So busy, you can't even
remember your own birthday.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
Gift first. Cigarette later.
Yours practically had
holes in the bottom.
I thought you could
use a new pair.
[TATSUMI]
That's right. She was killed.
My wife was murdered.
[DETECTIVE 8A]
What's Tatsumi doing?
I thought they pulled him
from the investigation.
[DETECTIVE 8B] I hear he
hasn't even taken a day off.
[DETECTIVE 8C]
They should really move him
out of the division.
I can't bear to watch this.
[DETECTIVE 8D]
He likes a repeat offender
out on parole for it.
[DETECTIVE 8E] Tatsumi's the one
who sent him up the first time.
[grunting]
[footsteps]
Hey, are you feelin' better?
[SHIMADA gasps]
Yeah. Let's get back
to it, all right?
Okay, if you're... sure.
[SHIMADA]
What's gotten into him?
Tch!
[gasps]
[rattling]
[door clicks]
[footsteps]
[SHIMADA]
Hey, I'm home.
--[SAE gasps]
--[SHIMADA] Sae?
[gasps]
[panting, whimpering]
What the hell? Sae!
[SAE]
No!
[gasps]
[SAE whimpers]
[growls]
[gasping]
[SHIMADA] My god...
How could I have forgotten?
Listen, Shimada.
I hate to do this to you,
but I gotta get outta here.
There's something I
need to take care of.
[SHIMADA]
Yeah, me, too.
Huh?
I was in the middle of it
when I wound up here,
and I need to finish it.
I have to, even if it
costs me my life.
[footsteps]
[DECIM]
Please excuse me.
I'm afraid the time
limit has expired.
We must now switch
to a linked format.
What do you mean "linked"?
There was a time limit?
[alarm blares]
[high-pitched cackling]
[SHIMADA, TATSUMI gasp]
[gasps]
These are the rules.
For the remainder of the game,
the part of the body
linked to the scoring puck
will be stricken with pain.
Really? Actual pain?
[DECIM]
Yes.
In your eyes, if a puck
with an eye design scores.
In your heart, if a puck
with a heart design scores.
Now then, if we can
please continue on
with the game.
[TATSUMI]
He's not making this up.
[SHIMADA]
This is crazy!
[TATSUMI] Mind if I ask
you something, kid?
Huh? Sure.
Will you tell me
what it is you wanna
take care of so badly?
Well, I don't know.
[TATSUMI] You don't have to
say it if you don't want.
No. I can tell you.
It was my sister.
Somebody assaulted her.
[SHIMADA] There was this guy
who had been giving her
a lot of trouble.
A stalker, you know?
I even told the police about it.
But they didn't do anything.
The police wouldn't
help you? I'm sorry, kid.
That bastard. I can't let him...
...just get away with it.
[TATSUMI]
Revenge, huh?
I know something about that.
It's what I'm after, too.
It is?
I'm sure this isn't the
kinda thing that you'd expect
to hear from a detective,
but when I get outta here...
[TATSUMI]
...somebody is going to die.
[whimpers]
[TATSUMI] My wife, you see.
She was murdered.
That's right. Yes,
thank you very much.
They said it would
be no trouble.
It should be on its
way here shortly.
Okay.
[WOMAN gasps]
[WOMAN panting]
It wasn't just one of them?
They're both killers?
Yes, it seems so.
It's a weird feeling.
Seeing the memories of a killer.
[QUIN]
Episode Nine: "Death Counter."