[MISAKI grunting]
[YOUSUKE]
So all the doors are locked.
They've sealed us in
here like it's a tomb.
Who the hell do they
think they are?
[MISAKI] They've shut down
the elevators, too.
[YOUSUKE] What do you think
they want? Why us?
[gasps] I've got it!
[YOUSUKE]
Wait! Where are you taking me?
Hey! This is the ladies room!
[MISAKI] Relax, you're
not my type. C'mon!
[YOUSUKE yelps]
Um. So why did you
drag me in here?
[MISAKI]
I know what's going on.
We're on a hidden camera show!
[YOUSUKE]
What?
[MISAKI] You watch TV, right?
What's your name, anyway?
[YOUSUKE]
Uh... Yousuke Tateishi.
[MISAKI]
And you don't know who I am?
[YOUSUKE]
Huh?
Does the name Misaki
Tachibana ring any bells?
[YOUSUKE]
Misaki, huh?
From that reality show?
[MISAKI]
Well, it took you long enough.
Don't meet many
celebrities, do you?
Uh. It's just different
seeing you in person.
[MISAKI]
How so?
You look younger.
Are you saying that
I look old on TV?
[YOUSUKE]
That's not...
Fine. Whatever.
So they do lots of
hidden camera shows
during the summer, right?
That's what this is.
[YOUSUKE]
Really?
[MISAKI chuckles]
There's no doubt about it.
I could tell my manager
was hiding something.
Okay, but, you're
sure about this?
That's why I dragged us in here
where there aren't any cameras.
Uh-huh...
[MISAKI]
And now that we know.
I need you to
work with me, okay?
Wait, work with you how?
[MISAKI sighs] You're not
as bright as you look.
I need you to act like you
don't know what's happening.
The director will
want our reactions
to seem natural, after all.
Yeah... I've never
done any acting before.
You'll be fine!
I'll quietly coach
you through it.
Okay? Pretty please?
Uh... I guess I'll try.
You're so sweet.
[WOMAN] If I could have you
press this button, please.
The roulette will
determine your game.
[MISAKI]
I'll push it.
Yeah, sure.
[game music plays]
[BOTH gasp]
Holy crap, this show must
have a serious budget.
[footsteps]
[GAME VOICE 4A]
Battle of Life!
I've never played this one.
[WOMAN]
The two of you will now
compete against one another.
The first player
to win two rounds
will be the victor of the game.
There's no set time
limit to worry about.
[MISAKI]
All right, then.
We should just sit down and
play without any strategies.
That's the most
realistic approach.
Yeah, okay.
Take your seat.
[GAME VOICE 4A] Choose your
challenging character.
[YOUSUKE]
Hey, what the hell?
I can only choose
one character? Wait.
[MISAKI]
Huh? I get to play as me?
There is no better publicity
than having your own game!
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER grunting]
[YOUSUKE]
Well that's flattering.
Are you serious?
They're making me out
to look like a loser.
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Ha! Hee! Charming!
[MISAKI]
Oh! That's my parasol.
Well, they've got
the details right.
[MISAKI]
What is this stuff?
They don't expect me
to memorize all that.
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER]
Fair warning!
I fight like I've got
nothing to live for!
Uh...
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Go on and laugh!
I'll make you take
celebrities seriously!
[gasps]
Very well then. Let's begin
the game, shall we?
[GAME VOICE 4A]
Round 1! Ready? Fight!
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER grunting]
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER grunts]
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER grunts]
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER]
Otaku punch! Otaku punch!
[YOUSUKE] I'm losing
even when I'm winning.
I need to hurry and
get this over with.
--[MISAKI'S CHARACTER] Para-gun!
--[MISAKI] Oh! I did it! What?
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Children's Toy!
[YOUSUKE grunts]
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Brand Blow!
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER grunts]
Take this!
You're good!
I don't know about that.
Oh, please, you're kicking
my butt, aren't you?
[MISAKI] Although, that
does make for good TV.
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER]
Shrine Pilgrimage!
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER screams]
[GAME VOICE 4A]
KO!
[MISAKI grunts]
Gah, my head!
[gasps]
[MISAKI]
Damn, that hurts.
[YOUSUKE]
Hey, are you all right?
[MISAKI] Yeah. Just a
sinus headache. Thanks.
Well, if you're sure.
[MISAKI]
Oh! One thing though.
[WOMAN]
Hm? What is that you're holding?
It's a device to assist
in our judgment.
Huh?
What?
[MISAKI] It's no big deal,
just let me win the next round.
[YOUSUKE]
But wouldn't that go against
the "realistic approach"?
[MISAKI]
Oh, silly boy.
Won't it be more exciting
for the viewer if we're tied?
[YOUSUKE]
Well, yeah, but--
You can still trounce
me in the final round
if you want. Okay?
Well, if it's just
for this round.
[MISAKI]
Thank you, love. Shall we?
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER grunting]
--[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER groaning]
--[MISAKI chuckles]
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Bubble Dream!
Yes! I've got you!
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER yelps]
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER grunts]
Shrine Pilgrimage!
[MISAKI]
Huh? What's the deal?
Is he trying to be a jerk?
[gasps]
[MISAKI]
Talk about luck!
[gasps]
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER]
Bubble Dream!
[GAME VOICE 4A]
KO! Misaki win!
[WOMAN C]
What's wrong with you?
I wish you'd never been born.
[YOUSUKE groans]
Oh, man.
[MISAKI]
Are you okay there?
Uh. I'm fine.
Good, you had me worried.
Can we have a quick chat?
Huh?
[thud]
[MISAKI]
You nearly won that round.
Yeah?
[MISAKI]
Did you forget about our deal?
No. I was just trying
to make it look good.
I didn't want it
to be too obvious.
[MISAKI]
Oh, that's what you were doing?
You're a smart kid.
Make sure to keep that up
for the final round.
Wait. But you said--
[MISAKI] Now, now.
This is television, right?
The star has to win.
[YOUSUKE grunts, sighs]
[WOMAN] That was pretty damn
cheap. Don't use that again.
Sometimes the truth
needs a nudge.
That's part of being an arbiter.
[WOMAN]
What do you mean?
I can be necessary, at times,
to create extreme conditions.
That's what you're gonna
call extreme conditions?
Rigging the game
however you see fit?
[MISAKI] What do you
mean it's not a show?
[YOUSUKE] It's weird, but
just think about it, okay?
Neither of us remember
how we got here, right?
Yeah. So?
I know that I was at home
playing a video game.
So how'd I get here?
Did someone bring me?
Maybe it was your mother.
Not even possible.
And why not?
Because she hasn't spoken
to me in years, okay?
Then what do you think this is?
I don't know.
But do you think your
family brought you here?
[MISAKI gasps]
Fine. Let's find out.
Hold on, what're you gonna do?
[MISAKI]
I'm gonna ask 'em. What else?
No. This is not a
hidden camera show.
Huh? You mean you're
not filming this?
[DECIM]
No, I'm afraid we're not.
I freakin' knew it.
Then, what the hell are
we even doing here?!
[DECIM] I'm sorry, but I cannot
answer that question now.
[growls] Stop screwing with me!
I'll explain everything
after the game is won.
You tell me now!
I sincerely apologize.
[gasps]
And what happens if I lose?
Don't tell me that...
that you'll kill me?
What?
[MISAKI]
You can't do this!
He's obviously so
much better than I am!
You can't honestly
tell me that's fair!
And is fairness really something
you've come to
expect in your life?
[DECIM]
I wouldn't think so.
Why should things
be different now?
[gasps]
[MISAKI] What am I supposed
to do? I can't win.
[DECIM]
Very well then.
Let's begin the
final round, shall we?
[GAME VOICE 4A]
Final round! Ready? Fight!
[MISAKI'S CHARACTER yelps]
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER]
Otaku punch!
[panting]
[MISAKI]
Somebody...
Please help me!
[MISAKI gasps]
What the--?
[GAME CHILDREN]
Mama!
What?
[GAME CHILDREN]
Stop picking on our mom!
Loving children attack!
My kids are gonna save me!
[GAME CHILDREN]
Come on! Let him have it!
[MISAKI]
What?
They were practically useless!
That's my little Takahiro!
I love you, sweetie!
What kind of move is that?
I'm winning!
[gasps]
Hey!
[MISAKI]
No! Come back here!
[grunts]
[MISAKI]
This can't be happening.
How could you do that to her?
Because it's necessary.
How? Explain this!
[thud]
[thudding]
[DECIM] We're incapable
of passing judgment
until we can see into the soul.
And the darkness
that dwells within.
[WOMAN]
But this is...
This is just dragging it
out of them by force!
--[MISAKI yelling]
--[thudding]
[panting]
[MISAKI] I might've got a
little carried away there.
[gasps]
Is he... Did I do that?
What's wrong with me?
[MISAKI] Yousuke! Yousuke!
Please, just wake up!
Yousuke! You have to wake up!
Open your eyes! Please. Wake up.
[MISAKI]
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to.
I-I wasn't thinking.
He won't wake up.
Call an ambulance!
Hurry! Are you listening to me?
I don't have my cell
phone! Call for help!
Please, don't just stand there!
[DECIM] We need you
to continue the game.
Huh? You what?
[DECIM] The final round
has yet to be won.
And that is the most
urgent matter at hand.
The final round? But
he's severely injured.
[DECIM] Please, continue
playing the game.
What's wrong with you?
You're both crazy. He needs
help. Just let us go.
[MISAKI sobbing]
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[YOUSUKE'S STEPMOTHER]
Do you know what?
I've got a secret wish.
You wanna guess what it is?
[YOUSUKE'S FATHER] Hmm?
I really don't think I could.
Well, someday,
I'd love it if Yousuke
felt close enough to me
to call me his mom.
[YOUSUKE'S FATHER]
That's a nice wish. Thank you.
[YOUSUKE'S STEPMOTHER]
Huh? No.
I should thank you.
Yousuke! Yousuke!
Yousuke!
[gasps]
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[YOUSUKE'S CHARACTER]
Otaku punch!
[MISAKI gasps]
You're okay?
[YOUSUKE'S STEPMOTHER]
It's suppertime!
Home-cooked attack!
[gasps]
[YOUSUKE'S STEPMOTHER grunting]
Thank you, Mom.
[YOUSUKE'S STEPMOTHER grunts]
--[MISAKI'S CHARACTER groans]
--[MISAKI gasps]
Damn it.
[grunts]
[yells]
[yelling]
[YOUSUKE]
Ugh, this sucks.
[thuds]
You always schedule things
without asking me first!
[MANAGER 4A]
I'm really sorry.
[MISAKI]
You're worthless!
[MANAGER 4A grunts]
Sachi?
I know I made you a promise.
But I'm afraid I can't make
it home tonight, sweetheart.
[MANAGER 4A growls]
Did Takahiro take his nap?
Right. You can count on it.
I'm doing my best for you kids.
[MANAGER 4A grunts]
[MISAKI grunting]
[yelling]
[MISAKI, YOUSUKE scream]
[GAME VOICE 4A]
WKO!
[MISAKI]
No.
No, but I have my children.
I have to take care of my kids.
[YOUSUKE]
Suicide?
It seems the two of you
tied for the championship.
[MISAKI]
We're not actually dead, are we?
Yes.
I'm afraid you have both
left the land of the living.
Following their deaths,
people are sent either
to Heaven or to Hell.
That's why this place exists.
To pass judgment on
who will be sent where.
You're sending us
to Heaven or Hell
based on that game?
[DECIM] If you will please
step into the elevators,
you will learn the
outcome of your ruling.
Ruling. Is this a joke?
Stop screwing with me!
Quit trying to
mess with my head!
[MISAKI] What gives you people
the right to make that decision?
Just who do you think
you are to judge me?
What the hell could you
even know about me?
I know everything
about you, in fact.
How can you call
this fair judgment?
You just tricked me
to get what you want!
As an arbiter, it's my job
to draw out the darkness,
and then, to evaluate
the state of your soul.
I don't care what you are!
[MISAKI sobbing]
It's always been like this.
My entire life,
everyone has lied to me.
Before I knew it,
I had five kids.
But I didn't care what
anyone thought of me.
And then, everything
suddenly changed.
My life was only beginning.
After all that misery,
I finally found happiness.
I finally had the chance
to make my children happy.
[sobbing]
How could I? Why did I do it?
Why did I kill myself?
Well, someday...
I'd love it if Yousuke
felt close enough to me
to call me his mom.
Why couldn't I just
give her that?
She was always so good to me.
Why am I so messed up?
[MISAKI]
Listen, please.
I'll do anything you want.
Please just send me
back to my children.
[DECIM]
Huh?
Send me back to them!
[gasps] Let me go!
Take your arms off of me!
Let me go! Let go of me!
Please, stop.
No matter what, you did
the best you could.
[gasps]
[YOUSUKE, MISAKI sobbing]
Both of you. You did
the best you could.
[YOUSUKE, MISAKI sobbing]
Thank you for playing.
Best of luck on your journey.
[QUIN]
Episode Five: "Death March."