[MOTHER 5A] To his delight,
Jimmy's family had moved
into a new home that winter.
The new house was filled
with fun toys just for him.
Jimmy couldn't be more thrilled!
Jimmy peered outside
to look at the snow,
and do you know what he saw?
There was a girl about
his age playing on the ice
with a cute little puppy.
Jimmy didn't need to
talk to the girl first.
He knew right away
that he would like her.
Her big smile promised
instant friendship.
Jimmy finally worked
up his courage
and called out to the girl.
When he spoke, she looked
in his direction and waved,
as if to say, "Come over here!
Come and play with me!"
Excited, Jimmy started
running toward her.
Poor Jimmy!
He didn't realize
there was a hole
hidden by the blanket
of fallen snow.
"Ow, that hurt!
Wah!" Jimmy began crying
out of pain and surprise.
But just then,
a hand reached down
to help Jimmy. It was
the little girl!
He looked up and saw
her big, friendly smile,
and he forgot all
about the pain.
His new friend had
come to the rescue.
[WOMAN gasps]
I wonder why I keep
having that dream.
[yawns]
Huh?
Weird. Has that
always been there?
[DECIM]
How are you doing this morning?
I'm all right, thanks.
Are you sure? You seem troubled.
I just had another
strange dream.
[DECIM]
Is that right?
What could it mean?
Who knows?
[gasps] What's that?
Why're you putting it up?
I couldn't tell you.
Nona told me to switch it out,
but didn't explain why.
[WOMAN]
Huh?
How much time do we have?
What, before our guests arrive?
Not much. They should
be here soon.
[WOMAN]
Oh, okay.
The memories?
[DECIM]
Yes.
However, there is no need
for you to go greet them.
[WOMAN]
Really? Why not?
Something seems a bit odd.
[elevator dings]
[WOMAN] What counts as
"odd" in this place?
[gasps]
[BOY grunts]
Watch it, kid! Stupid brat.
I didn't mean to.
[MAN 5A]
Hey!
Where the hell are we, anyway?
Right this way, please.
Welcome to the
Quindecim. Take a seat.
Quindecim? That's a dumb name.
So, what is this
place, then? A bar?
Yes.
My name is Decim, and I
will be your bartender.
Now, if you don't mind,
please come and have a seat.
Hello, buddy.
Oh, um, hello, ma'am.
You think you could
do me a favor?
Would you sit down over there?
[DECIM]
Now then.
You will likely find this
a strange question,
and I'm sorry to be abrupt,
but I'm afraid I must ask.
Do you remember anything at all
from just prior to
your arrival here?
Nah, I've got nothin'.
Okay. Very good.
Well, hold on a sec.
Yeah, there is somethin'. I feel
like I've seen you before.
Really? Are you certain?
[MAN 5A]
Yeah.
And ya know, if feels like
I've been here before, too.
It's all kinda fuzzy, though.
I can't remember any details.
All right. Thank you
for answering.
And what about you?
No. I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not sure why, but I
can't remember anything.
[DECIM] Very good.
Your answer has been noted.
Moving on. I will now--
[MAN 5A] Whoa, slow down
a second, would ya?
You didn't even ask
if I was thirsty.
Can't a man get a beer?
[DECIM]
Certainly, sir.
What about you? Would
you like some juice?
[OCULUS]
Well, Nona.
How long's it been now since
you were put in charge?
[NONA]
Hmm... About 82 years, I think.
Why do you ask?
[OCULUS]
Has it been that long already?
You've put in a lot
of hours, huh?
You might try remembering
that the next time
you second guess me.
[OCULUS]
Take a look at this, will ya?
It's a record of our scores.
If you do the math, you'll
notice that we've played
Solar System Nine-ball
5,769 times.
[NONA]
That many, huh?
Averages out to
about 170 per year.
You've got a lot of free time.
But did ya get a look at
how many losses I have?
I mean, I'm practically God,
and I can't win at billiards?
What's up with that?
Well, I don't think
humility is your problem.
What do you want
from me? It's the truth.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
So, why don't you
win more, then?
[OCULUS] Because you can
never go easy on an old man.
[NONA]
Hey, now.
Weren't you the one who told
me not to go easy on you?
[OCULUS] That was 82 years ago.
The request is expired.
Well, that's too bad.
I can't let myself take
it easy, not even once.
I'd go downhill fast.
[OCULUS]
Meaning what, exactly?
[NONA]
I'd get sick of it.
You're adorable,
you know that, Nona?
That's enough of that, thanks.
You know, I had a
sneakin' suspicion
that this was how
it was gonna end.
[NONA]
That was intentional.
Thought I would give
an old man a chance.
[laughs]
[WOMAN]
There you go.
Ah!
[MAN 5A gasps]
[MAN 5A yelps]
[WOMAN, BOY gasp]
Are you all right, sir?
That was quite a fall.
Is something wrong?
[MAN 5A gasping]
What is it, sir?
[DECIM] If something is
the matter, please tell me.
[yells]
[yelps]
Nobody move an inch!
Take it easy!
Yes, let's calm down.
[MAN 5A]
That's enough!
Don't say another word!
I'll stab him!
[gasps]
I remember it now!
It's that funny
way you talk, man.
Like you think you're better
than everyone else or somethin'.
I'm not goin' through
that again. Forget it!
[WOMAN]
He's been here before? But how?
[OCULUS] So, you're sayin'
you take it easy one time
and you'll be ruined for good?
That's just like you.
[NONA]
Yeah? Is it?
Honestly, I'm pretty surprised
you lasted as an arbiter.
We could make this
a no-talking game.
You take yourself so seriously.
Sometimes I think that
you're worse than Decim
when it comes to that.
[NONA]
Hmph.
[OCULUS] I can only imagine
how terribly you've suffered.
The trick is to find
ways to alleviate
the boredom for a little bit.
Arbiters certainly can't stop
passing judgments, after all.
Am I right, or am I right?
[OCULUS]
Aw, no!
[NONA] I'll show you how
I alleviate the boredom.
--[OCULUS groans]
--[NONA] Watch closely.
[NONA]
There, that's much better.
[OCULUS]
Come on! One more game!
[NONA]
No can do. I have to go.
There are other
managers in the tower.
Call one of them.
I'm a busy girl.
[OCULUS] But, Nona! You're
the one I wanna play!
[NONA]
Hey, Clavis. You ready?
[CLAVIS]
Yes, ma'am.
Man, at this rate when will I
ever be able to
turn things around?
[NONA] Heh. Maybe you
should go ask God.
If you'll excuse us.
[OCULUS]
I'm afraid God has been
gone for a long time now.
[MAN 5A]
Let me outta here, right now!
You wouldn't want the kid
to get hurt, would ya?
[BOY whimpers]
[DECIM]
Easy. Let's talk a moment.
About what?
Please bear with me.
Have you ever heard the story
"The Spider's Thread"?
[MAN 5A] What? Why bring
up that old tale?
What's going on here?
[DECIM]
Kandata is languishing in Hell.
But the Buddha dangles a
spider's thread down to him.
He does so because, just once,
Kandata spared a spider's life.
Kandata, who has long
dreamt of Paradise,
begins climbing up the thread.
However, many other sinners
soon follow after him.
Kandata fears that the
thread is going to break,
and so he seeks to shake
the others from it.
Who cares about your damn story?
Do you even get
what's going on here?
What would have been better
is if they'd been kept
from seeing the thread
in the first place.
Shut up, you freak!
[MAN 5A gasps]
[DECIM]
Much better.
[MAN 5A groans]
Are you okay?
Not again! Damn it, not again!
I am terribly sorry, sir.
I hate to be so rough.
But really, you must allow
me to speak with you.
Let me out of this, or... I'll--
[WOMAN grunts]
[gasps]
[BOY]
Oh, whoops.
[DECIM]
Ah--
[DECIM gasps]
You're no normal little boy.
[BOY chuckles] You still
haven't figured it out?
That's pretty pathetic, Decim.
[DECIM gasps]
Ugh! Didn't see that coming!
All I did was put her to sleep.
[voice deepening] Is she really
that important to you?
Interesting.
It's been a long
time, hasn't it?
Hello again, Ginti.
[GINTI]
That's the guest you were unable
to pass judgment on, right?
[DECIM]
Yes.
What happened there?
[DECIM]
It was an unusual situation.
When she came to
Quindecim, she could
remember that she was dead.
Yeah, that is weird.
Never heard of that happening.
As you might imagine,
I was therefore unable
to prompt her to play
the required game.
Ultimately, I wound up
having her memories
erased and her judgment
period extended.
[GINTI] So, have her memories
of being human returned?
No, they have not yet come back.
[GINTI]
Really?
Then what the hell is
she doing here with you?
She is assisting me
with my judgments.
[gasps] A human? Are you
screwing with me?
A human? Are you
out of your mind?
You've gotta be.
It's not crazy.
I have respect for people who
have lived a fulfilling life.
Additionally, her
observations are astute
and her opinions, fresh.
Frankly, I find her fascinating.
[GINTI] You say that
with a straight face,
like it's totally normal.
Am I gonna have to beat
some sense into you?
[GINTI]
Let's go!
[DECIM]
We can keep going if you'd like.
You've changed,
and I think I like it.
I'm happy to keep
playin' if you are!
But if you think you're gonna
beat me... you're crazy!
[groans]
Stop it!
Don't-- [groans]
[NONA] Too far! I didn't give
you permission for this.
Oh-ho! This place is destroyed.
You insisted on doing
this, so I let you,
but now you're making
me regret it.
[GINTI]
Can't move.
It's been too long.
I hope you are doing
well, and you, Clavis.
Hangin' in there,
thanks. Good to see ya.
[NONA]
You're fighting this moron?
What's gotten into you?
You never rise to Ginti's bait.
Moron?
True. I am usually immune.
Well, we'll let it go for now.
So. Can you guess
what I'm doing here?
[DECIM]
Uh.
[NONA] Do you know anything
about Quin's memory test?
I've heard of it,
but I don't know much.
Is that what this
is supposed to be?
Yep. Honestly, totally
hopeless, aren't you?
[laughs]
[NONA]
Shut up, moron.
[laughs]
[GINTI]
Little weasel!
[NONA] You paid too much
attention to the decoy.
Yes, ma'am.
What's supposed to happen
prior to our guests' arrival?
The information
bureau edits down
and compiles their memories,
which are sent to the
arbiters for review
before the game begins.
The memory compilations
are one of the bases
for our judgments.
[NONA] And today was
different because...
Today was different
because the boy's memories
were not sent.
[NONA]
Continue.
Initially, at least,
I was on my guard.
But then there was that man.
Because of him, your
attention was diverted.
That's correct.
Pitiful!
There's no such thing as a
human being with no memories!
The shock of dying makes
things hazy for a bit,
but their latent memories
don't vanish into thin air.
Yes, ma'am.
Testing the arbiters
in such a manner
is often necessary.
Do you know why?
No.
You draw out the
darkness in their souls
as much as possible.
Then you make your judgment.
To do that, you must
create extreme conditions,
and that requires intimate
knowledge of your guests' lives.
What is it?
[DECIM] Nothing. I'm
sorry for my mistake.
[NONA] To sum up, if the
memories aren't sent to you,
cancel the game. End of story.
Yes, ma'am.
You can get up now,
sleeping beauty.
[gasps]
[NONA] I'm finished here.
Get the elevator.
[CLAVIS]
I've already called it.
[DECIM]
One more thing.
[NONA]
Hmm? What is it now?
What shall I do
with this gentleman?
[NONA]
That's just a dummy with some
fuzzy memories implanted.
It's not human.
[DECIM]
That makes sense.
Well, carry on, you three.
[CLAVIS]
Will do!
Tch.
Well, Ginti.
Was there something else you
wanted to talk to me about?
--[GINTI] Huh?
--[CLAVIS chuckles]
You're one stupid,
stone-cold bastard,
you know that?
[CASTRA]
Uh-oh.
Your boy didn't do
too well, I take it?
How very perceptive
of you, Castra.
Quin's little test with
the memories, right?
And how many years has
he been an arbiter now?
It's been five years.
Say what you want, I still
prefer him to that moron.
You're talking
about Ginti, right?
What can I say?
I'm a sucker for men
who are pretty and dumb.
[NONA]
So, what's the situation?
[CASTRA]
Oh, you know. Same as always.
They're dying too fast.
We're talking 7,000
an hour, here.
The righteous just can't seem
to stop killing each other.
You'd think that
they'd lose interest.
[NONA]
Yeah, right.
I know Information's swamped,
but they're not the only ones.
Maybe you could put a word
in to Oculus for me?
[NONA]
I'll see what I can do.
The trick is to find ways
to alleviate the boredom
for a little bit.
[NONA]
Sometimes he irritates me.
There's laid back and then
there's just plain lazy.
What do you think I wanna
talk to you about, huh?
Judge that woman,
and do it right now!
An arbiter and a human
can't work together.
It's not possible!
Let it go, Ginti.
Decim is supposed to handle
this situation on his own.
Nona says so, and you don't
wanna go against her, do you?
[GINTI]
Come on, man, don't you get it?
Just looking at this idiot
makes me wanna punch something!
[CLAVIS] There's no reason
for us to get involved here.
Decim can pass judgment
however he wants.
Anyway, don't you have guests
coming? Let's get going.
Fine, I'm coming.
And for me? Do I
have any guests?
[CLAVIS] You've got the
day off, you lucky dog.
See ya later.
Thank you very much, Clavis.
[MOTHER 5A] "Let's play!"
said Jimmy to the little girl.
"It'll be fun!" But the little
girl just smiled at him
and didn't say anything back.
You see, the girl couldn't hear,
so she didn't know
what Jimmy had said.
Jimmy wanted to
explain what he meant
without using words, so he
ran, and he fell down,
and he played in the
snow, and he laughed.
And pretty soon,
the girl joined in, too.
Jimmy was very, very happy.
He didn't know her
name, but even so,
he knew that the two of them
would be good friends.
Nothing could change that!
That evening,
Jimmy told his mom about how
he had played with the girl.
Jimmy's mom listened to
everything he had to say,
and then she told him that
the girl's name was Chavvot.
Jimmy slowly sipped his
big mug of hot cocoa,
and as he did, he said
"Chavvot, Chavvot"
over and over again.
"Someday I'll be able
to tell her how I feel.
Someday" he promised the bright
stars in the winter sky.
[WOMAN gasps]
[WOMAN]
Wha--? Huh? That's strange.
I don't remember falling asleep.
[yawns]
[QUIN] Episode Six:
"Cross Heart Attack."