[RIKU]
When I was a child, I thought
the world was... simpler.
I thought there was
no challenge that
was unbeatable...
That if I tried hard enough,
anything was possible.
Everything was cut and dry:
You win, you lose,
or it ends in a draw.
[TET]
I need a way
that's more precise...
Tactics that are
more efficient...
I need a superior strategy!
[RIKU]
Even when you're up against
the best there is,
you could still imagine
how you can defeat them
the next time...
Such foolish, ignorant youth.
(Dragon roars)
[RIKU]
At least...
that's what I thought.
I thought it was all an
illusion, or a bad joke;
a vast world of stupid games.
But the truth is, life
in this world didn't
have to be so chaotic.
It didn't have to be
so random...
Unreasonable and unfair.
It never meant anything at all.
And so...
The next time...
Next time for sure...
(Crowd chatters)
[IZUNA]
Why...?
Why can't I win against you?
(Tet giggles)
[TET]
Not to brag or anything...
But I've only been beaten once
in my entire life, y'know.
[IZUNA]
Hpmh!
Grrrr...
(Angry whine)
It is the sixth
of the Ten Pledges.
"All bets made in
accordance with the pledges
must be upheld."
This law is absolute, per the
one true god who created
our world of Disboard.
[IZUNA]
Hmph.I'll crush you...
Next time, you're totally
crushed, thank you very much!
"Next time"?
Look... If you couldn't
beat those two, then
you won't ever beat ME.
Huh? You know about them?
You know about Sora and Shiro?
Sure do.
And I've got an interesting
story I can tell you
during our next game...
As thanks for this
wonderful prize.
(Izuna scoffs)
You're just trying to distract
me you dirty cheat. Thanks!
If you wanna talk, then
just start talking! Thanks.
[TET]
Very well, then I will.
It's an ancient myth you'll
never be able to tell anyone.
[IZUNA]
S'kay. I'm not listening anyway.
(Tet chuckles)
[TET]
Well... this story goes back
more than 6,000 years.
A bitter war raged,
ravaging the earth and
extinguishing the planets.
As time has gone on, no one
remembers it anymore...
And yet, this is one tale...
I will never forget.
[IVAN]
It's a big one, huh?
[RIKU]
Hm. The black ash is
really coming down.
We should hurry.
(running and panting)
[IVAN]
Ugh...
[RIKU]
Ivan?
[IVAN]
(Gasping) I'm okay.
What does the
Spirit Compass say?
[RIKU]
I can't get a reading
with all the ash.
We'll be relying on
our senses for this recon.
Don't let your guard down.
[ALEI]
Riku!
Come here, quick! There's a‐!
[IVAN]
No way...
[ALEI]
It's a world map, Dwarvish made.
And it looks like
the latest version too!
[RIKU]
That's not all.
This shows the balance of power
between the races and
the dwarves' tactical plan.
Ivan. Alei. Compare this
to what we've got and
make any corrections.
I'll make sense of this
the best I can.
[IVAN &amp; ALEI]
Ascheito!
(Powers up)
[RIKU]
Uhh...! A message?
From the dwarves?
Huh? "Fusion"... "Detonation"?
Exactly how much of this world
do they plan to destroy?
(Rumbling and crashing)
[RIKU]
Let's get out of here.
Alei. Don't take anything
that runs on spiritual energy.
[ALEI]
Yeah, but...!
[RIKU]
If you want to die,
go right ahead.
(Annoyed grunt)
[ALEI]
Dammit!
(Rumbling and crashing)
(Alei panting)
(Roaring)
[RIKU]
Ivan, this is an order.
You will die here.
[IVAN]
Ascheito.
[ALEI]
Ah! Ivan! Wait!
[IVAN]
Look after my kid, Riku.
Promise you will do that for‐
(Ivan roars)
I'm over here!
Come and get me, Demonia!
(Electric sparking)
[RIKU]
They say there used to be
something called "the Sun."
Its white flames lit
the heavens,
turning the skies the most
brilliant blue you've
ever seen.
And then there's an old story,
like something out of
a fairy tale.
The gods and their creations
waged eternal war...
The earth burned, choking
the heavens with soot
and raining down
the ashes of the dead.
[ALEI]
Ah! Riku!
(Riku grunts)
[RIKU]
These ashes...
It's the least we can do,
to honor them... I guess.
[COURONNE]
Non...na. Heh heh...
Here.
[NONNA]
Oooh, is that my name?
Y'mean that says, Nonna?
[YOUNG BOY]
Aww, I wanna see my name, too!
Teach me, Couronne!
[BOY]
Wait, I wanna go first,
Couronne!
[COURONNE]
Sure. One at a time.
[YOUNG BOY]
Aw, come on!
[LILY] Couronne! They're back!
[COURONNE] Oh...?!
[COURONNE]
Ah...
Riku!
(Gasping)
[COURONNE CRYING]
Oooh! Oh, you made it!
Riku! Thank goodness!
[RIKU]
Couronne...
[COURONNE]
Well... You took your time!
Were you like trying to give me
a heart attack or something?
And come on, seriously,
how many times do I have to
tell you to call me "Big Sis"?
[RIKU]
We got back as fast as we could.
[ALEI]
Uh...
[COURONNE]
Ohh...
[RIKU]
About Ivan...
[COURONNE] Ah! Riku‐!
[NONNA] Daddy!
[COURONNE]
Uh, Nonna! Nonna...
[NONNA]
Riku! Alei! I'm so glad
they're back.
Where's Daddy?
I want to show them my letter,
I wrote it myself!
[NONNA] Where's my Daddy?
[COURONNE] Nonna...
Listen to me, Nonna...
Uh...
[COURONNE]
Riku?
[NONNA]
Uh...?
[RIKU]
Nonna...
[NONNA]
Huh...?
[RIKU]
Your daddy...
your daddy won't be
coming home anymore.
[NONNA]
How... come?
Because he's dead.
(Gasping)
[NONNA]
You're lying!
[RIKU]
It's true Nonna.
[NONNA]
No, it's not! Daddy promised me
he'd come home!
He said we'd win!
He said when it was over
the humans would win.
[RIKU]
We WILL win.
It's why... it's why
your daddy fought so hard...
He did it... so the
rest of us could win.
That's not "winning" anything!
It should've been you!
You! You're the one
who should've died!
[COURONNE]
Nonna! Nonna, please!
(Riku exhales)
(Nonna crying)
[COURONNE]
Why don't you two go clean
yourselves up in the bath.
[RIKU]
I'll just dust myself off.
[COURONNE]
No. Take a bath.
You guys stink.
(Nonna crying)
(Couronne inhales)
[RIKU]
So we...
so we could "win" huh?...
I'm a gods‐damned hypocrite!
(Grunt)
Ah! I made him
throw his life away!
I sent him to his death!
(Grunts)
I did it!
It was me! I killed him!
I sacrificed him just so I could
live a little while longer!
Aah!
(Sobbing)
If this keeps going on,
then what's the point?
How far are we willing to go?
Do we kill half the people...
for the sake of saving
the other half?
How many is it going to take?
Do we keep going 'til there's
only one person left?!
When are we gonna be
done with this?
How long do we have to keep
living like animals?!
[RIKU]
No human born into a world
like this could die
without a purpose.
It's more that simply
having a reason to live:
the mind will not accept
death... if it has no meaning.
Ivan's death was not in vain.
The ruins of the elves' old
capital city hold a lot of
valuable information...
Things that most people
never get a chance to see.
In a place such as this,
does anything make
sense anymore?
Is it even possible
to find one's sanity?
Dwarves...?
No...
With destruction on this scale,
it must have been the Flugel.
(Grunts and strains)
(Exhales)
(Grunting)
Look at the size
of this thing...
(Gasp)
Was that... my imagination?
No!
(Gasp)
An Ex Machina!
[EX MACHINA]
(Speaking in a robotic pattern)
Investigating.
Adjusting for
current parameters.
[RIKU]
Stay calm. These things operate
as part of a collective.
They have a shared
consciousness with
their cluster,
which means others
must be nearby.
And that means...
[EX MACHINA]
Conclusion.
[RIKU]
If I make any hostile moves,
all the Ex Machina will
see me as a threat...
I must. Remain. Still.
[EX MACHINA]
I cannot resist you,
Big Brother,
you must make a woman out of me.
[RIKU]
Huh?!
[EX MACHINA]
Error.
Cannot... comprehend.
[RIKU]
I think I'm the one
failing to comprehend here!
[EX MACHINA]
Conjecture: Is this scenario
not sufficient to bring
you gratification?
Yeah, look, I'm real sorry.
But I'm not one of those weirdos
who gets off on being observed
by you guys, okay?
[EX MACHINA]
Query: Who are "You guys"?
[RIKU]
Oh don't play dumb with me.
I know all this gets sent to
that Cluster thing of yours.
Negative. This unit has
been disengaged from the
Cluster collective.
Disengaged you say? Uh...?
So then, you're on your own?
[EX MACHINA]
Correct.
[RIKU]
Well, okay then. Uh...
What does some stray Ex Machina
want with someone like me?
I mean, I'm just a human.
If you don't mind me asking.
Response: To analyze the
unique language humans
use among themselves.
The language referred to
as "the heart."
The heart, huh?
Reasoning: This unit's
investigation into the
existence of the heart
generated multiple logic errors,
causing this unit to
be disassociated.
Thereafter, further
observation has been
conducted independently.
"Observation"? So, your plan
is to study the heart
on your own...
and get the Cluster
to take you back, yes?
[EX MACHINA]
Desire. It is postulated
that dermal contact,
flesh upon flesh, results in
a unique exchange of emotions.
I request you
procreate with this unit.
(Riku pulls blade)
I don't think so!
[EX MACHINA]
Alternative: You may take
advantage of this unit
in any manner you wish...
though it possesses no orifice.
[RIKU]
Look, I said...
wait, no orifice?!
[RIKU]
Hmm...
[EX MACHINA]
Losen.
[RIKU]
Uhh!
[EX MACHINA]
Recreation. Erst...
Chess.
[RIKU]
Hm...
[EX MACHINA]
A challenge: I request
participation. In the game.
Conditions: If this unit wins,
it shall be taken home with you
and procreation shall occur.
I can only assume you
choose chess on purpose.
You guys are basically
walking calculators,
so there's no way I can win.
Still...
What if...
I DO manage to win?
Answer: You shall
take this unit home...
and then immediate
procreation shall occur.
[RIKU]
That's the same frickin' thing!
Well, whatever.
I guess there's no getting out
of it at this point is there?
Fine. I'll play along.
[EX MACHINA]
Conclusion: A game in accordance
with the aforementioned terms.
[RIKU]
Sure. I'll play you one time.
Except, I'll be making...
a slight change to these
little rules of yours.
(Data processing)
Uh.. Ah!
Ugh!
[EX MACHINA]
We have arrived.
[RIKU]
Um‐so... When it
comes to mobility,
you really don't use
any spiritual energy?
[EX MACHINA]
Correct.
Utilizing spiritual energy
would have saved
fifty‐five thousand, seven
hundred and eighty‐two seconds.
[RIKU]
Ugh...
[EX MACHINA]
Addendum: This unit
is a "Prufer,"
a model primarily
used for analysis.
Its capabilities are lesser
than other Ex Machina.
[RIKU]
With a half‐assed "race"
like this waging war,
it's no wonder
the world's gone to hell.
[RIKU]
What should I call you?
[EX MACHINA]
Meaning unknown.
[RIKU]
Your name. Don't you have one?
[EX MACHINA]
Understood.
Designation number:
Uber Cluster Zwei Null Sieben
Peh Err Vier
Funf Sieben Teh Neun.
[RIKU]
You kidding, that's your name?
Forget that. You're going
to need to go with
something easier.
[EX MACHINA]
Query: If this unit wins,
it will stay with Riku until
it is able to fully comprehend
the human heart.
Should this unit conceal
that it is a machine?
[RIKU]
The heart's like an unspoken
feeling that is formed through
mutual understanding.
And if you're gonna be with me,
then you're going to need to
dress like a human.
[EX MACHINA]
Query: Is self‐designation
an option?
[RIKU]
Sure, whatever.
[EX MACHINA]
Response: I shall be Schwarzer.
[RIKU]
Nope, that's hard to say
and weird. Not gonna
work for me.
Let's just go with "Schwi."
[EX MACHINA]
Unclear. Adjustment was made
for self‐configuration.
[RIKU]
Can we do something about
the way you talk before
we get started?
[EX MACHINA]
Laden. Adopting Personality
Eins Sechs Ein Null.
[EX MACHINA]
Tee‐hee‐hee! Is this better
for you, Big Brother?
[RIKU]
Ugh. Never mind!
Retort: Setting was the most
logical choice available.
[RIKU]
And what "logical" nonsense did
you use to position yourself
as my younger sister?
Answer: I merely presented what
was the most optimal option.
Yeah, well...
It'd be a big problem if
people were to start
asking about our past.
Just act shy, and don't say
more than you have to.
And quit starting every sentence
sounding like a robot...
Understood?
[SCHWI] (Speaking normally)
Understood.
Something like this?
Uh... Are you...
acting or something?
"Acting"? I'm not.
I have chosen a personality
matching the given parameters.
It's a trace emulation.
Hm... it'll do...
[RIKU]
I want you to stay
where I can see you.
And keep those clothes on.
Is there maybe something you
can do about that tail‐looking
thing you got there?
[SCHWI]
Negative.
It is Schwi's power source,
a nerve corer of
quasi‐spiritual circuitry...
Ah... Alright, fine I guess.
We'll just say it's
a fashion choice.
But, I'm going to say
this one more time:
Do NOT show that robot body of
yours to anyone else. Okay?
[SCHWI]
Yes. I will show it only to you.
[COURONNE]
Awww! She's so cute!
Who is she?!
[RIKU]
Found her on the way back,
at a colony that'd been
wiped out. She was in a...
[COURONNE]
Oh! So is she... your wife?!
[SCHWI]
His "Wife"?
[RIKU]
Uh...!
Oh c'mon, don't be shy.
Now your first priority
should be having kids,
and then next is food,
and then of course having
five or six more kids!
Would you please cut that out.
And you that goes for you too!
[SCHWI]
What does she mean?
[RIKU]
She doesn't mean anything!
[COURONNE]
What's your name?
I'm Schwi.
[COURONNE]
That's a lovely name.
So, how did you meet
Riku here anyway?
(Riku annoyed)
[SCHWI]
Well he...
He kissed Schwi.
And demanded that the two of us
partake in procreation.
[RIKU]
Uh... Uh no, I just...!
[COURONNE]
Riku...
You couldn't wait
could you, huh...
Don't you have
a shred of decency?!
(Slap)
[RIKU]
You could've worded that
differently, you know.
[SCHWI]
"Differently"?
[RIKU]
Never mind.
Look, could you at least try
to look a bit more mature?
You're making me
look bad over here.
[SCHWI]
Okay. But isn't this
the form that you prefer.
[RIKU]
Nah, that ain't my thing.
[SCHWI]
Then... what form DO you like?
[RIKU]
Now you listen here...
Do you even know what it means
when you ask that question?
[SCHWI]
I'm wanting to know
what you prefer.
[RIKU]
That's not something I can
really tell you with words.
You remember how I explained
the human heart?
[SCHWI]
I remember.
So then. Let's play.
[RIKU]
No thanks.
I didn't have much
choice before, but...
I find games pointless,
and I don't have the time
to waste on them.
[SCHWI]
What if...
they are not pointless?
What if you win, the prize
will be all the information
you desire.
For example...
the reason that
the Great War began.
And what it will take to end it.
[RIKU]
Uh! Gimme a break.
We humans don't have
any choice in that nonsense,
so there's no point
in bothering with it.
There's only one thing
I need to know how to do.
How to make it
through the day alive.
And that's it.
That's the whole reason
I brought you along.
The knowledge, the math,
the engineering tech
you Ex Machina contain...
If I can beat you,
then THAT'S what I want.
[SCHWI]
Hm... Understood.
Given the current state
of our world,
the fact that humans
have survived is...
an anomaly.
Even we Ex Machina cannot
calculate a reason for this.
As lifeforms, you are weak.
Your civilization is primitive.
You cannot utilize
spiritual power. And yet...
You have subsisted.
It defies all reason.
Yet there must be an answer...
a key to your survival.
And my theory is... that
it resides in the human heart.
And I intend to find it.
I wish to discover‐
Enough...
Hmm...?
[RIKU]
(scoff) You're so full of shit.
[SCHWI]
Riku?
[RIKU]
You do whatever you want.
You wage war whenever want.
You've taken everything from us,
and well I'm so sorry if you're
puzzled why we're still alive.
No wonder you know nothing
about the human heart.
(Grunts)
Okay fine, you wann know!
What I feel in
my heart hasn't changed
one damn bit since
the moment I was born!
You can burn in hell,
every last one of you!
(Schwi gasps)
Do you know how many people have
died because of you bastards?
You probably know exactly
how many! Don't you?!
And how many more
will you make US kill?
Riku... I have made you cry.
So therefore...
I assume...
I have said something terrible.
Something to hurt you.
(Riku sobs)
What I do know
about the heart...
is that deep inside it...
you wish to kill me.
Riku. You can stab me.
I will die.
Rather... Since I am
not a living being,
it will be a
permanent cessation,
with repair
not being possible...
A complete systemic failure.
I wish to know your heart.
That is all.
If this is truly what
your heart desires...
then I want it to be realized.
I want you to kill me.
(Riku gasps)
[RIKU]
Chad, Anton, Elma, Corey, Dale,
Silith, Ed, Darrel,
Dave, Larcus,
Vin, Eric, Charlie...
[SCHWI]
Riku?
[RIKU]
Thompson, Shinta, Yang, Zsa Zsa,
Zargo, Cray, Goro,
Peter, Arthur,
Morg, Kimmy, Dat, Cyril,
Vizzie, Wally,
Ken, Savage, Leroy, Bobo,
Couthon, Lito,
Shigure, Shao, Wolf, Bard,
Asso, Kenwood,
Peil, Ahad, Hound,
Barloff, Masashi,
Memegan, Karim... Ivan!
(Riku gasping)
Forty‐eight people...
Forty‐eight!
And I am the one who
ordered them all to die!
Too many people have died
during your Great War...
removed from this world
like dust being swept away.
And the one who sent
those people to die...
The one who told them to...
(Groans)
Riku?
(Crying)
Oh...
[COURONNE]
Riku? You awake?
Sorry, I know you're tired, but
if you don't mind.. I'd uh...
AHH! Sorry!
[RIKU] Uh...
(Couronne giggles)
Um, okay Schwi, do you mind
if I ask you why you're
sitting there straddling me?
[SCHWI]
Riku... You instructed me to
stay where you could see me.
[RIKU]
I only meant for you
to stay nearby.
[SCHWI]
Question: If I'm not in
your line of sight
then can you see me?
[COURONNE]
Oh, is this some sort
of roleplay?
[RIKU]
Close the damn door!
Oh, it's okay sweetie,
I understand...
Whenever you're done,
let me know and
Schwi can take a bath.
Uh... don't mind her.
Mph...
I see.
Riku said I can show my body
only to him. In that case...
[COURONNE]
Whaah! You have her trained?!
Couronne, would you please
just leave us alone?!
[COURONNE]
Oh wow, things sure are
moving quickly.
Okay, I'll let you two
have some privacy.
And I'll go kick out
whoever's in the bath.
(Riku groans)
[SCHWI]
I am... sorry.
[RIKU]
Sorry for what?
[SCHWI]
For being the aggressor
and yet asking about the heart.
It's illogical.
[RIKU]
I wouldn't say "illogical"
‐ it's insensitive.
[SCHWI]
My circuits... are capable
of sensitive transmission.
[RIKU]
Um, that's not what I meant.
In any case... I'm sorry that
I got way all worked up.
[SCHWI]
Is that a bad thing to do?
[RIKU]
Could be. I might lose it
and smack you,
and that wouldn't
solve anything would it?
[SCHWI]
Do you wish to strike me, Riku?
[RIKU]
Of course not,
I'm just making a point.
I, uh... I don't know...
Maybe I'm not so sure myself.
[SCHWI]
Riku. Let's play a game.
[RIKU]
Huh?
(Riku sighs)
What did you bring
that thing for?
[SCHWI]
Because... that's when
you smiled, Riku.
It's the only time.
[RIKU]
Uh...?
[SCHWI]
So...
Let's... play a game.
[RIKU]
Huh?
[SCHWI]
I wish... I wish to know
your heart, Riku.
But also... not in
a manner that hurts you.
I have a conflict.
I don't know what to do.
You mean you'd have to
hurt me in order to do it?
Can't you just go
back to your Cluster?
I'm sure you can learn
all you want about the heart
without forcing it out of me.
[SCHWI]
Yes. That's true.
But either way, I do not wish
to cause you harm...
Why is that?
[RIKU]
Wha...? You're asking ME?
(Data processing)
[SCHWI]
Stating possibility.
Answer: The unit has found
the Cluster pointless,
and meaningless, and irrelevant,
with personal analysis of
the heart taking prominence.
I want you to remain.
Error. Error. Error. Error.
[RIKU] Uh! Agh! What's going on?
Ah! Hey cut that out!
Conclusion: It seems
I don't want... to go back.
It seems?
Unable to quantify definitely.
Although...
It would seem so.
So it does... Heheh...
but it's a little confusing.
[SCHWI]
Pawn to E‐4.
[RIKU]
Hey, you could at least
let me have the first move.
[SCHWI]
The next turn is yours.
[RIKU]
Also, you're playing while I'm
sitting here brushing your hair.
That's not very fair, is it?
So, why's it so long anyway?
If you would prefer it
to be short, I will cut it.
Hehe. No, you don't
have to do that.
Heheh. You just don't
get it, do you?
[COURONNE]
Oh...
Hmm....
[SCHWI]
Riku.
[RIKU]
Hm? Uhh?
[SCHWI]
Here you go. I have designed
a compact telescope.
[RIKU]
Look I told you. I still
haven't beaten you at chess.
[SCHWI]
But I... thought this
was what you wanted.
So I made it for you.
Um... Huh...
[SCHWI]
That is where I met you.
[RIKU]
Uh, yeah.
There's something about
that place that's
always really bugged me...
but it's so far away
that I can't just get up
and walk there can I?
[RIKU]
Ugh!
[SCHWI]
We've arrived.
(Riku slow coughs)
Well you sure are the
observant one arent'cha? Hooray.
[RIKU]
Have you noticed?
The buildings are all destroyed,
but for some reason, the ground
here is mostly untouched.
[SCHWI]
That would be because of
the elves' protective magic.
[RIKU]
But why let everything get
completely wiped out
except for this one spot?
[SCHWI]
To the elves, this was
an important facility,
an emergency shelter,
or perhaps something else.
Something of more value.
A facility to research
and develop new weaponry.
[RIKU]
What the hell is this?
[SCHWI]
Protective glyphs of
the Old Deus Kainas.
[RIKU]
Kainas... That's the
creator of the elves.
[SCHWI]
Huh... These are not
protective glyphs.
And they do not correspond
to any available data
regarding elvish glyphs
or magical rites.
[RIKU]
It's probably some damn new
horrible foolishness
they invented.
They're as hell‐bent as the
dwarves to destroy the planet.
[RIKU]
"Aka Si Anse...
proof of concept reactor..."
[SCHWI]
Riku... you can read
the Elvish language?
[RIKU]
The best clues and information
out there is worthless
if you can't understand it.
To this day, the traits,
and the languages, and the
customs of the various races
have been passed down in
oral history, written works...
any means you can think of.
It's what we do ‐
because we lowly humans
aren't going to just sit back
and let ourselves get wiped out.
[SCHWI]
Oh...
[RIKU]
That being said...
I can't read a damn thing
else on here.
Especially this part.
It must be like a name, right?
[SCHWI]
If this is all
classified information,
then it is most likely that
it is in code. Encrypted.
[RIKU]
Yeah, you're right
and that's a problem.
It means even the names of
whoever's involved with this
have also been encrypted.
"Aka Si Anse..."
The only thing we know for sure
so far, is a bunch of
friggin' nonsense, huh?
(Gasp)
[SCHWI]
Riku, stand back!
Losen.
Einweg!
[SCHWI]
Run!
[RIKU]
Dammit!
[SCHWI]
Uhh!
[RIKU]
Schwi!
[SCHWI]
Oh...! Ah...
Ah...!
[RIKU]
Schwi!
[SCHWI]
Ri...
Ugh!
(Grunts and groans)
(Gasp)
Eh...
Schwi...
Schwi!
Uh... Schwi...
[SCHWI]
Their security system...
The elvish magic...
remains active.
[RIKU]
Huh?
[SCHWI]
Don't worry. It will be fine.
Losen.
Steh Apokryphen.
[RIKU]
Ah... What was that?
[SCHWI]
A special ability of
the Ex Machina.
If attacked, we can analyze,
emulate, and reproduce
the attack,
copying it.
But as a Prufer, I would
only be able to generate
less than 10% of
its original strength.
[RIKU]
Yeah, if you say so...
But you might still
tone it down a bit.
[SCHWI]
I'm sorry.
[RIKU]
Huh?
[SCHWI]
I broke my promise.
And I used spiritual energy.
[RIKU]
Yeah well. I guess
it's better than dying.
Anyway we should probably
get out of here pretty quick
before some band of freaks
comes and finds us.
(High winds)
[RIKU]
Dammit! We've got a soot storm.
[SCHWI]
I will be fine.
My system pumps a
decontamination solution
that purges the
impurities of the ash.
[RIKU]
You may be fine, but that
doesn't mean I would be.
[RIKU]
So, I see... you brought
the chess set, right?
[SCHWI]
Yes, I'm sorry.
[RIKU]
No, it's not that
I'm criticizing you.
[RIKU]
You wanna play a game?
You don't mind?
No, this is good.
We're stuck down here because of
the storm and everything.
It's a good way
to kill some time, right?
[SCHWI]
Hmm!
(Riku grunts)
[RIKU]
Come on! How do you
keep doing that?!!
One more time!
[SCHWI]
Riku... Why do you
keep challenging me
when you know that you
cannot beat me?
[RIKU]
"I can't beat you"?
[SCHWI]
Yes, well. You haven't yet.
Not even once.
(Riku sighs)
[RIKU]
Look, I'm just thinking about
this in the big picture.
The law of averages.
There's no way you can
beat me every single time.
[SCHWI]
Oh...
I... I understand. Partially.
[RIKU]
Huh?
[SCHWI]
The current conditions
upon this planet are
fatal for all humanity.
The fact that you exist is...
an aberration.
[RIKU]
Hmm...
[SCHWI]
This aberration...
Correction: This accomplishment
is possible...
Because of your heart...
your will.
(Riku annoyed)
[SCHWI]
Despite overwhelming odds,
humanity as a whole survives...
this is an objective fact...
and yet...
you refuse to accept that fact.
For some reason, you do not wish
to acknowledge what you are.
Why is that?
[RIKU]
Well, let me ask you this:
What's the point of surviving
when you live in a world
like this one?
You just run as hard and
as fast as you can, and you
keep running... but what then?
What the hell else do you do?
Just sit back and let yourself
get obliterated into nothing?!
And if you don't like that idea,
can you let 999 people die
for the sake of 1,001?
Will that change
anything at all?! Huh?!
[SCHWI]
Riku...
[RIKU]
Tell me this, Schwi:
What else can we do?
(Riku crying)
What should I do?
[SCHWI]
I wish to know as well.
So then... What does
your heart tell you, Riku?
[RIKU]
Heh... Just look at what
a freakin' mess I am, huh?
I asked you, 'cause honestly,
I don't know.
I'm afraid my heart's
not talking.
[SCHWI]
In that case...
What do you wish to do?
[RIKU]
Um... uh...?
"What I wish to do"?
[SCHWI]
Whatever it is...
I will help you.
I will be right by your side...
And I will stay there...
Until I understand your heart.
I shall keep watch over you...
to see what it is that
your heart truly desires.
I wish to do whatever
it is YOU wish to do Riku.
[RIKU]
Uhhh!
[SCHWI]
Checkmate.
[RIKU]
Schwi... That would've probably
been a pretty good time to maybe
call it a draw? I'm just sayin'.
[SCHWI]
Has there been any changes
in atmospheric conditions?
[RIKU]
Uh...? No...
(Laughs)
No... Hehe...
No, there hasn't.
[SCHWI]
Ohh...
[RIKU]
[BOTH]
It's beautiful.
[RIKU]
Huh?
(Chuckle)
[RIKU]
Schwi... it's kinda nice...
not being alone, huh?
[SCHWI]
Huh? Riku, you haven't always
been alone, have you?
[RIKU]
Nah. But like an idiot,
I've always pushed
myself to extremes,
trying to be something...
special.
But anyway...
If I were to just go by what
I want to do, well then...
things might actually
work out pretty well.
[SCHWI]
Oh...
[RIKU]
Schwi...
Tell me something.
What's the point of this war?
And what can we do to end it?
[RIKU]
When I was a child,
I thought the world was
a much, much simpler place.
I thought there was
no challenge that
was unbeatable...
that if I tried hard enough,
anything was possible.
Everything was cut and dry:
You win, you lose,
or it ends in a draw.
I thought I was seeing the
world with clear eyes.
But it...
But it was all such
foolish, ignorant youth.
And you know...
in the end...
It turns out I was dead wrong.
[SCHWI]
Huh?
You know what, Schwi...
together, I think we can
make things in this world
get interesting.
Yes. That's it there.
Those eyes are good, Riku.
I have... good eyes?
[SCHWI]
No.
Schwi... likes to
see those eyes.
I mean. Don't you?
[RIKU]
Uh?
Ah... Hehehe...
There you go,
bein' confusing again.
[SCHWI]
Huh?
(Riku laughs)
(Splash)
(Gasps)
[LILY]
This is really bad!
(Rumbling)
[COURONNE]
Please remain calm!
Head for the west exit!
Nonna, you go with the others.
[NONNA]
Mm‐hm!
[COURONNE]
Okay, now go!
(General panic)
[COURONNE]
Ah!
Riku! Oh!
(Riku sobbing, choking up)
[COURONNE]
R‐Riku...
[RIKU]
Dammit!
This place will get
turned to ash too?
Then what...?
Tell me, huh? What have I
done all this for?!
[COURONNE]
Riku. C'mon, you can't
worry about that now.
Why don't you just let me
take things from here, okay?
(Crying)
[RIKU]
Schwi. You put that
in writing, right?
[SCHWI]
Yes, I did.
[COURONNE]
Huh?
[RIKU]
Which means, Couronne,
that as of today,
you're head of the colony.
And that... is the site
for your new colony.
You'll be safe if you stay
on the western escape route.
Well, best of luck
to you and everything.
[COURONNE]
Hey! Riku, wait a second Riku!
Without you, me and the
rest of the camp are doomed!
[RIKU]
Nah, everything's gonna be fine.
Because from here on out...
no one else is gonna die.
[COURONNE]
Huh?
Riku!
Uhh...
Hm...
Hey guys! So what sort of
craziness are you two
cooking up, huh?
[RIKU]
Oh you know. Just a little game.
We're gonna take it easy
just pass the time.
[RIKU]
As of now,
everyone here is dead.
We did not make it
out of the colony in time.
We no longer exist
in this world...
We're Ghosts.
The day of the
final battle WILL come.
It's no use in hoping for
a future where it won't.
The world is an abomination.
So do we just run to stay alive,
praying for that last battle?
And if so, pray to who?
These goddamn butchers
who call themselves gods?!
Artosh, creator of the Fluegel!
Kainas, creator of the elves!
Okein, creator of the dwarves!
All of them claim to be the
one true ruler of this world,
fighting for their
precious throne
and doing nothing but destroying
everything in the process!
These pieces of shit don't
deserve any of our prayers!
It's time to open your eyes.
We can no longer rely on
hope to save us.
Which is why... we have to
build things up ourselves.
In the end, this world
is nothing but a game.
Those butchers are
after the Suniaster...
a conceptual device said to
grant absolute authority
over this entire world.
Which is why they have
devoted themselves to this
game where anything goes.
And so...
We're gonna make our own rules,
on our own terms.
And then...
We will win.
Number One: No matter what,
you must not kill!
The heart does not wish
for murder....
Number Two: You must let
no one die!
The heart doesn't want
anyone to die...
Number Three: You must let
no one discover you!
If we're discovered,
we're dead.
Number Four: No tactic
is off limits!
Not even the slyest trick
will be considered "dirty."
Number Five: Those guys' rules
mean nothing to us!
The heart doesn't give
two shits about their
bloody contest.
Number Six: Break any of
these rules and you lose.
The heart will gain nothing
from a victory that
violates our principles.
That's it. Now we do
whatever we want.
We are the Ghosts.
We will not kill a single member
of the other races,
including the Old Deus.
And we will not be discovered!
We are a phantom.
And we will guide the course
of this war to its fruition!
That will be our victory!
To finally see the end of
their goddamn war!
Our enemies are gods, with great
tools of violence and despair.
Now, this game was never
meant for us to play.
So winning means we must do
everything in secret
and behind the scenes.
And even if we win,
we can have no memory of it.
Because Ghosts don't exist.
They just vanish ‐ into
the void, into nothingness.
But know this...
If we can do this.
If we can master this game for
real, and if we can win it...
We can... we can die
with our heads high...
cause we lived the coolest,
most bad‐ass lives ever!
[SCHWI]
Oh...
[RIKU]
Okay, if you're willing
to play along.
And you're ready to get
started. Then stay here.
Uhm... I'm gonna be
honest with you.
No offense, but I really
thought that you guys were
a bit smarter than this.
(Men snickering)
A smart man would've left before
you finished your little speech.
Come on now, you didn't
really think there were
any "smart" people left
in the world, did ya?
And where else are you ever
gonna find a bunch of
crazier fools than these?
The smart have already
choosen death over this place.
And yet the smartest ones,
didn't bother being born!
You get what you ask for Riku.
You're the one who
chose us remember?
Yeah, that's right!
The one who leads
a bunch of dumbasses
is the biggest
dumbass of all!
(Laughter)
[RIKU]
Yes. Humans are foolish.
But it's takes a great fool,
to know how to not let
foolishness get them killed.
[SCHWI]
Oof! Oh...!
[RIKU]
We have stayed alive in a world
where life has no value.
Everyone has bet it all,
through science and knowledge
and intellect,
and made that happen...
They're all fools.
Incredibly weak and vulnerable.
Magnificent, weak fools,
all worthy of great respect.
Okay, everybody let's do this!
Let us pledge upon the wishes
of all our fallen brethren.
[MEN]
Ascheito!
[RIKU]
No. Not upon the memories of
the fallen: But the rules
we have vowed to follow.
To everyone here...
I pledge Aschento!
Okay... Let's get
this game started.
[SCHWI]
Riku... I am now certain.
I do not understand
the human heart.
[RIKU]
Hm?
[SCHWI]
All potential strategies have a
less than 1% chance of success.
[RIKU]
And you must be wondering why
everyone's so sure that
we can pull it off?
[SCHWI]
Mm‐hm.
[RIKU]
So uh, Schwi...
If you roll a die, what are the
odds it will come up a six?
[SCHWI]
A one in six chance.
[RIKU]
Yeah, maybe so...
But what if someone
who doesn't exist,
swaps it out for a die
that will roll ONLY a six?
[SCHWI]
Uh... You're talking about
manipulation of the variables.
[RIKU]
Yeah. I like to
call it "cheating."
Sounds fun, right?
We are the singularity
of the equation.
We'll make every prediction,
every strategy and calculation,
come together exactly how
we want it to.
If we pull it off, it'll be a‐
[SCHWI]
A miracle.
[RIKU]
Uh?
[SCHWI]
It would be an anomaly.
Success would be a distortion
of probability theory.
[RIKU]
I know...
Anything can happen though.
Zero or 100,
it doesn't really matter...
I mean, that's why they
call it a theory right?
Would you like me to
prove it to you?
Question: What are the odds
that, right here and now,
I were to profess
my love to you?
[SCHWI]
Intent unclear.
Estimation: Near zero.
[RIKU]
Yeah well... You're wrong.
Will you marry me, Schwi?
[SCHWI]
Cannot... comprehend. I decline.
[RIKU CRYING]
I'M SORRY! I KNOW!
THAT WAS TOO MUCH TOO SOON!
I MEAN I'VE NEVER EVEN
BEEN WITH A GIRL BEFORE!
(Riku crying)
[SCHWI]
Marriage...
A vow of intimacy humans
exchange in order to reproduce.
But Schwi is an Ex Machina.
[RIKU WHINING]
I don't care about that!
I just want you with me forever.
I just want you to
always be by my side!
[SCHWI]
But why? I already am.
[RIKU]
That's not what I mean okay!
I'm talking, like,
as a life partner!
[SCHWI]
Ex Machina cannot reproduce.
[RIKU]
I know, I don't care!
[SCHWI]
We cannot copulate either.
Riku, you would
always be a virgin.
(Riku gasps)
[RIKU]
I don't care about that!
[SCHWI]
You hesitated.
[RIKU]
Oh, quit nitpicking
the semantics!
[SCHWI]
It is not possible.
(Riku gasps)
Because...
[RIKU]
Schwi?
(Data processing)
[SCHWI]
Because... Because I...
(Dragon growls)
[SCHWI AS EX MACHINA]
Transmission:
From Prufer to Einzig.
[EINZIG]
Decision reached.
[SCHWI]
I destroyed your home, Riku.
It was me.
[SCHWI AS EX MACHINA]
Losen. Origin Zwei Acht
Null Sieben. Einweg.
[SCHWI]
I did it.
Can you... still say
what you just said?
[RIKU]
Schwi.
I already knew that.
Somehow, I already knew.
[SCHWI]
Oh!
But... how's that?
[RIKU]
Well... the first thing that
seemed a little off was...
You know... the first moment
we ever met.
I mean, why would you have
chosen to play chess
in the first place? Right?
[SCHWI]
Oh!
[RIKU]
And then, why else
would you just so happen
to be sitting there
outside of the settlement?
Heh... Wasn't very well
thought out, was it?
[SCHWI]
Even if that's so... Why...?
[RIKU]
Well... I guess, because
once I knew the whole story...
I kinda fell for you.
What can I say?
[SCHWI]
Uhh!
[RIKU]
Nothing will change the fact
that you wiped out my hometown.
But if not for that,
well then... we probably
never would have met.
[SCHWI]
Oh...
[RIKU]
It is what it is.
We can try and sugarcoat it,
but it won't change anything.
You can cry or feel bad.
Or promise to never do it again.
Maybe pity's why you
took an interest in me
in the first place.
Hehe...
But no matter your past...
in the present you're with me.
And in my future is where
I want you to stay...
It's called forever.
Being with you has
made me think that,
even in a world like this,
I want to live.
It's the only thing I can think
of that makes we want to smile.
So...
Will you throw logic
out the window
and choose to walk
this path with me?
That is... as my wife.
Uh! Schwi!
[SCHWI]
In every sense...
To all rational appearances...
it is absurd.
And yet...
Let me...
let me be by your side.
With you and you
alone Riku. Forever.
[RIKU]
And I the same with you.
[COURONNE]
Riku: Do you take Schwi
as your wife,
swearing to grow together,
support and love each other,
and to stay alive?
[RIKU]
Yeah, yeah, I swear.
[COURONNE]
Riku, please! You're supposed
to say "Ascheito"!
[RIKU]
Sorry. We sort of
got rid of that.
Now, it's "Aschiento."
[COURONNE]
It kinda bugs me that you've
been up to all this
crazy stuff...
without letting me
know anything.
Like, what the heck?
You all of the sudden tell me
you have a secret hideout,
and when I get here,
you're getting married!
I mean, what is that?!
[RIKU]
Can we just get on with the
stupid ceremony, please?
You're the one who
said we needed it.
[COURONNE]
Ahem! Do you, Schwi,
take Riku as your husband,
swearing to grow together,
support and love each other‐?
[SCHWI]
I swear.
[COURONNE]
Uh?
I swear to Riku,
the one who taught me
why I was born,
and gave me a heart...
I pledge myself.
I will not let you die, Riku.
We will live side by side,
right to the end.
Aschiento.
[COURONNE]
Eheheh!
And so, as your new
"Big Sister..."
I would like to congratulate
you on your marriage.
[RIKU]
Uh! Wait, Couronne!
[SCHWI]
Ahh...?
Uhh...
[COURONNE]
Ooo... You are so cute!
[RIKU]
Couronne, why are you...?
Well she is the one you chose
as your bride, right Riku?
[RIKU]
Uh!
[COURONNE]
So, in closing,
you shall carve
your names on this.
[RIKU]
On a rock?
[COURONNE]
Yes, on a rock.
If you guys are gonna
live in secret,
there can be
no official documents.
[RIKU]
That's your name...
[COURONNE]
Yes, my surname.
And from now on, it will be
the same for all three of us.
[RIKU]
Uh...
(Laugh)
Feels weird for us
to share a name.
[COURONNE]
Riku, Schwi...
I don't know what you are...
what either of you
are planning to do.
I mean, you two aren't
really part of this world.
But well...
I do know I have a
little brother I adore
and now a gorgeous
younger sister, too.
So...
I beg you... be careful
and don't do anything rash.
I don't want to lose my family!
Yeah. No one is
gonna die, Couronne.
Because this is one game...
we're sure to win.
You can trust us...
Okay, Big Sister.
(Warbeasts growling)
(Grunting)
(Warbeasts roar)
(Warbeasts gasp)
[WARBEAST]
I can smell it... the black ash!
[ALEI]
Well done, warbeast.
You can eat me
if you want, but...
I guarantee you,
I won't taste very good.
[WARBEAST]
Who the hell are you?!
[ALEI]
Your clan has made the west
coast of the continent
of Lucia your home...
but the dwarves are planning
to conduct an advanced
weapons test out there.
(Warbeasts snarl)
[ALEI]
And be warned,
this thing could even
kill an Old Deus.
It's a large‐scale explosive
device called an E‐bomb.
(Warbeasts snarl)
[ALEI]
Your kind can use
Blood Destruction, yes?
It could prove useful for you to
get into the dwarves' facility.
You could make quick work
of it, take care of things
however you like.
[RIKU]
The dwarves' fleet keeps
close watch on the warbeasts
and then moves into action.
The warbeasts, fearful of
the E‐bomb, flee Lucia.
Next, secret elvish information
is leaked to the dwarves.
And THIS...
is where it all comes together.
[THINK]
Who are you?
[RIKU]
Let's see... I'll just
call myself a Ghost.
[THINK]
I assume you have business here
that warrants barging into
my home unannounced.
[RIKU]
I was thinking the two of us
could have a little game.
[THINK]
A game?
[RIKU]
And the currency we'll
bet with is information.
If you win,
I'll tell you something.
If you lose,
you tell me something.
I don't know who you are
or where you're from...
and yet you think Nina Clive
would just accept
a challenge from you?
[RIKU]
I'll give you something
up front then:
Information on the Aka Si Anse
has been leaked to the dwarves.
[THINK]
Uh?
[RIKU]
Is that good enough?
As the Advocate and Caretaker
of Aka Si Anse Theory,
you should have the ability
to confirm if this information
is valid or not.
Am I mistaken?
[THINK]
Hm, very well.
I may not know who you are,
but this is something
I cannot ignore.
Therefore, here is my wager:
the Advocate of Aka Si Anse
Theory is in fact‐
[RIKU]
It's somebody else, right?
[THINK]
Uh...!
[RIKU]
Yes, I've already heard.
[THINK]
Hm...
[RIKU]
But I also know
that's not true.
[THINK]
Mmh?
[RIKU]
And that you will
resort to magic
to make me believe
your lie.
[RIKU]
Now then...
what shall I give you?
Ah... when the dwarves
learned of the Aka Si Anse,
they concluded that
it wasn't a threat.
And I have proof.
[THINK]
But that's ridiculous.
[RIKU]
It's true.
(Think gasps)
[RIKU]
And I have more information...
the dwarves are in possession
of a weapon of their own.
And it's even more powerful
than the Aka Si Anse.
[THINK]
The E‐bomb...
[RIKU]
Yes. A weapon of
tremendous scale.
One that could wipe out
the entire continent.
[THINK]
You're saying those
creatures who burrow
in the earth like moles,
have created something...
something more advanced
than the Aka Si Anse,
the culmination of
elvish spiritual magic?
Wait just a moment.
There have been times
that you've chosen to
lose on purpose.
Let me ask one last thing:
Are you our enemy?
Or are you our ally?
[RIKU]
I am neither your enemy
nor your ally.
I have but one concern...
you only suffer as few
casualties as possible.
[THINK]
Very well, Mr. Ghost.
To be clear, young man,
I can assume
you have shared this information
with me alone, yes?
Oh, and Mr. Ghost...
I guess I should tell you
my name is not Nina Clive...
Tee‐hee! Rather my
name is Think Nilvalen.
Did I fool you or did you
already figure it out?
[RIKU]
Huh, you tell me.
Did you ever once hear me
call you "Nina"?
[THINK]
Of course if you know
anything about me,
I am going to make you regret
ever trying to make me
your plaything.
After all, the rumor that elves
are relentlessly tenacious...
first began with none other
than the Nilvalen family.
(Riku grunts)
[SCHWI]
Riku!
(Riku groaning and coughing)
Riku, here!
It's a decontaminant!
(Riku gagging)
Riku, you lied to me!
You said it would
only be an hour!
You've been breathing black ash
for twice that time!
(Riku coughs)
(Riku coughing)
[RIKU]
I didn't have a choice.
I had to, or I would've
given myself away.
I had to do it.
And besides... I don't care
how smart you are...
no one could predict this sort
of suicidal behavior, right?
(Riku grunting)
[SCHWI]
Riku!
(Riku weak chuckling)
Looks like this may be
it for me, huh?
[SCHWI]
Mmph...
[RIKU]
So... How much longer
do you think I've got?
[SCHWI]
Riku, I won't let you die.
You have to stay alive
until I die.
[RIKU]
Oh yeah, and how long
do Ex Machina live?
[SCHWI]
I have another 892 years
in my service life.
[RIKU]
Huh?
(laughs)
Guess I'll have to
step up my game, won't I?
[RIKU]
And so, the first objective
was achieved...
moving the violent battle
lines outside of the
human territories.
[LILY]
Look at this. First the dwarves,
and now the elves.
Even the warbeasts are
leaving in droves.
What's going on?
[COURONNE]
Uh... Lily!
Keep an eye on things for me!
I'll be back!
[LILY]
Oh...? Huh? Hey! Couronne!
[RIKU]
The Ghosts continued to take
action from behind the scenes.
And just like we wanted,
the elves eventually became
allies with the fairies
and moved to ramp up their
contracts with the dragonia
in order to fend off
the dwarvish fleet.
Meanwhile, the dwarves became
allies with the gigants,
as well as several phantasma,
who were all on friendly terms.
Manipulated by the
Ghosts' information,
each of the major powers took
steps to guard against
the large‐scale destructive
weaponry of the other,
moving their headquarters
to the neighboring
continent of Ariela.
And well, that just so happened
to be the home base
for what was currently
the greatest threat of all:
The lord of the Fluegel,
the Old Deus... Artosh.
[SCHWI]
Einweg.
Twenty‐three units
are now installed.
That leaves...
nine remaining.
[RIKU]
And so, as each of the other
races sought to take advantage
of this situation,
the clock began ticking down
to the world's final battle...
Exactly like we wanted.
[RIKU]
Hey, Schwi... of all the gods,
is there a god of games?
[SCHWI]
Huh?
[RIKU]
And if, uh...
if I told you I'd met him,
would you believe me?
The stuff he does,
it's way beyond anything
I can anticipate,
so of course I lose to him
every single time.
And yet...
It's so much fun
that I can't stand it.
And it's like...
I just know that I can
beat him the next time.
I've been thinking about that
since this whole thing started..
And I have to do it...
I have to settle things
with him once and for all...
because that game of ours
isn't over yet.
[SCHWI]
If you believe this,
well then, I believe it too.
[RIKU]
Uh...!
[SCHWI]
If you say he exists,
then he does.
I do not doubt you.
Oh, come on!
Are you kidding me!
Why isn't someone here
to hear you say that!
They'll never believe me!
[SCHWI]
Oh! Oh, Riku!
(Riku groans)
[COURONNE]
Riku!
[SCHWI]
Oh?
(Couronne breathing heavy)
[RIKU]
Couronne!
[COURONNE]
It's just like you said:
we haven't lost a single
person to the war.
And sightings of the other
races have dried up too.
[RIKU]
Yeah, I bet.
[COURONNE]
Well, if you two are the ones
behind all of this,
then I'd say that you were doing
something pretty amazing.
But dammit, Riku!
Look at the shape you're in?
You need to be more careful.
[RIKU]
It's not a problem.
[COURONNE]
It's a BIG problem, Riku!
You're falling apart!
[RIKU]
We're almost there, okay?
Just leave me be.
[COURONNE]
But when is "almost"?
I want it to be over?
How long do I have to
keep worrying about you?
(Couronne starts crying)
[RIKU]
Listen to me, Couronne...
Do you know what the gods are
after with this war of theirs?
[COURONNE]
Uh...?
[SCHWI]
The throne of the One True God.
[RIKU]
Yup. According to Schwi,
it's something they refer to
as the Suniaster.
It's a kind of
conceptual device.
And it was designed so that
out of all those big, fancy
Old Deus idiots,
only one of them
can be called "God."
[COURONNE]
"Conceptual device"?
How are you ever suppose to
find something like that?
[SCHWI]
It will appear only
under one condition:
it must manifest itself
in front of the absolute
greatest power on the planet.
[RIKU]
And if there are ten gods
out there of equal power...
they will eventually
kill all the other nine
making whoever's left
their One True God.
That's their twisted way
of thinking.
[COURONNE]
What?! Then they're morons!
So that's the reason
we've been...?
[RIKU]
Couronne, they're even
dumber than you think.
Listen to this...
Their precious Suniaster,
we can make it show up without
going through all that trouble.
[COURONNE]
Huh?
[RIKU]
And that's why I've gathered all
these handsome fellows together.
The Aka Si Anse,
the E‐bomb,
the Heaven's Strike...
They're powerful enough
on their own,
but when put together
in one area...
They could blast a hole...
right through the planet.
Huh? The planet?!
All the Old Deus were originally
born from this world...
they all came from
the Spirit Circuit.
Which means the greatest power
in the whole wide world
is actually...?
Ump! The Spirit Circuit!
[RIKU]
We may be the weakest,
but we've set the stage
for the final scene.
We're gonna to use their
own strength against them
and turn the global balance
of power on its baffled
little head.
The Suniaster will appear,
and once it is acquired,
the One True God will be named,
and the planet will be rebuilt.
This operation will be
an all‐out assault,
so it must be done
using Schwi's weaponry,
which can skew power
directionality.
[SCHWI]
It will be an amalgam
of influence.
Installing 32 Einweg units
should, in theory,
allow us to wield enough raw
power to destroy the planet.
[RIKU]
There are nine installation
sites left.
And once everything is set up...
[RIKU &amp; SCHWI]
It'll be checkmate.
(Couronne gasps)
[RIKU]
Those fools will pierce
the planet's core themselves,
and we'll be there to snatch
the Suniaster right under
their noses.
And we'll do it without
anyone dying...
so when this over,
I wanna ask these gods...
[SCHWI]
Ohh...
"Hey there, how you doing?
Do you like losing?
How does that feel?"
[SCHWI]
Riku?
[COURONNE &amp; SCHWI]
Riku!
(Riku groans)
[RIKU]
Uhhh...
What did you tell them all
before you came here?
[COURONNE]
Huh? Uh...
Nothing, really.
[RIKU]
I bet the colony is
in an absolute panic.
Don't let them be
on their own for too long.
[COURONNE]
Hm! What's going on?!
You suddenly left
without saying anything...
and you never...!
Take care of Nonna and
the others. They need you.
[SCHWI]
Riku. Just sleep.
[RIKU]
I can't. We have to hurry and
finish setting up the Einweg.
[SCHWI]
It can wait.
The attack will not be
starting anytime soon.
Your predictions
are never wrong.
[RIKU]
Yeah, but...! (grunt)
[SCHWI]
You can rest for a little while.
You should... take a day off.
(Riku exhales)
[RIKU]
Hmm.. You're right.
I can probably use some time
to get my strength back up.
[SCHWI]
Yes.
[RIKU]
Um, Schwi... I'm sorry for
being such a burden.
[SCHWI]
Riku, please just sleep now.
You're not a burden.
(Riku deep breath)
Then, Schwi...
I have a favor to ask you.
[SCHWI]
Huh?
[RIKU]
Could you...
hold my hand while I sleep?
[SCHWI]
Huh?
Mm‐hm.
I will hold your hand
for as long as you need.
Don't worry, Riku.
(Riku exhales)
[RIKU]
Schwi, thank you for
coming into my life.
I mean it.
I really do...
love you so much.
Forever and ever.
Riku... I'm sorry.
I'll be back...
I'll be back.
[AZRIEL]
The elves have
the Aka Si Anse...
The dwarves have
their E‐bomb.
Hm, but...
they're both still weak,
and yet challenging
Lord Artosh!
The fools should get
squashed! Nya! Ah!
(Azriel moaning and groaning)
[RAFAEL]
You're the one being
foolish, Azriel.
We can't afford to make any
brazen moves ourselves.
Lord Artosh is awaiting
the right opportunity,
and so we must wait as well.
[JIBRIL]
Mph...
Rather tedious, isn't it?
(Device buzzes)
[SCHWI]
Eight more.
If I acquire the Suniaster,
then Riku will not die!
Riku, just hold on!
[JIBRIL]
Well now...
(Schwi gasps)
[JIBRIL]
Are you out here all by yourself
on this lovely day?
(Schwi gasps)
[JIBRIL]
I observed faint readings
of spiritual energy,
so I came to investigate,
and well...
what a most unexpected
bounty it has yielded me.
Some glorious scrap.
A pleasure to meet you.
[SCHWI]
Warning: Hostile action against
this unit will trigger
appropriate countermeasures.
From a single Prufer unit?
Isn't that cute.
I have confirmed there are
no Cluster readings
within a 100‐kilometer radius.
No one is coming to help you,
so I'd say this is
a wonderful chance
to remove that charming
little head of yours.
[SCHWI]
Number 1: You must not
kill anyone.
[JIBRIL]
Luckily for you, Ex Machina
have no understanding
of the concept
of death, do they?
[SCHWI]
Number 2: You must let
no one die.
[JIBRIL]
There's really no use
in resisting, and so‐
[SCHWI]
I refuse.
[JIBRIL]
Pardon?
[SCHWI]
This unit has been abandoned.
It has no worth.
Number 6: Break any of
these rules and you lose.
Therefore...
[SCHWI]
I'd like you to... drop this.
[JIBRIL]
Ohh!
Don't tell me an Ex Machina
is pleading for its life
out of a fear of death.
Oh, so then you're a defect,
cast out from your
own collective!
Oh, you are a
premium catch, indeed!
I cannot believe what a prize
I have stumbled upon!
What a treat this is! Hahaha!
[SCHWI]
I have determined our
respective combat capabilities.
My chances of winning
are... Nil.
And yet... in probability
theory, there is no "zero."
Laden. Code: Eins, Sechs,
Sieben, Drei, Beh, Sieben,
Vier, Drei, Eh, Eins,
Eff, Zwei, Funf.
Activate. Losen.
Final warning:
All armaments, firepower,
and combat maneuvers
shall be employed...
And you will
beg for your life.
[JIBRIL]
Oh, no! How precious...
I thought Ex Machina were
designed and constructed
to parse and emulate the most
optimal methods of destruction.
Hehe... I'm sorry sweetie,
but I think someone
has played a joke on you.
[SCHWI]
Over Boost!
[JIBRIL]
Hahaha!
[SCHWI]
Asyut Armor!
[JIBRIL]
Scattering the
elemental bones...
As a machine, I suppose you're
not very kind to the
environment, are you? However...
I might be able to do
something about that!
[SCHWI]
Your conviction is... unfounded.
(Jibril gasps)
[SCHWI]
Losen! Ender Apokryphen!
[JIBRIL]
Ohh!
[SCHWI]
Einweg.
I should continue my escape
until having reached a distance
where the Flugel cannot
detect me. That should work.
[JIBRIL] Oh, is that right?
(Schwi gasps)
[JIBRIL]
And just what do you have
in mind next?
[SCHWI]
Ah!
Uhh!
Uhh...
[JIBRIL]
Oh, dear. I thought I
was targeting the neck.
Perhaps my aim was
a little bit off?
[SCHWI]
Uh... Uhhh...
[JIBRIL]
Because obviously,
I can't imagine a machine
would have anything close
to resembling intuition.
Anyway, this is
growing tiresome.
All I need from you
is your adorable head,
The rest of you
I will bury in the dirt,
because that is exactly where
scrap metal belongs.
[SCHWI]
Keine Eintrag!
Uh.. Ugh!
Uh...
Riku...
I don't want to die...
I can't die.
We cannot fail...
because of me!
Ahh!
Ah... Ohh...
All I can do now...
All I can do...
All I can do for Riku is...!
(Crying)
[SCHWI]
My unique designation is
Uber Cluster Zwei Null Sieben
Peh Err Vier Funf
Sieben Teh Neun.
Requesting reconnection
with Einzig!
My analysis of the
human heart is complete!
I request synchronous
reconnection! Repeat...
[EINZIG]
You have been permanently
severed from the collective,
and your data has been judged
a source of critical error.
Your request has been denied.
[SCHWI]
That is out of code.
I dispute this refusal!
All Prufer reports and
analytical studies are
required to be sent to Einzig!
I strongly urge reconnection!
Reconnection is... is...
Einzig... No. Correction.
AH, NO!
They're mine, I'm not
sharing these with anyone!
[SCHWI'S INNER VOICE]
I love Riku. I don't want
to be separated from him.
This doesn't make any sense.
These errors I've
received from him,
are more than I can handle...
Your system is overloaded.
The data is essential
to the collective.
They're mine... They're all
mine and mine alone!
You can't just tell me
to hand them over!
Don't do this!
You have no idea what
you're asking me do to!
This is beyond your capacity.
Stop talking nonsense!
YOU CAN'T FEEL THESE THINGS!
(Signal drops)
(System powering up)
[EINZIG]
As calculated, your unit
is damaged.
[SCHWI]
I know...
[EINZIG]
The system is
contradictory and failing,
and yet still
manages to function.
This is an anomaly.
[SCHWI]
I know that as as well.
[EINZIG]
This status is not possible.
[SCHWI]
And yet it is.
It is the "heart" Riku gave me,
it shows me the truth!
[EINZIG]
In consideration of
said status...
It is deemed your unit
contains valuable sample data.
(Schwi gasps)
[EINZIG]
Initiating data synchronization.
Completion time is 251 seconds.
During which time,
further damage to your unit
is not permissible.
[SCHWI]
Alles Lesen.
Initiating the algorithm for
combatting unknown foes: Forme.
These emotions, this heart...
The life I received,
being born a machine...
I have 251 seconds
to survive...
So, I must...
bet it all!
[JIBRIL]
Are you trying to imply
something with those
gorgeous wings of yours?
A bit audacious, but brilliantly
constructed, my dear.
[SCHWI]
Schwi.
[JIBRIL]
Hmm? Pardon?
[SCHWI]
I never told you my name.
But that would be it.
It was a gift to me,
from the one I love.
[JIBRIL]
Oh, yes, where are my manners.
My name is Jibril. Pleased
to make your acquaintance.
But I'm afraid...
It is time for us
to say goodbye.
[SCHWI]
Do not play your enemies
at their own game.
And do not give them
the initiative.
Make them drop their guard.
Make them believe you're
an unworthy opponent.
No, make your enemies
keep their guard up.
Make them worry
about acting rashly.
If immediate action
doesn't fit,
then wait for the next move.
I can't die!
Not yet.
I cannot die!
Einweg!
(Gasp)
[JIBRIL]
Finally, a workable mistake.
You've caused me quite a
surprising amount of effort.
Mistake? What do you
mean by mistake?
(Signal breaking up)
[JIBRIL]
Allow me to explain...
I apologize for
calling you scrap metal.
It was shamefully crass, but...
I have deemed your presence
to be a threat
that needs to be eliminated.
You are an enemy worthy of
the full extent of my power.
(Signal breaking up)
(Signal restored)
[EINZIG]
Synchronization complete.
In this game...
victory goes to... me.
Losen: Keine Eintrag.
[SCHWI]
Riku.
Hello? Riku?
It's Schwi, and I...
I finally understand.
I... am so happy I met you.
And next time...
next time for sure...
we'll never be apart.
I truly love you.
(Young Jibril breathing heavy)
I didn't get her head!
Now the merchandise is gone...
And I used so much
of my energy,
that I turned into
this little thing!
What a waste of time...
Oh, this isn't worth
the trouble at all!
(Riku shaky breathing)
[RIKU]
I thought I could win
this time for sure...
so long as I had Schwi
and the others.
I don't know what cruel god
out there made us humans, but...
C'mon, please!
Just once!
Can't you let me win
just one goddamn time?!
Well?! If not...
(Sob)
why did you even give me
a heart to feel such pain?!
(Sobbing)
Schwi!
Schwi, why...?!
(Crying)
[SCHWI]
You have to stay alive
until I die.
[RIKU]
Oh... Yeah, that's right.
If my Schwi is gone, then...
what's the point anymore?
I have nothing left...
[EINZIG]
Spieler Riku.
[RIKU]
Huh?
Who are you?
[EINZIG]
I have no name,
but I shall call
myself "Einzig."
I am here to fulfill the wish
given me by the Preier,
the deceased called Schwi.
[RIKU]
Schwi?!
[SCHWI'S VOICE]
Rule number 2:
(Riku gasps)
You must let no one die.
The rules you came up with...
The conditions of failure...
They do not apply to
the loss of a tool.
the loss of Schwi.
[RIKU]
Huh...?
[SCHWI]
This makes check, Riku.
The rest is up to you.
[EINZIG]
Allow me to provide you with
some additional information.
[EINZIG]
First off: Given that
the various races
have gathered near the
Einweg installation points,
any movement on our part
will be immediately detected
by the Cluster,
with a 98% probability that
we will engage in battle.
Thus, only the 24 Einwegs
currently installed can be used,
meaning it will not be possible
to draw the energy downward
and into the planet.
(Riku angrily grunting)
However, it will be possible
to guide guide
the enegy southwest.
[RIKU]
Huh?
[EINZIG]
Second: We Ex Machina are
able to deploy weaponry
and this weaponry can be used
to analyze and replicate
any attack that is incurred.
Spieler Riku, you will take
control of this weaponry
and use it to drill
into the planet.
Allowing you to
manifest the Suniaster.
Ex Machina are but machines,
mere tools bereft of "heart."
We are designed to
complete a purpose.
And must carry out
the orders we are given.
As such... Now, Spieler Riku,
I shall aid you in your purpose.
Your orders, please.
(Riku sobs)
Schwi!
I understand.
The rules do not include...
the loss of a "tool."
Schwi! If this is
what you wish...
Then I wish to do
whatever you wish.
(Azriel laughing)
[AZRIEL]
Hm... That is just darling!
I never was a fan of the whole
healing procedure, nya!
It has been a long time since
I've seen you like this, Jibril!
But I still can't help but
wonder what the piece of
junk was up to.
Uh? Nya!
[FLUGEL]
Detecting multiple
heat signatures from
the aft side! It's...!
Nya! What is going on here?
Who had the never to
launch Heaven's Strike?!
[DWARF]
We've confirmed a preemptive
strike originating from
Avant Heim.
Prepare to launch the E‐bombs!
Fire the Aka Si Anse,
maximum output!
Aim for Artosh to starboard
and the Dwarven fleet
to the port!
A preemptive strike
from Avant Heim?
No.
This is...!
[AZRIEL]
Nya...
Those mechanical meownsters are
thumbing their noses at us...
Piles of scrap!
(Water boiling)
[FLUGELS]
Huh?
(Thundering)
[AZRIEL]
Lord Artosh!
[ARTOSH]
I have grown tired
of this charade
and now I must respond.
A being of all my power
shall confront the
attacks of the weakest.
Yes, you... monkey?
[RIKU]
The Heaven's Strike came
from behind Avant Heim,
fired in a way so that
no one was killed.
And as a result...
[EINZIG]
Cluster 11 is now in motion,
headed for Point Z.
[RIKU]
...all‐out war is on the verge.
[ARTOSH]
Take your positions.
[RIKU]
We're going up against
an Old Deus.
He will see right through
whatever plan we humans
come up with...
And be assured, he will
bring everything he has
to wipe us out.
That's how the
powerful think..
It's how they do things.
[ARTOSH]
The foolish know not
their place.
They are mindless apes
worth less than the dirt
under which they hide.
You can struggle,
but you will learn
that no matter how many
of you band together
and writhe upon the earth,
you are no match for the
strength of the heavens.
[THINK]
Fire the Aka Si Anse,
maximum capacity!
[DWARF]
Launch all E‐bombs!
[AZRAEL]
Heaven's Strike.
[RIKU]
Even the combined power of
the Aka Si Anse and the E‐bombs
could not stop the
enveloping fury of
Artosh's Heaven's Strike.
All of that energy will
collide and build into
a raging blaze...
becoming the brilliant light
that signals the end
of this world.
[THINK]
Uh?!
[RIKU]
And then...
(Think gasps)
[THINK]
It's turning away!
[RIKU]
All that energy...
[EINZIG]
We are machines,
tools bereft of heart.
We lived yet were never alive.
Let us die having lived!
Aus.
[EX MACHINA]
Jawohl!
[EX MACHINA FEMALE]
Cluster 11 has
incorporated 4,807 units,
and calculated emulation
and replication.
Synchronizing...
Losen.
I entrust you with Origin
Ein Und Null, The True Word,
the Starkiller: Stalemartyr.
[RIKU]
Okay then.
[YOUNG AZRAEL]
Ungh!
[RIKU]
That makes this a draw...
A stalemate!
(Think gasps)
[RIKU]
Sorry, oh you
so‐called "gods"!
The Suniaster...
(Riku inhales)
How many people have
died for this moment?
Schwi's comrades.
Life after life...
How many...
How many people have I
sent to their deaths?!
What have I done?
I was nothing but a fraud!
A con artist, gambling
with Schwi's spirit!
No... I can't...
I can't do this...
This can't possibly be a draw?!
(Gasp)
Oh...
Oh, Schwi!
I'm sorry, Schwi.
I lost.
Schwi...
If it could only be you and me,
the two of us together again...
Then next time, for sure,
I know we're gonna win, Schwi.
I know exactly how it would end
the next time around.
If gods can be born from our
very sentiments, then...
(Sobbing)
O God of the Game!
My life is worth nothing now,
but I'm offering it to you,
and for the first time in
my life, I'm praying to you.
I'm begging you...
that even if a loser
and a cheat,
someone who would steal
and fall into disgrace...
That even if these hands
are stained in blood...
Please! Please say it
all meant something!
That we meant something!
Anyone please!
Tell me you can put
an end to this war...
(Sobbing)
Please... take Suniaster.
(Gasp)
Uh...
(Laughs)
The hell?
So you were real after all.
Hey, let's play another game.
This time, I'll show you
that we can win...
Schwi and me, together.
Count on it.
[RIKU]
When I was a child,
I thought the world was a
much, much, simpler place.
I thought that there
was no challenge that
was unbeatable...
that if I tried hard enough,
anything was possible.
I thought I was seeing
the world with clear eyes.
And well...
huh... maybe I was.
[COURONNE]
Checkmate.
Right, Riku?
[RIKU]
If things are going well,
you think you could move
the white rook to E6 for me...
Couronne Dola?
Or I mean... Big Sis.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you so much...
for everything.
[COURONNE]
Riku... Schwi...
You two did something
truly incredible.
You put an end
to the eternal war.
And yet...
(Crying)
Why do I feel like this?
Why is it that I feel so...?
Why do I...
Why do I feel so cheated?!
[TET]
The game isn't over yet,
you know.
That may very well be check,
but it's not checkmate.
Hm? Still, if something
doesn't change...
Then we'll be locked in
a perpetual check.
Heheh! This is a first
for me, ya know?
It's ended in a draw!
[TET]
No one created you.
No one wished for you.
And no one asked for you.
Purely of your own will,
you went from beasts
to walking on two legs,
attaining knowledge and
becoming what you are today,
a nameless race.
But I, the One True God,
shall give you a name.
You are... Imanity!
[TET]
To all Exceed, the
self‐appointed "sentient races"!
First there was "Ascheito"
to honor the fallen,
then "Aschento" for
consent between the races,
but now you will use "Aschente,"
to swear upon the Ten Pledges!
As of this day, the world
will be forever changed!
Now let's keep this game going!
[IZUNA]
So, about that story...
How much of it was true and
how much was complete garbage?
[TET]
Oh, Izuna, if I told
the whole truth,
it wouldn't be an unspeakable
myth anymore, now would it?
[IZUNA]
Tet, you can be a real jerk,
you know that? Thanks.
(Tet giggles)
[IZUNA]
But well, I like how you
pet me, so I forgive you.
[TET]
Mm‐hm!
[SORA]
Izuna!
[SHIRO]
[TET]
Hm!
[IZUNA]
It's Sora, and Shiro,
and that nitwit, Steph.
[SORA]
Ahhaha! Oh, jeez,
where the heck did you go?
You really gotta look out,
there's a bunch of creeps
out there, you know!
[SHIRO]
Like you, you mean?
Or like me.
[IZUNA]
You beat me and just
took off, moron. Thanks.
[STEPHANIE]
They're absolutely right, Izuna.
There are no creeps in this
entire world worst than
these two right here.
Ah!
Huh?
Oh my God! What the heck
are you doing?! Ahh!
[SORA &amp; SHIRO]
Huh?
What is that writing?
It's Jibril.
Hi! Hello, hello.
[SORA]
Can you read this?
[JIBRIL]
Oh, it's an ancient language
from way back before Imanity
became one of the races.
[IZUNA]
Come to think of it,
most of our problems
are usually this
idiot's fault. Thanks.
Okay, let's see here,
it says...
Couronne Dola... Riku Dola...
and Schwi Dola...
"Couronne Dola"?
Yes! She was the
ruling queen of Elkia.
She was smart and full of joy,
and a bright soul,
who was never, ever
seen crying!
She was the pride of
the Dola family.
[SHIRO]
And who are the other two?
[STEPHANIE]
Oh, um... I have no idea.
[JIBRIL]
"Schwi", huh...?
That scrumptious little creature
was not a part of Imanity.
[IZUNA]
Mph...
I feel like I've heard
that name before. Thanks.
[SORA &amp; SHIRO]
Huh?
[IZUNA]
At least... I think so.
[TET]
As it turns out,
the world really isn't
all that complicated.
It's pretty simple, actually.
It's all just a game,
a very simple game.
'Course some will try
to make it difficult...
but you can handle them,
I know you it.
I know you can!
[SORA]
Now...
[SORA &amp; SHIRO]
Let's get this game started.