If there really is a
giant monster out there,
do you think they'll
authorize us to attack?
If this was a monster
movie, I guarantee
we'd be the first
to get killed off.
You know, curtain
raisers to set things up
till the main
character shows up.
Uh, that's not even funny, sir.
Whatever it is, we'll
find out soon enough.
(engines whirring)
(explosive noises)
(screaming)
(rumbling)
(thunder rumbling)
(yelling)
Didn't work, it's
just restoring itself.
What incredible
regenerating power.
It's all they can do to
keep it from coming ashore.
Well, at this rate,
I'll never get
through to Caster.
♪
Awesome, so awesome.
That is so totally
awesome, big guy!
The Lord has come.
The Lord has come!
♪
It's terrible, how could
this have happened?
In the long and winding
history of the Holy Grail Wars,
a foul up like this
is unprecedented.
According to our
observers' reports,
even though the Mion River
area is blanketed in mist,
a large number of onlookers have
already begun to gather there.
I fear we can no longer
handle this by ourselves.
We must petition the Mage's
Association for assistance.
(sighing)
What is Tokiomi doing right now?
My master left for
the scene with Archer
immediately after
Caster's monster appeared.
In that case, I will see to the
arrangements for the cover up.
Go to Tokiomi immediately and
assist him in any way you can.
I understand, Father.
♪
This sight has begun
to turn my stomach.
Mongrels though they may
be, they are still figures
of at least some slight renown.
Yet here they are working
together with all their might
to finish off that
disgusting thing.
Surely there are limits
to which one may sink.
Do you not agree
with that, Tokiomi?
♪
We must destroy that monster
before there are any more
witnesses to the battle.
The honor of the Tohsaka
family is at stake.
My king, that
monster is a vermin
that is ravaging your garden.
I humbly beseech you
to slay it yourself.
Dealing with pests is
the job of a gardener,
or is your intent to
mock my Noble Phantasms,
putting them on the level
of a gardener's hoe, Tokiomi.
I would never dream of such
a thing, but as you can see,
Majesty, this creature is beyond
the ability of the others.
It's the perfect opportunity
to demonstrate your true might.
I beg you, please take action.
♪
Hm.
(shouting)
(explosions)
It can't be.
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I've grown weary of watching
that disgusting creature.
No, King of Heroes,
wait, I beg you.
Tokiomi, I sacrificed
four swords
thinking it might
duty towards you.
Having been defiled by
touching that filthy thing,
I have no interest
in retrieving them.
Do not presume
upon my generosity.
You are the only
heroic spirit alive
able to defeat that thing.
Given its regenerative
abilities, the sole way
to defeat it is to
annihilate it in one strike.
Only your Sword of
Dissociation is capable
‐of accomplishing that so‐‐
‐You fool!
You dare suggest that
I draw forth Ea here!
Don't forget your place,
I should have your head
for being so impertinent
to your king!
I could use a Command Seal,
but if I did, it would shatter
my relationship with
the King of Heroes.
Father Risei and I had
originally arranged
for this Caster
hunting expedition
so that I could recover
the Command Seal I lost.
How could my plan be
backfiring so badly?
(whooshing noise)
Damn.
♪
What the hell is that?
There's a weird light hovering
in the sky at six o'clock.
It's not a helicopter.
Is it a UFO or something?
Control to Diablo One,
we need a situation report.
The situation is,
uh, well...
Diablo Two, gonna go down
to get a closer look.
Wait, Kobayashi!
Diablo Two, get back here!
Official inspection
from up close
will tell us what that thing is.
(screaming)
Kobayashi.
♪
Kobayashi!
A fearsome creature indeed.
It‐‐it ate it.
(evil laughter)
♪
Control to Diablo One.
What's going on over there?
Report!
Eyes, it has eyes.
It's absolutely
covered with eyes!
Eyes, what do you
mean it has eyes?
Shit, that thing
wants to eat me too.
Captain Ogi.
Diablo One engaging.
Wait, Ogi, engaging what?
I'll kill it before it gets me.
This is for Kobayashi.
I'm gonna pump you with
missiles, ya bastard.
♪
‐Berserker?
‐Oh man, what's he doing here?
You fool, stay down!
Now he decides to join us?
(growling)
♪
Isn't that...
Ah, so that mad dog
has turned up again.
This should be amusing.
(shouting)
My king, allow me to
deal with his master.
Very well, merely toy with him.
Then good luck to us
both, Your Majesty.
♪
(whooshing noise)
Dogs like you belong
prostrated on the ground.
Yet you dare to
climb into my sky.
Don't put on airs, you mongrel!
♪
Such impertinence.
How amusing.
I've not played a game like
this in quite some time.
For a lowly animal,
you're providing me
with no shortage
of entertainment.
♪
(breathing unevenly)
I hardly recognize you,
Kariya Matou.
Though you turned your
back on magecraft,
you still desired the Grail.
To think you'd slink back
in such a sorry state.
The very sight of you is
enough to invite whispers
that the Matou family
has fallen from grace.
(laughing)
Tokiomi Tohsaka,
answer me a question.
Why did you hand your daughter
Sakura over to Zouken?
What, you really
think that's what
you should be worrying
about at this moment?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
Do you even need to ask?
I did it because
I wished to give
my beloved daughter
a happy future.
You what?
All mages who have two children
eventually suffer for it.
The family's secret arts can
be passed to only one child.
They suffer over the
issue that one of them
must be cast down
into the common masses.
The simple fact is that my wife
is superior breeding stock.
Both Rin and Sakura were
born with equally rare
natural gifts and
magical abilities.
And so both my daughters
were in need of the protection
and nurturing attention
of a mage family.
For the future of one
daughter I must waste
the vast potential lurking
deep inside the other?
What father would wish
such a woeful tragedy
upon his children?
Common masses.
The memory of his children
and their mother on that day.
This heartless man
is writing it off
as something for
the common masses.
If I was to preserve the hopes I
had for both sisters' abilities,
my only option would
be to send one away.
That is why the Matou family's
offer was such a godsend.
If she were to be adopted
by a mage family,
it would give her that
much greater chance
of reaching the root.
A mage is someone who
is born with great power,
and before he knows
it, he will attain
even greater heights of power.
Even before a mage
embraces his destiny,
his responsibility to
do so is in his blood.
That is what it means to be
born the child of a mage.
♪
If I fail, it falls
to my daughter, Rin,
and even if Rin fails
in her quest, then Sakura
may yet fulfill the dream
of the Tohsaka family.
♪
You bastard, you want
them to fight each other?
Sister against sister?
Even if such a development
were to come to pass,
it is still best for the
future of my descendents.
What?
Glory will go to the victor,
and to the loser, honor to
the family of her forbearers.
The best outcome I could
possibly hope for.
You bastard, you're insane!
It is a waste of time to
try to explain it to you.
You don't comprehend
magecraft's grandeur,
and even turned your back
and walked away from it.
‐A lowly traitor.
‐Screw you, bastard!
(groaning)
(growling)
♪
(groaning)
I'll make all you bastards pay.
You filthy rotten mages.
I'll kill you all.
Zouken and you.
Every last one of you.
I'll kill you all.
When you turned down
the family leadership,
the Matou's magic secrets
were passed on to Sakura.
In spite of the fact that I
really should be thanking you
for my Sakura's future,
you are one man that
I simply cannot abide.
♪
The weakness revealed by
shirking of your obligations,
the deficient character
revealed by your lack
of indebtedness to it.
You, Kariya Matou,
are a disgrace.
Having crossed paths with
you again I have no choice
but to put you to death.
Don't talk so high and
mighty, you inhuman bastard.
You're mistaken, shouldering
one's responsibilities
is the first requisite
of being human.
It is those who fail to do so...
♪
...that are subhuman dogs.
‐Kariya.
‐Hear me now, bugs.
Devour this bastard.
Eat him alive!
Oh yeah, go get 'em, Bluebeard!
Crush 'em down, tear 'em apart!
This place is God's toy box!
Saber!
♪
I am much obliged, Saber.
(laughing)
I'll never be bored
again as long as I live.
I won't have to go through all
the trouble of murdering people.
They'll die in droves
without me lifting a finger.
They'll be flattened,
chopped to bits,
smashed, eaten.
They'll die and die
and die left and right.
I'll be able to see one kind
of guts and gore after another
that I've never seen before.
All day, every day,
all around the world,
everywhere I look!
It'll be nonstop, never‐end‐‐
(gasping)
♪
‐It stopped moving.
‐Hm?
(crowd murmuring)
What the‐‐hey, what happened?
(whimpering)
Huh?
(wind blowing)
That's so pretty.
Now I get it.
No wonder I never
realized it before.
Oh man, talk about
not being able
to see the forest for the trees.
It was in me.
I was looking for my own guts.
I didn't have to go
searching for it.
It was hiding right
there all along.
Ryuunosuke!
I finally found you.
I've been looking
for you my whole life.
What the hell, man?
If you were inside me all along,
I wish you would've
just told me so
in the first place.
(gunshot firing)
Ryuunosuke, my master.
How could you die and
leave me here all alone?
But never you fear,
dear Ryuunosuke,
for I, Gilles de
Rais, will fulfill
the solemn promise
I made to you.
♪
Ryuunosuke, watch closely!
Behold my offering to you!
I shall give you the
greatest "cool!" ever!
♪
I just put down the man I
believe to be Caster's master.
It looks like I was
right about him.
While all the other servants are
being distracted by the monster,
shall I eliminate
the next target?
Wait, Maiya, that's
no ordinary monster.
It's a creature with limitless
regenerative ability.
It's still possible
that it could reach
the shore before it dissipates.
If it does and begins
to feed, it's all over.
Caster will have a
new source of mana
to maintain his physical form.
If that happens, the damage
will spread even further,
and there's a risk
that the Holy Grail War
itself will break down.
Exactly.
But how do we kill an
indestructible monster?
The only way is to annihilate
it in a single strike.
To do that, its entire body
will have to be incinerated.
Leaving nothing, not even
the smallest scrap of flesh.
Anti‐Personnel Noble
Phantasms won't suffice.
An Anti‐Fortress one is needed.
Saber possesses just such an
Anti‐Fortress Noble Phantasm.
♪
However, because
of Lancer's curse,
she can't use it.
We'll just have to wait and see
exactly what they
can really accomplish
with their so‐called
chivalric spirit.
♪
Oh, this brilliant light!
‐You prolonged the inevitable.
‐The invincible king
is about to cry out the
true name of the miracle.
‐It is too painful to look upon.
‐Is he trying to kill himself?
‐We must stop its advance!
‐I'm counting on you, Saber.