Ah, Okeanos.
(snoring)
I have to ask, what brought
on this sudden outing?
Why are we going into town?
No reason, change
of scenery, that's all.
You've been whining
all the time about
wanting to see the amusement
district, haven't you?
The joy of window‐shopping
in a foreign land is every bit
as wonderful as
the thrilling joy of battle.
I feel really bad
for the countries
that got themselves invaded
for a stupid reason like that.
What is it, boy?
You sound like you
actually saw something
like that happen.
Never mind.
I was just thinking out loud.
♪
(nervous tittering)
No way.
This is horrible.
We worked so hard
to create this artwork!
How could they?
What kind of‐‐What kind
of inhuman monster
would so something like this?!
(sobbing)
Dear Ryuunosuke,
only a very select few
can fully comprehend
the immense importance
of true beauty and harmony.
To the vast majority
of common ignorant philistines,
beauty is but something
to be loathed and feared
and destroyed.
It is for that very reason
that we mustn't become
excessively attached
to our creations.
All things given form
and substance are destined
to one day break
and fade away.
It is therefore
absolutely essential
that we find joy in
the process of creation
instead of the creation itself.
So, whatever they break,
we should just make another?
Is that it?
Precisely so!
As always, my dear Ryuunosuke,
your understanding
of important matters
is your best virtue.
(sniffling)
Maybe we were just having
way too much fun and so God
decided to punish us?
Listen carefully to what
I say to you now, Ryuunosuke!
God does not punish humans ever!
He simply toys
with them, cruelly.
B‐‐big guy?
Once, long ago, I committed
spectacular atrocities
the likes of which
this Earth had never imagined.
Day after day,
I murdered and defiled,
yet no divine punishment
rained down on me.
Before I knew it,
eight years had passed
and my exploration
into the depths of evil
had been ignored.
In the end, it was not
God that destroyed me
and took away my life,
but rather the selfishness
of my fellow Man.
The church and the
state executed me,
not for anything wrong
that I had done,
but because they coveted
my wealth and my land
and wanted to take them from me
and make them their own!
What brought an end
to my evil deeds
was far from judgment;
it was simple theft
by a pack of criminals!
Uh, yeah, but, big guy.
There's‐‐there's
still a God, right?
Why ever would you think that?
You, who are without faith
and have never in your life
known a miracle.
Because the world
seems like it's so boring.
But then, the more you look,
the more you find all kinds
of neat and crazy
stuff around you!
I've always thought that way.
A world filled with so many
wondrous and amazing things
like this could never
have happened simply by chance.
If you set your mind
to enjoying it,
there's no better entertainment
than this unbelievable world!
I'm sure there's
a master entertainer
somewhere writing the story
of all five billion people
in this world.
If you wanted to describe
somebody like that,
what other name
could you possibly
call Him but God Himself?
Then, Ryuunosuke, do you
believe that it's possible
God loves humanity?
What do you mean?
He's head over heels.
I mean, if He's spending
every minute of every day
writing our story,
well, He could never do it
if He didn't love us.
In fact, I'll bet you
He's totally into it,
along with totally enjoying
the results of His own work.
He also loves all the things
that make humans look good,
like honor, courage, and hope,
and at the very same time,
He loves screams and blood
and utter despair just as much.
If He didn't,
there's just no way in Hell
the guts of living things
would be as cool and colorful
as they are.
So, I'm positive
the whole world
is filled to the brim
with God's love, big guy.
In this era of faithlessness
when the state has completely
abandoned the true will of God,
I had no idea that such
a vivacious new faith
had taken root and was
beginning to bear amazing fruit.
You have my admiration,
Ryuunosuke, my dear master.
Cut it out,
I'm starting to blush.
But wait, according
to your bold view of religion,
were not my blasphemies
nothing more than a silly farce?
Not at all.
You know, the best entertainers
will sometimes get
the most acclaim
of their careers
when they play
a really dark
and disturbed villain.
I think when you
get right down to it,
God probably loves
playing against
your cruel
and demented villain routine.
(crazed laughter)
♪
So both blasphemy and worship
are, in your eyes,
actually valid forms
of Godly devotion?
Oh, that's marvelous!
Truly, you are
the insightful bearer
of a brilliant
and important new philosophy!
A God who makes me a puppet
of man for His own sport,
and, at the same time,
is Himself but another clown!
I see; His vicious ways
finally make sense to me now!
Very well, then.
Let us go and paint
the gardens of
the puppet master God with
even more brilliant despair
and terror
and depravity.
We will show the author
of this wicked world
who hides up in Heaven that
God is not the only one here
who knows what entertainment is.
We're gonna do
something awesome again,
aren't we, big guy?
Cool, cool!
♪
All right, now.
I'll be in this
bookstore for a while.
(grunts)
As for you, you can
go do whatever you want,
but you're not to set foot
outside this arcade.
If I'm attacked and kicked
while I'm here, it's curtains
for you, too, understand?
Of course.
No conquering, Rider,
means no plundering either.
Huh?
Pay attention to me, dammit!
There's to be no shoplifting
and no eating without paying!
If you want something,
then pay for it with this money,
or am I gonna have
to use a Command Seal
in order to make you behave?
(hearty laughter)
Now, don't be rude.
Back in my day,
Macedonian etiquette
was the mark of a man of
culture in palaces everywhere.
I'm off.
Until later.
♪
(sighs)
"The king gave control over
the lands he had conquered
and the rights to
the taxes from those lands
to the local nobles.
He then mustered
his armies and marched off,
taking them further east."
Just like in my dream.
"He continued on his campaign...
♪
...because he wanted
to reach Okeanos,
the furthest ocean."
Hey, boy, where are you?
Ah, yes, here you are.
You know, you're so tiny,
you're impossible to see
between these bookshelves.
It was difficult to find you.
Normal people are smaller
than bookshelves, idiot.
Man!
So, what is it you bought?
Feast your eyes!
It just so happens that
the new Admirable Grand Strategy
videogame came out today.
First‐run, limited edition!
(laughs)
I suppose my luck must
be pretty good today.
You know, there's no
point is buying software
when you don't even
have a game console.
Yes, I took care of that.
Come on, boy, let's go
play in two player mode!
I bought us each a controller.
I'm not interested in low‐class
entertainment like that.
It's stupid.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you constantly trying
to narrow your own horizons
instead of broadening them
to the fullest you can?
Don't you ever get the desire
to seek out something fun?
Shut up.
If I had spare time
to waste on that,
I'd spend it all on a search
for truth rather than‐‐
So, what was it you found
so interesting on this shelf
over here?
Was it this one?
Well, I'll be,
this is a book about me!
You are a strange boy,
I am right here in
front of you every day.
If you wanna know
something, just ask me.
All right, fine then,
I'll ask you!
According to the description
of this history book,
you were really short back
when you were first alive.
So, how come you materialized
here in such an enormous body?
Huh, it says that I was tiny?
I've always believed
that you should never
completely trust what's written
in a book when you don't know
the person who wrote it.
(hearty laughter)
Wait a minute,
you mean to tell me
you're not mad
they got it all wrong?
Huh, no, it doesn't
really bother me.
That's strange.
Throughout history,
the people in charge
have always tried their hardest
to make sure future generations
remember them.
I suppose having your name
recorded in the history books
is a kind of noble immortality.
But if that means my name
and nothing else gets passed
down for two millennia,
I would have preferred
to have...even a hundredth
of that added to my life.
So, then...it's true
that you died in
your early 30s?
Hmm, yes, that one's true.
Oh.
Hey, big guy!
Get going out there
and show us some cool gig
that's gonna shock
even God, okay?!
You may look forward
to it, Ryuunosuke!
It will be the greatest "cool!"
you have ever seen in your life!
Seriously?
All right, I can't
wait to see it!
Uh.
(chanting)
(roaring winds)
Oh, yeah, something
really awesome
is gonna happen here,
I just know it!
Hey, why are you
being so quiet, boy?
Hmm?
It's nothing, I was
just thinking about
how boring you are.
What, you were?
See, you are bored,
just as I thought.
Just quit whining
and play this game with me.
That's not it!
You see, with a servant like you
who's practically
guaranteed to win,
I couldn't take pride
in winning the grail.
It would have been a lot
better for both of us
if my pact had been with
Assassin instead of you!
Mmm, I don't think that would
have worked out for you at all.
I think by now,
you'd be deceased.
Well, that's fine!
If I'm going to die
fighting in my own battle,
I'm not going to complain!
That's the reason why
I decided to join the Grail War,
and now...
I really don't know
what to tell you, boy.
If the wish you have
for the Holy Grail
was something that impressed me
in some form or manner,
I would be far more inclined
to enthusiastically obey
your every whim and desire.
But if all you want it for
is to add a few centimeters
to your diminutive stature‐‐
You have no idea
what you're talking about!
You don't need to be
in such a hurry.
Nobody said that
the Holy Grail War
would be the single
most important event
of your entire life.
There will be others.
What?
When the day finally arrives
that you find a way to live
that you can truly be proud of,
you'll be forced into
your own grand battle,
one that you will have to fight
whether you want to or not.
You will have plenty
of time, then,
to look for your battlefield.
I'm saying that I'm not
the only one here
who isn't satisfied
with this pact.
Mmm?
You don't like it
any more than I do, right?
Having me as your
sworn master, I mean.
You'd have been able
to win this war easier
if only you'd sworn
your allegiance to
a different master, right?
(sighs)
Probably, yes.
♪
Take a look, boy.
You see, you're looking at
the real enemy that I'm facing.
Now, try to draw
a picture of the two of us
standing alongside this enemy.
Draw it so you can tell
the difference in our sizes.
Wait, what do you mean, that's‐‐
Impossible, right?
Compared to the enemy
that we're about to take on,
you and I are the same,
just little dots.
What point is there
in trying to compare our sizes?
That is exactly why I'm excited!
The weakest and the smallest;
that's just perfect!
With a body tinier
than a poppy seed,
I will someday overtake and
even surpass the entire world!
Nothing can ever stop my quest,
for in my chest beats
the invincible heart
of the King of Conquerors!
So, what you're saying
is who your master is
makes no difference.
No matter how weak I am,
it really doesn't matter
one way or the other to you?
Now, where did you
get that stupid idea?
(grunts)
That miserable complaining
nature of yours is a sign
that somewhere
inside you is a conqueror.
No matter what you
want me to believe,
you are acutely aware
of how small you are
and yet, in spite of that,
you still struggle
to reach heights
greater than you could
ever begin to imagine.
It's not a compliment;
you're making fun of me.
Indeed, boy.
Face it, you are a stubborn
and incorrigible idiot.
Your deepest desires
are far greater than yourself.
Like they say, glory lies
beyond the horizon.
Back in the world
that I lived in,
that was the fundamental
rule of a full life.
Is that why you kept rushing
towards the east all the time
like some kind of idiot?
Of course, that's right!
I wanted to see Okeanos
with my own eyes, but, alas,
my glorious dream
was never realized.
Huh?
You never saw the ocean
like in my dream?
Even now, boy,
Okeanos remains
the place I strive for.
It is a never‐ending dream.
That sea in my dream
was really an image
of the heart that Rider
has been dreaming.
Laugh if you like.
I, who after 2,000 years
still dream the same dream
about a place he's never seen,
am a great fool.
So, you see, boy, a pact
with an idiot like you
is just perfect for me.
(gasping)
The river, I feel it.
♪
Can you see what is happening?
Could it be him, Lancer?
It is Caster, indeed.
He is positioned on the river
and is doing something;
however, I cannot
make out what exactly.
It's the perfect chance
to attack and put him down.
Agreed.
♪
If I can defeat Caster,
I can regain one of
the bonds with
Lancer that I lost.
I will go and engage him,
you stay here, Madam Sola‐Ui,
and bear witness
to the deeds I perform.
What do you mean?
But I have to go,
I'm a master now!
I'll be by your side.
You mustn't, Madam.
You do not understand
military matters
as Master Kayneth does.
That river will
become a deathtrap.
Please understand.
But, I‐‐
Unless, perhaps,
you still harbor doubts
as to where the true loyalty
of Diarmuid actually lies,
that he would fight
to serve his own ends?
♪
Lancer, go fight as you will,
I leave field decisions to you.
Fight the battle freely
and without any regret.
I am in your debt.
♪
If you return victorious,
I hope you'll grant
me a smile, Lancer.
(tires screeching)
Caster.
This incredible outpouring
of mana from him
leaves me no doubts.
Caster is in the process
of casting some
incredible magic.
Hmm?
Greetings and welcome,
Holy Virgin!
I am incredibly overjoyed
that we find ourselves
together again.
You just never learn,
you monster!
What is it you're
trying to do here?
I'm terribly sorry,
my dear Jeanne,
but you're not the guest
of honor this evening.
But if you care
to join us in our revelries,
it would give me
the greatest pleasure
and fulfill the deepest
wishes of my tortured soul.
At this banquet
of death and decadence
that I, Gilles de Rais,
have prepared!
You are welcome to come
and eat your fill and be sated!
(snapping noises)
And now, once again,
we raise the blood‐soaked flag
of salvation!
(rumbling)
Unbelievable, Caster
is being absorbed?
You who are
abandoned gather here!
I shall lead you,
I shall rule you.
The resentment and rage
of we, the oppressed,
shall reach onto the lofty
throne of God Himself.
God in Heaven, with
words of condemnation,
I praise Your holy name!
What in the world?
Oh, eminent God!
Oh, cruel God!
We shall pull you down
from your throne!
(thunder rumbling)
♪
Hail, King of Knights.
King of Conquerors.
Now, just wait a minute,
we're calling
a truce for the night.
We won't be able to have
any kind of meaningful fight
unless we deal with that
behemoth Caster created.
I have been going around
informing everyone
and Lancer has agreed to come.
He should be here
any minute now.
Understood, we will
fight alongside you.
Our alliance will be short,
but let us pledge our loyalties.
Hey, Einzbern,
you guys got a plan?
We haven't faced Caster yet
and Lancer told me
you fought him already.
What do you think
we should do?
Just defeat him
as quickly as we can.
That horrid monster
is maintaining itself
in this world
by using Caster's mana,
but if it gets
its own food source
and starts to become
self‐sustaining...
We must stop Caster before then!
Yes, I follow you.
We need to settle this
before it manages
to come ashore
and begins to feed itself.
The problem is Caster's
encased himself deep inside
those thick walls of flesh.
I'm not sure what to do.
Drag him out,
that's the only way.
If we can expose
his noble phantasm,
then my Gáe Dearg can destroy
the spell with one strike.
Lancer, do you think
you can strike Caster's
noble phantasm from the shore?
If I can just see it,
it'll be child's play.
Then Rider and I will act
as the advance guard.
Acceptable, King of Conquerors?
That is fine.
My chariot has no need
of roads, of course.
But, Saber, how are you going
to attack the enemy
in the river?
My body has been blessed
by the Lady of the Lake.
Water cannot stop me,
however many fathoms
deep it may be.
Oh, very impressive.
That is quite a rare skill.
I want for you to serve under
my command even more now.
You will pay for your words
some other time, but for now,
we need to drag Caster out
from within that monster
and destroy him.
(laughs)
Indeed, then I
shall take the lead!
Let us begin!
Yah!
(screams)
♪
Saber, good luck.
Let's finish this, Caster!
Now!
♪
Oh, yeah, go get 'em, Bluebeard!
A foul‐up like this
is unprecedented.
You dare suggest that
I draw forth Ea here?
Saber!
King of Heroes, wait, I beg you.
A fearsome creature, indeed.
Every last one of you,
I'll kill you all!