♪
Aniplex.
(electricity zapping)
♪
I am Iskandar, the
King of Conquerors!
In this battle
for the Holy Grail,
I am of the Rider
Class of Servants.
(whimpering)
Wh‐‐what the hell
are you thinking
announcing yourself that way?
You idiot!
Ow!
Ow...
♪
Fate has brought us
all together in this place
to do battle for the
possession of the Holy Grail.
But first, I wish to make
a proposition and offer.
What think you of
yielding the Holy Grail to me
and joining my glorious
and invincible army?
You will be treated
as honored allies,
friends, and brothers in arms!
Together we shall share
in the glory of battle
and the joy of world conquest!
♪
Hm.
I'm afraid that I
must decline your offer.
As tempting as
that offer may be,
I may give the Grail
to but one man.
My new avowed lord and Master.
And not to the
likes of you, Rider!
Tell me, Rider.
Did you come here
and interfere
with our battle, rudely,
merely to proffer
that ridiculous
and laughable plan of yours?
This is a grave offense
against my honor!
Hmm.
I'd be willing to
discuss compensation.
Enough!
Hm.
And further,
I am the rightful
king of Britain
and not merely
a knight of the realm.
I could never lower
myself to mere retainer,
even to a mighty king!
Ooh, you are king of Britain?
That is quite a surprise!
I would hardly have
expected the King of Knights
to be a little girl.
(snarls)
Then would you like to taste
of this little girl's blade,
King of Conquerors?
(sighs)
I suppose
negotiations have failed.
Such a terrible waste.
A truly awful shame.
Rider!
♪
I can't believe it.
That moron nearly
conquered the known world?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
So, you were the one
who did it, huh?
(gasps)
I'd been wondering
what twisted madness
had invaded your psyche
and compelled you
to steal my relic.
(laughs)
I never even imagined
that you yourself
had being planning to
enter the Holy Grail War.
Waver...
Velvet?
(gasps)
Now I know you're
not experienced
in these matters.
How would you like me to
offer you a private lesson?
What it really means for
mages to kill one another?
I'll teach you all
about the fear and pain
involved in such
noble endeavors.
You should feel honored.
(whimpering)
(gasps)
Hm.
Mage who is speaking now,
do I understand correctly
that you believe you
were to be my Master
rather than this boy
I'm sworn to serve?
That whole idea is
absurd and laughable!
Only one brave enough to openly
ride onto the battlefield
standing at my side could
ever hope to be my Master!
A coward who lacks sufficient
courage to show himself
is nowhere close
to being worthy of me!
(laughs raucously)
♪
Of course, there
are also others!
They're out there skulking
in the darkness, watching us!
What are you
talking about, Rider?
Saber and Lancer,
the skills and bravery you
showed were impressive!
Your duel was magnificent!
Surely the sound of your blades
and the fury of your battle
called other Heroic Spirits
here to bear witness
and glean knowledge
from your encounter.
Heroic Spirits,
born again through
the Holy Grail,
gather here and now!
Those too craven and cowardly
to show themselves here tonight
will draw the vicious
scorn of Iskandar,
King of Conquerors!
♪
Kirei.
Yes?
This is not good.
Not good indeed.
♪
Oh no, that's him!
The Servant that
defeated Assassin?
♪
So, two lesser beings
dare to name themselves kings
even in my royal presence.
I fail to see where
the problem lies, Servant?
For I am Iskandar,
the legendary King
of Conquerors
known through all
the lands of the world.
What nonsense!
You're deluding yourself!
I am the one true
king of the world!
All others are mongrels!
Pretenders to the name!
If you are that
insistent of your claim,
then why not name yourself?
No true king
should be troubled
by something as simple
as giving his name
to those he wishes
to challenge.
So, you would question
me, you filthy mongrel?
Me, the one true king?
If you cannot now
discern my identity
in the presence of
my magnificent glory,
then your ignorant blindness
will serve to seal your doom!
♪
I see now.
That is how he killed Assassin.
♪
That is his Noble Phantasm.
(laughs)
♪
Kill them all.
(roars)
Berserker?
So, King of Conquerors,
are you planning to
ask him to join too?
Perhaps not.
He doesn't seem
terribly interested
in civilized negotiations
of any kind, does he?
Hey there, boy.
How powerful a Servant
is this monster, huh?
I don't know.
I can't really tell.
What do you mean, boy?
Are you not a Master
chosen by the Holy Grail?
You're supposed to be able
to sense all their strengths
and weaknesses,
aren't you?
(whimpering)
I can't tell anything.
That black thing is
definitely a Servant,
but I can't read its
status or anything else!
Hmm.
It appears you'll be facing
another difficult enemy.
Yes, so it seems.
That spirit has some
curse or other ability.
It fully conceals nearly
everything about him.
But that isn't all.
With four other
Servants present,
we have to be very careful.
Why did he materialize here?
No sane Master
would ever choose
to send their Servant out
here under these circumstances,
certainly not right into
the middle of all this chaos.
Maiya, keep watching Assassin.
I'll look for
Berserker's Master.
♪
Who gave you permission
to look upon me?
You rabid dog.
♪
May your death
provide me some modicum
of entertainment, mongrel!
(explosion)
♪
Good God!
Is that truly Berserker?
For a madman completely
devoid of a soul or conscience,
huh, he is rather nimble.
Huh?
Come now.
Couldn't you tell what he did?
That black thing casually
snatched the first blade
that was flying
toward him out of the air
and used it to deflect
the second spear.
♪
You dare lay your filthy hands
on my precious treasures.
You must long for
a painful death, cur!
♪
No way, that's impossible!
All right now, mongrel.
Let us all just see how
long your parlor tricks
can keep you alive now!
♪
(battle sounds)
(explosion)
♪
(clattering)
Fool...
I belong among the heavens,
yet you would have me
trod upon the ground?
Your impudence has
guaranteed your death!
Mongrel!
When I am through with you,
nothing will
remain of your corpse!
♪
Gilgamesh is serious.
He plans to open the Gate
of Babylon even further.
Repeatedly exposing
his Noble Phantasm
to all the others.
Very rash of him.
Your decision, my Master.
♪
By the power of
my Command Seal.
King of Heroes, quell
thine anger and withdraw.
♪
You dare to order
a king to withdraw,
to leave the fight undone?
You have much nerve, Tokiomi!
♪
You were fortunate, mad dog.
You mongrels!
By our next meeting,
see that you culled
your numbers!
Only a true hero is worthy
to look upon my
glorious presence!
♪
Hm.
It would seem
that Archer's Master
has much less fortitude
and is far less
courageous than he is.
(gasps)
(rattling)
(roaring)
(explosion)
Irisviel!
Get back!
(explosion)
(roaring)
♪
What?
(roaring)
♪
(grunting)
So that's what it is.
Whatever he grabs
onto with his hands
becomes his Noble Phantasm.
♪
Saber!
(roars)
♪
Hey, Maiya,
have you gotten any visual
on Berserker's Master?
No, I haven't.
♪
This looks bad.
Damn.
♪
What are you, monster?
(snarling)
(grunting)
(battle sounds)
♪
(roars)
That's quite enough messing
around for now, Berserker!
You see, Saber has
a prior engagement.
If you insist on interfering
with that obligation,
you'll have to face me.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is your chance to defeat
Saber and take her out of play.
My Master!
I, Diarmuid,
will defeat Saber!
I swear it upon my honor!
If you insist
I kill her here and now,
then I will first defeat
that mad dog Berserker!
Please, my Master,
let it be so!
With my Command Seal,
I order you.
My lord!
You are to help
Berserker kill Saber!
Now!
♪
(battle sounds)
Lancer!
♪
(panting)
(footsteps)
♪
Sorry, Saber.
Irisviel, listen!
I shall hold them here!
While I do that, you
must leave this place
as quickly as possible!
Run!
Get as far away as you can!
Irisviel, please!
Run away!
It's all right, Saber.
Please believe in your Master!
♪
Kiritsugu is here?
Kiritsugu,
I know that you can
still turn this to a victory!
♪
All right, I'll kill
Lancer's Master now.
It's the only way
out of this situation.
Maiya, proceed with your
attack of Assassin on my mark.
Suppressive fire.
Right, acknowledged.
♪
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
(lighting
(Rider shouting)
Rider?
(explosion)
Ah, this Servant is quite
a tough one, isn't he?
Well, as you can see,
our dark malevolent friend
will be retiring
for the evening.
Master of Lancer!
I know not from whence
you are watching,
but do not sully a
battle between knights
with your petty tricks!
Have Lancer withdraw.
If you insist on
humiliating him further,
then I shall join
Saber against him.
And I assure you
that together
the two of us will
annihilate your Servant.
What will it be?
Fine; Withdraw, Lancer.
That's enough for tonight.
My thanks, King of Conquers.
It was nothing.
The flowers of a
battlefield must bloom.
I must know.
What was your purpose
in coming here,
King of Conquers?
Well, honestly, I try
not to think too hard
about such things.
Saber, first settle matters
with Lancer and battle.
And then, I shall face
the victor of your contest.
Be it you or Lancer.
Well, King of Knights,
goodbye for the moment!
It was a pleasure,
and I sincerely hope
to enjoy our next meeting
as much as I did this one.
Hey, boy, don't you
have anything nice
to say to the lady?
Hm?
♪
I really do wish
he'd man up a little.
Oh, well.
♪
(whip crack)
Fare thee well!
(oxen bellowing)
Saber!
Your left arm!
Yes, it was a painful blow.
It is as Rider says.
If I fail to deal
with Lancer first
and undo the curse
on this wound,
it will damage my chances
against the other Servants.
♪
Thank you, Saber.
I survived thanks to you.
The reason I could focus
on the battle before me
was because I had
you to stand behind me.
Saber.
The battle is only
beginning, Irisviel.
Tonight we saw the opening
gambits have an epic battle
that is only just
beginning to unfold.
♪
I know.
They were all
powerful adversaries.
Not one of them was
a conventional enemy.
So this is the Holy Grail War.
(laughs)
He turned and ran
like a cowardly rat
away from my Berserker.
(laughs)
And I also got to embarrass
that stupid arrogant ass.
Tokiomi, how I wish
I could have seen
the look on your face.
(laughs)
(coughs, vomits)
♪
(squeaking)
That damn Berserker
broke free of my control
and started fighting Saber.
Bastard!
If he keeps doing that,
my body won't last long.
But if I can
control him,
I can win.
♪
Just hold on, Sakura.
Begging your pardon,
Master Kirei.
What is it?
Master, I've come to
report that I've found
something of interest
outside the church.
A familiar?
Yes.
It was outside the barrier.
But it was clearly
sent here for the purpose
of monitoring this church.
♪
Awesome!
That was so awesome!
Hey, Bluebeard!
That was all real, right?
Right?
It was for real!
Not some kind of cool
special effect, right?
So awesome!
So, about this Grail War,
you're gonna do it, aren't ya?
Right, big guy?
Ah...big guy?
My wish has come true.
What do you mean by, uh,
wish come true?
(whimpering)
♪
Look at her!
The answer to my prayer!
Her extraordinary face,
her strong and noble bearing!
She is none other than
the maiden of my dreams!
The one perfect
woman in the world!
(weeping)
♪
You know this chick?
Yes indeed!
She was forsaken by God!
Died in abject shame and
terrible loneliness and now,
at last, she has
come back to life!
It is such a miracle!
What else could it be
but the fulfillment of
all my hopes and dreams!
Oh, maiden.
My holy virgin!
Soon I will come for you!
♪
I will bring you Saber's head.
The next strike
will be real!
Aren't you the one
who is mistaken here?
Let's have our guest
enjoy the magical workshop
of Kayneth El‐Melloi.
You dare sit there
and lecture me?
I have come for you,
my sweet and holy virgin!