♪
(panting)
(waves sloshing)
♪
What are we gonna do now, Rider?
Hmm.
♪
So what now, Mad Dog?
(yelling)
♪
(groaning)
Tokiomi.
♪
I'll kill you, bastard.
(yelling)
(whooshing)
♪
Saber!
They can't make it through.
♪
If only Saber could
use her left hand.
♪
Hey, Saber!
We're not getting
anywhere like this!
Let us withdraw!
Don't be a fool!
We must stop its advance!
That may well be, but
we're in a stalemate!
Just fall back for now!
I have an idea!
(whooshing)
Listen, everyone.
Whatever strategy
we devise tonight,
we first need to buy
some time to organize it.
For the time being,
I will drag that beast
into my Ionian Hetairoi,
but it will be impossible
for my elite troops to slay it
even if they
attack in full force.
The best we can hope for
is to halt its advance
within the Reality Marble.
And after that?
‐No idea.
‐Huh?
After swallowing
something as big as that,
my bounded field and
its army will only hold
for a matter of mere minutes.
In that short time, we must act.
Heroic spirits, I want
you to find some way
for us to prevail.
Boy, disembark!
You're staying here with them.
Huh?
Hey!
Once my reality
marble is deployed,
I will not know what is
going on in the outside world,
and so if anything happens,
concentrate and call to me.
I'll send a messenger to you.
♪
Saber and Lancer,
the rest is up to you.
‐Right.
‐Understood.
Yah!
(mooing)
♪
(growling)
You only prolong the inevitable.
♪
(dog barking)
Mom!
♪
What is that?
(screaming)
♪
(grunting)
How does plunging headfirst
into that filthy creature
sound to you, you mongrel?
♪
(growling)
After all that raging
and ranting against me.
When it comes time to act,
this is all you can do?
(grunting)
Is he trying to kill himself?
Kariya, consider
this an act of mercy.
(speaking foreign language)
(yelling)
I can't kill you.
I'll kill you.
Tokiomi...
(gasping)
(groaning)
(screaming)
What now?
I know he said he'd
buy us some time,
but if we don't think
of something really fast,
We'll be right back
where we started.
Come on now, Einzbern.
Don't you have any ideas?
Say something!
(cell phone ringing)
Wait a minute.
I don't know how to use this.
Iri.
Um, no, I'm‐‐wait, who is this?
Ah, well, you must
be Rider's master.
Good timing.
There's something I
wanna discuss with you.
Who‐‐who are you?
That's not important.
Caster's disappearance‐‐I gather
that was your servant's doing?
That's right, basically.
Question‐‐Rider's reality
marble, when he releases it,
can he put down the
contents in a specific area?
To a point.
He can get within 100
meters or so, I think.
It should be possible.
Rider has control over where
he enters back into this world.
Good enough.
When the timing seems like it's
right, I'll send up a flare.
Release Caster
directly underneath it.
Can you do that?
I can, probably, I think.
One more thing‐‐give
this message to Lancer.
Tell him Saber's
left hand contains
an anti‐fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
(beeping)
Something the matter?
Well, he asked me
to give you a message.
Saber's left hand has an
anti‐fortress Noble Phantasm.
♪
Is this true, Saber?
I see.
Do you think it's capable of
obliterating Caster's monster?
I believe so.
But Lancer, my blade
and my pride are the same.
This wound you inflicted on me
is a mark of pride, not shame.
If that loss was the price
of securing Diarmuid
Ua Duibhne's aid,
then it was worth
a veritable host.
♪
Listen, Saber,
I cannot abide this Caster.
He finds the despair of
others both right and good
and takes pleasure
in spreading terror.
On my word as a knight,
his is an evil that I
cannot let go unchallenged.
♪
Lancer, no, you mustn't do that!
Must it be Saber who is
victorious today or Lancer?
No, it is neither of us.
What must triumph here today
is the path of chivalry.
Agreed, heroic Arturia?
(snapping)
(wind blowing)
♪
Lancer.
I entrust our victory
to the single strike
of the King of Knights.
I'm counting on
you, brave Saber.
♪
Rest assured, Lancer.
Upon my blade, I will prevail!
♪
That is from the
Arthurian legends.
♪
Saber!
Berserker?
Why now?
♪
(gun firing)
(growling)
You dare turn your back
on me, you lowly mongrel?
Blasphemy!
What?
(exploding)
Saber!
What the hell does
Berserker think he's doing?
I've finally regained the use
of my left hand and now this.
♪
(grunting)
Regardless of its own
self awareness of this fact,
a soul instinctively
seeks out joy in its life.
He was the only one
you ordered Assassin
to investigate
thoroughly enough
such that you could
understand those circumstances.
And this was due to your
unconscious interest in him.
♪
(spluttering and groaning)
(screaming)
♪
Still too soon.
What are all these tremors?
An omen that Rider's
reality marble
is approaching its
limits, I imagine.
♪
Come, Rider.
I am Mithrenes,
Soldier of the Hetairoi.
I have come here to act
as my king's eyes and ears.
♪
Tell him to wait for our signal,
then release the bounded field
and dump Caster at
the designated location.
Can you do it?
We can, sir, but it will
be a race against time.
We of the Hetairoi
are no longer able
to slow the progress of that
horror within the bounded field.
I understand that!
I know!
♪
Damn that Berserker!
Can't we do anything about him?
Allow me.
Lancer!
♪
I am putting an end
to this mad warrior!
(growling)
♪
It's all or nothing.
Archer!
♪
(gun firing)
There it is!
‐Right under there.
‐Yes, sir.
♪
(crashing)
Finally‐‐what took
them so damn long?
♪
Oh.
(mooing)
♪
All right now, Saber,
show me your best!
I shall judge your
worth as a heroic spirit
with my own two eyes!
♪
The light.
It shines bright.
It is the true embodiment
of the sad yet noble
dream of all soldiers
past, present, and
future who lie dying
on the fields of battle,
clutched to their hearts
with their last breath,
holding aloft their dying wish,
making certain that their
loyalty will not be in vain.
The invincible king is
about to cry out the true name
of the miracle she
wields in her hands.
♪
That name is...
Excalibur!
(whooshing)
(whimpering)
This brilliant light!
There is no doubt,
this is the light
from when Jean
and I were blessed
with such profound joy!
(whimpering)
(gasping)
What...have I...
(exploding)
(waves crashing)
Did you see that,
King of Conquerors?
Such is Saber's brilliant skill.
Having seen such light,
you still refuse to
grant her your respect?
Hmm‐‐that light is a result
of her accepting
the hopes and dreams
of the people of her time.
It hurts me because
it's so bright.
And because I know
that this burden
was thrust upon the
shoulders of a little girl.
What I see is what
became of a girl
who was never allowed
to admire butterflies
or flowers or fall in love,
but was instead taken hold
of by the curse of ideals.
It is too painful to look upon.
Which is exactly what
makes her so endearing‐‐
the unattainable
dream she held so dear
was certain to explode
in a brilliant flare
that would burn her to ash.
The tears of bitter
lamentation she shed,
how sweet they'd have tasted
as she laid there dying.
You and I will never get along,
Babylonian King of Heroes.
Really?
You only now realized that fact?
What are you going to do, Rider?
Perhaps give vent to your
righteous anger here and now?
It would give me great
pleasure were I to do so.
But if you and I
were to do battle,
it would mean expending
more energy tonight
than I would care to.
Of course, if you were to decide
that you couldn't pass
up the chance to attack,
I would be forced
to respond in kind.
This once, I shall
allow you to escape.
There would be no
satisfaction in crushing you
if you were not in your prime.
(laughing)
Or is it that you
yourself are injured
from being shot down by
that ridiculous lunatic?
I respond to
provocation with death.
We'll save it for next
time, King of Heroes.
Ours will be the epic battle
that will determine
who is the champion
of the Holy Grail War.
♪
Don't be so certain.
I have yet to decide
if there is but one
who is worthy of the gift of
my greatest treasure, Rider.
You glorious fool
who strives to achieve
that which man was
not meant to have.
In all of Heaven and Earth,
none but I, Gilgamesh,
can truly appreciate
your destruction.
♪
You who shine so
brightly yet so briefly,
come to my arms.
This I have decided.
♪
I am first Bure of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Saber, I am glad I
was able to meet you.
Splendid‐‐for this night,
Arturia Pendragon
accepts your challenge.
‐Come then!
‐I come for you!