♪
(motor rumbling)
Irisviel.
♪
(honking)
Have I lost them?
If I can't see them anymore,
then I'll sense them.
♪
A chariot?
I have you now, Rider.
♪
Hey, Rider, check it out!
Doesn't it seem like
she's following us?
Well, well, if it
isn't Saber herself.
This saves us having
to search for her.
Hey, boy, tell me something.
Motorcycles don't usually
travel that fast, do they?
A motorcycle, that thing?
No, no way, that's impossible!
Of course, with
Saber's skill at riding,
we don't really
know what it can do.
This will be fun!
Well, I will also
have to do my part
to make this exchange
with her interesting.
Huh‐‐we're going down?
Change of plans.
I shall use an ordinary race
to settle things with the girl.
♪
Yah!
Whoa!
I'm okay, but just try
and be careful, okay?
(laughing)
Don't worry!
Nothing in heaven or on Earth
can stop me from
being victorious!
Yah!
♪
This is bad.
I'm reaching the
machine's limits.
At this rate...
and I'm so close.
♪
Invisible Air!
No way.
♪
She's closing the gap!
She's gonna catch up to us!
Ha‐‐a mechanical
contraption like that
going so fast is splendid!
But this is a battle
chariot we are riding.
It's a fair race, but
it needn't be polite!
(yelling)
This is what you get if
you want to chase Iskander!
♪
(gasping)
Excellent!
You really are the
proud King of Knights.
Truly the beautiful
flower of the battlefield!
♪
Do not underestimate me!
(yelling)
♪
Rider!
Prepare yourself!
♪
(grunting)
Irisviel isn't here?
Impossible.
That was definitely Rider.
So then where is she?
(gunshot and crying)
Did you really think
you could trick me
by imitating a servant?
Rider's master lacks
the intel‐gathering skills
to have found that place.
Tohsaka could not possibly
have attacked in his state.
And so, by process
of elimination,
only the Matous could
have abducted Irisviel.
(ripping and panting)
Answer me, where is Irisviel?
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Then where is Kariya Matou?
Kariya?
I have no idea
where that fool is!
(gunshot and crying)
I don't know‐‐I really
don't know anything!
He left this morning
with some guy
who said he was the
overseer from the church!
♪
Did you see Overseer?
Hmm.
♪
Kirei Kotomine.
I didn't expect the real Rider
to suddenly appear there.
Truly a fortuitous development.
You seem to have been
blessed by good luck.
It favors you on the
battlefield, Kariya Matou.
Father, was this deception
really worth the use of two
of my three command seals?
You don't need to
worry about that, Kariya.
Now, hold out your hand.
♪
As long as you work with me,
you may use your command seals
without the
slightest hesitation.
Hmm, very impressive.
A transformation
ability of all things.
(yelling)
His Noble Phantasm
is far too good
for someone of
the Berserker class.
There are lots of
stories of him succeeding
by disguising himself
as another knight
in pursuit of some heroic deed.
Even with the command seals,
this is the best result?
Your servant's obsessive
fixation on Saber
is awe‐inspiring.
Enough, be gone Berserker!
♪
This woman, is she really
the vessel for the Holy Grail?
More accurately,
her insides are.
Don't worry about
a thing, Kariya.
As promised, I shall gladly
give you the Holy Grail.
But before that, there
is the other promise
you made to me, Father.
Oh, that‐‐
everything is arranged.
At midnight tonight,
go to the Fuyuki Church.
You will find
Tokiomi Tohsaka there.
♪
Don't forget, now, Kariya.
Tonight at midnight, your
wish will be fulfilled.
♪
Now then, I've sent Kariya away.
I don't know who you are,
but I suggest you
show yourself now.
(laughing)
Ah, you sensed me.
You are indeed a
veteran inquisitor.
So you're Zouken Matou.
That's correct.
Rider, are you sure?
We're really going to
attack from right here?
From this range?
Straight ahead?
The sword of light we
saw her use against Caster
has a delay before activation.
We'll strike then.
Why would you do
something so crazy?
Precisely because it is, boy.
If she loses after all this,
her defeat will be bitterly
devastating and complete.
She may even change her mind
and decide to be
my vassal after all.
You wanna win her that badly.
Right now, on the battlefield,
she is like a star
fallen down to Earth.
Only as a part of
my glorious army
will she truly be able to
shine in her full brilliance!
♪
In all his campaigns,
he was never interested
in his opponent's
power or wealth.
Without destroying
or degrading them,
he sought to rule
their very souls,
thus was he the
King of Conquerors.
Very well, Rider.
Win by whatever means you wish.
Boy, it seems you are
finally beginning to understand
the meaning of conquest.
♪
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let us go now!
(speaking foreign language)
Wind!
♪
(yelling)
Ex...
♪
...calibur!
(whooshing)
♪
What is it you
want, Zouken Matou?
(laughing)
Well, to tell you the truth,
I was quite interested
to see what sort of clever
deception you would employ
to destroy Kariya.
You would let the Matous's
chance at victory slip away?
(laughing)
Actually, the sheer pleasure
of watching Kariya suffer...
is something I
shall never tire of.
Victory for the Matous
or a miserable end for him,
it's a difficult choice.
Hmm.
So, you enjoy watching
your own flesh and blood
suffer like that.
Indeed.
I would've thought
that you of all people
would understand that sentiment.
How so?
Well, you give off exactly
the same scent as I do.
♪
That of a hungry,
wiggling little maggot
irresistibly attracted by
the rotting meat of Kariya.
Oh, scary, scary!
You are truly a
dog of the church.
I tease you at
my own peril, eh?
I can assure you
that we shall see each
other again, young one.
By the next time we meet,
see to it that you've
allowed your true nature
to fully ripen, so that
you and I might fight
on an equal footing.
♪
Hmm.
Rider?
(gasping)
I'm sorry, boy.
I screwed up.
Rider, use Ionian Hetairoi!
The chariot is all I
will use against Saber.
I understand, but still.
(tires squealing)
Wait, she left.
A motorcycle‐‐hmm.
It's magnificent.
What the hell?
Those are your first words
after she's defeated you?
‐By the way...
‐Huh?
...how are we supposed
to get back to town?
Well, I suppose
we'll have to walk.
I was afraid of that.
♪
How many more days do I have?
How many more times can I fight?
♪
But I can't die now.
Not yet.
♪
(crashing)
Tokiomi Tohsaka!
(grunting)
So did you think you
killed me, Tokiomi?
Well, you blew it.
Until I make you pay for that,
I'll keep coming back to...
Tohsaka!
♪
What?
Kariya?
(gasping)
Aoi?
No, wait, it wasn't me!
He was...
(thudding)
(whimpering)
Are you satisfied now, Kariya?
Now that Matous are sure
to win the Holy Grail War?
But I‐‐I didn't.
Why?
Ripping Sakura completely
out of my life wasn't enough?
Of all the cruel
things you could've done,
you had to kill him
right in front of me?
Why?
But he‐‐it was all his fault!
If it weren't for what he did,
no one would've
ever had to suffer!
You, Aoi, or Sakura!
‐You could've had a happy life!
‐You shut your mouth!
What could you‐‐
what could you
possibly know about it?
You...
you've never...
(crying)
You've never loved
anyone in your entire life!
There was someone I loved.
She was warm and kind.
I wanted her to be
happier than anyone else.
For her, I would
lay down my life.
That's why I've endured
this pain until now.
Endured, endured,
endured, endured,
endured it all!
I can't let her deny
everything I've been through.
A lie, a lie, a lie,
I do have someone‐‐
there is someone in
this world that I love!
Who did I do this for?
Whose fault is it?
If I'm going to die,
I may as well!
(birds chirping)
(choking)
(gasping)
(panting)
(screaming)
Hmm, it was trite
and full of clichés,
but still, I have to say,
not bad for your first script.
Well, Kirei?
What are your impressions?
♪
It seems the taste
of wine changes
far more than I ever expected.
(chuckling)
Well, then I believe that
you're finally beginning to know
what it means to
expand your horizons.
♪
If it will taste as
wonderful as this has,
then I would dearly love
to sample it once again.
♪
Waver Velvet orders you!
Keep your eyes open to the end!
For tonight, I
shan't be holding back.
I'll just out‐maneuver
and eliminate him quickly.
How do he and I differ?
If he does not doubt,
then what is he?
If I'm here, who am I?