♪
Aniplex.
My apologies for
keeping you waiting.
As you can imagine,
things have been
rather hectic this evening.
(laughs)
I'm sure it
couldn't be helped
given the
extraordinary situation.
It's going to be
rather difficult
to cover all that up.
Well, perhaps.
What has happened
is far too much
for the holy church
to handle by herself,
and so we are
accepting any
and all aid proffered
for assistance
in this effort.
Now the,
down to business.
Regarding my request,
I'm curious as to what
your decision is, Father.
I speak, of course,
of the reward offered
for Caster's defeat.
(singing in Japanese)
♪
This is wonderful.
Once I receive
the command seal
for killing Caster,
Diarmuid and I
will finally be truly
connected forever.
(slice)
(gasps)
(screams)
My right hand!
It's gone, it's gone!
I need it or I...
I cannot call Diarmuid,
I won't be able
to make him care for me.
My right hand.
My right hand,
my right hand,
my right hand!
Hand...
my right hand.
(thump)
Success.
I have secured Sola‐Ui
over in New Town.
I removed the command
seals in her right arm.
Fine.
Get out of there immediately.
Lancer should be
returning any time now.
Roger.
(gun clocks)
(gun shots)
♪
I saved Kariya Matou.
Without doubt, he could
threaten my master.
There is no excuse.
This is an act of rebellion.
But what is this I'm feeling?
It is not regret.
Could it be...
that I'm excited
about this?
Of course, it's true
that in the defeat
of the Servant Caster
and his master,
the Servant Lancer
played an important part
in the overall
conduct of the battle.
A fact varified by
a number of reports
from various observers.
Then it's clear.
As master of Lancer,
I have the right
to receive one
of the command seals.
It's not that simple.
Lord Kayneth Archibald...
I am unsure whether
it is at all inappropriate
to consider you
a master at this point.
Father, my pact
with Lancer
was from the outset
executed jointly
by myself and my
fiancee, Sola‐Ui.
And is Sola‐Ui not the one
currently supplying mana
to the servant?
And is she not also
acting as defacto
caretaker for
the command seals?
Yes, that's true.
I've temporarily
given her custody
of the command seals.
However, the rights
accorded by the pact
still legally reside with me.
After all, Father,
the petition I submitted
to the church to be
considered a master
was filed in my name
and did not include Sola‐Ui.
Very well, I agree.
Your rights as a master
shall remain intact.
Now, Lord Archibald,
extend your hand, please.
♪
Take this and
drink from it.
This is my blood,
the blood of the
everlasting covenant
which will be poured
out for you
and for all mankind.
Do this in my memory.
♪
(laughs)
I hope you will
continue to fight
a noble battle
for the Grail
as a worthy master.
Yes, of course, Father.
(gunshot)
(wheels squeaking)
I'm down to
a single command seal.
My situation
remains dire.
I cannot allow
the other masters
an opportunity to acquire
an additional seal,
not if I intend to
possess the Holy Grail.
(door bangs)
Mistress Sola‐Ui.
You complete incompetent!
You useless bumbling fool!
You couldn't even
protect a single woman
from being attacked?!
Huh.
I'm sick of all
your talk of chivalry.
I am grievously
sorry, Master.
She may have been
a mere substitute,
but you even failed
to protect your own master
from nearly being killed!
What good are you
as a servant, I ask you?
I'm amazed you had
the unmitigated nerve
to return here alone.
Please understand,
my master.
Mistress Sola‐Ui
and I never entered
into a proper pact,
and as such we could not
sense each other's presence.
That's no excuse.
You should've taken
special care to ensure
her safety.
My master, fret not.
Mistress Sola‐Ui yet lives.
She continues
to supply me with mana.
That's irrelevant!
You are not her servant.
And therefore you can
not discern her location.
So it doesn't matter
in the least whether or not
you know if she's alive.
Oh, Sola‐Ui, I should've never
given you those command seals.
I could not
dissuade her, Master.
I share in the
responsibility.
I really can't believe
you had the nerve
to say that.
Don't try fooling me, Lancer.
It was you who
encouraged Sola‐Ui
to become ambitious.
I would never
do that, Master.
It's just as it
was in the legend.
Are you truly incapable of
seeing your Lord's fiancee
without attempting
to seduce her?
My master...
please retract
those words right now.
Have I struck
a nerve, Lancer?
You're nothing but a beast
who swore an oath of
eternal loyalty to his master.
And then gave into
prurient lust
when the moment
suited him.
My master.
My lord.
Why will you not understand?
Master, I wished only
to defend my honor,
to fight well
in noble battle,
and achieve victory
on your behalf.
Don't you ever speak to me
in that manner, Servant!
Understand your place.
You're nothing but
a spectral ghost,
granted form and
substance by magic.
You dare to sit there
and lecture your master!
It is absurd
and unacceptable!
If you are so dissatisfied,
I believe you have
but one option available.
Use your precious pride
to resist my command seal.
You'll never win.
You servants are
mere puppets,
and this seal the string
that controls you.
Lord Kayneth.
Master.
What now?
Don't tell me,
you still have
something to say to me?
No.
That isn't it.
Something's approaching
this building.
(car approaches)
Look, Saber, it's just
as Kiritsugu said.
There are traces
of a magical barrier,
but it's very strange.
It hasn't been
properly maintained.
It's already starting
to... fall apart.
I did not expect
to see you here, Saber.
Well, my...
allies found this
place and informed me.
They said that this
was your location.
You would not happen
to know where my master's
betrothed is,
would you, Saber?
My master has not
heard from her.
No, I do not.
What of it, Lancer?
Never mind, forget it.
Anyway, are you
sure about this?
I am certain you did
not come to engage
in idle chit‐chat?
After all, you must
be completely exhausted
after employing that
technique against Caster.
No more so than all
the other servants.
I'm certain.
None of them will be
fighting further tonight.
They will focus
on defense.
That is why we needn't
worry about being interrupted.
Dawn is nearly upon us.
But this may be
the best night
for us to finally
finish our battle.
What say you, Lancer?
Hm.
Brave Saber.
The only thing in
this world that still
grants my heart peace
is your honor
and the purity
of your fighting spirit.
(sword clinks)
♪
(metal clanks)
Her attacks
are too weak.
♪
Saber, why?
You will not use
your left hand?
Don't get the
wrong idea, Lancer.
If I use my
left hand here,
the shame is certain
to dull my blade
against your
powerful spear.
A dulling such as
that would be fatal.
Saber.
Therefore, Diarmuid...
(whips blade)
...this is my best strategy,
the path that will
allow me to defeat you.
(laughs)
Pride is in the
blade of chivalry.
Saber...
I am glad I was
able to meet you.
♪
I am first Bure of Fianna,
Diarmuid O'Dyna.
I come for you.
Splendid.
For this night,
Artoria Pendragon
accepts your challenge.
♪
Come then.
Why does he not win?
If he has no certain
path to victory,
should he not escape
with his master instead
of risking defeat?
Right now our highest
priority should be
to locate and rescue Sola‐Ui.
Why can't he not
understand even
that simple concept?!
He's a useless servant!
(metal clatters)
♪
(metal clanks)
Why him?
Of all people?
♪
This is...
a Self‐Geis Scroll.
A powerful magical
item that has been used
throughout the ages
to forge an absolutely
unbreakable pact between
one mage and another.
"Binding spell.
Affected party,
Kiritsugu Emiya.
The crest of
the Emiya family
orders the following actions:
the pledge is to be
obeyed by the affected party
upon fulfillment of the
terms described herein.
Pledge that Kiritsugu,
son of Norikata,
fifth heir to
the house of Emiya
will be forever
forbidden from harming
Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald
and Sola‐Ui
Nuada‐Re Sophia‐Ri,
or from intending
to, by his hand,
harm or injure them
or cause them pain
in any way whatsoever.
Terms.
In principle, the curse
of the Geis cannot
be removed by any means
known to the mage world.
Even if you forfeit
your life, as long
as the magic crest exists,
it will bind
your soul
even in death."
It's true that if
I do what's written
on this scroll,
he cannot kill me?
But under these terms,
my fight, the fight
for which I prepared
my entire life...
will end here.
The Grail.
And the Archibald
family pride.
He asks me to
throw it all away?
♪
(gun cocks)
(gasps)
(cries)
Sola‐Ui.
(loud squish)
♪
Use your remaining
command seals
to compel your servant
to commit suicide.
The terms of the
agreement have been met.
(Lancer growls)
You wanna win!
You wanna win
so desperately.
You desire the Grail
so desperately,
you have crushed‐‐
you have crushed
my sole remaining wish.
And you just stand there!
Do you not feel
any shame at all?!
I will never forgive you.
I will never
forgive any of you!
You inhuman monsters
who have ruined
the honor of a knight.
Let my blood taint
your dreams forever!
May the Grail be cursed!
May the wish it grants
bring disaster!
And when you fall into
the searing pits of hell,
you'll remember the
hateful rate of Diarmuid!
So now the Geis binds you?
Yes, it is sealed.
I can longer kill
you or Sola‐Ui.
♪
(gunshots)
I can't, but...
(whimpers)
♪
Kill me.
Kill me now.
Sorry.
Our pact forbids me to.
♪
(slices)
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I finally recognize
you as the lowly beast
that you are.
I believed that our
paths differed,
but we shared
a mutual goal.
I was a fool
to think this.
Until now, I placed my
faith in Irisviel's words,
and thus did not
doubt your intentions.
But now...
I can no longer believe
that your desire for the Grail
has anything to do
with salvation.
Answer me, Kiritsugu!
What is the true reason
you desire the Grail?
Even should my sword
at the end of this war
win the Grail.
If that means I must
yield it to you, I must...
Answer her, Kiritsugu!
After everything
that has happened,
you owe her an explanation!
You know, this incident
is the very first time
you've seen how I kill, Iris.
If you only eliminate
a master, the servant
may enter into a pact
with another party.
So I had to eliminate
the master and the servant
simultaneously.
No, Kiritsugu.
Not to me.
Talk to Saber.
She's the one who needs
to hear your words now.
No.
Honor, glory...
there's really no point
in speaking to a killer
who extols the
virtue of such things.
You would even insult
chivalry to my face, monster!
A knight cannot
save the world.
Knights call certain
methods of fighting good,
and others evil,
acting as if
there were some sacred
nobility to the battlefield.
Such illusions created by
heroes throughout history
have led countless
young men to their
bloody deaths,
all for the sake of
this glory and honor
they all extol.
They are not illusions!
Even the taking
of a life in battle
as an act as a human being
must have ideals,
otherwise every war
would bring the very
fires of hell to this world.
And there you go...
you heard her, Iris.
Our heroic spirit over there
considers a battlefield
to be better than hell.
What a joke.
A battlefield is hell itself.
There's no hope
to be had on one.
There is nothing but
unspeakable despair.
Just a soulless
cry we call victory.
Paid for by the pain
of the defeated.
But humanity has never
recognized this truth.
And the reason is that
in every era a dazzling
hero has blinded the people
with their legends and kept
them from seeing the evil
of bloodshed they bring.
True human nature
has not advanced
a step beyond the Stone Age.
Tell me this, Kiritsugu.
Do you force Saber
to endure such humiliation
because of your hatred
for the heroic spirits?
Of course not.
Personal feelings
don't enter into it.
I will win the Holy Grail
and save the world.
And I will wage
that war with the most
appropriate weapons
I have at my disposal.
Justice and righteousness
cannot save the world.
I care nothing
for such things.
Kiritsugu, don't
you understand?
If you do evil
to stop evil,
that rage and hatred
will give rise
to new conflict.
Kiritsugu Emiya,
I do not know
what betrayed you,
or what has caused
you to lose all hope,
but your sorrow
and rage are found
only in those who at one
time sought for justice.
Kiritsugu, in youth,
your true self,
wished to be
a hero, did it not?
A hero to save the world.
You believed in that.
You desired it
more than life.
Am I wrong?
♪
I will break this
endless cycle.
The Grail will make
that possible.
I'll ensure that the
blood I spill in Fuyuki
is the last that
humanity will ever shed.
If that means I must
stain my hands with
every evil in the world,
I don't care.
If that will
save the world,
then I do it gladly.
(car putters off)
Kiritsugu has left, hasn't he?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!
This cannot be allowed!
An alliance at this stage?
Let me tell you
the truth behind
the Holy Grail War.
Go and tell them
we accept to die
to make his dream a reality.
Such a boring end.
I'll see you soon, Father.