♪
(hooves stomping)
Rider, over there.
♪
Are you scared, boy?
Yeah, I'm scared.
I'm wondering if
this is what you mean
when you say that
your heart is dancing.
Hm, it seems you're finally
starting to understand.
♪
(engine rumbling)
The enemy is inside.
♪
(explosions)
Berserker?
(singing in Japanese)
♪
Are they having a party here?
Where is that little
chariot of yours?
Well, the thing is,
I'm embarrassed to say I
lost it to Saber in a battle.
Did you forget my decision?
I believe I told you
that I would fight
and defeat you when you
were at full strength.
True, the weapons at my
disposal are somewhat depleted.
However, Iskandar tonight
is less than perfect,
and thus, is far greater
than perfection itself.
So I see.
Indeed the aura that
is emanating from you
is unusually potent.
It appears you have come
before me actually believing
that you have a
chance of victory.
Hm.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
Our banquet's last question.
I shall allow it, speak.
Well, this is purely
hypothetical of course,
but were my Ionioi Hetairoi
armed with your Gate of Babylon,
it would create the most
powerful army imaginable.
Hm, so?
Why would you not
ally yourself with me?
The two of us together
could conquer the universe
and beyond if we desired it.
(laughing)
You never cease to
amuse me, mongrel.
It has been ages since I
laughed so hard at gibberish
spouted by one
who is not a fool.
But unfortunately,
I have had one comrade
and he is all I ever
intend to have.
Furthermore, there is no need
for there to be two kings.
The lonely path
of kingship, eh?
With all respect
due to a king,
I shall challenge your
strong unwavering spirit.
Very well, show me what
you think you can do,
King of Conquerors.
You are a usurper truly
worthy of my judgment.
(clank)
Are you guys actually
friends with each other?
I could hardly be
unfriendly to him.
After all, he may very well be
the last person I ever see.
Don't be stupid, you're not
gonna be killed here today.
I won't allow it!
Have you forgotten
my command seal?
You are right, ha.
You are exactly right.
Gather here, my
glorious comrades!
Tonight we shall become
the greatest legends
in all of eternity!
♪
Our enemy is the
mighty King of Heroes,
a most worthy opponent.
My warriors, let us show
the first heroic spirit
our noble path of
ultimate conquest!
(cheering)
♪
(shouting)
Come to me, Lord of
Conquering armies.
Now you will be privileged to
behold the sight of a true king.
(yelling)
(explosions)
♪
(breathing unevenly)
(groaning)
♪
Why are you suffering so much?
Because of Berserker.
He must fight a
battle right now,
and needs mana.
Why?
Because that priest said so.
‐That priest?
‐Yeah.
He made a promise to
me that he'd give me
the Grail once he got it.
If I have the Grail,
I can save you, Sakura.
You're going to save me?
Yeah, of course.
Remember, I promised that
we would all play together
like we used to with
your mom and sister.
Then I'll be able
to see Mother again?
See your mother.
♪
(screaming)
(gunfire)
♪
Ahhh!
(shouting)
Now.
♪
No good.
Can he see it?
♪
He knows the lengths
of my blade.
Could he be some
knight I once knew?
From your skill I assume you
to be a knight of some renown,
and so I ask, if you know
me to be Arturia Pendragon,
King of Britain and
founder of Camelot...
...name yourself right now
as a knight's pride demands.
Challenging me with
your identity concealed
is tantamount
to using deceit.
(growling)
(evil laughter)
Who are you?
♪
Impossible.
That's Arondight.
It can't be you.
(growling)
♪
(loud clang)
Sir Lancelot.
(growling)
But why, my friend?
You were esteemed as
the greatest of all
the Knights of
the Round Table.
How can you be Berserker?
(grunting)
Stop!
(shouting)
Lancelot.
(groaning)
You may indeed
have saved them,
but you never led them.
Because I never
really led them.
Enraptured by a false
idol of a humble king
who always serves others.
My ideals, my kingship.
You're just a little girl.
Did how I rule
drive you to this?
(snarling)
Please stop, Lancelot.
(army screaming)
Uniting dreams beneath
a banner of conquest.
I praise your
efforts at least.
But foolish warriors,
have you not learned?
♪
Dreams disappear when
the dreamer wakes,
every last one of them
with no exception.
♪
Therefore, it was
inevitable that I would be
the one to stand in your way.
King of Conquerors,
now know the end of
your eternal dream.
I shall show you
the stark reality.
Here it comes!
Now, awaken Ea!
A stage worthy of
you has been set!
♪
Look up and behold,
at my liege!
♪
Hang on, boy!
What?
(rumbling)
That sword is the
Anti‐Universe Noble Phantasm
that can destroy all creation?
♪
(crowd screaming)
Hm.
Rider.
I just remembered, there
is something important
that I must ask you.
Master Waver Velvet,
would you be willing
to serve as my retainer?
(breathing shakily)
♪
You...
...you are my king, sire.
I will serve
you with devotion.
Do me the honor of leading me.
Let me dream what you dream.
Ah, very well.
♪
As king, my duty is to
inspire others to dream,
and as my retainer, it is your
sacred duty to see my dream
to the end and share it
with future generations.
♪
Now live, Waver.
See all of this through.
Live long and tell
everyone you meet
of how your king
comported himself,
of the last charge of Iskandar.
♪
(cries)
All right, it is time
to go, Bucephalus!
(horse neighing)
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon.
Challenge the unattainable.
Speak of conquest
and make it real
for my men and for those
who watch behind me.
♪
(yelling)
(screaming)
♪
(clank)
(chain jingling)
Hm.
I swear to the gods, it
is just one strange toy
after another with
you, isn't it?
(grunts)
Have you awakened from your
dream, King of Conquerors?
I suppose I have.
However, once again,
during this glorious campaign,
my heart was able to
dance a good deal.
Feel free to challenge me
again as often as you like,
King of Conquerors.
This entire world is my garden
until the very end of time.
Thus, I guarantee you this,
it will never bore you.
It will always
be entertaining.
(sighing)
(waves crashing)
That sounds very good.
Now I see.
It was the beating of my heart
that was the sound
of Oceanus' waves.
(sniffling)
♪
Child, are you Rider's master?
No, I'm not.
I am his retainer.
Hm?
I see.
But child, if you are truly
a loyal subject to him,
your duty now is to avenge
your fallen sovereign.
♪
If I challenge you, I'll die.
Yes, of course you will.
I can't do that.
I was ordered by
him to survive.
♪
Your loyalty is splendid.
Never allow anything
to tarnish it.
♪
(crying)
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in paths
of righteousness
for his name's sake.
Yea, though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
Thou preparest a
table before me.
Thou anointest
my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and
mercy shall follow me
all the days of my life.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and
mercy shall follow me
all the days of my life.
♪
You would steal the
Holy Grail from me?
What're you doing, Saber?
What a difficult
person you are.
It's impossible, the Grail
longs for a life of its own,
‐longs for its own birth!
‐Welcome home, Daddy!
I knew you would
come, Kiritsugu.