♪
Aniplex.
What of Rider's
Noble Phantasm?
Equal to that of
Gilgamesh's Gate of Babylon.
In other words,
too powerful
to be given a rank.
Hmm.
It all ended exactly
as we planned.
If we'd gone against Rider
without this new knowledge
and unprepared,
we would not have been
able to defend ourselves
against him.
♪
This will begin
the second stage.
We will use the information
Assassin gathered for us
to have Archer
defeat our enemies
and in the process,
discover the means
to defeat Rider.
Yes.
Thank you for your
fine work as a Master.
♪
It is my belief
that last night's attack
involved all of
the existing Assassins.
Understood.
By the way, Maiya,
where are we with our
new base of operations?
Tomorrow morning.
I will take Saber
and madam there.
Good, thank you.
Of course, goodbye.
(paper rustling)
No sign of movement
at the Tohsaka residence.
Since Assassin's attack
on the very first day,
Tokiomi hasn't
left the building.
An unsettling silence.
♪
Matou Master
appears undefended,
an easy target.
But...
(metal smashing)
(explosion)
Berserker's strange
special ability
suggests that he
should be left alive
to distract
Archer and Tohsaka.
Lord El‐Melloi should have been
removed from battle already.
But Lancer still remains.
We must discover his
new Master's identity
as soon as humanly possible.
Caster's location
remains unknown.
But last night
several children
vanished from
this city again.
They continue
their atrocities
with no apparent
plan whatsoever.
♪
Rider and his Master
are constantly on the move.
Tracking him is difficult.
However large‐hearted
he may seem,
he is a dangerous foe.
Furthermore,
I'm quite concerned
about the Ionioin Hetairoi
that Maiya reported.
♪
But more importantly...
Is it safe to
assume that Assassin
has been
completely destroyed?
In that case,
his Master...
♪
If his plan was
to work with Tohsaka,
using Assassin to
spy on the others,
then he should have never been
able to leave Fuyuki Church.
But that isn't
what happened.
His ambush at
the Fuyuki Hyatt,
his attack in
the Einzbern Forest,
both actions
defy explanation.
♪
Of course it all fits
assuming he was after me.
But why, why pursue me?
Two days ago,
he should have had no way
of knowing for certain
that I am Saber's Master.
♪
Kirei Kotomine,
who are you?
(door opening)
♪
(snicker)
You seem to be in rather
fine sprits today, Archer.
I still see little
value to this Grail.
But even if it
is trash, that's fine.
It seems I found
another form of pleasure.
Here in this world that
you've constantly mocked
for being vile and
full of imposters.
That remains unchanged.
However, I am now curious
to see this Holy Grail War
through to its end.
I am fond of lives
full of hubris.
Those who harbor
grand ambitions
but are unequal to the task.
The mere sight
of such people
gives me great enjoyment.
There are two
kinds of arrogance,
one where you are
unequal to the task
and one where your
dreams are too big.
The former is just
commonplace stupidity.
But the latter
is a rare species,
difficult to find.
But they are identical in
that both kinds are fools,
are they not?
Isn't the
foolishness of the few
a more precious commodity
than the wisdom of the masses?
There are those
that are born human,
but harbor wishes that
man was not meant for
and have renounced their
humanity in its pursuit.
I simply never grow weary
of watching their
grief and despair.
Kirei, what of you today?
For once, you seem
almost strangely pleased.
I'm simply relieved.
I've finally been freed from
a most unpleasant burden.
What becomes of the Command
Seals once they disappear?
According to theory,
Command Seals ultimately
return to the Grail.
And the Holy Grail repossesses
the unused Command Seals
from any Master who
has lost his Servant
and has withdrawn
from the war.
Also, if for whatever reason
a Servant loses its Master,
the Grail will
give those seals
to a newly chosen Master,
assuming one can be found
before the war is over.
The Command Seals stay
a part of this world
until their use.
At the end, any
remaining seals
are given to the
overseer for safe keeping.
So, depending
on what happens now,
a new Master may yet appear
and enter the
fight for the Grail.
Possibly.
But the Holy Grail does
not deem many on this Earth
to be worthy of that role.
Thus, when a replacement
Master is sought,
the Grail tends to
select one of those
whom it had
previously considered
and deemed suitable
for participation.
♪
What's the matter,
continue with your talk.
Go on.
There is an unspoken
reason that the Holy church
gives asylum and
protection to those Masters
who have left the war.
In the event a place should open
among the remaining Masters,
there's a high probability
that any unpaired Masters
will receive the
Command Seals left behind.
This is why Grail War
Masters try to kill
rather than injure or
temporarily incapacitate
enemy Masters.
Well, then from
that perspective,
is there not a good chance
that the Command Seals
will be given to you again?
Impossible.
If as Tokiomi
has always suggested,
the Holy Grail
only chose me
as a support mage
to the Tohsaka team.
I have fulfilled that
duty and am finished.
Tokiomi already
possesses a winning strategy
for dealing with the remaining
Masters and their Servants.
There is simply nothing
more for me to do.
If I may opine,
Tokiomi's hypotheses have
been dubious from the start.
He has never struck me
as a man truly fit
to be backed by the power
and prestige of the Grail.
I must say, I am surprised
that you have such harsh words
to offer regarding
your own Master.
Kirei, you seem to be mistaken
as to who serves whom
in my relationship
with Tokiomi.
He is treated
civilly as my vassal.
And he supplies me
with mana as an offering.
I answered his
summons precisely
because those were
the terms of our pact.
I'm curious, what do you make
of the Command Seals then?
I hate them, but if
a vassal is trying
to become a better vassal,
I don't mind listening to
a differing opinion or two
from time to time.
By the way, Kirei, you
mentioned earlier that Assassin
had fulfilled all his missions
before he was destroyed.
What of the
matter we discussed?
You mean your interest
in learning the motives
of each Master for
desiring the Grail?
Yes, they completed
that investigation.
I should have had an
Assassin present the report
to you in person last night.
That would have
saved me the trouble
of having to‐‐
No, this is better.
I'm not interested in what
that walking shade has to say.
Kirei, this report
is meaningless to me
unless it comes
directly from your lips.
Hmm.
(car motor humming)
How does it feel
to drive a car, Saber?
Do you like it?
Yes, I think this is
a splendid vehicle.
I can not help but wonder
what would have happened
had these existed
back in my time.
Irisviel, are you certain
it is all right with you
that I drive this vehicle?
You seemed to thoroughly
enjoy the act of driving
when we were out
the other night.
No, this is fine.
If you're happy
driving the car
then I'm happy, too.
I have to say,
the skills of a Servant
are absolutely amazing.
This is your first time
touching this machine,
yet you're driving
it perfectly.
Oh, thank you, but I'm finding
the sensation somewhat odd.
It's like
I'm employing skills
I was taught
a long time ago
that were buried deep
within my memory.
Rather than understanding
it intellectually,
my body instinctively
knows what to do next.
(cars zooming)
Still, do you really
think this is a wise idea?
The estate that is to be
our new base of operations
lies precisely in the heart
of the main battlefield.
Don't you worry about that.
Because secrecy is the
hallmark of the Grail War,
the Tohsakas and Matous
have openly established
fortifications in the city.
The Einzberns are unusual
for building that castle
in such a distant location.
On the contrary, this
new base that Kiritsugu
has secured might
be more advantageous
than the castle
we'd been using
because its location is
unknown to the others.
(cars zooming)
(birds chirping)
It's another
very unusual building.
From now on, this place will
be your base of operations.
Ah, if you can take
those for me, Saber.
Yes, of course
I can, Irisviel.
Maiya, what does
this key open?
It appears quite
different from the others.
It's for the
storehouse in the yard.
It's fairly old,
but I've confirmed
that is is solidly built.
There was really no
time for preparations,
so this may be somewhat
lacking as a proper residence.
That's fine‐‐for now
so long as it keeps
us out of the rain,
that's sufficient.
(engine starting)
Now then, come on, Saber,
let's go and
explore our new place.
Yes, let's.
I think this is like one of
this country's haunted houses.
I'm sure all the hallways
have wooden floors
and the room's floors
are woven grass
with nice partitions
made of paper.
(giggle)
I told him once I wanted
to see a Japanese mansion.
Maybe Kiritsugu
remembered I said that.
Is our new base of operations
not what you expected?
No, it's not that,
I like it well enough,
but this isn't really an
ideal base for a mage.
There are a few things
that could be better.
The magical barriers
are well laid out,
but for a workshop it's‐‐
well, when it's this
open to the outside,
the magic has lots
of ways to leak out.
I would have preferred
a more secure room
walled off with
stone or clay.
Ah, this is ideal!
(footsteps echoing)
It's a bit small,
but I'm sure I can
craft my spells in here
just as well as I did
back at the castle.
Perfect.
Inscribing the
magic circle here
should be good enough
to make it my own.
All right then, let's
get started, shall we?
There's a lot
of work to do.
Will you help me, Saber?
We'll draw a magic
circle right there,
six feet in diameter.
Right.
I'll need your help most
once we start to
craft the mercury.
And don't worry,
I'll tell you exactly
how to do it.
Will you do me a favor?
Could you bring
in the ingredients
we left out in the trunk?
Irisviel, I must
ask you something.
It seems all day today,
you've acted as if
you've been carefully
avoiding touching anything.
Have I been imagining this?
Driving the car,
holding the keys.
Those matters by themselves
would not have
caused me to worry,
but now it is
beginning to appear
as if you're not even going
to handle your own magic.
If you were not
feeling well today,
it is important that
you tell me about it.
It is my duty to
ensure your safety
whenever it is necessary.
So I must know
if anything is wrong.
You're absolutely
right, I'm sorry.
I couldn't
keep this hidden
for very long anyway.
Your hand?
Saber, I'm going
to squeeze your hand
as hard as I can using all
the strength I can, okay?
All right, go ahead.
Irisviel?
Are you sure you
are not pretending.
I know it's weak, but this
is all I can do right now.
Just touching your fingers
is the most I can manage.
Grasping something
or picking it up
is beyond me.
Dressing this morning
was so difficult.
♪
But, but what is
the matter with you?
Have you been injured?
No, I'm just not
feeling too well.
So I've disabled
my sense of touch.
Just shutting down
one of my senses
allows me to control
my power quite a bit
and it means that
I can continue
to do everything
else I must.
Being able to
do things like this
is the specialty
of a homunculus.
But Irisviel, that simply can
not be all there is to it.
What exactly is
wrong with you?
Should you not
go see a doctor?
What if it's serious?
Perhaps you may
have forgotten, Saber,
but I am not in any way
a normal human being.
If I happen to catch a cold,
I can't even go to the clinic
like everyone else does.
I suppose you could
say my condition stems
from an inherent
flaw in my creation.
Don't worry about it.
Of course what this means is
I'm going to
need for you to do
a few things for me.
From now on, I'll need
you to drive the car
like you did today.
And you'll have
to help me set up
and perform my
magical rituals.
I'm sorry, but I'll
be depending on you,
my brave and gallant knight.
Yes, I'll help.
I apologize for
prying into the details
of your private life.
Forgive me.
It's really okay.
Now, why don't we get
started on that circle
before it gets too late.
If I rest in
a magic circle
that's connected
to local lay lines,
my condition will improve.
At least it should
start to a little bit.
Understood.
Then I shall retrieve
the materials right away.
With regards to Lancer's Master
and Ryder's Master,
they appear to have
no wish in particular
that they plan to ask for
should they happen
to win the Holy Grail.
They simply seek victory as
a means to win glory as mages.
Now then,
as for Caster's Master,
he seems to have
no real understanding
as to what the Grail is.
He is only taking part
in the Holy Grail War
as an extension of his
interest in killing for fun.
Regarding Berserker's Master,
he is immature and seeks
a measure of absolution
above all else.
For a time, he had severed all
ties with the Matou family,
yet he is now demanding
that the family set free
the younger Tohsaka
daughter whom they adopted.
She is currently being
groomed to be the next head
of the Matou
family in his place.
He has been given
the assignment
of winning
the Holy Grail
to secure his end of
a bargain for her release.
In addition, he appears
to have a past relationship
with Tohsaka's wife.
In a sense,
it might be said
that between all of the
five competing Masters,
he has the most unrefined
and banal motives
of them all.
What is it?
Continue, Kirei.
It's Saber's Master.
Hmm.
He is merely
a hired mercenary
retained by the Einzberns
to achieve their
long‐held dream
of attaining the Grail.
I was a fool to expect
more from him, hmm.
What an utter disappointment.
It seems he turned out
to be just another mongrel.
With dull and
stupid reasons
for seeking out and
stealing my treasure.
Exactly like all
the rest of them.
You cause me to go to all
that trouble investigating
and that is all
you have to say?
Think of those whose effort
has been wasted on you.
Wasted effort?
What wasted effort?
The work put in
by you and Assassin
has paid off
rather handsomely.
Are you mocking me,
King of Heroes?
Is that it?
You don't understand.
That's to be expected.
You are an obtuse man
who can not even recognize
his own joy.
Regardless of its self
awareness of this fact,
a soul instinctively
seeks out joy in its life.
This expression of the
soul appears in the form
of interest or appreciation.
Thus, Kirei,
having you tell me
what you've seen and heard
was of great interest
and importance to me.
And was very
instructive, indeed.
What you spoke about
at the greatest length
was what actually
interested you the most.
For now, let us
just set aside the man
you've deliberately
avoided speaking about.
A conscious interest is no
more than a simple obsession.
That being the case,
of the remaining
four Masters in the war,
of which one did you speak
about most passionately?
Berserker's Master.
Kariya, was it?
Kirei, when you
told me about him
you spoke of his
motivations in great detail.
His circumstances
are complicated.
Thus they required the
most detailed explanation
out of all of them.
Hmm, you are wrong.
He was the only one
you ordered Assassin
to investigate
to a thorough enough degree
such that you can understand
those circumstances.
And this was due to your
unconscious interest in him.
I accept that I made
an error in judgment.
It's true that
in the long term,
Kariya Matou
poses no threat.
He was not
worth the attention.
My overestimation
of his abilities
has invited your unnecessary
speculations about me.
Is that so?
Then imagine for me
a scenario in which
chance and fortune ensure
that Berserker and his Master
survive the many battles
and lasted until
the end of the war.
Can you imagine
what would happen then?
What do you think?
Listen, Kirei.
Is it not time that
you finally understood
the actual question
that I am asking you?
Tell me, Archer,
what could possibly be
the point in imagining
Kariya Matou's victory?
No point.
There is no point at all.
Come now, don't be
so angry with me.
Think about
it for a moment.
The fact that
Kirei Kotomine
never recognized
the futility
in such a speculation.
Do you not agree
there is a clear,
unshakable meaning here?
Explain for me, Archer.
It is like this.
If you had been given
the same question
but regarding
the other Masters,
you would have perceived
that there is no point to it
and you would have rejected
it as a waste of time.
However, that was not
how it went with Kariya.
For him, you abandoned
your usual sharp wits
and wasted your time
in pointless thought.
You ignored the futility
and the waste of effort,
you found enjoyment
in the exercise.
Celebrate, Kirei, you
have finally understood
what pleasure
is at long last.
Pleasure, are you
talking about joy?
Indeed.
There is nothing in
Kariya Matou's fate
that could bring
a man any joy.
His tortured life is nothing
but an endless string
of suffering and tragedy.
For him, a quick
and unexpected death
would actually
be a blessing.
Kirei, why must you
define joy so narrowly?
Where is the paradox in
finding suffering and tragedy
simply other forms of joy?
There is no one
fixed type of joy.
You are confused because you
fail to understand that.
This is something that
can not be allowed!
King of Heroes, a sick and
human monster such as yourself
may find joy in
some small amount
of another's pain.
But that is the soul
of a Godless sinner!
An evil that
must be punished!
Thus, I have sworn
to follow the path
of pure faith in my life.
And so you have defined
joy itself as a sin.
It's astonishing to see
how far you've twisted it.
You never cease to be
a source of fascination.
Delightful.
(gasping)
This pain.
Aarrgh.
Ah, exactly as I expected.
I must admit that did
not take very long at all.
Impossible.
This can't be, no Servant has
been freed from their pact.
Why has the Holy Grail
chosen a new Master?
It appears that
the Holy Grail
still expects much more from
Kirei Kotomine in this war.
Kirei, you should go and
heed the Grail's summons.
Without a doubt, you
have some hidden reason
to seek this
mystical wish granter.
I have a reason
to seek the Grail?
If this wish granting
device is truly omnipotent,
then it can give
shape and substance
to the wish that lies
within the darkest
depths of your heart.
A wish of which
even you remain unaware.
So you claim that since
I do not know my desire,
I should use the
wish granting device
as a means to
learn what it is?
That can only happen
if I enter the war
as an independent mage
and systematically
crush six other wishes.
If I selfishly seek
possession of the Grail
for my own desires,
that means that I will
have ruthlessly betrayed
my own teacher and mentor.
Then you will need to have
a strong Servant on your side
to fight for you.
If you would seek to
do battle against me.
Of course
before any of that,
you must steal a new
Servant for yourself.
One already
summoned and controlled
by one of the other Masters.
In that case‐‐
no, I won't say it.
Everything from this point
forward is up to you.
Do it all exactly
as you desire.
That is the true
meaning of pleasure.
Pleasure leads to
the experience of joy.
And joy will lead
you to happiness.
Your path is
now clear, Kirei.
So clear there is no longer
any need to hesitate.
♪
Then I shall
take the lead.
It's the perfect chance
to attack and put him down.
Let's finish this, Caster.
The whole world
is filled to the brim
with God's love, big guy.
And now once again,
we raise the blood‐soaked
flag of salvation!