♪
Aniplex.
(wind blowing)
(footsteps)
♪
(lightning striking)
(carriage rumbling)
(footsteps running)
Irisviel.
Are you all right?
They waited for
Kiritsugu to leave
before launching
a frontal assault.
That sudden lightning
and that unscrupulous
appearance of his.
The enemy.
His likely Rider.
♪
(carriage rumbling)
Whoa!
(metal jangling)
Huh?
Hello, Saber.
Rider?
I came because I wanted
to see your castle.
It's kind of gloomy here,
don't you think, hmm?
And what's with the
tasteless armor?
Are you going out to
fight someone right now?
Why aren't you wearing
your fashionable clothes
like I am tonight?
‐Rider.
‐Hmm?
What are you doing here?
You mean you can't tell?
I've come to drink,
what else does
it look like
I've come
here to do?
So stop standing
there like statue
and show me
around this place.
Surely you have a garden here
suitable for a banquet.
Honestly, this castle
is far too dusty to be in.
(wood smashing)
(liquid sloshing)
(gulping)
The Grail is said to
be fated for the hands
of the one most
worthy to possess it.
And the epic battle
taking place here in Fuyuki
will determine exactly
who that person is.
And if it's simply a
means to decide that fact,
there's hardly a
need for bloodshed.
After all, if the heroic spirits
can agree on our rankings,
then the matter can
simply settle itself.
Oh.
Then I assume you
wish to compare
your rank against
my own, Rider.
Indeed I do.
As one who also
claims the title of king,
you can not refuse
this opportunity.
You might consider
this a Grail dialog,
rather than a Grail War.
And the matter of who
among us who is most suited
to claim the Holy Grail
will become clear to us as we
drink our fill and converse.
I believe that is
quite enough nonsense.
You mongrels.
♪
Archer, what are
you doing here?
Ah, yes, well,
I saw him in town so I
thought I might as well
invite him to
our little gathering.
You're a little late
don't you think, goldie,
though it stands to reason
since you traveled by foot
unlike myself.
You actually chose to
hold a banquet of kings
in a depressing
place like this?
How will you recompense me
for the rudeness
of calling me here?
Oh, why don't you
just relax yourself.
Here, start with
a little drink.
♪
What is this
disgusting swill?
You really thought we
could discern a hierarchy
of heroic spirits with this?
You don't like it?
This cask was among
the very best I could find
at the city marketplace
this afternoon.
You are pitifully
ignorant of true drink.
Of course you believe that.
Stupid mongrel.
♪
Ah!
Now behold and
acknowledge your folly.
This is the beverage
of a true king.
A fine treasure, indeed.
Aaahhh.
(liquid pouring)
(gulping)
Ah, magnificent.
My treasury houses only
the very finest of drinks
and the finest of swords.
This alone should
indicate which among us
is the greatest of kings.
Archer, your finest
drink is indeed worthy
of the finest vessel
in all of history.
But the Holy Grail
is not a drinking cup.
First, we must hear what wish
you would have the Grail grant
should you win it.
The wish is what gives
the Grail its purpose.
You are not
ruler here, mongrel.
Already you
wantonly disregard
the time honored rules
which dictate we
fight for the Grail.
Hmm?
Besides all that, the Grail
already belongs to me.
All of this world's
treasures without exception
trace their origin
to my treasure house.
They do, do they?
Then I assume that means
you once held the Holy Grail,
you can identify
it by sight.
‐No.
‐Huh?
Do not consider me as
you would a lesser being.
The amount of wealth
in my treasury
long ago surpassed
my own knowledge.
But that the Holy
Grail is a treasure
also means that
it belongs to me.
And any who would
take it for themselves
is not but a filthy scoundrel
and a common thief.
Your words are no
different than Caster's
senseless and insane rants.
It appears he
isn't the only Servant
to have gone
completely mad.
Come, let's not go that far.
However, I believe
I now have a clue
as to what goldie's
actual identity is.
So then, Archer, you suggested
if we desire the Grail
we must first
get your permission?
Indeed, however there
is no reason whatsoever
for me to reward lowly
mongrels of your ilk.
Wait a minute, you're
going to be stingy?
Fool, my magnanimity
is limited to my vassals
and to my loyal subjects.
Which means, Rider, if you
were to swear fealty to me,
I could lend you
a Grail or two,
whenever you felt
the need for one.
Sorry, that is totally
out of the question.
But tell me, Archer, surely
you have no special interest
in the Holy Grail
itself, do you?
Of course not, but I must
render my judgment upon those
who would dare to
steal treasure from me.
It's simply a
matter of principle.
Hmm, I'm curious, Archer.
On what morals and reasoning
are these principles
of yours based?
It is the law,
my law which I set down
as the rightful king.
Perfect.
Living by one's own law
is the epitome of kingship.
Nevertheless, I desire
the Holy Grail so badly
I could almost taste it.
And it has
always been my style
to just take
what I want.
After all, the Great Iskandar
is the King of
Conquerors, is he not?
Right and wrong
are irrelevant.
You break the law
and I will punish you.
There is no place
for discussion.
Hmm.
Which means that all
we have left to us
is to meet on
the field of combat.
So then, Archer, would you
still like us to help you
finish this off tonight?
There'll be plenty of time
to kill each other after.
Indeed, or do you dare
sit there and cast aspersions
on the superior drink I did
you the honor of providing?
No, of course not,
I wouldn't dream
of letting this
drink go to waste.
(liquid pouring)
King of Conquerors.
Hmm?
A moment ago you agreed
that the Holy Grail's
rightful ownership
lies with another
and not yourself.
And yet you would
just take it by force?
What makes the Grail
so important to you?
Reincarnation.
‐Huh?
What?
Wait a minute, wasn't
your goal supposed to be
world conquest?
Ah!
Idiot, as if I would leave the
conquering to some mere cup.
Conquering the world
is my dream to make true.
The wish I would ask
of the Holy Grail
is the first step
towards that goal.
Mongrel, you would dare
challenge me for my treasure
over something so trivial?
Even in magic lends
us form in this world,
ultimately we remain Servants.
I wish to live
as flesh and blood
within this world
in which I find myself.
And with
nothing but my body
I shall defy both
heaven and Earth,
succeeding in that endeavor is
the true meaning of conquest.
Thus it begins.
Then proceeds onward
and finally is finished.
Such is the path
of my conquest.
Hmm, then the
matter is settled.
I shall take great pleasure
in killing you myself.
You don't have to
remind me of the obvious.
I have every
intention of plundering
your abundant storehouse
until it's been laid bare,
so get ready.
That is hardly fitting of
how a true king should behave.
Oh, well then, let us hear what
you would ask of the Grail,
if you were to win it.
♪
I wish for my
homeland's salvation.
With the omnipotent
wish granting device,
I shall avert Britain's
fate of destruction.
They're having a drinking
party of all things?
Shall I continue to leave
Archer to his own devices?
Hmm, it can't be helped.
After all, when one
is King of Kings,
it simply wouldn't
do to turn one's back
on an interesting invitation.
Incidentally, Kirei, how do you
judge the relative strengths
of Rider and Archer?
Rider may very well
possess a trump card
that surpasses
the gordius wheel.
I believe we should
put this to the test.
Hmm, with Rider
and his Master drinking
and their guard's down,
a better chance
to attack them
will never again
present itself.
The odds of victory don't
matter to our overall plan.
Even if Assassin is defeated,
as long as he can gauge
their relative strengths,
our objective will
be accomplished.
We do have the option
of launching an attack
right now, Kirei.
I have no objections.
I believe it will
take roughly ten minutes
to summon all the Assassins.
Fine, give the order.
It is a large gamble,
but even if it fails,
we stand to lose nothing.
Use a command seal to give
Assassin the following order.
Be victorious no matter
the cost, got it?
Hey, King of Knights,
did you just say
that you would change fate?
Does that mean that you wish
to change events long past?
Indeed, even if it is a
wish that a miracle alone
can not fulfill.
If the Holy Grail
is truly omnipotent,
then surely...
(snicker)
Um, Saber, just so
I am clear on this,
it was back during
your time that his country
you call Britain
was conquered and fell?
When it was under
your rule?
Correct, that is why
I can not allow it.
And that is why
I regret it.
Why I want to
alter that outcome,
for it was I and none
other who was to blame.
(snickering)
Archer, what's so amusing?
You call yourself a king and
are praised by all as such,
and yet you feel regret.
(laughing)
How can I not laugh
at such nonsense?
Saber, surely you
do not really mean
that you would erase
the marks that you yourself
have left on history?
I do, and what of it?
Why do you laugh?
My beloved country to which
I devoted my whole life
was destroyed.
Why is my sadness
about that strange?
Did you hear
that drivel, Rider?
what this little girl
who calls herself
King of Knights said?
Her beloved country to which
she devoted her whole life.
Why is that
humorous to you?
For their
country's prosperity,
a true king should be
willing to make any sacrifice.
You are wrong.
The king does
not devote himself.
It is the nation
and the people
who must devote
themselves to the king.
You have
reversed the concept.
I what?
Those are the words
of a brutal tyrant.
Just so.
We are heroes precisely
because we are tyrants.
However, Saber, if a
king regrets his rule
or regrets the manner in which
his rule came to an end,
that king is
nothing but a fool,
worse than the
tyrant you disdain.
Iskandar, your reign ended
with all your heirs slain
and your great empire
broken up by civil war.
Do you mean to say you have
no regrets about that end?
None at all.
Not if it came to pass
by my own decisions
and by the
considerable sacrifices
of my many retainers.
Its destruction
was inevitable.
I shall mourn it and
shed tears over it,
but I shall
never regret it.
But you‐‐
Let alone
undo it all!
Such an act would be
an insufferable insult
to all those who fought and
bled and died alongside me.
It is only a warrior who can
find glory in destruction,
worthless is a king who
fails to protect the weak.
A just rule
guided by just laws,
those are the true
duties of a king.
So you, the king
of your realm,
are a slave
to what is right?
I am.
Kings are martyrs
to their ideals.
That is not the way
a person should live.
If I rule a
nation as king,
I can not expect
to live as a person.
King of Conquerors,
you seek the Grail
merely for
your own benefit.
And as such, you could
never understand that.
You, who became a ruler
only to satisfy
your endless greed.
A king without greed is
even worse than a figurehead!
(gasp)
Saber, you said you would
martyr yourself
for your ideals.
In life you must
have been something
akin to the purest
of all the saints.
A proud and noble figure
at the very least.
But who can truly admire
the rough and thorny path
that a martyr must
follow in life?
Who actually dreams
of such an ending?
(wind blowing)
A king must be
greedier than any other.
He must laugh more loudly
and rage for much longer
and embody the very extreme
of all things good and evil.
That is why his retainers
envy his very existence.
And adore him as well.
And why the flames
of aspiration
to be just as
the king is
can burn
within his people.
♪
Proud king of chivalry,
the righteousness and
ideals you embraced in life
may have indeed
saved your nation
and her people once.
However, surely you must
know what became of those
who were saved by you.
But then were left
to fend for themselves.
What are you saying?
♪
You may indeed
have saved them,
but you never led them.
You never showed them all
what a king
should really be.
You abandoned your men
when they lost their way.
Then alone and
untroubled by that fact,
you went on to follow
your own pretty little
ideals to the end.
Thus, you are no true king.
You spent your life
enraptured by a false idol
of a humble king who
always serves others.
You're just a little girl.
♪
I...
(laughing)
What are you
laughing at, Archer?
Oh, nothing.
I simply felt that
your anguished face
was a rather lovely sight.
It was the face
of the virgins
who showered me with
flower pedals in my bed.
A woman after
my own heart.
Bastard!
(sword clanking)
♪
Huh?
Hmm.
Ah.
♪
Ahhh.
(yelping)
♪
Assassin.
So is this all
your doing, goldie?
Tokiomi, what a shameful cur.
This isn't fair.
Why are there so many
Assassins surrounding us?
We are one divided into many.
An army and also one.
A Servant with many shadows.
And one.
♪
A Servant with
separate bodies
for each of his
multiple personalities?
(sword clanking)
Rider, um, I...
Oh, calm yourself.
Nothing to
worry about, boy.
Even those rude enough
to interrupt our banquet
may yet show us which
is the greatest king.
So I suppose you'll
invite them all
to our little banquet as
well, King of Conquerors?
But of course, a king's
words are meant for all
to hear and absorb.
If they have come
here to listen,
it matters not if
they are friend or foe.
♪
Now then, don't hold back.
Any who would speak with us,
come forth and take a cup.
This drink is
as your blood.
(crashing)
♪
(laughing)
Very well.
As I said, this drink
is as your blood.
If you insist on
spilling it here tonight,
then so be it.
(wind howling)
Saber, Archer, here is our
banquet's final question.
It is, does a king
always stand alone?
The king must indeed
be alone, always.
No, no, you obviously
don't understand.
I suppose I'll just have
to show you both right now
exactly what a
real king is all about
when faced with an
adversary like this one.
♪
Huh?
A reality marble?
That's impossible.
A mental image materialized
into the real world.
(snicker)
My glorious armies once
rode across these sands.
A place that all the
heroes who stood with me
through joy and sorrow
will never forget.
♪
I can make this world as
real as real can ever be.
Because it still exists
deep within our hearts.
♪
Behold my endless armies.
Their bodies utterly destroyed
and their souls offered
to the current world
as heroic spirits of old.
And still,
these legendary heroes
pledge their loyalty to me.
My bond with them
is my greatest treasure.
My path to kingship.
The ultimate noble
phantasm that I possess!
I order in Haitari.
(yelling)
♪
Wait a minute, so each
of these is a Servant?
(whinnying)
It has been a
long time, partner.
♪
Hear me!
A king must
live a grand life
and embody his people's
image of admiration.
Aye, aye, aye.
♪
He who is worthy
of all heroes envy
and he who leads
their way, that is a king!
Therefore, the king
is not alone,
for his will equals that
of all who would follow him
to his ultimate
glory combined!
Aye, aye, aye!
Now then, shall we begin
our battle, Assassin?
As you can see,
what we have created
is a vast plane and with
our superior numbers,
we hold the advantage.
Annihilate them!
(yelling)
♪
Aaarggh!
(yelling)
♪
That ending wasn't as
much fun as I'd hoped for.
We have said all
there is to say.
I suppose that
will do for today.
Wait, Rider,
I have not finished.
You may keep silent.
Tonight was for a
conversation amongst kings.
But I no longer recognize
you as a king, Saber.
(lightning striking)
Little girl, you must
wake from your sad dream
and see the truth.
If you don't,
you'll someday lose
even that modicum of pride
you retain as a heroic spirit.
The dream of a king
you spoke of earlier
is a curse and a burden
which blinds
and cripples you.
A what?
(wheels rattling)
♪
Pay that base mongrel
no heed, Saber.
You are correct, follow
the path you believe in.
Your agonizing pain
and terrible sorrow
as you bear a
burden of kingship
that is too heavy
a weight for any
is quite a splendid and
marvelous thing to look upon.
Keep at it, oh great
King of Knights.
It is possible you may
prove worthy of still
more of my
magnificent love.
(laughing)
♪
Saber.
I remember now.
There was once a knight
who left Camelot
claiming the
king didn't understand
how others felt.
Well, perhaps that‐‐that
sentiment was shared
by all of the knights
who sat with me
at the round table.
♪
This will begin
the second stage.
I'm not in any way
a normal human being.
But Irisviel, that
simply can not be
all there is to it.
Do it all exactly
as you desire.
Your path is
now clear, Kirei.
But that is the soul
of a Godless sinner!