♪
Aniplex.
By my third command seal,
I order you again.
Stop!
Now, Saber, destroy
the Holy Grail.
(explosion)
How could I possibly
hope to know a man
from merely three
commands alone?
I, I never even knew
the hearts of those
who served me well,
and were closest to me.
Perhaps all this
was a punishment
meted out to a king
who cannot understand others.
(explosion)
(dog barking)
(rumbling)
That can't...
♪
It can't be.
It's impossible!
♪
Daddy?
Ilyasviel, what's wrong?
I had a really scary dream.
A dream where,
where I become
a really big cup...
...and then I dreamed
that these seven
gigantic lumps
started to come into my body.
It felt like they were
gonna tear me apart.
It's really scary,
but I can't run away.
And then I hear the voice
of Lord Justice.
After that, a big black hole
opens up above my head,
and then the world burns.
♪
Daddy looks at it all
and just begins to cry.
♪
Mother, is Daddy okay?
Is he scared and alone?
‐Is he in trouble?
‐It's okay.
Daddy's doing the
best he can for you.
He'll make certain that
our prayers are realized
so you'll never have to be
scared again, Ilyasviel.
♪
That's right.
I know he will.
Daddy always works very hard.
He'll finish all of
his important work,
and he'll come home as
soon as he possibly can.
♪
Hey, Sakura.
Come on.
Uncle?
I'm here to save you.
It's okay now.
Let's go.
It's Sakura!
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
(cries)
Kariya.
Hi, Aoi.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
Thank you so much.
‐Daddy Kariya!
(insects skittering)
You're such a fool.
Never disobey Grandfather.
Where am I?
You're a difficult
man to look after.
Digging you out from
underneath all of this rubble
was quite a
troublesome endeavor.
Gilgamesh, what happened?
Who can say?
That mud spit me
out and here I am.
I imagine it to be an
obvious message from heaven
that I should return to
this age to rule the world.
Are you saying you have
achieved incarnation?
Infuriatingly enough.
I can't believe we struggled
over that ridiculous thing
as if it were actually
a wish‐granter.
This ill‐conceived and
disappointing play remained
a meaningless farce
right to the very end.
But I was shot.
I don't get it.
(gasping)
I have no heartbeat.
Did you somehow heal
me and bring me back
to life, Gilgamesh?
The fact is I
really have no idea.
To my eyes, you
still seem quite dead,
but the two of us were
connected by our pact.
When I regained flesh
within that mud,
perhaps you were
trapped in some sort
of magical nonsense of your own.
Impossible, you're saying
that thing granted me life?
All the other
servants are gone,
so I suppose we must be the
ones who have won the Grail.
Kirei, behold the
result of our victory.
If it is true that
the Grail grants
the victor's heartfelt wish,
what you see before you,
Kirei Kotomine, is your wish.
It is exactly what
you most desired.
(chuckles)
Hm?
(laughing)
This is it, what the
hell does this make me?
What manner of dark evil?
What manner of cruelty?
This, this is my wish?
This horrible destruction
and tragedy?
This is the joy I sought?
Could something so
twisted, so corrupt,
have truly sprung
forth from the seed
of Father Risei Kotomine?
(laughing)
No way, it is impossible!
Did my father sire
a soulless demon
more evil than
the devil himself?
(laughing maniacally)
Are you satisfied now, Kirei?
No, no, not yet.
This isn't nearly enough.
Yes, it is true that
my life of questions
has finally found its answer.
However, the problem solving
process itself was skipped over,
and the solution was
just simply handed to me.
How is it that I'm supposed to
accept all this at face value?
♪
The formula that yielded this
strange, unsettling answer
should exist somewhere
as a greater,
clearer principle
one can understand.
No, not should, it must.
I must question,
I must search.
I must dedicate the
remainder of my life
to fully understanding it.
You know, you never
fail to bore me.
As you like, your questions
would slay the very gods.
I shall watch you
seek out your answer.
♪
Angra Mainyu.
I will reach it
again, and next time,
I will see it to the end.
Its birth and the
proof of its existence.
♪
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I accept your challenge.
♪
What's the matter, Kirei?
Nothing.
♪
I remember the
look on his face,
the tears in his eyes
over finding someone
alive in the rubble.
A man filled with joy
from the bottom of his heart.
He looked so happy to me.
It was almost as
though it had been him
who had been saved
that day, and not me.
♪
He's alive, he's alive!
He's alive!
And then, so fervently
that even as I teetered
on the brink of death,
I felt jealous of him.
He said, "Thank you,"
that he was glad
he'd found someone,
that by saving even one person
he had saved himself.
♪
And now for our next story,
the explosion that occurred‐‐
I hope that Alexey made it back
to his home in England safely.
He called me this morning
from Heathrow Airport.
That idiot forgot all
about the time difference.
Oh, he called?
I didn't hear the phone ring,
but then, it's just
like him to do that.
(chuckles)
Hey, Grandpa and Grandma,
I have a favor to
ask, if it's okay.
What is it, Waver,
speak your mind.
Actually, I'm thinking of taking
some time off from school.
Of course I'll talk to Dad
in Toronto about it first.
There's something that
I wanna spend my time on
more than studies at school.
‐Oh?
‐My goodness.
But what brought
all this on, dear?
Is it school, you aren't
fed up with it, are you?
No, it's not that.
You see, so far I haven't
really been interested
in anything besides studying.
I'm regretting that a little.
And so...
I'd like to do some traveling.
Oh my, did you hear
that, Glen, my dear?
Waver just said something
that sounded exactly
like something Alexey would say.
Anyway, there's a lot
I'd have to do first,
and I'll need money
to do it too.
For starters, I was thinking
of finding a part‐time job.
And so, um,
to make a long story
a lot shorter,
if you wouldn't mind too much,
could I possibly stay here
until I get
everything worked out?
Of course you can,
Waver, dear.
It will be so wonderful
to have you live here
with us for a while longer.
We'll have to celebrate today.
Oh, look at this.
He was just a spirit,
so I don't get
how he could've possibly
left such a mess behind.
I really did want him
to take me with him.
I guess it basically means
that I'm just not there yet.
I'm not ready.
He never even got the
chance to open this.
Too bad.
(bag rustling)
♪
A limited edition with
an original t‐shirt.
Does anyone even
want stuff like this?
What an idiot.
♪
I know that my redeemer lives,
and that in the end,
he will stand
upon the earth.
And though, after my skin
worms destroy this body,
yet in my flesh shall I see God.
I myself will see him
with mine own eyes.
I am not another.
How my heart yearns within me.
Amen.
Rin, it was
an excellent debut
for the young new head
of the Tohsaka family.
Your late father would've been
very pleased with you today.
Well done.
You haven't quite
grown fully accustomed
to your crest yet I see.
Does it hurt?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
It seems that
Tokiomi's preparations
for you were flawless.
I imagine that all the
magic the Tohsaka family
has accumulated, Rin,
will pass to you
without incident.
Well, why don't you go
and fetch your mother now?
Yes, I'll do that.
Come on, Mother, let's say
our last goodbye to Father.
Rin, is it someone's
funeral today?
That's right,
Mother, Father died.
Oh dear.
Then I should take out
Tokiomi's black suit.
Oh, and Rin, help Sakura
get changed, will you?
My, what should I do?
I have to get myself
ready to go too.
Goodness, dear, your
necktie isn't on straight.
(giggling)
You need to look good.
After all, you're the
father of Sakura and Rin.
I have to go away, I'll be
leaving Japan again for a while.
Do you have any
immediate concerns?
None at all, I don't need
your help for anything.
We will next meet
six months from now.
At that time, I will conduct the
second crest transplantation.
Take care that
you are in peak
physical condition
when I return.
I know, you don't
need to tell me.
Rin, you are now the head
of the Tohsaka family
both in name and reality,
and to commemorate this day,
I'd like to offer you
a very special gift.
An Azoth dagger.
When my master acknowledged
the results of my training
and declared it
finally complete,
he presented this to me.
But given the circumstances,
I think you should have it.
This was my father's?
(sniffles)
(wind blowing)
I'm here again.
(cries)
Everyone...
Lance‐‐Lancelot.
♪
Because I could not stop myself
from loving Guinevere,
I was never able
to forgive myself.
(screams)
But, King Arthur,
you never once spoke
of my many sins.
You never sought
atonement from me.
You simply continued
to stand before us
in your righteousness.
But deep in my heart
I desired judgment
at your hands.
Had your anger judged me,
had your righteousness
condemned me,
I might not have fallen
onto the path of madness,
and my quest to atone and
save my immortal soul.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I...
I am unworthy.
But this much I can
say with certainty.
‐King Arthur.
‐One day, friend,
I will claim the Grail.
You were the greatest of
all kings who ever lived.
All of those at the Round
Table who served you‐‐
It was not I.
Felt the same as I did.
I shouldn't have
been king.
♪
After that day, I visited
the Einzberns many times.
But as I had not
returned with the Grail,
Jubstacheit never opened
the forest's barrier for me.
And so, I never
saw Ilya again.
However, I swore
that Ilyasviel would
be the final person
I would ever lose.
My life was meant to
be one solely of loss.
But everyone is still here,
just like when we met.
(faint hammering)
Once I was able, I
adopted my son Shirou,
the little boy
I saved that day.
Hey.
‐Hey, old man!
‐Hm?
If you're so tired you're
gonna fall asleep, go to bed!
Huh?
Right, I'm fine.
♪
When I was little,
I really wanted
to be a hero.
What are you talking about?
You don't want to anymore?
Did you just give up?
Yeah, unfortunately.
Seems that wish has
an expiration date.
When you grow up, it's
hard to call yourself one.
♪
I wish I'd realized that sooner.
I see, well, guess there's
nothing you can do about it.
Yeah, right.
I guess not.
♪
(sighs)
It really is a
nice moon tonight.
Fine, since you can't do it,
I'm gonna be a hero for you.
‐Hm?
‐You're an adult now,
so you can't do it
anymore, but I still can.
Just leave it to me.
I'll make it happen.
♪
All right.
You do that.
I can rest easy now.
♪
Tell me, Kerry, what do
you wanna grow up to be?
♪
Well...
what I wanna be
is a hero.
♪