♪
Aniplex.
(seagulls calling)
(children laughing)
‐Hey!
‐Come on, Kerry!
‐Hurry!
‐Hurry up!
‐Kerry, jump in!
‐Come on!
‐It's so nice!
‐Hurry up!
(laughs)
(children marveling)
(seagulls calling)
(grunts)
(children marveling)
That was sweet, Kerry!
That was so cool!
You're so awesome.
‐That was nothing.
‐You're so cool.
That was really great.
(horn honks)
‐Shirley!
Kerry!
Sorry I'm late.
♪
Hey, Kerry,
do you know where this
island's name comes from?
Uh‐uh.
Oh, isn't Arimago
the word for crab?
Yep.
Long ago, this was a place
where they would make offerings
to the sea gods.
But then one day a
girl who was very poor
and had absolutely nothing
to feed her sick mother
took some of the food that
had been set out by the village
as an offering.
The sea gods were
so upset by this
that they cursed the
girl and transformed her
into a crab.
That's where it comes from?
What an awful story.
Well, according to the legend,
the shrine where the village
worshipped those gods
was located way up
in the mountains,
right about the place
where your house is.
♪
That's why none of the
villagers in this area
ever want to go up there.
They say it's bad luck.
They tell me that if
I go there too often,
I'll end up cursed for life.
You're kidding.
Really?
But everyone's nice to me.
Of course they are.
You're not an outsider
to them anymore.
♪
In the village,
they just treat you
like you're my little brother.
(sighs)
Your little brother, huh?
You know, Kerry, you've
really settled in nicely here.
Yeah?
Back when you first arrived,
everyone used to
really bully you,
saying you had a weird name.
Hey!
(grunts)
You were the very first
one to call my name weird,
and it was your big
idea to call me Kerry.
Well, yeah, because
your actual name
is really hard to say.
Kerry, uh...
Kerry...
Kiritsugu.
Jeez.
Kerrystugu!
Not even close.
Really?
(laughs)
Oops.
♪
(birdsong)
Okay.
Hm?
Hey, Dad, is that a new one?
That's right.
This would make
my 100th success.
Amazing.
These flowers don't wither.
That's because I've
altered the flow of time.
They will never
grow beyond this,
but they will never die.
Unbelievable.
The big question is whether or
not we can get the same theory
to work on humans.
(panting)
Sorry for the wait!
Shirley, what you got?
Check it out.
It's my first
successful flower.
Shirley has been
watching closely
and learning while
she assists me.
She does seem to have the
natural gift to be a mage.
Aw, come on now, Professor.
You did most of the work.
I only did a little bit,
and it was right at the end.
Maybe, but it's amazing.
Uh, hey, Dad?
Huh, what?
You think I could give it a try?
What Shirley did, I mean.
That'd be great!
I think if you had
a little bit of help,
you could do it.
Right, Professor?
No.
Kiritsugu, it's still
too early for you.
Mm.
This isn't a game.
There are dangers.
I only let Shirley
try it because she has
the necessary knowledge
and experience to succeed.
Hm.
♪
Father Simon, why won't
you try to understand?
Shirley.
Everyone in town has
the professor all wrong!
Shirley, listen to me.
You must stop going
up to that mansion.
♪
Let's talk inside.
I think Dad should spend some
time with the villagers too.
♪
I don't know.
Father Simon just has it
in for him for some reason.
He keeps lecturing
me all the time.
He says if I stay
working there,
I'll get possessed
by a demon someday.
Check this out.
He gave this to me yesterday.
Says I should always
keep it near me.
He told me that it's
a powerful talisman.
♪
So you're not scared,
you know, of my dad?
Not at all.
I realize that magical
research like he does
isn't exactly normal.
But the professor's
research and discoveries
are a big deal.
I mean, they
could make history.
Actually, I think
he's amazing.
♪
Are you sure you should be...
What; It's sharp and
it's really easy to use.
♪
Well, see you tomorrow.
Shirley, something wrong?
Keeping a flower
blooming forever.
It's really amazing magic.
But you're doing
it too, Shirley.
The work with flowers
is all I can do.
But he can do a
lot more than that.
The medicines he makes
could make human beings
effectively immortal.
I really want him
to use his power
for the good of
the whole world
so that everyone
will finally understand
how incredible he is.
He's given up on that.
But, Kerry,
I think you can do it.
Oh, come on.
You're the best
student he's ever had.
If anyone could
carry on his work,
it'd be you.
Kerry, I'm not
really his student.
At best, I'm his assistant.
Running his errands,
helping out.
(gasps)
See, I'm not his student.
Far from it.
So even when Father Simon
says bad things about him,
there's nothing I can say.
Kerry, you're his heir,
there's no doubt about it.
You do realize that
everything he's working on now
he plans for
you to continue.
It's just a little
too soon, that's all.
Hey, come with me.
(nocturnal nature sounds)
(gasps)
Whoa.
♪
Tell me, Kerry,
what do you want
to grow up to be?
Huh?
If you decide to take
up your dad's work,
what do you think
you'll use it for?
It's a world changing power,
and one day it will be yours.
♪
So, go change the world.
You can do it.
I guarantee it.
♪
Well, I, uh...
That's a secret.
♪
Hm.
Then I guess I'll have
to wait until you grow up
to see what you're
gonna do with your power.
I'll stay with you
until that day comes, okay?
♪
(giggles)
(stammering)
Yeah, right, whatever.
(laughs)
(grunting)
Stop it!
No way!
(door opens)
Oh, good morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu, you didn't go into
my workshop last night, did you?
Huh?
No, I didn't.
I see.
Listen, don't leave the house.
Huh?
Stay here.
Don't go into
the village today.
(door slams)
What's gotten into him?
(birdsong)
Shirley's late,
I wonder why.
Hey!
Have you guys
seen Shirley?
Uh‐uh.
(panting)
(chickens clucking)
Shirley?
(knocking)
Hm.
(glass clinks)
Huh?
(violent clucking)
(clucking)
What the?
What happened?
(blood spurting)
♪
(gasps)
(blood spurting)
♪
Kerry.
Shirley!
(whimpering)
♪
I...
I only wanted
to prove him right.
His resear‐‐research.
(whimpering)
But I guess
it didn't work.
(screaming)
♪
Kill me.
Use that.
Please.
You have to kill me.
♪
Do it now
before it's too late.
♪
Please do it!
I can't stop.
Can't hold it back anymore.
Hurry!
(gasps)
(grunting)
♪
Hm.
Are you certain it was
Shirley who did this?
♪
(weeps)
Kerry, I want you to stay
here for the time being.
I'll go inform the village.
♪
(grunts)
Agh!
(panting)
(gasps)
(footsteps)
♪
(rapid breathing)
(banging)
♪
(whimpers)
(banging)
(glass shatters)
(snarling)
♪
(whimpering)
(man stammering)
(crowd screaming)
♪
Agh!
What?
What is all this?
♪
(grunting)
Father Simon?
♪
(whimpering)
(grunts)
(explosion)
♪
(snarling)
(gunshot)
Yah!
(cocks gun)
(gunshot)
♪
(roaring)
(snarling)
♪
(gunfire)
Agh!
(whimpering)
Looks like we got here
just a little too late.
Wait a minute.
Who are‐‐who are you?
Agh!
(gunfire)
Don't you think you should
worry about yourself first?
Well, if you just
sit there like that,
you'll be joining
them soon enough.
So what's going on?
Who did all this?
Why would they
burn the village?
Surely you must have
heard of them before.
You would know
them as vampires.
The name we use
is Dead Apostles.
Apostles?
They drink blood to
increase their numbers.
Nearly everyone
living on this island
has become one now,
and here we are having
to clean up the mess.
So, we have two groups
down there right now
trying to eliminate them all.
One of the groups is made
up of Church Inquisitors,
those who believe beyond
the shadow of a doubt
that it's all right
to slaughter anyone
who defies the will of God.
They'll show no mercy to
any Dead Apostles they find,
and they'll kill
anyone they even suspect
of having had
their blood sucked.
The other group is from
the Mage's Association,
and they're harder to explain.
Suffice it to say,
they'd very much like
to keep the secret of who
made such bizarre things
as the Dead Apostles
to themselves.
Naturally, since their
motto is All To Ourselves,
they'll kill anyone they
suspect of knowing the secret.
They'll do anything
to cover this up.
It was the mages who set
a torch to the village.
So then whose side are you on?
I'm something
akin to a salesman
to the Mage's Association.
All right, it's your turn, kid.
Time to answer
one of my questions.
I'm looking for a mage
who's marked for sealing.
What's a mage?
I suppose that word doesn't
really mean anything to you.
There was someone who
became a Dead Apostle first,
someone infected
them with the medium
that turns people
into those creatures,
the trigger that started
their transformation.
The son of a bitch mage
who conjured that medium up
should be laying low
somewhere on this island.
Can you think of
any likely spots
where I should look?
♪
(footsteps)
(flames billow)
Oh, good.
There you are.
You're okay.
Well, thank goodness.
Didn't I tell you not
to go into the village?
Dad, why were you
researching Dead Apostles?
How did you know about that?
Shirley used the
magic on herself.
Oh, well, that's
most unfortunate.
But you can't change
what's already happened.
It just means Shirley gave me
an answer I was looking for,
that's all.
Dad, will‐‐will you use me
like you used Shirley?
Don't be stupid.
A Dead Apostle that can't
control its blood lust
is a failure.
But the Emiya
family research
requires an unlimited
amount of time.
The Root will
never be attained
by someone with a mortal body.
It was a time consuming task,
but it seems to have
ended in failure.
I'm going to have to
reconsider my entire theory.
Kiritsugu, let's save this
matter for another time.
For now, escaping comes first.
It's not too
late to escape?
I suspected something like
this might happen one day,
so I've kept a motorboat
hidden on the south coast.
(footsteps)
I'm sorry, Kiritsugu,
but we don't have time to
let you gather your things.
Come on.
I'm gonna do it.
There's a Bounded
Field around the forest,
an extremely powerful one.
It'll take a little bit of
time to break through it,
but I'll be able to get in.
I have to be the one.
(clanging)
(panting)
♪
(stammering)
(panting)
♪
Tell me, Kerry...
What do you want
to grow up to be?
(gunfire)
♪
(whimpering)
(grunts)
♪
That Bounded Field, I was able
to break through it easily.
♪
Are you mad or stupid?
It was only dumb luck
that you showed up in time.
If this man had escaped,
he'd have continued his
Dead Apostles research
somewhere else.
Yeah, well, that's a
pretty crappy reason
for a kid to kill his father.
♪
You're a good
person, aren't you?
I'll get you off this
godforsaken island.
You can decide the
rest for yourself.
Wanna take anything?
♪
Nothing at all.
After leaving the island,
I spent the next
several years
living with
Natalia Kaminski.
That meant choosing
the same path as Natalia,
the solitary path of a
highly skilled master hunter.