(door squeaking)
(creaking)
Finally made it.
Hey, Waver!
No, no, not there.
Over here.
Grandpa, what are
you doing up there?
Enough with the questions,
just come on up here.
Let's talk for a while.
He wants to talk?
Why do we have
to talk on the roof?
Grandpa, can't it wait a while?
Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
He really does like you, boy.
Rider, come on, they're
just under my spell and‐‐
Oh, go up there.
The old man seems to have
something important he wants
to tell you.
Relax, boy, I'll patrol
the area and keep watch.
Don't be shy.
That's not the problem.
(sighs)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
I love it up here.
This is the best place
to catch the first rays
of the morning sun.
Take a seat.
Here, I even have
some coffee for you,
it'll warm you up.
Grandpa, just how long have
you been sitting up here?
When I woke up this morning
and checked in on you,
I saw you hadn't
made it back yet,
so I thought I'd
take the opportunity
to watch the sun come up
while I waited for my grandson
to come home.
When you were just a tyke,
we used to come up to the roof
on clear nights
and stargaze all the time.
Do you remember?
Yeah, I guess.
When Martha and I
decided to live in Japan,
we made sure to build
our house up here in
the hills of Miyama
and built it with
a large skylight,
so we could easily
gain access to the roof.
We dreamed of sitting up here
gazing at the beautiful sky
with our grandchildren
alongside us, entranced
by the stars as
much as we were.
We never thought our wish
would actually
come true, though.
(gasps)
In all these years,
our real grandchildren
never once came up here
to watch the sky with us.
Sadly, whenever
I've come up here
to stargaze, I've always
been alone until now.
Now, Waver, you really
aren't our grandson, are you?
(gasps)
♪
It's very strange,
the way Martha and I
were so completely convinced
that you were actually part
of our family.
To be honest, you were
a bit too nice to be
our grandson.
You really messed up there.
♪
I suppose you're pretty mad.
Well, I guess I probably
have every right to be, Waver.
But lately, Martha's
been acting so happy
and smiling nearly
every moment of every day.
I couldn't have imagined
her like that before.
Really, I'm very grateful
to the both of you.
It's been quite a blessing.
Besides, it doesn't seem
to me you decided to move in
with Martha and I
because you intended
to cause us any harm.
So, what do you think?
If you can, Martha and I
would really like it
if you'd stay with
us a while longer.
♪
I'm sorry,
I can't promise that.
I can't even guarantee I'll
make it back here safely.
So, I gather you two
are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I can't even begin
to venture a guess as
to how important whatever
it is you're doing is to you,
but when you've had
a long life like me
and look back on it all,
you come to realize that
there is absolutely nothing
in this world so valuable
or so important that it's
really worth risking
that life for.
♪
I guess it's been
about 40 hours
since I last slept...maybe more.
To win the battle
and summon the grail,
one must perform the ritual
at the location of one of
the four Fuyuki ley lines.
At two of them, the church
and the Tohsaka Estate,
Kirei Kotomine
was nowhere to be found,
which leaves the other two:
Here at Mt. Enzo and
the Fuyuki Citizens Building.
Given the ley lines'
relative power,
this one is more likely.
Even if he's chosen
the Citizens Building,
I can launch
a frontal assault there.
♪
If Maiya were still alive,
I would have sent her
to secure it.
♪
Once again, I'm all alone.
Come to think of it,
I never really figured her
into my plans.
♪
Since last night,
I've been searching
the whole city
for Irisviel's location,
but I found no sign of her.
I am deeply sorry.
(splash)
Well, then, if you need me,
summon me using
the command seal.
Wake up.
Can you hear me, woman?
♪
So, it's you, Kirei.
This building was once
the place where Caster's
young master hid,
though it appears
that Kiritsugu Emiya
was never able to locate it.
Soon, the Holy
Grail War will be over.
It's likely that I'll be the one
that will have
the power to grant
the wish of the Einzberns.
Are you so unhappy
that it would be me?
There is but one man to whom
I would entrust the grail,
and it is certainly
not you, Inquisitor.
Kiritsugu Emiya has already
seen right through you, Kirei.
He recognizes you as his
most dangerous enemy.
You can't escape.
Your words are as
the gospel to my ears.
Kiritsugu Emiya is exactly
as I imagined him
to be after all.
How laughable.
You couldn't be any further
from him if you tried.
What did you say?
Even though Kiritsugu
can see through you,
the reverse is impossible.
You have none of
the wonderful things
that he carries deep
inside his heart.
Why do you speak of me
in such a manner, woman?
I freely admit it,
I'm a man who is empty
and desolate inside.
So, how do he and I differ?
Devoted himself to one
fruitless war after another
for years?
Senseless slaughter,
utter recklessness,
wasted effort?!
If he does not doubt
or find this life
pointless as I do,
then what is he?
(coughing)
Tell me, what is his wish?
What would he ask
of the Holy Grail?
What prayer would he entrust
to the wish‐granting device?
(heavy breathing)
Very well, I'll tell you.
Kiritsugu Emiya's wish
is humanity's salvation,
an end to all warfare
and bloodshed and suffering...
forever.
True peace upon the Earth.
(light grunting)
What was that?
You can never understand it.
That is the difference
between you two;
he has something
to believe in.
(shudders)
Conflict is
intrinsic to humanity.
To eliminate it
completely would mean
the elimination
of humanity itself.
As an ideal,
it's totally futile,
nonsense that
a child would spout.
Yes, and that is why
his only hope is for
a true miracle.
Many times, Kiritsugu
has been forced to...
to sacrifice the lives
of people he's loved
because of his beliefs.
Yes, you see, he's far
too kind to chase ideals.
He must love even knowing
it will mean losing that love.
I understand.
(whimpering)
♪
(grunting)
(snapping)
♪
I understand well.
So, that is Kiritsugu Emiya.
♪
At last, I see it,
my reason for fighting.
♪
Kiritsugu Emiya,
I shall grind your ideals
to dust right before you,
along with the Holy Grail
you long for.
(clock ticking)
Oh, you finally woke up, boy.
I thought I told
you to wake me up
at nightfall.
Did you forget?
Oh, sorry, but I thought
it might be good to take
our time with preparations.
Tonight, there is
no reason to rush.
How come?
I can't say why exactly.
It feels like everything
will be concluding tonight.
Uh‐huh.
The night air
seems way too still.
Is that because there
are fewer participants
still in the fight?
(globe spinning)
From now on,
only the truly strong
remain in the battle.
(bursts)
W‐what was that?
It's a very strange mana surge.
I felt something
similar before.
(bursts)
Look at that pattern.
What is it... some kind
of secret code, do you think?
Four and seven
in different colors.
"Success and victory."
If they're
sending up that signal...
...does that mean that
someone got the grail
and the war is over?
No, it's coming up from
a completely
different direction
than the church is,
which means that the church
didn't send the message.
In essence, somebody
is getting way ahead
of themselves and claiming
to be victorious.
That says, "If you object,
come and get me!"
It is an obvious challenge.
It looks like
the big showdown
is going to happen tonight.
I see, that means
this is it, then.
Quite right, boy!
Now that we have
our battlefield,
I must go forth and bring honor
to the rider class and ride
gloriously into
the final fray!
(zapping)
Come now, my steed!
(neighing)
Now then, boy, it may
not be as smooth a ride
as by chariot, but‐‐Huh?
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Come on!
From this point,
only the truly strong
can continue, right?
♪
My servant, Rider,
by his command seal,
Waver Velvet orders you...
fight until you attain
the victory you seek.
♪
And by my command seal,
I further order that you,
Rider, go now
and win the Holy Grail.
♪
And by command seal,
I further order, Rider,
take the world for your own.
I will not tolerate failure.
♪
There, it's all over.
I'm no longer your master.
Go, go wherever you wish.
I don't even wanna see you.
(grunts)
(yelps)
I'll certainly be
on my way in a moment,
but after all those
annoying orders you just gave,
surely you're prepared to
see this though to the end?
You total idiot, listen to me!
I used the command seals
and quit being your master!
Why would you still
wanna take me, dammit?!
I'm not your‐‐
Master or not, boy,
you are still my friend
and always will be.
Huh?
(chuckles)
♪
I'm...you mean...
you're really
okay with me?
You want someone
like me by your side?
What are you saying?
After all the battles you
and I have seen together,
you have to ask that?
Idiot.
(neighing)
Up until now,
have you not faced
the same enemies as I have?
That means you're my friend.
So, be proud
and consider yourself
my equal.
♪
(blows nose)
All right, I shall begin
by obeying the first
of your orders.
Now, boy, keep your
eyes open to the end!
(neighing)
Well, let's see
what she can do.
Right before my open eyes!
(neighing)
♪
(bursts)
(engine puttering)
He chose the place
least suited to
the required ritual
only to gain the early
initiative in battle.
In other words, his plan
is not to obtain the grail,
but rather to use it as bait
to lure me and
the other masters
into a trap,
then kill us all.
♪
That simplifies things.
If he's going to be
this incompetent,
I'll just outmaneuver
and eliminate him quickly.
♪
Kirei Kotomine.
Hm, very impressive.
I must say, you look
particularly ferocious
tonight, Kirei.
Now what will you do?
Do you wish for me
to stay here and wait?
Unleashing all of your
power at this close range
could endanger
the ceremony itself.
If you want to fight it
full strength you'll have
to go out and meet them.
Very well, what if this place
falls under attack
while I'm gone?
Will you allow me
to utilize the command seals
to save myself?
I will, but I do not guarantee
the Holy Grail's safety.
For tonight,
I shant be holding back.
That would be
the worst outcome,
but if that should happen,
it will be fate.
Kirei, you seem to have finally
found your reason to fight,
but have you still no prayer
to offer the Holy Grail?
I can think of
nothing I want.
My only hope is that nothing
will interfere with the conduct
of the battle
we're about to enter.
Honestly, Kirei,
as I suspected,
the only recourse is to let
the grail reveal what hides
within your heart.
♪
Oh, if it appears as if
Saber will be arriving here
before I can return,
just have Berserker
entertain her for
a little while.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber,
what happened to
the doll that was
so important to her?
The Holy Grail's vessel
is inside of her, is it not?
I took her life.
I had no reason to let
her continue living.
(chuckles)
♪
(sobbing)
Are you crying?
Are you, Mother?
Hey, Mother,
I had a scary dream.
I dreamed that I
turned into a cup,
and then I dreamed that
these seven gigantic lumps
started to come into my body.
It's okay, it's okay.
I would never
let that happen.
I promise that will never
happen to you, Illya.
I know in my heart
that you'll be released
from the shackles of fate.
♪
(screeching)
(gasps)
♪
Where am I?
Inside the Holy Grail?
This shouldn't be happening!
(yelps)
If I'm here...
who am I?
♪
That's right, this is
inside the Holy Grail:
The omnipotent
wish‐granting device
that will dispel all
the world's sadness
and remove all
its suffering.
I will have the power
to make that happen.
The end is nearly at hand.
♪
Our enemy is
the mighty King of Heroes,
a most worthy opponent!
Our noble path
of ultimate conquest!
King of Conquerors,
know the end of your
eternal dream.
I shall show you
the stark reality.