(birds chirping)
♪
Kiritsugu.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You really came?
You really came to see me again.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
My last task
is to return this to you.
♪
Take it.
From now on, you will be the one
who will be needing Avalon.
When you begin your final
battle for the Grail,
I'm sure it will aid you.
You know what?
I'm really happy.
To love, to be loved.
To have a husband and daughter
for nine whole years.
♪
I'm grateful.
You gave me everything.
You gave me all the
happiness in the world.
Something that was
never meant for me.
I'm sorry, I wanted
to show you much
more of this world.
No, it was enough.
If there's still any
happiness left to experience,
I want you to give it
all to our sweet Ilya,
to your daughter.
Our angel, our beloved Ilya.
♪
I want you to promise
to bring Ilya to this
country someday.
Promise me that you'll show her
everything that
I didn't get to see,
amazing things.
Blossoming cherry trees,
and the summer clouds.
I will.
Okay, I have to go.
Yes, you be careful.
I love you.
(door opening)
Saber is heading to
Rider's hideout right now.
Is that correct?
Yes, she's on her way.
I'm going to kill
Tokiomi Tohsaka.
If Rider and Saber
engage in battle
there's a good chance
Archer will also appear.
I'll hit him there.
I want you to stay here
and watch over Iri.
I understand.
Um, Kiritsugu.
Finally.
You look focused.
Just like you used to.
(car engine whirring)
♪
I don't feel a
servant's presence.
♪
There's no barrier?
What's going on?
(birds chirping)
(chewing noisily)
So, is that good?
Nope, it's awful.
Guess Japanese cuisine
isn't that good after all.
Boy, you walked right by
Okonomiyaki Shoki in Newtown
without even stopping to look.
Their modanyaki was
a thing of beauty.
Too bad you didn't
pick up any of that.
If you wanna eat there again,
you're gonna have to recover
enough so that you
can materialize.
Do you recognize this spot?
This is the place
where I summoned you.
It's the Fuyuki location
with the leylines
that suit you best, remember?
You should be able to recover
much more quickly here.
I've decided that I'm
staying here all day.
Just sleeping, that's all.
So take my mana,
as much as you want.
Just don't kill me.
Maybe it'll help you feel
a little bit better.
(chuckling)
If you had already
figured it out
you should've said
something earlier.
Finding out afterwards that
someone's been onto you
the whole time is‐‐well,
well, it's a bit embarrassing.
You idiot, you should've
just told me about it!
If you aren't at full strength
at the exact moment I need you
I'll be the one who
ends up in danger.
Why didn't you say
anything, Rider?
I thought that maybe
I could tough it out
a little while longer,
but the fatigue
from the river battle has hit
me harder than I expected.
Yeah, well, when it's
all said and done,
your Noble Phantasm
consumes a ton of power.
At first, I didn't
really notice.
Because it wasn't
affecting me I thought
it was all incredibly
efficient or something.
♪
Rider, honestly,
instead of using mana
that was supposed to come
from me, you managed to use
your own stored
power, didn't you?
And not only that,
you did it twice.
What's the big idea doing that?
Well, you know,
I mean, when you get right
down to it, as a servant,
I'm a natural soul
eater of sorts.
If I involve you when I expend
mana at my maximum rate
it could put your
life at serious risk.
Yeah, but I'm fine with that.
This is a battle
that I got us into.
Unless I bleed
or make sacrifices,
there's no point at all
of winning this war.
Hmmm.
All I wanted was
to prove myself,
that I could‐‐that
someone just like me
can take whatever it is he
wants with his own two hands.
But boy, I hope you
realize that all of that
only applies if the
Grail truly exists.
You know, I once did
something similar.
Fought ferociously for something
that might not
have even existed.
‐Oceanus.
‐That's right.
I said I'd show them Oceanus,
and they were so swept up
by my story that
they all followed me
on my quest without
a single doubt.
Many died along the way,
all dreaming of Oceanus
until the very end.
When I gained this
era's knowledge,
it hit my really hard.
I'd had no idea the world
was an enclosed sphere.
What a bad joke.
But even so, when I saw the map,
I had no choice
but to accept it.
It seems I've had my fill
of letting people
die for fairytales.
If the Grail's existence was
certain, I'd have no objection
to you risking your life
in an effort to possess it.
But unfortunately,
that is not the case.
Even so...
don't you forget, I
am still your master.
(laughing)
Boy, learned to talk
back now, have you?
Excellent.
It's true, your magic circuits
are more powerful than usual.
If I rest all day
I should be ready
to go another round
come nightfall.
Oh yeah, another round?
What exactly are you
planning to do next?
Hm, good question.
I'm thinking that we
should begin with Saber.
At the rate you're regenerating,
how much will you be able
to recover by tonight?
If I only use the
Gordius Wheel for flight,
there really shouldn't
be a problem.
However, I'm afraid I'll
only be able to employ
my Ionioi Hetairoi
one more time.
‐I see.
‐We should probably save it
for the later fight with Archer.
Then Rider, I don't get it.
Why is it you wanna
fight Saber first?
I must defeat her,
and no one else.
As a heroic spirit, it
is my responsibility.
What's that mean?
If I don't show that
silly girl the right path,
the path to true kingship,
I fear she'll never learn.
That would be too sad
to bear thinking about.
Whatever, have it
however you want.
Boy, quit keeping yourself
awake and just go to sleep.
Rest is the battle
that you face right now.
Mmm.
♪
I am the shunned, the scorned,
the despised.
Who the hell are you?
My name is unworthy of praise.
My body unworthy of envy.
I am the shadow cast by
the heroic spirits' light,
the darkness born in the
shadow of shining legend.
(gasping)
Thus do I hate,
thus do I resent.
I feed on the lamentation of
those who sink into darkness,
and curse those who
shine so brightly.
Her shadow is my shame.
Her honor remains
forever unsullied.
Thus am I forever
looked down upon.
You are the sacrifice.
(screaming)
(chains jingling)
Healing won't help me.
I'm going to die soon.
♪
Damn it.
(evil laughter)
♪
Really, what a sorry
sight you are.
You look absolutely terrible.
♪
Now I don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
I'm not blaming you for
your current condition.
To be perfectly honest,
I never would've imagined
that you'd hold
out for this long.
You've really surprised me,
and so, I shall give you
the ace I've kept hidden up
my sleeve, secreted away
for use at precisely
this stage of the game.
Take it.
(groaning)
♪
It works quickly, doesn't it?
The worm I just gave
you is very special.
It was the first to feed
on Sakura's innocent purity.
How does it feel, Kariya?
For an entire year
it has been devouring
the girl's life energy.
It's a magnificent mana source.
Now, go back and fight, Kariya,
and make good use of
the precious life force
you've stolen from young Sakura.
Go and use every ounce
of your flesh and bone
to acquire the Holy Grail,
if someone such as you is
even capable of it, that is.
Hey, Maiya.
I'm curious as to why
you fight for Kiritsugu.
Because I have
nothing else in life.
I can't remember my family or
my own name for that matter.
Maiya Hisau was the name on
the very first fake passport
that Kiritsugu made for me.
(wind blowing)
All I remember is that the
place where I came from
was a terribly poor country.
The wars never ended,
even though there was no
money to maintain the armies.
But day after day, they
continued to kill one another.
Then one day,
someone had an idea.
Rather than conscript
and train soldiers,
it was cheaper and faster
to abduct children
and send them out
to fight the battles.
You mean, you were one of them?
♪
Aim at the enemy and
pull the trigger.
That was my sole
function in life.
I threw everything else away.
As a human being,
I'm dead inside,
but the outer shell
continues to function.
Still working just
like it did before.
That's always been my
life, but regardless,
Kiritsugu took me in, so
however he wants to use me
is fine by me, and that's
the reason I'm here.
♪
To tell you the truth,
madam, it was your passion
for all this that surprised me.
You've been secluded in the
castle where you were born,
knowing so little
of the outside world.
So I simply can't imagine
why you would fight
this hard for Kiritsugu's dream.
To change a world you've
never really seen.
Well, I‐‐you're right.
I cannot truly understand
Kiritsugu's ideals,
or why he holds them
close to his heart.
It's as you say,
I've been sheltered,
and I know practically
nothing of the world
that Kiritsugu longs to change.
All the ideals I speak
of are merely words
that I learned from him.
♪
But please don't
let him know that.
I've always told
him that I thought
he was doing the right thing,
and also that those same ideals
were worth giving
up my life for.
And I pretended that
I understood him.
Then, madam, in that case,
have you no wish or
longing of your own?
My wish?
Oh yes, I have one.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber
to prevail and win possession
of the Holy Grail.
You mean, you support
the Einzbern's desire
to attain the Third Magic?
No, what I desire is an end
to conflict in the world.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes
true and fighting everywhere
comes to an end, the
battles for possession
of the Holy Grail here in Fuyuki
will be no exception.
I want this fourth
battle to be the last
of the Holy Grail Wars.
You mean, for your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail
to get the Grail,
then Ilya's next.
It's unfortunate, but
that is the destiny
that an Einzbern
homunculus must bear.
So my wish is to
be the last one.
If that comes true she'll
be able to live out
her life as a
normal human being.
Maiya, what will you do
after Kiritsugu reaches
his goal and saves the world?
I don't expect to
survive that long.
And even if I do,
there'll be no reason
for me to exist anymore.
I'm sure it will be
that kind of world
once Kiritsugu changes it.
But you do have
a reason to exist.
You think so?
You must look for
your real name,
and then go out
and find your family.
Those aren't things
anyone should forget.
You must learn who you
are and etch yourself
into the memories of others.
So live, Maiya,
for yourself and for me too.
I'll do my best, but
all that has to wait
until after the battle ends.
Right now we must be cautious.
Both he and I
must stay on constant guard.
The one who died
was Tokiomi Tohsaka.
♪
Oh, Maiya, you
really are stubborn.
(explosion)
♪
(gunshots)
‐Maiya!
‐Iri!
By my command seal, I order you!
Saber, go to the
storehouse immediately!
Kiritsugu.
♪
What happened?
Maiya!
♪
Saber.
Don't try to speak.
Hurry, follow him.
Don't let him escape with her.
Rider took madam with him.
‐But if I leave‐‐
‐Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
And Kiritsugu will come soon.
So, hurry.
♪
Maiya, you have to try and hold
on until Kiritsugu returns.
I shall bring
Irisviel back safe.
♪
Rider, I can't believe it.
It was Rider.
Yes, I understand.
You mustn't cry, not over me.
♪
You need to save those
tears for your wife.
You can't cry here.
Be strong, you have to finish.
So don't cry yet.
You can't break.
‐You can't.
‐Maiya.
You know, this morning,
you finally looked
like Kiritsugu,
like your old self.
Don't lose your
resolve over this.
Promise.
(breathing unevenly)
♪
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, your task here
is finished.
(wind blowing)
Maiya.
Maiya?
♪
‐Where is Irisviel?
‐Don't forget now,
‐tonight at midnight.
‐Nothing on Earth can stop me!
‐Do not underestimate me!
‐It was all his fault!
‐If it weren't for what he did!
‐Oh, scary, scary.
Are you satisfied now, Kariya?