♪
Aniplex.
(door opens)
♪
(footsteps echo)
(groans)
♪
(singing in Japanese)
Murdered?
I can't...believe it.
Why would anyone kill him?
It's unthinkable!
This cannot be allowed!
It must also be
regrettable for you
to lose your
father in this way.
It is.
Father Risei
was very dear.
He was just like
a second father to me.
It's been one
unexpected disaster
after another.
I think it might
prove necessary
to formulate a new
plan right away.
(door opens)
(door creaks closed)
Why did you not
tell Tokiomi?
Tell him what?
I pity your father.
He died believing
his son to be
a pious man of God.
Or...
perhaps that was
his salvation.
Does your father's death
arouse no feeling in you?
He was killed, after all.
You could at least attempt
to appear a little upset.
I am.
I'm furious to no end.
Furious, you say?
Are you...
furious because you were
unable to kill him yourself?
♪
Saber?
Irisviel,
how are you feeling?
It appears I've made
you worry about me again.
I'm sorry.
No.
As long as you
are truly fine.
That is all that
really matters to me.
But then...
(gasps)
It's okay.
It's Maiya's presence
you are sensing.
Tohsaka?
Yes.
He requests that we
present a united front.
Wait, an alliance?
At this stage?
The thought of dealing
with Rider and Berserker
must have Tohsaka
feeling father uneasy.
And so, assuming that we
would be the most amenable,
he has invited us to meet.
Meaning that he considers us
the weakest of
the remaining teams.
Tohsaka said that he wishes
to meet with you tonight
over at the Fuyuki church.
You should know that
from the very start
Tokiomi Tohsaka has made
elaborate preparations
to try and ensure
his victory in
this Grail War.
And it's also likely
that in total secret
he controlled
Assassin's master,
Kirei Kotomine.
If that's true,
and Tohsaka exerts
some influence
over Kotomine,
then I believe it
would be a mistake
if we choose to
ignore this offer.
Yes, you're right.
Kirei Kotomine?
Remember this, Saber,
if there is anyone
in this war who can
defeat Kiritsugu and claim
the Holy Grail for himself,
it is the man named
Kirei Kotomine.
Go and tell them.
We accept.
♪
Father?
Hi, Father!
♪
Rin, your father
says that he would
like to speak with you.
♪
(gasps)
Rin...
keep the Mage's Association
in your debt
till you grow up.
After that, I leave
the rest to your judgment.
I'm certain you'll
be fine on your own.
The Holy Grail
will appear one day,
it is the Tohsaka
family's duty
to claim it.
Above all, if you wish
to be a mage, Rin,
it's a path you
cannot avoid.
Here, take this.
Oh!
♪
I have to go now.
You know what to do, right?
Yes.
♪
I'll see you soon.
Take care, Father.
♪
First, allow me
to thank you
for coming here
at my behest.
I very much appreciate it.
Let me introduce
Kirei Kotomine,
my long‐time apprentice.
While we were once
honorable competitors
in this battle
for the Holy Grail,
all that is now
in the past.
He has lost his servant,
and as a result,
has yielded his rights
as a master.
This Grail War is rapidly
heading toward its conclusion.
The one's remaining are,
as anticipated, the masters
of the three great houses
along with one outsider.
Now, what is your appraisal
of the state of the war?
I have no opinion.
We control the most
powerful servant, Saber,
and don't need to wait
for the best time to strike.
We shall simply continue
to win each battle.
Hm.
Unfortunately
for the Matous,
it is my opinion
that they erred
in their strategy.
They have imposed
a draining servant
upon a frail master,
thereby hastening
his self‐destruction.
Rider is likely to be
the victor between them.
The Grail must not be
allowed to fall into
outside hands.
The two of us should be
able to agree on that much.
Any alliance is
out of the question.
However, if you wish
to discuss the order
in which we approach
our enemies, we may
be able to come to some
equitable agreement.
Go on.
We can settle things
with the Tohsaka team
after defeating
the other masters.
We are prepared to
agree to such a proposal.
So a temporary
conditional ceasefire?
That is a fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
The first is that you
agree to share with us
any and all information
you may have gathered
concerning Rider
and his master.
Agreed.
Our second condition is
that Kirei Kotomine
be removed from
the Holy Grail War.
Kirei?
I am not suggesting
in any way he be killed,
but I insist that until
this battle is over,
he be expelled from Fuyuki,
or better yet,
from Japan entirely.
Immediately, before morning.
Would you explain why?
Because of the bad blood
between the Einzberns
and the so‐called Inquisitor.
If the Tohsaka team
continues to protect him,
we will find ourselves
unable to trust you
under any circumstances.
What does she mean?
Kirei.
(engine growls)
Well, Saber,
how do you like
Kiritsugu's present?
Very much so.
It is more like
a horse than a car is.
It seems to suit
me much better.
I shall go ahead then
and scout out the
route ahead for us.
(engine grumbles)
We should go now as well.
(engine turns over)
Ma‐‐madam, what's the matter?
Please drive, Maiya.
You sure?
Tohsaka will suspect
something's wrong.
What's happening to me
really isn't unexpected.
It was actually inevitable.
Honestly, the fact that
I've been able to function
as a human for this long...
is really quite a miracle.
Does Kiritsugu
know about this?
Yes, but don't tell Saber.
She has a crucial
battle to fight
ahead of her.
I don't want
to distract her
with all of this.
But listen, Maiya,
there's something
I need to tell you.
I am a homunculus
created specifically
for the Holy Grail War.
You know about that, right?
Yes.
Grandfather Acht
ingrained in the vessel
an instinct for
self‐preservation
so that it would avoid
all danger and safeguard
the Grail to its completion.
He disguised the vessel
so he could hide it
in plain sight
and called it Irisviel.
That is who I am.
But how?
Then that means
that you are...
Very soon now.
I will revert back
to what I originally was.
When that happens,
I won't even be able
to talk to you
or anyone else
like this anymore.
That's the reason why
Kiritsugu gave me
Saber's scabbard to keep.
Avalon, are you familiar
with its effects?
It halts aging and provides
an infinite healing ability.
Or so I'm told.
Its effects are
what have prevented
the hollow
shell that is me
from collapsing
in on itself.
Of course, they stop
working as soon
as Saber is away.
And I start to deteriorate.
Madam, why are you
telling me all this?
Because, Maiya Hisau,
under no circumstances
would you ever pity me.
You would accept
me for what I am.
That's why I tell you.
Madam, Irisviel,
I'm afraid I've always
thought that you
were beyond my reach.
No, I'm not really.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Even if it costs
me my life, Irisviel,
I will see you through
to the very end.
And so please...
please die now
for Kiritsugu Emiya
to make his dream a reality.
Thank you.
I really wish
you had told me
of your troubled history
with the Einzberns.
Unfortunately,
I have no choice.
You must withdraw
from the Holy Grail War
immediately.
♪
Kiritsugu Emiya,
who are you really?
Will I leave this place
never even learning that?
Still thinking about
what to do even now?
Could you truly
be so slow, Kirei?
The Holy Grail
beckons to you still.
And even you yourself
still long to jump
into the fight and claim it.
For as long
as I remember,
I've spent my life in
search of a single thing.
I've devoted every moment
and endured
great pain for it,
but all of that
has come to naught.
Yet I sense that the
answer to my question
is closer to me now than
it has ever been before.
After all of that
self‐reflection,
why in the world
do you still hesitate?
Because I fear
that when I've
learned all the answers,
it will result in
my utter destruction.
(telephone rings)
Understood, well done.
Ah, you've just received
an exciting bit of news,
I take it.
We've finally learned
the exact location
of the stronghold
where the Einzberns
have been hiding.
(maniacal laugh)
As I live and breathe!
You honestly amaze me.
You were planning
to continue all along,
weren't you?
I did hesitate.
I was even prepared to give up.
But in the end,
it is just
as you say, Archer...
I know no other way
than to keep asking
the question until
I find an answer.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
♪
JN424.
The gospel of John.
♪
"God is spirit,
and those who worship Him
must worship in
spirit and in truth."
♪
(maniacal laugh)
However, Kirei,
there remains for you
a rather grave problem.
Were you to participate
in the Holy Grail War
on your own behalf,
Tokiomi Tohsaka
becomes your enemy.
In other words,
you are in the same room
as an enemy's servant
with no real plan
to actually defend
yourself from him.
A dire situation,
would you not agree?
No, not at all.
I came with something
to trade for my life.
Really?
Gilgamesh.
Let me reveal to you
the truth behind
the Holy Grail War that
has been kept from you.
And that is?
The magical ritual
held here in Fuyuki
is an attempt by
the winning mage
to open up a passage
directly to the root
by the sacrifice of
the souls of seven
heroic spirits.
The activation
of the Holy Grail
can only be achieved
by the killing of all
seven servants.
That's correct,
all seven.
You understand?
That's the reason
my master has worked
so hard to avoid
using his command seals,
because when
all the battles
are finally over,
he will require them
to force his own
servant to commit suicide.
So then the loyalty
Tokiomi has shown me
has all been nothing but
a lie from the very beginning?
To put it yet another way,
my master is first
and foremost a mage
down to his very core.
He may worship
a heroic spirit,
but he harbors no
illusions about his idols.
Well, Tokiomi,
at last you have
shown some hint of promise.
That dull excuse
for a man will
finally be able
to provide me
with a measure
of entertainment.
Now then, what
will you do, Gilgamesh?
Will you now choose
to remain loyal to Tokiomi
and then punish me for
rebelling against him?
Ah, a fair question, indeed.
Regardless of his treachery,
Tokiomi still supplies
me with the mana I require.
Were I to abandon
my master, it would
hamper my ability
to remain materialized.
Oh, come to think of it,
there is a partnerless
master I know of.
One who is actively
searching for a servant
that is free and
unbound by a contract.
Hmph.
Now that you mention
it, you're right.
But of course,
there is a question
of whether that man
is a worthy master
in the eyes of
the King of Heroes?
He will suffice.
He is a bit stiff
and humorless, perhaps,
but he has great
potential for growth.
He may yet prove
himself a fine source
of entertainment for me.
Hm.
I've been waiting
for you, Kirei.
I came to say goodbye
and thank you before
I departed Fuyuki.
First, I'd like to say
that I'm still very proud
to have had you
as my student.
I hope you will
maintain good relations
with the Tohsaka family,
as throughout the years
your late father always did.
All right?
Your words honor me.
Once this Grail War
has finally come to an end,
Kirei, I'd like for you
to help train my young
daughter, Rin,
to be a mage.
It's rather simple,
but in essence,
this is a will
I've prepared.
I thought it prudent
to be ready in the event
the worst happened
and I did not survive.
It leaves the entire
wealth of the Tohsaka family
to Rin.
And names you as
her legal guardian
until she comes of age.
Leave it to me.
I shall do all I can
to look after your daughter
and keep her safe from any harm.
Thank you.
Kirei.
What is this?
A little something for you.
A gift from me.
Open it.
An Azoth dagger.
It symbolizes your
mastery of magic,
and marks the completion
of your apprenticeship to me.
I am without words.
You are far too kind to me.
I am filled
with gratitude,
my master.
It is I who thanks you,
Kirei Kotomine.
Now I can finish
preparing for
the final battle
of this war.
Oh my, look at the time.
I'm sorry to have
kept you here
for so long.
(whips blade)
I hope I haven't made
you miss your flight.
♪
No.
You needn't worry
about it, my master.
(plunges dagger)
(Tokiomi chokes)
♪
You see, I never got around
to buying myself a ticket.
♪
(thump)
Master.
How like my father you were.
Even at the very end,
you never really understood me
or my inner
motivations, did you?
♪
Hah.
Such a boring end.
Look at that.
Such an idiotic expression.
He did have
a dematerialized
servant at hand
that he depended on.
It was natural for
him to lower his guard.
So, you have learned
to adjust already, have you?
I praise you for your
studious aptitude.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel a little
better about not having
had the chance
to kill your father?
So you have no
qualms about this,
Gilgamesh, King of Heroes?
No, not so long as
you continue to amuse me.
Otherwise, Kirei...
Well, you are the one
who ought to question
your own resolve.
♪
My will creates your body,
and your sword
creates my destiny.
If you heed
the Grail's call
and also obey my
will and my reason.
Yes, I swear your
offering will be my flesh,
Kirei Kotomine,
my new master.
♪
Now, Kirei,
let us begin.
Put an end to this farce,
and as a reward
for your loyalty,
I shall give you
the Holy Grail.
Very well then,
King of Heroes.
May you have your fill
of amusement from me.
Until such time I
find the answer I seek,
I shall gladly play
the fool for you.
♪
Tell me, Kari,
what do you wanna
grow up to be?
You must stop going
up to that mansion.
What is all this?
You can decide
the rest for yourself.
It's still too early for you.
It's a world‐changing power,
and one day
it will be yours.