♪
Aniplex.
(tires screeching)
See, see?
I told you so!
This car takes the
turns really fast!
Well, that's because you're
a surprisingly good driver.
(grunting)
(Saber laughs)
I know!
You may not believe it,
but I practice all the time!
(tires screeching)
Of all the toys Kiritsugu
has brought me over the years,
this is my absolute favorite!
This is a toy?
(engine revving)
At the castle, I was
only allowed to drive
around the courtyard,
so this is great!
Shouldn't we have maybe
hired a professional driver?
No, that would be boring.
I mean, it could
be really dangerous.
What if the enemy were to
suddenly launch an attack
against us?
Well, I suppose
you have a point but‐‐
Stop the car!
(tires screeching)
Irisviel, get out of the car
and stay very close to me.
This presence...
it's a Servant!
♪
I have come for you,
my sweet and holy virgin!
♪
Do you know this man?
I've never laid eyes on him.
Oh no!
Are you saying that
you've forgotten my face?
Forgotten you?
I've never met you in my life.
You mistake me for another.
Agh!
It's me!
It's Gilles de Rais, my darling!
I have prayed for
your resurrection
and have been waiting for
a miracle to reunite us!
To that end, I've
come all this way,
to the end of time, my Jeanne!
Who is Jeanne?
I know not your
name, I assure you.
Nor have I any idea
who this Jeanne might be.
No...
No, you can't
have forgotten!
Not your former identity!
As you have seen fit
to give me your name,
then I must, in keeping
with the chivalric code,
give mine.
My name is Arturia,
the heir to Uther Pendragon,
and King of Britain.
I enter this battle
in the Saber class.
Oh no!
How tragic!
It's so very sad!
She's lost her memory
and gone completely insane!
(weeps)
Curse Him.
Curse Him!
Such cruel
tortures God inflicts
upon my beautiful maiden!
Such horrible injustices!
Enough!
You embarrass yourself!
Awaken, O fair one.
You have no need to call
yourself Saber any longer.
Because the Holy Grail
War has already ended.
The Grail has
chosen me, Gilles,
to be its champion,
with no fighting at all!
For, you see, my one
and only eternal wish,
the resurrection
of Jeanne d'Arc,
has finally been granted!
(loud crashing)
♪
Ha...
If you mock
the true prayers
of all the other
heroes again,
the next strike
will be real!
Now rise!
Has your heart been
sealed so tightly,
my dearest Jeanne?
Very well.
That's too bad.
If drastic measures are
called for to free your heart,
I will take my leave
of you to go and prepare.
I swear to you, Jeanne!
I will not rest until
I can free your soul
from the terrible prison
of God's cruel curse.
♪
It's very difficult
to deal with one
who ignores everything
that you're saying.
Next time, I shall
strike before he speaks!
His type completely
infuriates me.
However, this encounter may have
actually been a fortunate one.
I sensed that he was
too dangerous to face
without the full
use of my left hand.
♪
Following Saber's Master
has yielded unexpected fruits.
We found Caster as well.
Of course, we must follow him.
(cracking)
Ah, no, no.
The thumb needs
to go like this!
That's nice!
Perfect in fact!
(clanging)
Welcome back, big guy.
(sighs)
(forceful blood spray)
Hey!
What the hell?
Accursed God!
He keeps an iron
grip on Jeanne's soul,
refusing to let go!
By Jeanne I assume
you mean the girl
you saw in the crystal ball?
We must prove the cold
hear talked to her!
That God's power is
gone and my love wasted!
That no deed
no matter how foul,
no crime no
matter how horrible
is worthy of God's punishment!
Yeah, I get it.
You're even cooler
than I thought!
Therefore, we require
greater depravities,
greater blasphemies.
We must erect a veritable Tower
of Babel of human sacrifices!
Mmm, uh, so basically,
from now on it's
quantity over quality?
Indeed!
Exactly so!
Impressive, Ryunosuke.
Our first step will be
sacrificing the eleven
in their cells right away.
And then, we'll go acquire some
more children for our revelries.
(grunts)
It's kind of a waste,
don't you think?
Uh...
We interrupt this
regularly scheduled program
to bring you this
important breaking news.
An unexplained
explosion has occurred
in the Fuyuki Coastal
Warehouse District.
We go live to the scene.
Why did you fail
to finish off Saber
when you faced her?
Not once but twice.
You made me waste
the Command Seal,
and yet you couldn't
finish the job, idiot!
Was your encounter with Saber
really that much fun for you?
It wasn't like that, Master.
I swear on my
honor as a knight,
as a Servant
of the Grail War,
I will bring
you Saber's head.
You don't need to
swear to me again!
Of course you will!
You made a pact with
me to defeat all others
for the Holy Grail.
And now you sit there
like a sniveling fool
swearing to bring me
the head of Saber?
What about this do
you not understand!?
Aren't you the one
who's mistaken here,
Lord El‐Melloi?
♪
Sola‐Ui.
Lancer actually did well.
I'm afraid you're the
one who made the mistake.
Saber is a highly skilled
and powerful Servant.
I simply couldn't allow
a chance to defeat her
pass me by without trying.
He inflicted a wound
on her that cannot heal.
By letting her go, you can
defeat her at your leisure.
If you're that
concerned about her
and her lauded abilities,
why didn't you go after
her Master instead?
You merely stayed
hidden and watched.
Rather pathetic.
♪
Honestly, Kayneth.
It isn't that you
don't understand
your distinct advantage
over all the other Masters.
You were the one
who ensured that.
You made a special alteration
to the usual Master‐Servant pact
that no one other than
I knows anything about.
You control Command Seals,
and I act as an
additional Master
and supply the Servant mana.
Brilliant.
You weren't the Evocation
Division's brightest star
for nothing, you know?
♪
But we must take
care at the beginning.
Must we now?
So you'll hide while you make
Lancer take all the risks?
All right, that's
enough of that.
Any more will be an
insult to my Master.
As a knight, I cannot allow it.
No, I didn't
mean it like that!
I've overstepped my bounds.
I'm sorry.
♪
(alarm ringing)
What?
What's going on?
(phone ringing)
♪
Yes, I understand.
There's a fire on
the lower levels.
It can't be anything but
an act of arson, of course.
Arson?
Tonight, of all nights?
They wish to empty the building.
Then it's an attack.
(laughs)
Saber's Master will want to take
down Lancer as soon as possible
to lift his spear's
curse and make her whole.
Lancer, go downstairs
now and defeat her.
Don't just drive
her off this time.
Understood, Master.
Let's see to it
that our honored guest
enjoys the amazing magical
workshop of Kayneth El‐Melloi.
A perfect workshop
requiring an entire floor.
Twenty‐four layered barriers,
three mana generators,
dozens of ghosts and spirits
roaming as guard dogs.
Thousands of traps
and parts of hallways
that open into other worlds.
(laughs)
We shall avail ourselves
of all the magical techniques
we have at our disposal.
I shall make you
retract your statements
that I am pathetic very shortly.
Oh?
I look forward to it.
♪
(chatter)
Mr. Archibald!
Mr. Kayneth
El‐Melloi Archibald!
Are you present here?
Yes.
That was me.
Don't worry.
Both Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald
and his wife
Sola‐Ui have exited.
♪
Hm.
Oh, I see.
Yes, yes, that's right.
♪
Everyone has evacuated.
Good.
♪
Everything is ready on my end.
And you?
All green.
Just give the word.
♪
(rapid tonal dialing)
(beeping)
(explosions)
(panicked chatter)
(cell phone beeping, ringing)
Maiya?
The target never even
moved from his position.
He didn't leave the
hotel before the explosion.
A free fall
from 150 meters.
No magical
barrier known to man
could've saved him from that.
(child crying)
Maiya, withdraw.
(gunfire)
(crowd gasping)
♪
To blow up the
entire building...
I can't believe a mage would
actually do something like that.
Then again, I suppose he is
excellent at outsmarting mages.
Kirei Kotomine.
Oh?
I don't believe
we've ever met.
Or do you have a good reason why
you would know who I am already?
Well, in that case,
I can guess who you are.
(scoffs)
Don't make me stand here
doing all the talking, woman.
One word from you will suffice.
Tell me, where is the man
who should have been here
instead of you?
♪
(gunfire)
(grunting, panting)
♪
Not bad, not bad at all.
You seem to have some training.
♪
(hissing)
(grunts)
♪
Hm.
(footsteps)
There's no way she
threw this gas canister.
(footsteps)
No matter.
Just the knowledge that
someone was here to save her
from the situation means
tonight wasn't a total waste.
Master Kirei.
I thought I gave
you explicit orders
to stay hidden and
not to expose yourself.
My apologies, Master.
But there is some important news
that I thought you should hear
without delay.
We've located
the Servant Caster.
♪
After having Assassin perform
a detailed investigation,
we learned that
Caster and his Master
have kidnapped
children from their beds
in the town of Miyama
and the next town over.
By dawn, they had taken fifteen.
I would imagine that
they are the serial killer
that's been
reported in the news
and that everyone
is worried about.
They use magic without
even the slightest hesitation,
and seem to be doing absolutely
nothing to hide their tracks.
It is quite possible that
they are not even thinking
of the Holy Grail War.
A mad Servant
out of control
and a Master who doesn't
even try to control him.
Why are people like them
participating in the Grail War?
This is something we
cannot ignore, Tokiomi.
Their actions are in clear
violation of the rules
by which we are all bound.
Of course.
As one responsible for
guarding the secrets of magic,
this cannot be allowed.
Uh, we shall have
to eliminate Caster
as well as his Master.
Yes.
But the problem is
that defeating a Servant
requires a Servant,
and we can't
send my Assassin
without exposing
our deception.
Ah.
♪
Minor rule changes fall
completely under my purview.
We'll have all of the
Masters work as a group
to defeat Caster.
♪
Archer?
There are far
fewer bottles here
than in Tokiomi's room,
but of higher quality.
I must say that's
some apprentice he has.
What is it you want?
Apparently, there are those
in this war other than myself
with an abundance of
time on their hands.
What do you mean?
Otherwise, a Master existing
under the kind
protection of the Church
would hardly need
to wander about.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Are you dissatisfied with
your Master, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi invited
me to this world
and maintains my form here.
His greeting was worthy
of my elevated station,
and so I felt that I
had to respond to that.
But I never expected
that he'd be such
a dull and boring person.
So you are unhappy
with him as your Master.
He wants to reach
the Vortex of the Root.
What a boring and
tedious little plan.
The unflinching desire for
the "Root" is unique to mages.
It's not for outsiders
to comment upon.
In a sense, the
path to the "Root"
is the path to an
escape from this world.
For us, who are interested
only in the world itself,
it may well be a tedious plan.
Is that so?
True.
I am full of love
for this universe
that is my personal playground.
I have no interest in
realms outside my dominion.
This "Root" of yours does
not concern me in the least.
Perhaps.
But the Grail
is not a device
specifically designed
to seek the Root.
When we say that
it is omnipotent,
we mean that it has
limitless potential
to alter even the reality
of the material world.
So you're saying
the other Masters
have motives
other than Tokiomi's
for wanting to obtain
the Holy Grail.
Tokiomi is an archetypal mage,
and at the same time
extremely orthodox.
What the other Masters seek is
one form or another of success
here in the material world:
prestige, desires, power.
That suits me fine.
I love every one
of those things.
You are a king who rules over
the profane and the vulgar,
Gilgamesh.
So what is it that
motivates you, Kirei?
♪
What do you want
from the Holy Grail?
Me?
Nothing.
I have no real desire for it.
I seriously doubt that.
Doesn't the Holy Grail
call only those Masters
whom it considers
worthy of possessing it?
So they say.
But why did it choose me?
I have no ideal
or other desire.
So why choose me
for this battle?
No ideal or other desire?
Then why not simply wish
for something like joy?
Ridiculous!
Wish for joy?
You'd ask me to
long for something
that blasphemous and sinful?
Blasphemous and sinful you say?
That's going a
little far, isn't it?
Why the connection
between joy and sin?
Well, I...
True, joy gained by evil means
could be considered sin.
But joy may be attained
through good deeds as well.
What kind of philosophy
calls joy itself a sin?
It's absolutely ludicrous.
Joy is another
quality that I lack.
I seek it, but never find it.
Kirei Kotomine,
I find myself
interested in you.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
Be seated.
True joy, you see,
might be thought of
as a form of the soul.
The question isn't
whether it exists or not,
but whether you know it.
Kirei, you have yet to see
what form your soul has taken.
That's what it
actually means
when you claim that
you lack joy in your life.
You're just a mere Servant
and you dare sit
there and lecture me?
Don't get cocky, mongrel.
I am a king who has
tasted all the pleasures
the world has to offer.
Hold your tongue and listen.
♪
Kirei, you ought to
learn what pleasure is.
Look first to the outside.
I know.
Why not begin by joining
me in my entertainment?
♪
I have no time to waste
on pointless trivialities.
Don't be like that.
You can do it between the
jobs Tokiomi assigns you.
To begin with, your
task is to keep watch
over the five other Masters,
isn't that correct?
What of it?
You should investigate
not only their plans,
but their motivations for
obtaining the Grail as well.
Then give that
information to me.
That would be possible
if I ask the Assassins.
But, Archer, what does
any of that matter to you?
I've already told you.
I enjoy watching humans.
One or two of them are
sure to be interesting enough
to keep me
entertained for a while.
Compared to that
dull Tokiomi at least.
♪
Very well, Archer.
I will accept.
But it will take
some time to do it.
That's fine.
I shall wait patiently
as I avail myself
of these drinks.
♪
My reason for
seeking the Holy Grail?
I said far more
than I should have.
♪
I know that it
certainly isn't joy.
♪
However, if I can
learn about him,
will I also be able to learn
what it is I seek as well?
♪
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I am temporarily altering
the rules of the Grail War.
Could eventually
kill yourself.
We could escape
if we go now.
It will be my lance alone
that takes Saber's life.
My fight with you is
no longer over the Grail!
Don't get conceited,
you savage!