♪
(crashing)
(gasping)
♪
Rider?
What the hell?
What do you think you're doing
breaking the shutter
open like that?
Why didn't you go
through in spirit form
like when you entered?
I cannot carry these things
while I am in my spirit form.
And don't whine so much.
You sound like you're some kind
of common thief
or street urchin.
Well, if you aren't a thief,
then what the hell are you?
Something entirely different.
A cowardly thief sneaks away
in the night full of fear.
If you stride away
bursting with song proudly,
then what you are
is a conquering king!
Just what I needed‐‐
now get out of here!
Get lost‐‐get lost now!
Very well‐‐then I shall
leave you to carry the spoils.
Try not to drop them.
♪
Oh, man, why is
this happening to me?
♪
(panting)
I‐‐I don't get it.
The summoning worked, so
why do I have to do all of this?
What's so important
about these books, anyway?
It's important because
we are preparing for war.
And one cannot wage war
without having proper maps.
Hey, boy, where are
Macedonia and Persia?
You can't talk to me like that!
I'm your master‐‐
(grunting)
I am well aware of
my status as servant
and yours as my master.
After all, we forged
a pact, did we not?
Mhm.
But I'm interested in learning
where all my old
territories are located.
♪
I think they're here.
Hmm.
(laughing)
I spent my life
conquering that land,
and look how puny it is!
Very well.
I can't wait to get started!
All right, then.
Where exactly on this map
are we sitting right now, boy?
Here.
So, the other side
of the round land.
Hmm.
Good news indeed.
This will guide us well
in the coming battles.
Guide us well?
First, to the other
side of the world,
due west, and we
go as fast as we can.
And we shall conquer every
land that we pass through!
I shall return to
Macedonia in triumph,
and my people
will hold a festival
in honor of my great revival!
(laughing)
Now how splendid will that be?
Why do you think
you're here, anyway?
You didn't forget
the Grail War, did you?
Hmm, that's right.
Speaking of the Grail,
I have neglected to
ask one small thing.
What will you do with the
Grail once you possess it?
Why‐‐what's it
to you what I do?
I mean, what do you care?
If you are also intent
on world conquest,
then that would
make you my enemy,
because the world
cannot serve two lords.
Wha‐‐
No, I don't want that!
Look, I'll tell you
what I really want, okay?
I just want people
to treat me fairly.
I wanna make all those
idiots back at the clock tower
who never even bothered
to give me a chance
to admit to me
that they were wrong!
Small!
Small.
And narrow‐minded and stupid!
You mean to tell me
that in this battle,
your only concern is for
your ridiculous reputation?
And you dare call
yourself my master?
What a terrible
disappointment you are.
(groaning)
If you wish so desperately
for others to fear
and respect you...
(grunting)
...perhaps you should try
using the Holy Grail's power
to grow another 30 centimeters
and add a little bit of muscle.
He's supposed to be my servant!
He can't talk to me that way!
I'll show him!
I address the command seal.
In accordance with
the Grail's laws,
I order this man,
Iskander the Conqueror...
Calm down, Waver.
A master can only
use his command seal
to compel his servant's
obedience three times
and that's all.
If I use all my command seals,
I won't be able to control
him when I really need to.
As long as I get the Holy
Grail, it doesn't matter.
I really don't give a damn
what you do after that, so‐‐
Enough, boy!
I shall acquire the
Grail for you as you wish.
Yeah, well, you seem
awfully confident about that.
Do you have any idea
how you're gonna do it?
So you wish to see my power‐‐
is that what you're
trying to tell me?
Well, of course I do!
You need to prove to me
that I can rely on you
no matter what the situation!
(chuckling)
I am Iskander,
King of Conquerors!
With the swing of my sword,
I declare my supremacy!
(yelling)
♪
(thunder rumbling)
(static crackling)
♪
This is the ox chariot
that King Gordius
once offered up to Zeus.
Its renowned reputation
must be the source
of my designation as
a rider class servant.
If you want the Grail,
then find me
another hero or two‐‐
someone worthy for me to fight!
Until then, I shall entertain
myself by sitting here
and looking at these maps.
That will not pose
a problem, will it?
(grunting)
All right!
I'm not gonna lose
today‐‐you just watch!
♪
Ah, I found one.
No way‐‐where is it?
Oh, gee, I'm sure I
didn't overlook it!
That's the very first
chestnut bud today!
First point to me.
I'm not gonna lose!
♪
Oh, there's one!
Right here!
Ahhh.
You see‐‐I found one too!
I found my second over here.
Huh?
Hey, that isn't
a chestnut branch.
It's kind of, Ilya.
That branch is actually
from a tree called a wingnut.
It's almost like a chestnut,
so as far as I'm concerned,
it's a chestnut bud.
‐Huh?
‐That's no fair!
No fair, no fair, no fair!
The whole time
we've been playing,
you've been cheating!
Yes, but your daddy can't win
this game against you otherwise!
If you keep on cheating
like you've been doing,
I won't play this game
with you ever again!
I don't want that!
I'm sorry, Ilya, I apologize.
Do you promise not to
cheat like that anymore?
Yes, I do.
Okay then.
I challenge you
to one more round.
A true champion
accepts all challengers!
Indeed, I'm very
honored, your highness.
Wow, I'm so high up!
♪
What's got your
attention out there, Saber?
It's interesting.
Your daughter and Kiritsugu
are playing outside.
♪
Are you surprised?
I was under the impression that
my master had a colder heart
than he's showing now.
Well, I can see why
you might think that.
If that really is
Kiritsugu's true self,
then I am afraid I must've
gravely offended him
when we first met.
(laughing)
Irisviel, you really
don't have to laugh at me.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering if
you're still concerned
with our reaction
when you were summoned?
Yes, somewhat.
True, I did pretend to be a
man during my original life.
But surely there was
no need for you two
to be so shocked
when you saw me.
I'm so sorry, but we
just couldn't help it!
Your legend‐‐I mean,
King Arthur's legend
is extremely famous.
Well, if that's the case,
do you think he might
underestimate my ability
simply because I am a woman?
No, never.
Not at all.
Then again, if he's
upset as you think he is,
I'm certain that
there's another reason.
Such as?
He's probably upset
at all the people
who were around you at the time.
The selfish ones, the ones
cruel enough and uncaring enough
to force the role of King
upon an innocent little girl.
It was inevitable
that would happen.
I had resigned
myself to that fate
when I drew forth the
sword from the stone.
I believe that that upsets him
even more than anything else,
your resignation to your fate.
Well, then he forgets his place.
He hasn't the right
to question decisions
made by those of my time,
including those
decisions I made myself.
That's why he says
nothing about it to you.
I'm afraid that Kiritsugu Emiya,
and the hero Arturia will
never get along with each other.
He must've resigned
himself to that fact.
He wants to use the Holy
Grail's power to save the world.
That is his ambition
and yours, correct?
Yes, but you must understand
that I get my beliefs
directly from him.
My own desire for the
Grail is exactly the same.
♪
It is my fervent
wish to save Britain
since I could not
protect it in life.
I think what you and Kiritsugu
seek is right and just,
something to be proud of.
♪
Our next match won't
happen until you come back
from your trip
to Japan, will it?
That's right.
How long do you think your work
will keep you and
Mommy away from home?
When will you come back?
I should be back here
in two weeks or so.
Your mom won't be back
for quite a while, though.
Yeah, Mommy told me
about that already.
She said we'd be
apart for a long time.
She also told me that even
if we don't see each other
for a long, long time,
she'll always be
right here by my side,
so I shouldn't
ever feel lonely.
She told me that
before I went to sleep.
I'm gonna be
together with Mommy,
well, forever and ever and ever!
I see.
♪
Listen, Ilya.
Daddy?
Can you wait for me, Ilya?
Even if you're lonely, can
you last till I come home?
Mhm!
Good, then I promise
you I'll be home
before you know it.
Fill, fill.
Fill her up, fill.
Repeat four times.
Or was it five times?
Um, and then I have to destroy
it each time it's filled.
Wait, is that right?
All right, now,
fill and fill and
fill and fill and fill.
Okay, that's five times.
Right!
At all three murder scenes,
officials tell us
a mysterious pentagram
was found drawn in
the victim's blood.
‐Police speculate‐‐
‐Do you think that maybe I went
a little bit too far?
(thudding)
♪
Hey, do you believe in
terrible demons, kiddo?
All the newspapers
and magazines right now
are saying I'm some
kind of terrible demon.
But suppose demons like that
really did exist in the world.
I mean, wouldn't that
be awfully rude to them?
You've gotta be pretty
clear about these things.
Yo, I am Ryunosuke
Uryu, and I am a demon!
Ah‐ha, I don't know if that's
the right way to go about it.
But look, I found
this little baby!
It's some dusty old book
from deep inside
our big storehouse.
Looks like some of
my ancestors were doing
a bunch of research on how
to go about summoning demons!
So, like, I've just gotta find
out if there really are demons!
Understand?
But you know, if a
demon really did appear,
it would be pretty stupid of me
to just chat with it for a while
and then just send it back
to whatever pit of
Hell it came from.
So, kid, if a demon
does show up around here,
would you mind
letting it kill ya?
(whimpering)
(screeching)
(laughing)
I wonder what it's like
being killed by a demon!
How many people get to find out?
♪
Wait a minute, what's that?
(static crackling)
♪
I'll ask you, you
who calls to me,
oh, summoner who manifests me
within the vessel of a caster,
I ask you your name.
Who?
Who art thou?
♪
Um, uh, well,
I'm Ryunosuke Uryu,
and I'm currently
working odd jobs.
My hobby is murder
of all varieties.
I really like kids and
sometimes young women.
Very well, the pact is
now officially sealed.
It's my irresistible desire
to possess the Holy Grail
exactly as you do.
The sacred vessel of paradise,
the cup of awesome and
terrible power will be ours!
The Holy‐‐what?
Anyway, how would you
like a little snack
just to kick things off right?
Here, wanna eat this kid?
(screeching)
♪
Wow, that's human
skin, isn't it?
(speaking foreign language)
♪
(screaming)
(ripping)
Don't be frightened, little boy.
You'll be fine.
(ripping)
Can you stand?
All right, now, little boy.
You can leave the room through
that door right over there.
You think you can manage that?
Hey, what are you doing?
Shh.
(screaming)
♪
Terror has its
degrees of freshness.
The more intense the fear,
the more all of the
other emotions die.
Terror, in its truest sense,
is not a static state,
but rather a dynamic one.
It is the sublime
moment when shining hope
turns to utter despair.
Did you enjoy that?
The tantalizing flavor of
fresh terror and bloody death?
♪
Cool!
You are awesome!
You are the coolest thing ever!
Okay, look, I don't know
anything about this Grail crap,
but from this moment
on, I am with you.
Let's go kill!
I want you to take me out
and show me even cooler ways
to torture and kill!
Ah‐‐the name is
Ryunosuke, correct?
What a magnificent
omen to be blessed
with such an understanding
master like yourself.
I feel my darkest dream
is nearly within my grasp.
Oh, hey, I didn't get your name.
What is it?
You wish to know my name.
Let me see now, in this era,
the most common name
for me would be, uh...
perhaps for now I'll
just call myself Bluebeard.
The church contacted me.
They said that
the seventh servant,
a caster has finally appeared.
The final servant
has been summoned?
Then it's time.
Indeed.
You are to leave here now,
and head immediately
to Tohsaka Manor.
And once I arrive?
The Manor is
surrounded by a number
of powerful magical barriers,
but they should be
child's play for you.
(laughing)
Are you sure about this?
I was under the impression
that you were allies
with Tokiomi Tohsaka.
Don't you worry about that.
Even if it means you have
to engage Archer in battle,
there's no need to fear.
No need to fear Archer,
one of the three great Knight
classes of the Grail Wars?
♪
I leave the rest to you.
Eliminate Tokiomi
Tohsaka at once.
♪
(whooshing)
This will be easy.
(groaning)
You are nothing
but a slimy worm.
Who gave you permission
to look up at me?
(exploding)
No need...to fear that, he says?
(whooshing)
(exploding)
♪
You are not worthy
to gaze upon me.
A filthy worm like you
should face the ground,
crawl on your stomach, and die.
♪
At last, it's time for the
fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
It's unspeakably ugly.
The item I left
you, where is it?
This will be fun!
Welcome!
Grant me victory in this fight!
I will, without fail.