♪
Aniplex
(click)
♪
(grunting)
Hurts, huh?
Mages carry the pain
of that crest forever.
♪
You know, I think
your dad really gave you
the perfect name.
(panting)
♪
Your origin is based on
cutting and tying, kid.
The nuance is a little different
than destroy and regenerate.
If you cut a thread
and then re‐tie it,
it will be thicker
where you cut it,
isn't that right?
In that sense, it
carries a connotation
of irreversible change.
(grunts)
Kiritsugu, with the
characters for cut and tie,
these will be your
ace in the hole.
♪
I've powdered some of your ribs
and put a little bit in here.
Your origin will materialize
in anything shot by this bullet.
If your target attempts
to use any magic against it,
it will cut his circuits
and thoroughly fry them.
Just one shot will
incapacitate him.
I've made 66 in total.
Don't waste them.
(grunting)
♪
(panting)
(grunts)
♪
Natalia, do you read me?
I'm almost there.
Roger.
(panting)
(grunts)
♪
Natalia, do it.
(panting)
♪
(shouting)
(splash)
♪
(panting)
(gun cocks)
Huh?
♪
(whimpering)
(gunshot)
♪
(gasps)
(panting)
♪
In the end, after
leaving the island,
I spent the next several years
living with Natalia Kaminski.
♪
That meant choosing the
same path as Natalia.
♪
The solitary path of a
highly skilled master hunter.
♪
Natalia belonged
to no organization.
She was a total freelancer,
interested only in the
money she could earn.
The Mage's Association
and the Church,
the rivalry between those
two enormous organizations
kept her business booming.
♪
During that time,
I witnessed many tragedies
like the one on Arimago Island.
♪
I also learned that
all around the world
on every single continent,
the same horrors
happened every day.
♪
(gunshot)
(gunfire)
♪
Just missed.
(grunts)
(gunfire)
♪
Are you trying to be
a hero or something?
♪
Was there no meaning to it?
I thought‐‐
I thought I had
killed my father
to keep more people
like them from dying.
(laughs)
Killing merely one
man isn't the solution.
It's not that simple.
♪
Kill every single person
all around the world
who's like our target here.
If you could somehow
manage to do that,
maybe it would be possible.
♪
No matter what happens, do
whatever you must to survive.
That's a rule I
set for myself
when I got started
in this business.
Regardless of what you face,
put your own life ahead
of anything or anyone.
♪
Look, kid, if you
try to save someone
and you get yourself killed,
it'll all be for nothing.
I don't think it's
possible to save everyone.
♪
But I do want to save as
many as I possibly can.
Well, suit yourself.
(birdsong)
(phone ringing)
This target really is
a nasty piece of work.
Do you know him?
The Mage Odd Vorzak.
He's a Dead Apostle who
uses his bee familiars
to create his ghouls.
The Mage's Association has
put a huge bounty on his head.
You know a lot about him.
He causes destruction
wherever he goes.
The last town he
visited was completely
and utterly annihilated.
Our town.
♪
(lighter strikes)
Natalia, can I have
one of those too?
How old do you have
to be in your country
to smoke tobacco?
I won't try to stop you,
but they aren't good for you.
♪
What's his destination?
There's a flight from Paris
to New York in four days.
Vorzak will be on board.
I'll be handling this myself.
This guy is
a clever target
who managed to give
me the slip once.
You gotta clean up
your own messes, right?
So, even you fail sometimes?
That should tell you
how tough he really is.
♪
What should I do?
I'm fairly certain
he has associates
working for him in New York.
I want you to go there
and eliminate them.
♪
Then you'll fight Vorzak alone.
He can't keep his bees
with him in a carry‐on
when he flies.
I see.
There's no risk of him
getting away from you this time.
(Natalia laughs)
Shut your mouth, kid.
♪
Kid, do you copy?
(radio static)
Roger.
Loud and clear.
All right, good luck
to both of us then.
♪
(gunshot)
(grunting)
♪
That was much easier
than I expected.
Yes, well, I'm just
glad you were able
to kill him with
a minimum of force.
(flames billow)
All right, Kiritsugu,
his corpse is in
the passenger cabin.
Are you ready to carry it out?
I've secured a vehicle.
The only thing we
need now is a doctor
who will carry out
our sick patient.
(Natalia laughs)
I don't have a license,
but that's okay.
(whimpering)
(groaning)
Hey.
Natalia, what's wrong?
A ghoul!
(buzzing)
We have a big problem here.
He was keeping the bees
inside of his own body.
Natalia, you have to get out.
I'm not exactly close
to the ground here.
I didn't come prepared
to sky dive out of here.
(crashing sound)
(Natalia laughs)
This isn't good.
Looks like they've
taken the cockpit.
(sighs)
I've got no choice.
Natalia, what
are you gonna do?
I am coming home.
I'm coming home alive
carrying Vorzak's body.
But first I need to do
something about this plane.
(Kiritsugu start to speak)
You got something to say?
Yeah.
You can do this, Natalia.
(laughs)
That'll do.
Prepare a nice warm
bed for me and wait.
(seething)
(grunts)
♪
(radio static)
Hey, kid,
do you read me?
You didn't fall
asleep, did you?
Reading you loud
and clear, Natalia.
We've both been up all night.
It's a rough morning.
If you'd slept in
a bad last night
with me stuck up here,
I would have to kill you
after this is over.
Now, I have good
news and bad news.
Which do you want first?
Isn't it a rule that you always
start with the good news?
Okay.
I guess I'll start
with the good news then.
For the time being, I'm alive.
The plane is also undamaged.
I made it up to the
cockpit fairly easy,
though repairing the comms
array wasn't easy at all.
I also think
I can pilot it,
assuming the controls
are similar to a Cessna.
Have you contacted
the control tower?
I have.
At first they
thought I was pulling
some kind of prank.
Those kind folks say
they'll escort me in.
All right.
And the bad news?
I'm the only one here who
hasn't been bitten or stung.
300 passengers and crew,
they're all ghouls now.
All that separates me from the
Night of the Living Flying Dead
is the damn
cockpit security door.
Spooky, right?
(exhales sharply)
Given everything
you've just told me,
will you be able to make
it out of this alive?
Well, the cockpit door
is actually pretty tough.
They're scratching
at it as we speak,
but they can't seem
to break it down.
It's the landing
that's worrying me.
This thing may be too big
for me to handle by myself.
Natalia, I know you'll
be able to manage it.
(laughs)
Were those words
of encouragement?
It's good to hear
them from you.
(laughs)
I can handle the landing.
But what do I do with all
these monsters in back?
Hm.
Don't worry about that.
I have it all
worked out, Natalia.
Hm?
(laughs)
I can always count on you.
50 more minutes till
we get to the airport.
That's a little bit too
long to spend praying.
Kid, keep me company
for a while, okay?
I can do that.
♪
Way back when
you first said
you wanted to help
me with my work,
I really didn't
know how to respond.
You just didn't look ready to
relent no matter what I said.
So, I showed that little
promise as a student?
No, it's not that.
You had a lot of potential.
Too much.
What does that mean?
The ability
to pull a trigger
to kill regardless
of your feelings
is a skill most
killers take many years
to fully develop.
You had that skill
from the very start.
It's a hell of a gift.
But choosing your occupation
based solely on your talents
doesn't necessarily
guarantee your happiness.
If you think only
of what you should do
and completely ignore
what you want to do,
then you're just
a simple machine,
a force of nature.
That isn't how a
human being should live.
I'm surprised.
You know, I always
thought of you
as a much colder
person than that.
What are you talking about?
Of course I'm cold.
In all these years,
have I ever spoiled you
or coddled you even once?
True, you've always been
a rather strict teacher.
You never held anything back
and taught me what you could.
(latches clicking)
Under normal circumstances,
training a boy like you
is the father's job.
But...well...
(Natalia sighs)
I'm afraid
that in your case
I basically took
away your chance
for that kind
of upbringing.
Anyway, I...
I did feel a
little bad about it.
This was the only way of
life I knew how to teach you.
So you consider
yourself my dad?
I'm a full‐grown woman,
you rude little jerk.
At least call me mother.
You're right.
Sorry.
I spent an
awfully long time
on my own in this
bloody business.
So long that I even
lost track of the fact
that I was alone.
But...it's been pretty
entertaining in its own way,
having something like
a family in my life.
For me too.
For all these years,
I did always think
of you as a mother.
I was happy to have you.
Look, kid, I think we'd
better quit saying stuff
that'll embarrass us next
time we see each other, okay?
(Natalia laughs)
You're throwing me off my game.
I've got to land this
thing in 20 minutes or so.
If I'm laughing over what
we were just talking about
and screw up, I'll end
up dead, you know?
♪
Sorry, I'll stop.
You know, maybe I'm just
getting too old for this job.
Maybe the reason I
screwed up so badly
is because playing
at having a family
made me lower my guard.
If that's true,
I should walk away.
Maybe it's time to retire.
If you quit this job,
what would you do
with your life?
If I weren't working...
(laughs)
The only thing
left for me to do
would be to really act
like a mother, I guess.
(seagulls calling)
♪
Natalia, you are...
...my real family.
♪
(missile roaring)
(explosion)
(seagulls calling)
Did you see that, Shirley?
I killed someone again,
just like I did with my dad.
I didn't screw up
like I did with you.
I saved an awful lot of lives.
If Natalia had landed
that plane safely,
there's no telling
how many people
might have died.
Her sacrifice
prevented all of that.
So I...
Shirley, I...
(weeping)
(screaming)
Shut your mouth.
Just shut up.
Bastard!
(wailing)
♪
Tell me, Kerry,
what do you want
to grow up to be?
♪
I...
I want to...
♪
Who are you?
What a bad joke.
How does the life you
took from Sakura feel?
By my Command Seal,
I order you!
You look focused
just like you used to.
This is a battle
that I got us into.
You know what,
I'm really happy.