Well, everything went smoothly.
These games of yours
are tiresome and tedious
and squander
my precious time, Tokiomi.
I am very grateful,
Your Highness.
♪
King of all Kings, Gilgamesh.
Your deeds tonight will
establish your prowess as king
and they will reveal which
of our foes we must hunt
and eliminate.
I ask only that you
stay your hand for just
a little while longer.
Very well.
For the time being,
I shall amuse myself
with simple reconnaissance.
This age truly fascinates me.
I take that to mean
the modern world
is to your liking?
It's unspeakably ugly,
but that is fine
in its own way.
The important thing
is whether any of
the treasures available here
are truly worthy of me.
Of course, if I find
there is nothing in this world
that deserves my adoration,
you will pay dearly
for summoning me.
Of that, you can
be certain, Tokiomi.
Worry not; the Holy Grail
is surely an item fit
to please the King of Heroes.
That will be for me
to ultimately determine
and me alone.
No matter, I'll play along
with your little schemes
for the moment.
Everything of value
in this world belongs to me,
so I can assure you,
no matter how precious
this grail of yours may be,
I will never let a lowly mongrel
even touch it
without my consent.
Tokiomi, I'll leave
the details to you.
♪
(sighs)
My, my, honestly,
I'm amazed Gilgamesh
materialized within
the archer class
considering their reputation
for solo combat skills.
Well, I can let Kirei
handle things from here.
For now,
everything is proceeding
according to plan.
♪
Assassin was killed?
Hey, Rider, this is big news!
One of the seven is already out!
♪
Hey.
(gunfire)
Come on, don't you get it?
Assassin was killed!
Mm‐hmm.
Rider, the Holy Grail
War has started!
I've been out gathering
information day after day
after day after day,
every single damn day!
You sit around eating cookies
watching stuff on the VCR!
You're worse than a familiar,
worse than a rat!
And I told you that
I always want you
to take spirit form
when I don't need you.
I'm giving you all the manna
while you're doing nothing
but eating and watching!
Quit your whining.
Nobody cares if
Assassin is dead or alive.
The only thing he's good at
is skulking around
in the shadows.
He could never pose
a threat to me.
Anyway, boy, here,
this is what matters!
This, the big black
thing they call a B‐2!
It's wonderful!
I'm thinking about
buying 10 or so.
What do you think?
(sighs)
For that much money,
it'd be faster to just
buy the whole country outright.
Oh, I see.
So, the question
is where to procure the money.
Were there some
major city nearby,
such as Persepolis,
we could simply plunder it
and get what we need.
For the moment, I think
that the biggest obstacle
for us will be this Clinton guy.
He will prove a more formidable
opponent than Darius III.
Well, regardless of all that,
I think it's a pretty good thing
that Assassin was eliminated
right off the bat.
I mean, aren't you
the type who prefers
to face his enemy head‐on?
So, it's good news
for us that the guy
who uses sneak attacks
and devious tricks
to fight his battles is out.
We could get some good use
from these Tomahawk things, too.
Saber, Lancer, Archer,
the three great knight classes,
not to mention the Berserker,
whose sole skill
is to break things,
are gonna be toast
when you use that
noble phantasm of yours.
That just leaves
Caster to worry about.
If we could only find out
what his true
identity is, we could‐‐
How was Assassin taken down?
Huh?
Tell me.
Who was it that defeated him?
You saw it, right?
I, uh, I think it was
Tohsaka's servant.
It was brutal:
his brilliant appearance,
his quick attacks,
everything was golden,
bright, and flashy.
It all happened so fast,
I couldn't tell what‐‐
You fool!
If I am to fight someone,
it will be the victor
of all the other battles
between the servants.
Why weren't you paying
attention to how he won?
Well, it matters not.
Did anything else strike you
about the flashy gold man
or the way he fought the battle?
But...but it was
the middle of the night
and it was all over in a second.
Hey, Rider, normally
a servant only has one
noble phantasm, right?
Yes, of course, that's the rule.
But how many isn't
the correct way
to conceptualize
a noble phantasm.
As I'm sure you already know,
a noble phantasm is
the physical manifestation
of a hero's most
indelible legend
or most famous tale.
Sometimes, it may be
a specific ability
or a special method of attack.
So, then, is there
a noble phantasm
that consists of throwing
dozens of swords at an opponent?
A sword that makes copies
of itself, really?
Huh, yes, it's possible.
That could still qualify
as a single noble phantasm.
But, wait,
those swords weren't copies.
Each one of them had
a completely different shape.
Ah, forget it,
we'll just have
to discover each
of our enemies' identities
as we encounter them.
(yelps)
(coughs)
Do you really think
that would be wise?
Yes, actually
it'll be more fun!
Food, sex, sleep, and war!
Whatever you do,
you should always
enjoy it to the fullest;
that is the secret of life.
(chuckles)
All right now, let's go
see if we can find ourselves
some invigorating
entertainment outside.
We ride forth, boy!
Prepare yourself!
Uh, we ride forth?
To where?
Well, to somewhere.
We can go anywhere!
Oh, come on, now!
Let's face it,
you can't have been
the only one who was
watching Tohsaka,
which means that news
of Assassin's death
is making the rounds.
The others are probably
going to spring into action
all at once, but we
shall crush each of them
as we come across them.
Go find and crush them all?
It won't be that easy.
I am Rider
and my speed far exceeds
that of any other servant
I will face in this war.
(chuckles)
Wait, wait, wait, not here!
You'll blow up the whole house!
My servant has been lost.
I have forfeited my rights
as a master and cannot continue
the Holy Grail War.
In accordance with the treaty,
I, Kirei Kotomine, ask that
the church grant me sanctuary.
Request granted.
In my role as overseer
of this war, I, Risei Kotomine,
guarantee your safety here.
Enter in peace.
Father, isn't this
church being watched?
No, this holy place
has been declared
a neutral sanctuary.
The Holy Church will censure
any master who dares defy
the decree.
Then, you're sure
it's safe here?
Mmm.
But still, you should
keep watch just in case.
Post a guard here
at all times just to be sure.
Yes, understood.
Tell me, who was
observing the battle?
Before the battle,
I detected the presence
of familiars from
four separate masters.
Two days ago,
I was able to confirm
the summoning of
the final servant, Caster.
All of the Holy Grail War
servants should have now arrived
and the fighting
will begin shortly.
One unaccounted for.
I had hoped that all the masters
would be watching
and taking note
of the encounter.
At this point in the war,
observing the three
families' estates
would be a master's
obvious course of action.
That's right, and if they
can't even think to do that,
it would never even begin
to occur to them to worry
about the existence
of us assassins.
(chuckles)
We spirits of the shadows
shall sneak up behind
those masters who believe
Assassin to be dead.
We shall sneak up behind them,
and this time, we shall become
true shadows in the darkness.
The battle for
the grail is now at hand.
At last, it's time for the
fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
These tired old eyes
of mine will finally see
a wondrous miracle
be performed.
(jet engine roaring)
Oh, my!
So, this is where
Kiritsugu was born?
Well, Saber, how did
you enjoy your journey
through the sky?
It was really
nothing to speak of.
It was far simpler than I
had actually anticipated.
Yes, well, I suppose
that flying must be
nothing special to
a real hero, right?
No, that's not it.
Upon materialization,
all servants receive knowledge
of the modern world.
If required, I could
even pilot this aircraft
with relative ease.
You could?
Are you serious?
My riding skill
allows me to command
any beast or vehicle,
with the only exception
being phantasmal
or divine beasts.
Once I put the saddle
between my legs and take
the reins, I'm in control.
The saddle between
your legs and take the reins?
(chuckles)
What is it?
Did I say something
amusing to you?
Uh‐uh.
Still, you must be
the only servant
who has flown in
an airplane in physical form.
I apologize for that.
If only I could
take spirit form.
No, I didn't mean it
like that, really.
I never get tired
of watching you.
Irisviel, is there
something odd about me?
No, no, not at all.
When you laugh like that,
there seems to be some
hidden meaning behind it.
What is it?
I want you to be frank with me.
It means that your being stuck
in physical form isn't without
its merits.
It's given me many
enjoyable hours
of choosing outfits for you.
Irisviel, is this manner
of dress truly common
for women of this era?
I choose it for you
to balance out my own outfit.
You don't care for it?
No, it is fine.
It is rather easy
to move in, and besides,
I'm used to dressing as a man.
This place is so very alive!
Kiritsugu was supposed
to have arrived here
in Japan already, wasn't he?
That's right,
12 hours before us.
But, don't worry,
he'll find us as soon
as he's certain
the time is right.
For the moment, we'll just
have to keep an eye on things
so that we can act
when the time comes.
We've come all this way,
I'd like to enjoy the city
before the fighting starts.
That's dangerous.
We should first concentrate
on securing a base of operations
and discuss plans
with Kiritsugu.
Well, yes, I suppose
you're right about that.
But it's such a waste;
we've come all this way
to such an exciting place!
That, and...
it's my very first
time travelling.
Oh?
This is the first time
I've ever ventured out
into the world outside
the confines of my home.
Are you telling me
that you spent
your entire life
inside that castle?
♪
You see, I was a puppet
created specifically
for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it isn't
as though I'm wholly ignorant;
Kiritsugu brought me
movies and videos and pictures,
and he's tried in every way
to teach me everything he could
about the outside world.
But this is the first time
that I've actually been able
to see it with my own eyes,
and so, please, forgive me!
I got overly excited.
♪
Please stop the car.
Walking through the city
will be a brand new experience
for me as well.
♪
It is a knight's duty
to serve as escort;
I shall do my very best.
Come with me.
♪
(knocking)
The equipment you requested
arrived a little while ago.
Madam Irisviel and Saber
have just arrived here
in Fuyuki as well.
All the other masters
will likely assume
that she is Saber's master
and act accordingly.
Understood.
There was an incident last night
at the Tohsaka Estate.
I recorded this footage.
(zapping)
What's your analysis of this?
It seems too good to be true.
There seem to be
insufficient time
between Assassin's infiltration
and the Tohsaka
servants' attack.
Assassin has a skill
that masks his presence,
making it improbable
he was detected in advance.
It is my opinion that Tohsaka
was expecting an intruder.
In a battle amongst servants,
learning their identities
is quite critical.
Why would Tohsaka expose
his servant like he did?
He must have had
a very good reason.
I suppose he had to.
Tell me, what became
of Assassin's master?
He took refuge in
a church last night.
The overseer declared him
to be under his protection.
Assassin's master
is Kirei Kotomine.
Maiya, send a familiar
to watch the Fuyuki church.
Are you certain of that?
Masters are forbidding
to take action inside
the neutral zone.
That's been established
around the church.
Place it just far enough away
that the priest won't
be able to spot it.
Very well, understood.
♪
The item I left you,
where is it?
Right here.
♪
(cocks gun)
Approximately two seconds.
I'm surprised.
Indeed.
I was just thinking,
Illya weighs a lot less
than that Walther.
She's...eight years old already.
♪
Focus on the matter at hand,
just empty your mind.
♪
Think of nothing else
except your plan.
♪
It's wonderful!
Almost like a mirror
that reflects the night sky.
♪
It's fun to walk around
a strange and wondrous new town
accompanied by
a gallant gentleman.
Did I really make
an acceptable gentleman escort?
You were absolutely
perfect, Saber.
You really were the most
wonderful knight a girl
could ever hope for.
You honor me, Your Highness.
♪
Saber, do you like the sea?
I suppose; I don't really know.
In my country,
and way back in my time,
the sea was a source
of attacks by barbarians
from the mainland.
I never felt
any affection for it
and often hated it.
I feel kind of bad.
You're a girl, just as I am,
but when you were King Arthur,
you never had the luxury
of enjoying simple things
like this, did you?
So, what about your desires?
Surely, you would
have much preferred
to have Kiritsugu escort you
around town today, right?
Of course I would,
but he couldn't.
It would only cause him
pain and suffering.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy
the time he spends with you?
When he's happy,
for some reason,
it seems to cause him pain.
(gasps)
An enemy servant?
Yes, making its presence
known from the shadows,
100 meters ahead.
It appears to be inviting us
over to go and see it.
How thoughtful;
it wishes to decide
on a battlefield.
Shall we take it up
on its invitation?
I'd like nothing better.
♪
Come on, Rider, let's get
down from here right now!
Take me down!
But why?
This is a nearly perfect
vantage point to survey
the whole land.
I'm leaving!
No, wait!
Take me back down,
I can't handle this!
Oh, calm yourself.
Waiting is a large part of war.
I wanna go...
I wanna go back to England.
I told you not to be
in such a damn hurry.
You see, things have finally
begun to unfold out there.
(laughs heartily)
This is going
to be a lot of fun!
♪
Welcome.
I have spent the entire day
searching the city for
a worthy foe.
Everyone just slinks away,
hiding in their little holes.
You, alone,
have accepted my offer.
That pure energy
surrounding you;
you are the servant
called Saber, I presume?
Indeed, I am,
and I presume that you
are the one
that's called Lancer?
Being unable
to honorably name myself
to my opponent in combat
troubles me more than
I can describe.
I harbor an enormous
dislike of these rules.
♪
(forceful wind)
Saber, please...be careful.
I can use my healing magic
to act as combat
support for you.
But, more than that, Saber‐‐
Just leave Lancer to me.
It troubles me that
his master is in hiding
and has not yet shown himself.
Perhaps they plot something.
Watch yourself.
And, Irisviel,
from this point on,
I entrust you
to watch my back.
Very well, I will, Saber.
Grant me victory in this fight.
I will, without fail.
♪
Let's see what you can do,
my adorable King of Knights.
Tales of the Saber class'
magic resistance were true.
This man is impressive.
That's enough fun
for now, Lancer.
What's going on with Saber?
I'll go, take me
with you, dammit!