(buzzing)
♪
Fionn mac Cumhaill,
hero of Ireland and leader
of the Knights of Fianna,
and my daughter, Grainne,
are pleased to announce
their engagement!
Everyone, this night,
I want you all to celebrate!
That striking man with
the mole beneath his eye,
what is his name?
He is a knight of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Diarmuid...
♪
(slamming)
Traitor.
You will suffer
for this, Diarmuid.
Take me with you.
We must run away.
♪
Rejoice, Grainne!
Fionn has
recognized our marriage.
♪
Did you believe I'd forgotten
what happened with Grainne?
(gasping)
A dream?
♪
That dream I had...
It was the legend
of Diarumuid.
Could those have been the
memories of my servant?
(groaning)
Where am I?
I see that you're awake now.
(grunting)
Sola‐Ui!
What is a meaning of this?
Wh‐‐what am I
doing this place?
So I gather that you
have no memory at all
of what happened to you?
I‐‐I was shot.
I defended myself with the
Volumen Hydragyrum, but...
...what happened to my body?
Your body's magic circuits
have misfired somehow.
You're lucky you
didn't die instantly.
For now, I've only been able
to regenerate your organs.
♪
But your magic circuits
were utterly destroyed.
I'm afraid you'll
never use magic again.
But I can't...
I can't...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too soon to give up.
It will be all right.
We haven't lost yet.
Sola‐Ui.
If the Holy Grail is truly
an omnipotent
wish‐granting device,
then healing you completely
and making you whole again
should be more than
possible for it.
We need only to win.
If we succeed and
claim the Grail,
everything will
return to how it was.
So, with that
in mind, Kayneth,
why don't you give
the Command Seals to me?
That way, I can take
over as Lancer's master.
I'll win the war and
bring the Grail to you.
No.
I won't.
Oh, you don't
believe in me then?
Me, who will marry
into Archibald family?
No, I just...
Sola‐Ui, do you think...
...Lancer would
actually just abandon me
and then swear fealty to you?
I do.
He is a Heroic Spirit here
by the Grail's invitation.
He desires the Holy
Grail just as we do,
even if he must
take on a new master.
He will accept it for
the sake of his goal.
He won't!
Lancer isn't the fine
man you think he is!
And why do you say
that, Kayneth?
When I asked him
what he would wish for
if he had the Grail,
he said to me,
"I have no interest
in the Holy Grail."
A servant with no desire
for the Grail is impossible!
He's hiding something
important from me.
But no matter.
What deep, dark secret
he's trying to keep hidden,
as long as I bear
these Command Seals,
he must obey me
unconditionally.
Kayneth?
I won't give you
the Command Seals.
(sighing)
Oh, Kayneth,
you still don't get it.
Don't you see?
We must win this war
no matter what the cost.
(cracking)
(groaning)
Listen, Kayneth.
With my limited
skills as a healer,
it is quite impossible
to remove any
Command Seals by force.
The bearer's willing
consent is the sole way
for me to take them
without resistance.
If you truly
cannot accept this,
you will leave me no choice.
I will have to
amputate your right arm.
What's your answer?
(whirring)
(sighing)
How is she?
She's going to be all right.
Magical healing can
put a tremendous stress
on the patient.
I think it will take some
time yet before she wakes up.
Watch her for a while, okay?
You're going to report
to Kiritsugu now?
Yes, Saber.
I'm sure he's worried too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
I'd like you to
speak to him for me.
Tell him I feel that we must
pursue Caster immediately.
But, Saber.
Inaction on our part
will mean the deaths
of many more
innocent children.
(sighing)
(knocking)
May I come in?
How long before Maiya's back?
Not too long, but she
has to stay in bed
for another day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stay here.
I'm going to go
follow Kayneth.
No, Kiritsugu, wait a minute.
Did Saber tell you?
She thinks we should go
after Caster right away.
Apparently so.
Are you angry at Saber for
not interfering with Lancer?
Iri, saving a few children,
or even a few dozen
for that matter,
is not our goal.
Saber probably never doubted
that Lancer would
spare me that day,
but if Lancer had
betrayed her, then what?
Our Grail War would have
ended right then and there.
There's no need to tell
her where I'm going.
(door opening and closing)
Lancer, please show yourself.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, how
fares Master Kayneth?
Not well, I'm afraid.
But I've done
everything I can for him.
This isn't your
fault, Lancer.
Kayneth brought
it upon himself.
All it means is
that the Grail War
was far too much
for him to handle.
It's not that, I just...
Diarmuid, don't you see?
He isn't worthy of
being your master.
(gasping)
Kayneth has
abandoned the battle,
giving his right as
your master to me.
As a knight, my loyalty
is eternally pledged
to Master Kayneth.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, I'm sorry,
but I cannot consent.
You what?
As a servant, do you
not manifest physically
in this world using my mana?
And now I also have
Kayneth's consent,
as well as the Command Seals.
Before I am a servant
of the Grail War,
I am foremost a knight,
and a knight can only
serve but one master.
Am I so unworthy of
being your master?
I have already told you
that is not the issue.
Look me in the eye
when you speak!
Lancer, fight beside me.
Please, you must protect me.
Lend me your support.
Come and help me
win the Holy Grail!
I cannot.
If Master Kayneth has given
up his quest for the Grail,
then I no longer have
any interest in it.
We require a
miracle to heal him.
He has no chance otherwise!
We need the Grail
for that miracle.
If you're feeling
responsible for all this,
if you desire to give him
back his life and his dignity,
you must win the Holy
Grail for your master.
Mistress Sola‐Ui, do you
speak as Master Kayneth's wife
and seek the Holy Grail
only on his behalf?
Is that what you're saying?
Uh, well, yes.
Yes, of course.
That is your only desire?
You'll swear to it?
Yes, I swear.
As the wife of Lord
Kayneth El‐Melloi,
I shall bring my
husband the Grail.
♪
(sighing)
That look in her eyes.
It is the same
as Grainne had.
♪
I don't hate them
for what happened.
However, fate was
simply too cruel
to allow it to
happen any other way.
♪
What I seek from this life
is the loyalty
denied me in my last.
I wish to keep that sad
fate from happening again.
But...
In my previous life, I threw
myself into many battles...
...oftentimes, ignoring
the lives that would be lost,
and, so, I understand
Kiritsugu's reasoning.
However, the Holy Grail
War has very clear rules.
It is supposed to be a proxy
war conducted by servants
to avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
Isn't that true, Irisviel?
♪
If Kiritsugu and
Lancer's master
had not engaged
in a secret battle,
we could have
struck down Caster.
We would no longer
have to worry about
more innocent
children being killed.
Lancer and I could
have finished our duel
in an honorable fashion.
Is there no chance of
Kiritsugu changing his mind?
♪
If you believe only
one thing, believe this:
For Kiritsugu and me to make
our ideal world a reality,
you are absolutely essential.
♪
(laughing)
Uh...
You know, it does a man
good to watch you drink.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
You should have told us
you had a guest coming over.
I'd have cooked
something special for you.
No, no, don't
trouble yourself.
The simple pleasures
of home and hearth
are what are truly
best in this world.
Oh, my, you are such a
flatterer, aren't you?
(laughing)
We couldn't help but worry
over how Waver was doing
at his school in England,
but if he's managed
to make friends
with a strapping
man like you,
well, I guess we were
worried over nothing.
Hm, not at all.
It is I who am in his debt.
See, he even picked
out these fine pants.
Look at the craftsmanship.
They're fit for a king.
So, how long will you
be in Japan, Alexei?
Oh, I should have all
my work here wrapped up
in about a week or so.
Well, I was just thinking
that, if you like,
you could stay
right here with us.
I'm pretty sure that
there's space enough
to put another futon
in Waver's room.
‐Right, Waver?
‐Futon?
Oh, yes, the bedding that
they sleep on in this land.
Sleeping on a futon does
take some getting used to.
It's strange to sleep on
the floor instead of a bed.
I think that is what is
best about traveling
to distant foreign lands.
My favorite thing in life is
the surprise of the unknown.
Surely, Asia gives me the
most enjoyment in any age.
I couldn't agree
with you more.
(laughing)
I've told you!
Take the spiritual form
when you come and go!
Yes, well, had I done so,
I would not have been
able to retrieve this.
I even managed to procure
this fine pair of pants.
And anyway, boy, it was you
who ordered me to do it.
(clanging)
Why must I, the
King of Conquerors,
go forth to draw water
from some country river?
Because it's a lot
more productive
than eating junk food and
watching all those videos.
Hmm.
♪
What is this, are you
playing at being an alchemist?
I'm not playing.
I am an alchemist, idiot.
How interesting,
what is that?
Spell casting residue,
remnants of magic
left in the water.
And that means someone
was recently using
magic near the river.
If we follow the trail,
it may be able to show us
where to look for Caster.
Hey, boy, did you
know ahead of time
that you were gonna
find something like that
lurking out there
in the water?
Of course not, but
this town is unique
in that water flows
straight through its center,
so water was the
obvious place to look.
♪
Rider, was there anything
between here and here?
A sewage pipe, or maybe
an irrigation channel?
Oh, yes, there was one of
considerable size down there.
That's it.
If we follow it,
it will probably lead us
right to Caster's hideout.
Hmm.
Boy, are you certain
you aren't a mage
of not inconsiderable skill?
Look, a truly skilled mage
wouldn't have to
do it this way.
As a skill,
it's pretty basic.
Wait a minute, you're
making fun of me, aren't you?
No, boy, quite the opposite.
To accomplish
something so impressive
using a simple method
outshines those who use
a more complex technique.
As your servant, I am proud.
Right.
Now that we have his location,
he's as good as ours.
Shall we go give him a good
beating right away, boy?
Wait a second.
We're talking about
engaging Caster here.
‐I know.
‐No, you don't.
When it comes to
defending his lair,
he has a tremendous
advantage over any attacker.
What kind of moron would just
go bursting in the front door?
Listen here, in a
combat situation,
enemy and ally positions
can practically
change by the second.
If you fail to
attack the enemy
when you know his location,
it will be too
late for regrets
once you've
missed your chance.
Really, and what's made
you so eager today?
Shouldn't I be?
My master has
finally contributed
something of worth to
our great endeavor.
As your loyal servant,
I must also do my sacred duty.
Seek out and
defeat the enemy
and bring back
his head to you.
Ha‐ha, do not be
so quick to give up
before we have even begun.
Let us go and see
what we can find.
It may well work out
better than you imagine.
Ah!
You see, I was
right, wasn't I?
Everything has
worked out splendidly!
(grunting)
♪
Hmm, unfortunately,
Caster appears to be away.
♪
Is this some kind of
water storage system?
Hey, boy, I think
it would be best
if you didn't see this.
What are you talking about?
If Caster isn't here,
we should at least search
for clues to his whereabouts.
It'd be dumb not to.
That may be so,
but don't do it.
Boy, this is far
too much for you.
Oh, shut up.
(clicking)
(crackling)
(sighing)
(gasping)
♪
(gasping and retching)
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you not to look.
Shut up!
Damn it, stop
making fun of me.
Damn it.
This is no time for
pride, foolish boy.
Your reaction is natural.
If I saw someone who
could look on all of this
and still remain unmoved,
I would punch them hard.
What do you mean you'd
punch them, you idiot.
What about you?
You look fine, just
like you always do.
That's because now is not
the time for emotion.
Huh?
(clanging)
Because my young master
is in mortal peril!
♪
Assassin?
But that's impossible.
Assassin's dead.
I saw him die.
We can't afford to
be surprised, boy.
(gasping)
♪
But how?
The how of it is totally
irrelevant to us now.
However, one thing
here is for certain.
Anyone in this
war who believed
in Assassin's untimely
demise, as we did,
has been thoroughly deceived.
(growling)
♪
They ran.
Didn't they?
Do not let your guard down.
We killed two,
but there appeared to
be an additional two.
At this rate, who can
say how many assassins
there truly are out there?
This is Assassin's
preferred terrain.
We should withdraw
from here at once.
Should we really
leave it like this?
Perhaps you'd find something
if you were to look,
but let it go.
For now, we'll just have
to break what we can.
If nothing else, it will
serve to slow Caster down.
♪
(lowing)
(crying)
♪
With his hideout destroyed
and completely in ruins,
Caster will no longer
be able to hide.
He'll be forced to
come out of the shadows,
into the open,
and show himself.
Then after that,
it won't be too long
before we put an end
to him and his master.
All right.
I get it!
Quit doing that!
(laughing)
Let us be off, boy.
♪
Do not let it
trouble you, Kirei.
Indeed, it is unfortunate that
Assassin was exposed to them
before we could
discern the nature
of Rider's ultimate weapon.
But from this encounter,
we found out that
Rider's master
is a mere third‐rate mage.
Yes, but had they
not been discovered...
You think that other options
would have become
available to you?
Yes.
Hm.
While your plans are
certainly important,
you must see to it
that you remain refined
and relaxed in all matters.
Dignity is required
even during battle.
But I never expected
that he'd be such a
dull and boring person.
We will certainly
have another chance
to see Rider's
ultimate attack.
Have Assassin to
continue to monitor Rider,
but remind them to take
great care as they do.
Yes, my teacher,
it will be done.
♪
You used too much
mana all at once.
But I'm certain there's
something I can do to help!
I just can't believe
she went to Fuyuki.
Behold, the family
magic of the Matous.
We were just about to
get the party started.
I can't accomplish
anything this way.