♪
Master Kiritsugu!
Your child has been born.
♪
She's so cute, she's adorable,
and so small, so very delicate.
Look, Kiritsugu.
She has your eyes too.
♪
She's beautiful.
I'm so happy that I
could give birth to her.
♪
Iri, I...
I will be the cause
of your death.
♪
I know.
The Einzberns have
dreamed of the day.
It is the very reason I exist.
When I came to know your ideals,
I made your wish my own.
You made me who I am today.
You have guided me on my path.
You offered me a better life
than that of a simple puppet.
You needn't pity me,
because I am part
of you already.
‐So‐‐
‐But...
I have no right
to hold that child.
None.
♪
Kiritsugu, don't forget.
You're striving to
make a whole new world
where no one cries.
This is what your whole
life has been about.
Eight more years,
and your fight
will come to an end,
and our ideal
will become reality.
The Holy Grail will save you.
I'm certain of it.
So take this child, Ilyasviel,
and hold her close.
Hold her and be proud,
like any other father would be.
♪
‐A Command Seal?
‐Yes.
The mark identifies
you as a participant
in the Holy Grail War.
A stigmata bestowing
upon you the power
to command a servant.
Kirei Kotomine.
The Holy Grail War,
the battle for an ancient
relic that performs miracles.
But why me?
Normally, those
chosen by the Grail
as masters for the servants
are experienced and
accomplished mages.
It is highly unusual
for someone like you,
who has no connection
to magic whatsoever,
to be chosen to participate.
Heroic servants.
I still find it strange to
command the summoned spirits
of ancient heroes to
fight as familiars.
Of course, I know all this can
be very difficult to believe,
but heroes from every age
and nation will come back
to life in the modern world,
killing one another
to vie for supremacy.
That is the Holy Grail War.
Also, there is an unspoken
agreement among all involved
to keep this all secret.
To ensure this rule is kept,
someone of the Holy Church
is always sent as an observer.
Should one of us
really be judging?
A secret battle between
godless magicians?
A Mage's Association member
would be too partial
to one party to assure fairness.
And so once again, just as
we did some 60 years ago,
we've recruited your
father to watch over
and referee our battle.
My father will be
coming to Fuyuki?
But wait, how can this
be considered fair?
It's a conflict of interest
for the overseer's child
to also be a participant.
Tokiomi?
Perhaps it's time
we got to the point.
Kirei, everything we've
spoken of thus far
is just the official background
of the Holy Grail War.
However, there is an additional
reason I've introduced you
to Mr. Tokiomi
Tohsaka here today.
And what would that be?
Actually, we found
proof a long time ago
that the Holy Grail that
will appear in Fuyuki
is not the sacred relic that
belonged to the Son of God.
So I gathered, otherwise,
an order to retrieve it
would've been given to us of
the Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
Be that as it may,
Fuyuki's Holy Grail
is far too powerful to ignore.
It is an omnipotent
wish‐granting device.
Who knows what disaster
it could unleash
should it happen to fall
into the wrong hands.
In which case, the best course
of action would be to ensure
that the Fuyuki Grail
falls into the right hands,
hands that would not misuse it.
The Tohsakas are a family
of mages, but they are mages
with a long history of
friendship with the Church.
We know what kind
of person Tokiomi is,
and more important
than anything else,
the Tohsakas' ultimate
intentions for the Grail
are plain and honorable.
To reach the root.
That is the Tohsaka
family's sole desire.
But the Einzberns and
Matous have both forgotten
the wish we once
shared with them,
and have other less
altruistic plans now.
It goes without
saying that the plans
of the other masters
will be even worse.
Who knows what dark desire
they may harbor for the power
of the Grail should
they obtain it.
That being said, I assume that
the goal of my participation
is to ensure Tokiomi
Tohsaka's victory,
rather than to prevail myself.
To achieve that goal we will
conduct ourselves in a manner
that will maintain the
appearance of us being enemies.
However, we will actually
be working together
in total secrecy to soundly
defeat the other five masters,
and assure our
victory in the end.
And so, Kirei, you will
be officially transferred
from the Church to
the Mage's Association
where you will
become my student.
The official orders
have already been issued.
You must go to Japan and
study the principles of magic,
and become a mage of
sufficient strength and skill
to command a servant
in the Holy Grail War
in three years time
when the battles begin.
♪
Now then.
Do you have any
questions for us, Kirei?
Only one.
How exactly does the Holy Grail
go about selecting its masters?
What kind of
criteria does it use?
Hm.
The exact criteria
it uses is unknown,
but it chooses those
masters who need it most.
So all the participating
masters have a reason
to covet the Grail?
Not necessarily.
I'm told that in the past there
were cases where Command Seals
appeared on those whom you
would never have expected.
Oh, I think I understand.
You're still puzzled at
being chosen to be a master
by the Grail, aren't you?
♪
I didn't expect Kirei to
give his consent so quickly.
My son would jump into fire
if the Holy Church
ordered him to do so.
To be honest with you,
I'm even a little shocked.
From his perspective, he's
being drawn into a senseless war
that has absolutely
nothing to do with him.
No, this is as it should be.
Perhaps this ordeal
will do him some good.
Only a few days ago,
my son lost his wife.
I believe that a complete
change of scenery
and a difficult new
mission to focus on
may be exactly what he
needs to nurse his wounds.
♪
Hi, Aoi.
Kariya, it's good
to see you again.
You're back from your trip?
This one seemed to
last a long time.
Yeah, I guess it did.
Uncle Kariya!
Uncle Kariya, welcome back!
Hi, Rin.
Did you bring me
a present again?
No, Rin, you're being very rude.
Here.
(giggling)
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
You are very welcome, Rin,
I'm glad you like it.
(indistinct conversations)
Where's Sakura?
Sakura's gone now.
‐What did she mean?
‐Sakura is‐‐
well, she's no
longer my daughter
or Rin's little sister.
She's now with...
the Matou family.
But why?
The Matous want a child
who carries in them
the blood of a mage.
You know why, better
than anyone else.
♪
The head of the Tohsaka
family decided to give
our ancient allies, the Matous,
that which they requested.
It wasn't my place to speak out.
You're all right with that?
When I married into
the Tohsaka family,
when I decided to marry a mage,
I knew what might
be required of me.
And you're all right with that?
The reality is that a
clan bearing mage blood
can never expect to enjoy the
happiness of a normal family.
That's not true!
When you married him you wanted
happiness, you wanted‐‐
Enough!
This is between the
Tohsakas and the Matous.
You left the world of
mages a long time ago.
This doesn't concern you.
♪
If you get the chance
to see Sakura again,
please be kind to her.
She was always very fond of you.
So, the failure
actually had the nerve
to show his face here.
I distinctly
remember telling you
to stay far away
from this house,
and to never darken my
doorstep again, Kariya.
I heard you adopted the
Tohsaka's second daughter.
Then you have sharp ears.
Is it really so
important to keep mages
in the Matou lineage
that you have to do this?
Would you tell
me we're wrong to?
You of all people?
Tell me who's fault
do you think it is
for our present
reduced circumstances.
Kariya, had you only agreed
to carry on the family name
and to learn the
secrets of the Matou,
things would never
have gotten this bad,
and that little girl would
still be with her mother.
You're not fooling
anyone, you vampire.
You only want the Grail to
give yourself eternal youth.
You just wanna live forever.
(laughing)
Nearly 60 years have
passed since the last time
the masters gathered, but
the Matous have no pawns yet
to offer for the
fourth Holy Grail War.
Though you have it inside
you, your brother Byakuya
lacks the power needed
to control a servant.
But even if we forfeit this
round, we could still win
the next in 60 years
if we prepare ourselves.
The Tohsaka girl's womb
will one day bear us
a powerful mage,
one who could prevail.
She has a lot of potential,
that one, she could be the key.
So then in other words, if you
can get your hands on the Grail,
you won't need Sakura
Tohsaka anymore.
What is it you're
scheming, Kariya?
A trade, Zouken.
Next year I will return from
the Grail War, Grail in hand,
and in return, you
will release Sakura.
Don't be a stupid idiot.
You're a failure and you haven't
trained a day in your life.
You actually believe
that in a single year
you'll achieve the power
to control a servant?
You have the secret magic
to make that happen
and you know it, using your
special worm techniques.
‐So?
‐You can implant me
with your crest worms.
Kariya, you want to die?
The Matous should
rely on themselves
to gain what they want.
I won't let anyone
else get involved.
Surely you're not concerned
for my wellbeing, Father.
(snickering)
If what you're trying to do
is keep her out of all this,
Kariya, I'm afraid
you're a little late.
You bastard, you didn't!
♪
For the first three days
in there she did nothing
but constantly
scream her head off.
But on the fourth, she settled
down and finally stopped.
Early this morning, I threw
her down into the worm pit
to see just how long she'd last.
She's been in there for over 12
hours and she's still breathing.
The Tohsakas have very
powerful inner spirits.
‐Sakura!
‐What will you do now?
She's a broken little girl
ripped from the life she knew,
and violated by worms
from head to toe.
But if you still wish to
save her from this ordeal,
I might be willing
to think about it.
I agree.
But I intend to
continue her education
until you show results.
That point is not negotiable.
I still expect to achieve
victory in the next war
60 years from now, but
should you somehow manage
to retrieve the Grail in
this war, all the better.
Naturally, I'll no
longer need the girl.
In that case, her education
will only last a year,
and then she'll be free
to go where she wants.
You won't renege on your
words, Zouken Matou?
You can start by serving as
the breeding ground for a week.
If you don't die or go insane
then I'll concede that
you're actually serious
and will keep my
word completely.
(insects skittering)
It's finally here.
(keys clicking)
What does it say?
It's a report from the spies I
sent to the London Clock Tower.
It says that the Grail chose a
master from within the tower,
the headquarters of
the Mage's Association.
‐Who is it?
‐A rather big problem.
The eldest son of
the Archibald family,
a ninth generation mage.
Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald.
(clock chiming)
In the world of mages,
a long and distinguished
lineage is everything.
Nothing else matters.
This is because magic
will not yield up
her secrets in a
single generation.
A parent passes on the
fruits of a lifetime
of magical training
to his child.
Thus, the older
the family of mages,
the greater their power
ultimately becomes.
You are no doubt
wondering why I begin
today's lecture with
something so basic.
It is because a student
from this class submitted
a fascinating paper
to me yesterday.
"How Wizardry Should Be
in the New Century."
It attempts to make a case
objecting to the longstanding
traditions of
which I just spoke.
It claims that if one were to
achieve a deep understanding
of the techniques and
precise control over
mana application, it
would allow one to overcome
any difference
in inherent ability.
In short, even someone
with diluted blood could,
through his own efforts,
become a master mage.
To be honest, I've
learned something
from reading this paper.
Silence, please.
I will be perfectly frank.
This paper is nothing but
immature juvenile fantasies.
Huh?
Blood determines a mage's
powers and abilities.
This is a hard and unchanging
reality of this world.
Even for you, Waver Velvet.
I am very, very disappointed
that one of my students
would indulge in this
moronic nonsense.
Sir, I was only trying
to raise a question
the Mage's Association
has become too
reluctant to address.
Mr. Velvet, if I
recall correctly,
your family has produced mages
for only three generations.
Isn't that right?
Listen to me, compared
to the Mage's Association's
long and illustrious history,
your family is no more
than a newborn baby.
Don't you think a baby
should learn to speak
before it tries
to voice an opinion?
He made a fool of me,
he made a fool of me,
he made a fool of me!
Is that any way for
a teacher to act?
Reading my paper
made him jealous
and he couldn't handle it!
The pompous ass is
afraid of my talent.
That's why he embarrassed
me in front of everyone.
Whoa!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You're in the Spiritual
Evocation Department.
‐Why aren't you in class?
‐Well, uh,
Mr. Archibald asked me
to run an errand for him.
That's why I was in a hurry.
I see, that's great.
Would you mind giving this to
him when you go back to class?
Okay, sure, why not?
Just make sure he gets it,
it's supposed to be important.
It's important?
Package origin, Macedonia?
(thunder rumbling)
♪
This is it.
So it seems that all the rumors
about that bastard
Kayneth Archibald
preparing to fight in some
kind of mages tournament
in the Far East soon are true.
♪
The Holy Grail War.
According to the
legend, 200 years ago,
the Einzberns, the Makiris,
and the Tohsakas,
collectively known as
the three first families,
worked together to
summon the Holy Grail,
said to have the power
to grant any wish,
and eventually succeeded it.
But the Holy Grail
would only grant
one of the family's
supplications.
Their cooperation quickly turned
to violent and bloody conflict.
That was the beginning
of the Holy Grail Wars.
Ever since then,
once every 60 years,
the Holy Grail appears
in the city of Fuyuki.
It selects seven mages
from across the globe
to compete for it,
and grants them powers.
Each magically summons
a heroic spirit
known as a servant.
Archer, Saber, Lancer,
Rider, Assassin,
Caster, Berserker.
Divided into these seven
classes of warriors,
the servants, guided
by their masters,
fight each other to the
death in secret battles
to determine who is
worthy to win the Grail.
♪
So it appears that this
Grail War is a battle
of pure strength
where stupid titles
and influence mean
absolutely nothing.
That looks like it's
the perfect place for me.
Wait, in order to summon a
servant some kind of relic
related to them is needed
to act as a catalyst.
A relic.
♪
(thunder rumbling)
(machine whirring)
That device always strikes
me as being indecent.
There's a report
from the Clock Tower.
It looks like Lord El‐Melloi
has acquired another relic.
His participation in
the war is certain now.
It troubles me that two of the
slots are still unaccounted for.
Don't worry, when the
time comes, the Grail
will select seven,
regardless of skill.
The ones it selects to
round out the group are‐‐
well, often weak
and inexperienced.
Don't concern yourself.
Speaking of matters of
real concern, Kirei,
I trust that no one followed you
or saw you enter this mansion.
No, don't worry.
No familiars or devices,
visible or invisible,
are watching me or
this mansion right now.
‐On that‐‐
‐You have my guarantee.
No matter what tricks
or deception they use,
no one can deceive
the eyes of Hassan,
the spy heroic spirit.
There is no trace of
anyone following my master
or watching this house.
Please, you can put
your mind at ease.
If a servant has been
manifested by another master
my father is certain
to be aware of it.
The other mages will
not take action,
at least for a
little while longer.
Assassin, you may go, continue
guarding the surrounding area.
As you wish.
It's only a matter of
time before that changes.
Very soon now this place will
be swarming with familiars
and magical devices sent by
other masters to spy on me.
‐What is that?
‐Another investigation.
I've been gathering
what information I can
on the Einzbern master.
Nine years ago, the Einzberns,
a family notoriously
proud of their pure blood,
suddenly allowed an outsider
mage to marry into the family.
♪
The Einzbern mages have devoted
themselves solely to alchemy,
rendering them unfit for combat.
Their losses in
previous Grail Wars
can all be traced to that fact.
They must have finally
run out of patience.
The man they chose was
perfect for their needs.
♪
Kiritsugu Emiya,
the man known as
the Mage Killer.
We finally found the relic
we've been searching for
in Cornwall all these years.
If you use it as a catalyst
you'll be able to summon
what is widely
considered the strongest
of all known
sword‐wielding servants.
Kiritsugu, this is the greatest
gift the Einzbern can offer
to the man who is working
in service to our needs.
Thank you, Elder, I am honored.
This time there are
to be no survivors.
You are to hunt down the six
other servants and eliminate
them, and fulfill the
third magic, Heaven's Feel.
Yes, sir.
Kiritsugu Emiya?
Yes, I know that name.
So, even the Holy Church
has heard of this man.
Kiritsugu Emiya,
the Mage Killer,
was quite infamous in his time.
Officially, he was a rogue
mage who didn't belong
to the Association, but
the higher ups found him,
shall we say, convenient
for their own purposes.
It sounds to me like he
was quite similar to us.
Executioners for
the Holy Church.
Far worse, I assure you.
He spent his life as a
freelance master assassin
who specializes in
exterminating mages.
He knows what mages are capable
of, so he deals with them
in a way that is unlike
a mage as possible.
Read that.
Sniping, poisoning,
bombs in public places.
He once brought down
an entire jetliner
just because his
target was on it.
A man who will do anything
without a second thought.
♪
It is because mages
function outside the laws
of the regular world that
we must diligently obey
the strict laws that we
have set for ourselves.
But this man lacks
even a single trace
of a mage's pride or honor.
The methods he employs
are unforgivable.
Then tell me,
what does this
Kiritsugu Emiya gain...
by hiring himself
out as a killer?
Money, I would imagine.
As you can read in that report,
he's been involved in more
than just mage assassinations.
He's appeared in war
zones all over the planet
offering his services
as a mercenary.
I see.
May I borrow this for a while?
(printer whirring)
Let's go over what we
know, Iri, all right?
Of the seven masters that
the Grail will choose
we have identified four of them.
Tokiomi Tohsaka,
Tohsaka family head.
Fire mage, uses jewel
magic, very formidable.
Kariya Matou.
So they took the kid
who left the family
and made him a master, huh?
That old man must be desperate.
Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald.
Wind and water affinity.
He's a top expert in necromancy,
summoning, and alchemy.
‐And next‐‐
‐Kiritsugu Emiya.
Newest member of the Einzbern
family and their trump card,
and the man that I love.
And the fourth master‐‐
no, I mean the fifth one,
is representing the Holy Church.
His name is Kirei Kotomine.
He's from the Church?
He's the son of the overseer,
Father Risei Kotomine.
Reports say he studied
under Tokiomi Tohsaka
starting three years ago,
splitting with him
after his Command Seal appeared.
Did something happen?
This is his personal history.
Read it for yourself.
Kirei Kotomine followed
his father on pilgrimages
around the world
since childhood,
graduated from the St. Ignatius
School of Divinity in Manresa,
skipped two years,
graduated valedictorian.
He sounds pretty impressive.
But then suddenly, he
leaves the primrose path
and volunteers for
the Holy Church.
Why would someone like
that decide to work
for a secret
Church organization?
Maybe because of his father?
It says here that
Kotomine is a member
of the Holy Church's
Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
Then he would've pursued that
path from the very beginning.
But until he arrived at the
same place as his father,
he changed positions
three times.
At one time he was
even an inquisitor.
‐An inquisitor?
‐A heretic hunter.
In essence, exactly what I was.
A ruthless mage killer.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
His assassinations were
always carried out in clusters
over a relatively
short period of time.
During the same
general time periods,
he appeared in a
number of war zones,
but only when the combat
was at its fiercest.
It was almost as if
he had some obsession
with chasing his own death.
These were clearly the actions
of a man bent on suicide.
♪
So then why is he doing this?
Alchemy, necromancy, summoning,
divination, healing.
Interesting, look at all the
categories of magic he studied.
Why did he try to study so many?
He gets almost to the point
of mastery of a discipline,
then switches to another field,
and never looks back again.
It's‐‐it's as if he throws away
everything he's learned
like yesterday's trash.
Iri, this man,
Kirei Kotomine, terrifies me.
He has no concept
of self interest.
His actions are
completely disconnected
from any thought of
risk versus reward.
No way, there's no way
he's just a freelancer
in it for the money.
He's never shown any passion
for anything at all in his life.
He believes in
absolutely nothing.
He has no deep desire,
no wish of any kind
to be granted.
A man like that‐‐
Then what is he after?
Why would he put his life at
risk to get the Holy Grail?
But the Grail chose him
to be one of its seven
masters for this war.
You're right, he must
have some reason
we don't know about
to want the Grail.
But I can't even begin
to imagine what it is,
and that terrifies me.
♪
Kirei Kotomine.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
His endless string of battles
came to a sudden halt
nine years ago, and he
virtually vanished from sight.
It appears that his final
encounter with the mages
of the North, the Einzberns,
is where he at last
found his answer.
So, I must ask the question,
what did he seek
in those battles?
What was he looking for?
And what exactly did he find?
♪
Well, you just barely made it.
If the Grail has chosen
you, that must mean that
you've made at least
some progress as a mage.
I'll give you that much, Kariya.
But look at you.
You look like bloody hell.
Is your left leg
working all right, eh?
(groaning)
♪
Now don't get angry, you know
if you get the crest worms
inside you worked up too much
they'll simply devour you.
Either way, I'd give you
perhaps a month at best before
they do their damage and
drain the life out of you.
‐That's plenty.
‐What did you say?
I said that that will
be plenty of time.
Kariya, this is your present
for surviving an entire year.
I found the perfect
relic for you.
Don't let your loving father's
kindness go to waste.
(chuckling)
I did it, I've got
a Command Seal too!
The Grail chose me as a master!
My incredible talent has been
recognized by the Grail!
I can't just sit here.
I have to prepare
to summon my servant.
Mikina Nishimoto, the missing
sixth grade girl from‐‐
‐Good morning, Waver.
‐Good morning, dear.
How did you sleep?
Morning, Grandpa and Grandma.
Fuyuki's getting bad these days.
Yes, it really is.
By the way, Martha,
it's very strange.
I've heard roosters
making a big racket
since the sun came
up this morning.
What's that all about?
It's because there are
three roosters in our yard.
‐What're they doing there?
‐I don't know.
I've been wondering where
they might've come from.
Oh, sweetie, you
want some coffee?
‐Mhm.
‐Waver.
‐What happened to your hand?
‐Crap.
‐That mark.
‐What mark?
You didn't have that mark
on your hand yesterday.
Ah, bugger!
I really wish you
hadn't noticed that.
‐What's wrong, Waver?
‐What is it, dear?
Nothing's wrong, here,
have some coffee.
I put lots of milk in it.
You two like coffee, right?
They were all stabbed
using a similar,
if not identical, weapon.
(sighing)
What a pain in the ass.
Do I have to start their
hypnosis all over again,
starting from me being their
grandson back from abroad?
(rooster crowing)
I need to think of a cover story
for those roosters I stole too.
I can't believe
they really found
the legendary
Excalibur's scabbard.
There's not a scratch on it.
Is this thing really
1,500 years old?
The object itself is a
type of conceptual weapon.
It doesn't rust or degrade as
ordinary physical objects do.
Just like in the legend
surrounding its existence,
it heals its owner's wounds
and halts the aging process.
Of course, that's
only when supplied
with its original owner's mana.
In other words, the master
can use this in tandem
with the summoned heroic spirit
to protect himself during
the course of a battle.
That's just like you.
What you're saying is that
a tool is just a tool?
That's right, I am,
and that goes for
the servant too.
No matter how famous
the heroic spirit,
when summoned as a
servant they're nothing
but a tool for their master.
Anyone who lets their fantasies
get the better of them
will never have the wherewithal
to win this battle.
And because you're the way
you are, my great‐grandfather
decided this scabbard was
the perfect relic for you.
What do you think?
Does his gift not satisfy you?
Of course it does.
Acht did a wonderful job.
None of the other masters
have something this powerful.
What's wrong with it then?
Given how perfectly the ancient
relic is connected to it,
the heroic spirit,
the one we're after,
will surely respond
to the summons,
the King of Knights,
Arthur Pendragon.
My own compatibility with
him is a secondary concern.
But Arthur, the
wielder of Excalibur,
is sure to be the strongest
Saber class servant
the Grail Wars have ever seen.
That's true.
I'll have a servant far stronger
than any other in the battle.
The question is, how
best to use that power?
How to make it work for us?
To be honest, in
terms of ease of use,
Caster or Assassin would
be far better suited
to the way I usually fight.
What good will it do
to worry about that
before you've even summoned him?
After all, we don't know what
the King of Knights was like,
and besides, no matter
what your strategy is,
once he learns of your
ideals, of your dream,
he'll understand,
I know he will.
♪
Just like I did.
What is it?
I've found my strategy,
the way to get the best use.
From the strongest servant
fighting in the battle.
(grunting)
Hello, Rin.
Oh hello, Kirei.
Heading out?
That's some heavy
luggage you have there.
That's right, I have to go live
with the Zenjou
family for a while.
You're staying to fight
alongside my father
in a coming war, aren't you?
That's why I'm here
as his student,
to help him and
to learn from him.
Kirei, can I depend on you?
Huh?
Will you promise to protect
my father to the end?
Will you promise
to keep him safe?
I'm sorry, but
that's impossible.
If this battle were
going to be simple enough
that I could honestly
make that promise,
we wouldn't have to send
you or your mother away
from here to keep
you safe and sound.
I guess that means I just
can't like you no matter what.
Rin, you shouldn't
just blurt out
what you're really
thinking like that.
People might start to cast
aspersions on your father.
He is the man who's
educating you after all.
My father has nothing
to do with it!
Listen, Kirei, if
you somehow get sloppy
and because of that my
father gets hurt or worse,
I'll show you no mercy, got it?
Rin, what're you
doing out there?
How come you're yelling at him?
Um, I...
‐Well, you see‐‐
‐Oh, she was just giving me
a bit of encouragement before
we said goodbye, ma'am.
Rin, allow me.
That big suitcase is far too
heavy for you to carry alone.
No thank you, I'll
carry it myself.
Kirei, do your best to
take care of my husband.
Please help him to
achieve his desire.
I will do my best.
Please, don't worry.
(knocking)
Excuse me.
You've arrived at a
very opportune time.
The relic I made
arrangements for
finally arrived this morning.
Have a look.
What is it?
A fossil of the very first skin
shed by a snake on this world.
If we use it as a catalyst
and are lucky enough
to summon the heroic
spirit that we're after,
total victory is
as good as ours.
(groaning)
Hey, Sakura.
Did I startle you?
Yeah, your face is‐‐
I know.
Seems I lost a little
bit of it to the worms
that are inside me.
I guess I'm just not quite
as tough as you are.
Uncle Kariya,
you're turning into
a different person, aren't you?
Yeah, maybe.
You know, I don't have to go
to the worm pit again tonight.
Grandfather said there will
be a more important ceremony
‐that I have to attend.
‐Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm going to the
basement tonight instead of you.
Uncle Kariya, are you
going somewhere far away?
Well, I have an important job
that I need to do for a while.
I might not have much
time to talk to you then,
at least until I get back.
‐I see.
‐Hey, Sakura.
When my job is finally over,
you wanna go somewhere
and just have fun?
With your mom and
your sister too.
I don't have anyone I
can call Mom or Sister.
Grandfather said that I
should just think of them
like they never existed.
I see.
♪
‐Uncle?
‐All right then.
When this is all over let's take
Aoi and Rin from the Tohsakas
and go somewhere as far away
from this place as we can get.
We can hang out and have
fun like we used to.
Does that mean we'll
see them again?
Yeah, you will.
You have my word on that.
♪
All right.
‐I have to get going now.
‐Mhm.
Bye‐bye, Uncle Kariya.
♪
Bye‐bye.
I assume you've memorized the
summoning spell correctly?
‐Sure.
‐Very well.
But I'm going to have
to add two extra lines
to the basic incantation.
What do you mean?
It's really quite
simple, Kariya.
Because of your short
time in training,
your rank as a mage is
somewhat lower than that
of the other masters that
the Grail has summoned.
That will affect the
servant's base abilities.
This means we have to boost
the servant's parameters
by attempting to modify
the servant's class
as much as possible.
Kariya, to that end,
I want you to add
the affinity insanity
to the servant
you summon today.
♪
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill.
Repeat five times,
but when each is
filled, destroy it.
For the elements
silver and iron,
the foundation stone
and the Archduke of Pacts,
and for my great
master, Schenewerk,
raise a wall
against the wind
and close the gates
of four directions.
Come forth from the crown
and follow the forked road
leading to the kingdom.
Is a simple ritual
like this really enough
to summon a heroic spirit?
Surprisingly, yes.
You see, the summoning ritual
doesn't require a big
elaborate evocation.
The actual summoning is
preformed by the Grail itself.
My job as a master
is to firmly anchor
the heroic spirit in this
world and to supply it
with enough mana
to take physical form.
That should do it.
Iri, put the relic on the altar.
That is the final step.
Heed my words, my will
creates your body,
and your sword
creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call
and obey my will and reason,
then answer my summoning!
I hereby swear that I shall
be all the good in the world,
that I shall defeat
all evil in the world.
Then let thine eyes be clouded
with the fog of
turmoil and chaos.
Thou who art trapped
in a cage of madness,
and I the summoner
who holds thy chains!
Seventh heaven clad in
the great words of power,
come forth from this
circle of binding,
Guardian of Scales!
♪
Behold him, Kirei.
We have won the battle.
Victory is ours!
♪
Impossible.
I ask you...
♪
Are you worthy to be my master?
I think what you and Kiritsugu
seek is right and just.
The world cannot
serve two lords.
Then I promise you,
you are not worthy
‐to gaze upon me.
‐You are so cool!
Eliminate Tokiomi
Tohsaka at once.