(helicopter droning)
This way, sir.
(siren wailing)
What is that?
♪
All of you,
return to your post.
Looks like an enormous
ball of mercury doesn't it?
It's almost as if the
damn thing is alive.
♪
I need to get
this out of here...
What's the matter,
is something wrong?
I need to get
this out of here,
this out of here.
Sir?
Load that thing
onto the truck!
Quickly!
♪
I'm afraid I must inform you
that the Grail War
is in grave peril.
We have identified
Caster's master
as the person behind the
recent kidnappings in Fuyuki,
a disturbing
revelation, indeed.
Thus, in accordance with
the emergency powers
granted to me as overseer,
I am temporarily altering
the rules of the Grail War.
Masters are to hereby
cease all ongoing combat
in pursuit of the grail
and focus on the
elimination of Caster instead.
And the one who succeeds
in defeating Caster
and his master
will receive an additional
Command Seal as their reward.
These are the unused
Command Seals left behind
by the fallen masters
of past grail wars.
One of them should prove
to be of immeasurable value
to whoever receives it.
Once Caster's destruction
has been positively confirmed,
the Holy Grail War
will recommence
until a victor emerges.
Now then, if anyone
has questions,
please ask them now.
But, of course,
that offer is limited
to those who can actually
speak in human languages.
(fluttering)
Well played, Father.
Now all the masters
will do whatever they can
to hunt him down
and destroy him.
There were five familiars
gathered at the church
for my announcement,
which means that...
Which means that the elusive
missing master Lord El‐Melloi
is still very much alive.
Indeed.
And the offer of a
Command Seal as the reward
should draw him out
given that he's
already used one of his.
Of course, the other masters
will be drawn out as well.
They'll seek to keep the
Command Seal from the rest
by making certain they can
claim it for themselves.
That's true,
but it also means
that the master
who wins the seal
will gain a formidable
advantage over the others.
Naturally, it's not ideal.
Once Caster has been
thoroughly weakened
and is on the run from
all the other masters
who are chasing him,
Archer must be the one
to deal the final blow.
Um...
Excuse me, is this
the Mackenzie residence?
I have a delivery.
Yes, that is the name of
this domicile's residents.
Well, then, might there
be a Mr. Iskandar,
King of Conquerors here?
That would be me.
I see, right.
I should've known.
Uh, could I have
your signature
on this receipt here?
My signature?
Very well.
You have my thanks.
Well, thank you very much
for your business, sir.
(grunting)
(laughing)
To have the entire world
emblazoned across my chest.
What a great feeling!
Wait, why are you
dressed like that?
The package I was
awaiting arrived.
So you went
outside the house?
Ta‐da, I merely tried out
that mail‐order
thing I heard about.
But I told you that
you were never to leave
the second floor!
If the residents
are not at home
and you are off
somewhere all day
occupied with your familiar,
who else is there
to answer the door?
I had no choice.
A summons to appear by the
Holy Church is a big deal
and I had to go.
Don't be so grouchy.
After seeing
Saber last night,
I came to a realization.
If one wears modern attire,
there should be no
issue whatsoever
with going outside
the domicile.
Hey, wait!
Stop!
At least put on some
pants before you go out!
Oh, yes, leggings.
That's true, I forgot.
Everyone in this
land wears them.
Do I have to wear them?
Yes, of course you have to!
And just to be
perfectly clear,
I'm definitely not going
to make a special trip
all the way to town
just to buy you a pair
of triple XL pants, understand?
You won't, why?
Boy, would you
actually stand in the way
of my triumphant
conquest of the world?
You conquering the world
and whether or not you
have pants have nothing,
not even the slightest
thing to do with each other!
Before you start planning to
go screwing around outside,
why don't you go out
and do your job
and beat one of the
other servants?
Then I'll buy your pants
or anything else you want.
Very well.
I understand.
Do you swear
that once I defeat
one of the other servants
you will go and buy me
a modern pair of pants
so that I can go outside?
Unbelievable.
You really want to
put on modern clothes
and go walking
outside that much?
The King of Knights was
walking around outside.
I simply cannot allow
myself to be undone.
I like the design
on this shirt.
It is fitting attire
for a strong ruler.
Look, we have to go find
and defeat Caster too.
What the hell are we doing?
There is a powerful
barrier over Mount Enzo
with Ryuudou Temple
at its center.
Because of that, except for
natural spirits like servants,
anything can enter only
via the temple path.
Keep that in mind as
you're using Saber.
There are three other spots
where the ley lines converge:
Tohsaka Manor, Fuyuki Chapel,
and this new residential area,
east of the city center.
Consequently, this means
that there are four locations
in Fuyuki that have all the
spiritual characteristics
needed for the
grail to appear.
In the war's second phase,
when there are fewer
servants left in the fight,
we'll have to secure
one of these spots
as our base of
operations, won't we?
Yes, that's correct.
Well, that just about
covers the lay of the land.
Are there any questions?
Is there anything that
you aren't clear on?
I understand perfectly.
It was an adequate
explanation.
Kiritsugu, can we assume
that all the other masters
will go after Caster?
It's a safe bet.
However, we have an advantage
as far as Caster
is concerned.
In his madness,
he believes that our Saber
is actually his Jeanne d'Arc
which is to our benefit.
We need only wait
for him to come to us.
But, master,
that is not enough.
His evil deeds
must be punished.
We should take the
fight straight to him
before he can do
any more damage.
♪
Iri, do you have a handle
on this forest's
barrier spells?
Yes, I do, however,
our real problem is
the unbreakable curse
on Saber's left hand.
Eighteen hours
have already passed
since your defeat of Canaan,
but Saber's wound
has still yet to heal.
Lancer must still be alive.
Shouldn't we go find
and defeat Lancer first
so we can face a battle with
Caster at our full strength?
That isn't necessary.
You just need to use
your knowledge of the area
to confuse the enemy,
keeping Saber moving around.
You won't have her
fight Caster?
No, someone else will deal
with him even if we don't.
The masters and servants
hunting Caster in a frenzy
will make excellent
targets for us.
I'll attack from their
flanks and take them out.
Master, you can't.
To what depths do you intend
to sink in your pursuit?
You do insult to
heroic spirits.
Why do you not allow me
to go out and fight?
Do you mean to imply
that you cannot trust me,
your own servant?
There's a truce
against everyone
but Caster, isn't there?
It'll be fine.
This overseer of ours
can't be trusted.
He harbors Assassin's
master in his church
and doesn't say anything
about it to anyone.
He may also be
working with Tohsaka.
We should be skeptical
of his actions.
All right, dismissed.
♪
Kiritsugu.
If...
If I...
If I decided to
abandon everything
and simply run away
from all of this,
Iri, would you
consider coming with me?
But what about Illya?
She's still waiting
back at our castle.
I'd return for her,
killing anyone in our way,
and then I would just...
I'd give all I have
for you and Illya,
and no one else!
Could we really get away?
We could escape
if we go now!
You're lying.
That's a lie.
You could never
run away from this.
You would never
forgive yourself
for abandoning
the Holy Grail,
for failing to
save the world.
You would be
riddled with guilt,
and as your first
and final accuser,
you would eventually
kill yourself.
I'm scared.
He‐‐Kirei Kotomine
is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Canaan as
bait to draw me out.
He anticipated my actions.
I've already
sacrificed you, Iri,
and I've left Illya behind,
but the most
dangerous of them all
has already set
his sights on me,
the one that I had hoped
to never cross paths with!
I won't allow you
to fight alone.
I will protect you,
and Saber will, too,
and also Maiya is here.
(gasping)
Kiritsugu.
An attack.
We're lucky I hadn't
sent Maiya out yet.
We can mount an
all‐out defense.
Iri, find us a
remote‐viewing crystal ball.
♪
There they are.
Irisviel.
He's trying to lure us out.
It looks like
he has hostages.
I'll have to go out there
and do what I can
to save them.
♪
He knows that
we're watching him.
Just as I promised
you last night,
I, Gilles de Rais, have
come for you, my darling.
I wish to see you,
fair Jeanne,
my enchanting and
radiantly beautiful
holy virgin of my dreams.
Irisviel.
You may take your
time if you wish.
I have come fully
prepared for a lengthy wait,
and will be as
attentive and patient
as you need for me to be.
(snapping)
Now, children, it's
time for us to play
some hide‐and‐seek.
The rules are simple.
You need only to elude me.
But if I find you...
No, don't!
(screaming)
♪
Run, children.
When I count to a hundred,
the chase begins.
Well, Jeanne, how long
do you think it will take
for me to catch them
all and win the game?
♪
Saber, go!
Defeat Caster!
Yes!
♪
Huh?
Welcome, fair Jeanne.
How do you like
this horrible sight?
Does it not pain you?
Do you despise me, Jeanne?
Yes, I'm sure you must.
I'm certain you'll
never forgive me
for turning from God's love.
Unhand the child, monster!
Jeanne, if you so dearly
wish to save the boy,
then, child,
you should rejoice
and be exceedingly glad.
God's devout messenger
says that she will save you
from the fate of
your departed friend.
(shouting)
(crying)
It's dangerous here.
Now, you need to run.
Just follow this path
and you'll find a castle.
(sloshing)
♪
(grunting)
Ha‐ha, do you not
remember what I told you?
I said that the very
next time we would meet
I would be prepared for you.
Very well.
My fight with you
is no longer over.
The Grail!
♪
(whooshing)
Oh, my fair Jeanne,
how noble, how beautiful!
Oh, holy virgin,
even God's beauty
pales before you.
Caster, I take up my sword
solely to destroy you!
Prepare!
♪
(grunting)
If only I could
use my left hand.
Even Caster's mana
isn't infinite.
If she can last
until it runs out,
Saber can with this
battle, right, Kiritsugu?
More importantly,
there's still no sign
of other masters
entering the forest.
Maiya, take Iri and get
away from the castle
in the opposite
direction of the fight.
But why can't I
just remain here?
With Saber fighting
away from you,
it simply isn't
safe for you here.
At least one of
the other masters
is certain to have
had the same idea.
All right, I'll go.
(groaning)
What's wrong, Iri?
It appears that
another one has arrived.
(screeching)
(heavy breathing)
How is this?
Is there no end to his mana?
Impossible.
The source of his mana is...
So that book is
your Noble Phantasm?
That's right, the
grimoire left to me
by the legendary
teacher, Prelati,
gives me the ample means
to command a demonic legion
to do my will.
What do you think,
my fair Jeanne?
It brings back
memories, doesn't it?
Everything is just
as it was then.
Your indomitable warrior
spirit and noble bearing
proves you to be none
other than Jeanne d'Arc!
So why, fair Jeanne,
why do you not awaken
to the truth of this?
Do you still believe in
God's grace even now?
Faced with mortal peril,
you still believe a
miracle will save you?
How terribly tragic.
Have you forgotten the
Battle of Compiègne?
Even after that
awful humiliation,
you still chose to
remain God's puppet!
♪
(grunting)
Ah!
(coughing)
Rather pathetic.
Such swordsmanship
is unworthy
of the title King of Knights.
Hmm.
Who are you?
And who gave you leave
to interfere with
our private affair?
Yes, well, that is my
question to you, monster.
It will be my lance alone
that takes Saber's life.
Ah, no, it was my prayer!
It was my Holy Grail that
brought her back to life!
She is mine, intruder.
Every scrap of flesh,
every drop of blood,
even her very soul
belongs to me!
Listen, Caster,
I am not gonna comment
on your bizarre
notion of romance here.
So if you really believe
that you're gonna make
Saber yours here today,
then go ahead and try it,
but know that I, Diarmuid,
will never allow you
to defeat a crippled Saber
in any sort of
battle before I can!
You came to help?
Don't get the wrong idea.
The only thing that
brought me here today
was the order to find
and defeat Caster.
And, so,
I believe cooperation
is our best option, right?
Mmhmm.
Just to be perfectly
clear, Lancer,
right now, I could kill
a hundred of those things
with just my left arm.
Hmm, a mere hundred of
them is child's play.
♪
You will pay.
Don't be conceited,
you savage!
Fervor, mei sanguis.
(whooshing)
(exploding)
♪
Kayneth El‐Melloi has arrived,
the ninth patriarch of
the Archibald family.
Mage of the Einzbern,
come forth and let us duel
for possession
of the Holy Grail
with our lives and
our sacred honor.
♪
(whirring)
(exploding)
♪
Mechanical traps,
of all things.
Have you fallen
so low, Einzbern?
Very well, then this
is no longer a duel,
but an extermination.
♪
(gasping)
I see.
Automated probes.
(whooshing)
(crashing)
I found you, pathetic rat.
Now scalp!
Time alter, double accelerate.
♪
Huh?
Oh.
He manipulated
the flow of time
to greatly accelerate himself
by using his own body
as a reality marble.
It seems that he knows
a little magic after all.
Still, only a miserable,
little coward would depend
on petty tricks after
being trained as a mage.
Perhaps dying will
teach him his place.
Ire sanctio.
(whooshing)
If he's manipulating
his inner time,
it must be placing
enormous stress on his body.
♪
I found him.
Now then, how far can you
run as exhausted as you are?
(chuckles)
♪
Time alter, triple stagnate.
These things don't have eyes.
If I can slow my
internal time to a third
and lower my pulse
and respiration
as far as they can go,
they can't sense me.
♪
Kayneth!
You're a fool!
It's a waste of time.
♪
Hmm.
Maiya, no!
You're a disgrace
to mages everywhere.
Tremble down to your soul!
Sink into despair!
Strike him, Jeanne d'Arc!
By whose order do
you dare attack?
Prepare to die, monster.