♪
‐Madam?
‐Huh?
Please hurry.
♪
(gasping)
Madam?
Another intruder
has just arrived.
They're waiting for us in
the direction we're headed.
We'll run into them
if we go this way.
Understood.
Let's circle around
to the north side then.
♪
Madam?
The one who is coming is...
Kirei Kotomine.
♪
Maiya, the orders that were
given to you by Kiritsugu
were to protect me
from harm, right?
Yes.
‐But...
‐But what?
We mustn't let him
get to Kiritsugu,
no matter what we have
to do to stop him.
Isn't that what
you're thinking?
(rustling)
Madam, how did you...
What a coincidence.
I was thinking
the very same thing.
Maiya, Kirei Kotomine
represents the most
dangerous threat
that Kiritsugu has
ever had to face.
You and I are going
to hold him off here.
Understood, Maiya?
I apologize.
But, please prepare
yourself, madam.
I will.
Please don't worry about me.
Do whatever you
think you have to do,
what you believe to
be necessary to win,
and not what Kiritsugu
ordered you to do.
Right.
(laughs)
What's funny?
Isn't the human heart
a funny thing?
(gun firing)
♪
Hmm, you repeat an attack you
know to be absolutely futile.
♪
(clattering)
(gasping and grunting)
♪
Scalp!
(heavy breathing)
♪
He was somehow able to breach
Volumen Hydragyrum's
autonomous defense?
He couldn't have.
His ineffective
childish attack
simply rolled me
into lowering my guard!
I shall take steps to
provide for a much swifter,
more efficient
defense from now on.
You're disgrace to
mages everywhere,
you piece of lowborn trash!
For spilling my blood,
you will pay with your life.
♪
He knows exactly how
powerful this is now.
It's not going to
work on him twice.
Next time, he'll channel all
his mana into his defense.
Yes, that exactly
what I need him to do.
(gun firing)
(whooshing)
Huh?
(gun firing)
(clanging)
An illusion?
Maiya, no!
(grunting)
♪
(clanging)
(gasping)
(grunting)
(coughing)
♪
(choking)
Madam, please don't.
Woman, this may come
as a surprise to you,
but I haven't come
here to this place
in order to defeat you.
I'm well aware of
that, Kirei Kotomine.
I know what you desire,
but I will not allow it.
You will never reach Kiritsugu
Emiya tonight or ever!
We will stop you...
‐...right here.
‐Madam!
He's a skilled executioner!
An expert at hunting mages!
Regular magic won't be
enough to stop him!
(whooshing)
Kiritsugu taught me a lot
more than how to drive a car!
He taught me to
live and to survive!
Shape ist Leben!
(squawking)
♪
(grunting)
‐Look out!
‐Not so fast!
♪
(whooshing)
Maiya!
Finish him!
(banging)
(sighing)
It can't be.
(banging)
(hissing)
(cracking)
(banging)
(clanging)
Hm.
(grunting)
You bastard‐‐ah!
(thudding)
(screeching)
I'm honestly stunned
that we've made so little
progress with these things.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds
that Noble Phantasm,
our situation
will not improve.
I see, so that's his secret.
Of course, if you plan to
go over and knock the book
from that pale freak's hands,
you've got a problem.
You'll need to get pass his
big wall of monsters first.
Well, then, what say
you to taking in
all‐or‐nothing gamble?
It feels a bit shameful,
but there's no glory
in simply fighting
these ugly things.
Very well,
count me in, Saber.
I shall clear a path for you.
We will have but
one chance at this.
Lancer, can you
run on the wind?
I understand.
It's child's play.
How delightful!
Have you two said
your prayers?
Tremble down to your soul!
Sink into despair!
Superior skill can
only defeat so many
before being completely
overwhelmed by sheer numbers.
(laughing)
It must be humiliating!
You will die!
Suffocated under a
horde of monsters
that know nothing
of honor or glory!
There can be no greater
disgrace for a hero!
Oh, that beautiful
face of yours.
Make it twist and contort
in pain for me, Jeanne!
♪
Strike Air!
(zapping)
♪
Ah!
Prepare to die!
♪
Strike him, Gae Dearg!
Ahh!
♪
(groaning)
(screeching)
♪
Damn you.
Damn you, damn you,
damn you, damn you, damn you!
Damn you!
Did you like that?
Had Saber had the use
of her left hand,
well, you would've
experienced the same.
Prepare to die...
...monster.
(grunting and screeching)
(exploding and shattering)
(crumbling)
Pathetic.
I didn't come here and
join the Holy Grail War
only to fight in this
ridiculous sort of battle!
♪
(whooshing)
Where is he?
Find him.
(banging)
(shattering)
There you are...
...you skulking little rat.
♪
Surely you don't expect
the same trick to work on me
a second time,
do you, lowborn scum?
The fact that you succeeded
in landing a single blow
wasn't due to any
great strategy of yours.
It was a fluke.
A stroke of luck,
plain and simple.
Now I'm going to teach
you the difference.
I shan't let you die easily.
I shall use healing magic
to regenerate your
heart and lungs
while I rend every millimeter
of your lowborn flesh.
In excruciating
pain and despair,
you will die as you suffer.
And while you die,
you will curse them,
you will curse the cowardice
of those who hired you.
You will curse the Einzbern
for making a mockery
of the Grail War!
Insolent fool!
Fervor, mei sanguis!
(clanging)
Hm.
♪
I knew you'd do that, scum.
(whooshing)
Hm.
Ah!
You struggle in vain!
(grunting)
(whooshing)
(clanging and grunting)
Disgusting.
He is nothing but
a sniveling coward!
Lancer.
Is something wrong?
It's my master.
He's in danger.
It seems, he left me here and
breached the castle himself.
I'm certain that the danger
comes from my own master.
Lancer, hurry to his side.
Go to your master as aid.
King of Knights,
you have my thanks.
Think nothing of it.
You and I have sworn
to settle matters
in a manner
befitting two knights.
Let us keep our pride intact.
(whirring)
That must mean that all went
according to Kiritsugu's plan.
(clinking)
Your origin is based on
cutting and tying, kid.
To cut and tie.
The nuance is a
little different
than destruction
and regeneration.
If you cut a thread
and then retie it,
it will always be
thicker where you cut it.
Isn't that right?
In that sense,
it carries a connotation
of irreversible change.
(inhaling and exhaling)
I've powdered
some of your ribs,
and also put a very
special part inside of here.
Your origin will materialize
in anything shot
by these bullets.
It's especially
powerful against mages.
If they attempt to use
any magic against it,
your origin will
interfere with and destroy
their magic circuits which
will reconnect improperly.
The more powerful the mage,
the more their magic circuits
will run haywire
and short out.
Naturally, they will
never be able to recover
either as a mage or human.
These will be your
ace in the hole.
"Origin Rounds".
I've made 66 in total.
Don't waste them.
(sighing)
(retching)
(grunting)
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
(clicking)
(clanging)
I'm sure you must know
how easy it would be
for me to skewer you
right now, correct?
Master of Saber.
So that's it, is it?
I shall not let you
kill my master,
nor will I kill
Saber's master.
Neither of us wish for our
duel to be ended that way.
Never forget this.
The reason you
survived our encounter
is the nobility demonstrated
by the King of Knights.
(crashing)
Woman, I have one question.
It appears to me
that the two of you
came here to challenge me
with the intention of
protecting Kiritsugu Emiya.
By whose order do
you dare attack?
You do not possess
Command Seals,
so you are not
the Einzbern Master.
Most likely, you
are a homunculus
charged with protecting
the Grail vessel.
There's no way that
someone like that
would ever be stupid enough
to risk going to the
front lines of the battle.
So I ask again.
Tell me now.
Who ordered you to fight me?
(grunting)
Hm.
Master Kirei.
Caster, as well as
Lancer and his master,
have left the forest.
Saber will arrive shortly.
My lord, it is
dangerous here.
Hm.
(grunting)
(screaming)
Fascinating.
So it's red after all.
(clanging)
♪
Impossible.
Could these women
have challenged me
of their own accord without
being ordered to do so?
No.
Kiritsugu Emiya is like me.
He is alone and empty inside,
understood by no one.
♪
He must be.
Irisviel!
Can you hear me?
Saber.
Stay awake.
You must stay awake.
I'm going to call Kiritsugu.
Be strong until then.
Where is Kirei,
the enemy who was here
just a minute ago?
He escaped.
Had I been only
a second faster,
this would never
have happened to you.
What happened to Maiya?
Her wounds are grave,
but not life‐threatening.
I'm more concerned about you.
You've lost so much blood.
Huh?
Irisviel, how...
How can this be?
I want you to
carry Avalon, Iri.
What?
But, this is a Noble Phantasm
that heals its
bearer's wounds.
I think you should keep it.
No, Iri, unless its original
owner, Saber, is nearby
to supply it with mana,
the scabbard won't
function at all.
You will be the one
who'll be working
with Saber from now on.
So you should have it.
Keep it within you as
a conceptual weapon.
Additionally,
tell no one of this,
not even Saber herself.
♪
From the moment you touched
me, I felt Avalon's power.
Thank you, Saber.
♪
Kirei Kotomine.
That inquisitor
is as dangerous
as I imagined he'd be.
No, even more so.
We were lucky today.
But there's no telling
what will happen next time.
All I know for certain
is that I can't let him
get to Kiritsugu
no matter what.
But, I'm not the only one
here who is protecting him.
Isn't that right, Maiya?
Next time, we'll win for sure.
We'll both protect
Kiritsugu, okay?
♪
Because my young master
is in mortal peril!
Dignity is required
even during battle.
I'm sorry, but
I cannot consent.
Why don't you give
the Command Seals to me?
Lancer's not the fine
man you think he is!