♪
Aniplex.
(flames flickering)
♪
(crystal tinkling)
(crackling)
Ah!
What?
♪
(sigh)
(coughing)
(whimpering)
Rin.
♪
(kids playing)
(sobbing)
Hey!
You losers shouldn't
gang up on someone
and bully them like that!
You guys suck,
you really suck!
What's your
problem, Tohsaka?
There's nothing here
that concerns you.
Yeah, in that case,
why don't you do
the same to me?
And then it will concern me.
Come on, this is getting lame.
(sigh)
Here.
You used too much
mana all at once.
Maintain a calm mind.
In order to control magic,
you must first achieve complete
control of your thoughts.
(crystal crackling)
(gasping)
Lose control and
the mana will suddenly
rebound back to your body.
Too much power or
power in the wrong form
will endanger not only you,
but those around you.
Strive to consistently
maintain the proper flow.
That is the Tohsaka
family motto.
It means always
remaining reserved
and elegant.
(gasping)
You shouldn't let
them get way with it
when they try that stuff.
If they're in the wrong,
you just have to get mad
and do something about it.
You're amazing, Rin,
the way you always
speak your mind like that.
I'm not amazing at all.
I think it's normal.
I mean, it's only natural.
That's right,
it's only natural.
(gasp)
♪
Hold out your hand.
Oh.
Father, oh please
teach me more.
How do I make
something like this?
Well, my dear, that
might be a bit difficult
for you right now.
♪
But if you work
hard every day,
you'll be able to
make it eventually.
After all, Rin, you're a
daughter of the Tohsaka family.
♪
Hey, Rin, could
you please show me
how to do this part?
Of course, which part?
‐Yeah, me too.
‐Me too.
Oh, this was on
page 23 of the textbook.
You see, you just did
the math wrong here.
For this problem, it's
just like this example, see?
♪
Kotone, have a seat,
I'll help everyone in turn.
Okay.
♪
Do I really have to go and
live with the Zenjo family?
Once the Holy
Grail War begins,
it will no longer be
safe for you in Fuyuki.
But I‐‐but I want
to do something
to help you with
the Grail War, Father.
Rin, you mustn't cause
trouble for your father.
Do you think that
we're in the way?
Not at all.
Please try to understand,
I need to make
preparations for the battle.
Those preparations include
doing what's necessary
to ensure your safety.
And for me to do that,
you simply can't
stay in Fuyuki.
But I'm certain
there's something
I can do to help!
(punching)
(whimpering)
That's right, I just
haven't learned how to yet.
So, all I need to do
is study on my own.
I don't understand
any of this.
What is this?
Tease!
Oh.
(pounding)
(screaming)
(voice speaking German)
I have to close it.
It won't move.
(screaming)
Rin!
Are you all right?
(whimpering)
(gasping)
It's still too soon for
you to read this book.
Some things in this world
contain their own mana.
♪
This is called
a mana compass.
Normally, it doesn't
point to anything
except for mana
traces in the area.
Rin, try generating
mana in this.
Okay.
(humming)
(clicking)
Ah.
You see?
And with that book.
(sparking)
Anything that provokes
a reaction like that
is beyond your ability,
so be very careful.
Ah.
I'll give this to you as
an early birthday present.
Oh, thank you
so much, Father.
Once the Holy Grail
War is all over,
you and I will try
some real jewel magic.
♪
And then strange
things began to happen.
♪
(sigh)
They said we have
study hall again.
(kids talking)
There was another kidnapping
on the news this morning.
...the sudden
disappearance of children
has police
investigators baffled.
The teachers have been
in a meeting all day.
They said we won't
have fifth period today.
All right!
But they said we
should stay home.
Why?
Another kidnapping.
They say only children
have been kidnapped.
Hey, did you hear?
Uh.
♪
Apparently there's no
body inside the coffin,
it was in such bad shape.
It definitely happened
in Fuyuki, right?
♪
(phone ringing)
My name is Tohsaka and
I'm in Kotone's class‐‐
The person you are
calling is not home.
Please leave your
message after the beep.
Thank you.
♪
(train rumbling)
Please be safe.
Kotone.
(train rattling)
This is Fuyuki at night.
♪
It's different
than during the day.
Ooh, it's really
cold and creepy.
♪
What is this?
I've never seen it do this.
Does this mean there
are traces of magic
all around here?
♪
I've got to find Kotone.
(footsteps running)
♪
(dial whirring)
(sigh)
♪
Huh?
Someone out with
their kid this late?
♪
What was that flash?
(footsteps running)
(crashing)
(sigh)
♪
Oh, no.
(car approaching)
♪
That was close.
If I'm spotted,
they'll take me home.
♪
(laughing)
Come on, you've
got to walk, kid.
♪
(gasps)
Two of them?
♪
He's gathered more kids.
But why?
Wait, why am I hiding?
I can't accomplish
anything this way.
♪
(explosion)
(footsteps echoing)
(door squeaking)
Looks like no one's here.
♪
(scream)
Hey, hey you?
Kotone, Kotone, Kotone!
Something's
been done to her.
What do I do?
Think, Rin.
♪
Well now, are you
lost little girl?
No, um I...
Perfect timing.
We were just about to
get the party started.
But we still don't
have enough guests.
Want to help?
It'll be fun.
(gasps)
(screaming)
When it comes to parties,
the more the merrier
I always say.
♪
No!
What, what just happened?
Don't run from me.
♪
Is he controlling them
with that bracelet?
♪
(boxes crashing)
(struggling)
♪
(glass breaking)
Ow!
I've got it.
♪
Well, well, you're
gonna help me after all?
(whimpering)
♪
Huh?
What is that?
You use too much
mana all at once.
I can destroy that!
(explosion)
What?
♪
Kotone!
Rin?
What's going on?
(crying)
This is not
the time to cry.
Run!
Hey, wait!
♪
Oh, man.
I hope the big guy
won't be too pissed.
♪
(sirens wailing)
Where's Rin?
(heavy breathing)
It's gonna be okay, sweetie.
Good, it's done.
I did it, Father.
What?
(cans rattling)
Ah!
♪
Anything that provokes
a reaction like that
is beyond your ability,
so be very careful.
♪
Ah.
(bats flutter and screech)
♪
Rin, I just can't
believe she went to Fuyuki.
Rin!
Rin.
Rin is fine.
She's just asleep.
Kariya.
What's happening here?
What are you doing here?
(gasp)
Your face.
Behold the family
magic of the Matous.
You offer your flesh and
your life is slowly devoured.
That is the magic's price.
But Sakura will be fine.
I'll save her before
this happens to her.
Zouken's only
desire is the grail.
He gave me his promise
that he'll release Sakura
as soon as I win it for him.
If you win the grail?
Yeah, so don't worry.
My servant is the strongest.
It won't lose to anyone.
Considering what
she's been through,
hope would be nothing
but cruel torture
to Sakura right now.
So, pray for her
since she can't.
Pray for my victory,
for Sakura's future.
♪
Kariya, wait.
Someday I'm sure we'll
all play in this park,
just like we used to
back in better days.
And Rin and Sakura
will be sisters again.
So, Aoi, you don't
need to cry anymore.
♪
Kariya, are you going to
die and kill Tokiomi too?
♪
Mother?
Rin, I was so
worried about you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(whimpering)
Master Kirei, are you certain
that you wish to allow
Tokiomi Tohsaka's wife
and daughter to go free?
It's fine.
You are to
continue monitoring
Berserker's master.
Understood.
(car speeding)
♪
It wasn't much, but I did
manage to do something.
♪
I guess I'm not a
full‐fledged mage yet.
I passed out
half way through.
That means I need
to work harder.
But that's just for now.
I have plenty of
time to train more.
And someday, I'll take
my place as a Tohsaka mage.
I'll have to
practice really hard
and obey my father
so that I'll be ready
when that day comes.
And when the
time does come,
I'll do it to the
best of my ability,
as elegantly as I can.
♪
A king without greed is even
worse than a figure head!
Worthless is a king who
fails to protect the weak.
We stand to lose nothing.
A reality marble?
I shall take great pleasure
in killing you myself.
Wasn't your goal supposed
to be world conquest?
Argh!