♪
You have a charm spell.
Apologies, but I'm
afraid it's a little curse
that I was born with.
There's really nothing
that can be done about it.
Blame it on my birth,
or if you prefer,
the fact that you
were born a woman.
Surely you don't
actually believe
that a pleasant face
and a charming swagger
will save you from the
bite of my blade, spear man.
I certainly hope not‐‐
it would spoil the fun.
I see now that the tales
of the Saber classes'
resistance to magic are true.
Very well‐‐I prefer
not to kill a girl
who's throwing herself at me.
It would sully my reputation.
I'm pleased that my first
opponent is made of stern stuff.
Oh, so what you
desire is a fair fight.
I consider myself
fortunate to encounter
such a strong and proud hero.
Then let us begin.
♪
(exploding and clanking)
It's started.
Someone has put up a barrier,
probably the master
of the enemy's servant.
From up on that crane,
it would be possible
to survey the whole battlefield.
Indeed‐‐that certainly
is the best vantage point.
Anyone seeing it would agree.
All right, you circle
around to the Eastern Wharf.
I'll go the other
way and take the west.
You and I need
to find good spots
where we can be
totally invisible
while we closely
monitor both Saber's battle
and that crane, got it?
Yes, understood.
♪
Now, then, let's
see what you can do,
my adorable King of Knights.
♪
(clanking)
Saber is watching both
spears simultaneously.
Lancer's greatest advantage
is his opponent's uncertainty
as to which he will use.
The long spear in the right hand
or the short spear in the left?
Which was the Noble Phantasm?
If I could be certain
which one it was,
I could attack and defeat him.
If only we knew his true name.
♪
Whoever he is, he's
a master of the spear.
However, that is not enough.
(whooshing)
♪
What's wrong, Saber?
You're on the defensive.
This man is impressive.
♪
Curse that blade of hers.
Without knowing
its exact length,
I can't get close
enough to strike.
The fact that she's able to
repel my strikes so easily
means that she must
be a master swordsman.
♪
Hmm, Maiya, northeast
of Saber and Iri.
On the roof of that
warehouse, it's Lancer's master.
Can you see him?
♪
Negative‐‐I can't see
him from my position.
Understood.
I'll take him out from here.
(wind blowing)
♪
Assassin?
There is activity at
the warehouse district
at the mouth of the Mion River.
It seems the first
battle has finally begun.
Not the first battle.
To the others, this would
be the second battle, Kirei.
It would appear
that Lancer and Saber
are the combatants in this one.
Can you ascertain their status
utilizing Assassin's eyes?
With ease.
Saber's formidable abilities
are especially high.
Most of her parameters
are ranked A or higher
on the standard scale.
I see.
It's no wonder they are
considered the strongest class.
Saber likely presents a
greater threat than Lancer.
Can you see other masters?
There's only one person
besides the servants
who is out in the open
and visible to Assassin.
She's standing next to Saber.
It's a woman with silver hair.
Huh, that means that
Lancer's master is wise enough
to remain hidden from view,
and that he's not a novice.
He understands the rules
of the Holy Grail War.
Wait a minute‐‐a
silver‐haired woman?
Yes, a Caucasian...
with silver hair and red eyes.
Very unusual.
She doesn't look at all human.
An Einzbern Homunculus.
It seems they created
another artificial master.
I thought that the only pawn
Yupstehide had on the board
was Kiritsugu Emiya.
It would appear
that I was wrong.
So then that woman
is the Einzbern master?
Either way, she's certainly
going to be a critical factor
throughout the rest
of the Grail War.
Kirei, keep a close eye on her.
Agreed.
I shall keep one Assassin
tasked to her at all times.
♪
I see him, too.
But Assassin should be
dead, so why is he here?
I knew something had to be up.
Let's see how
this all plays out.
Continue to observe Assassin.
I'll watch Lancer.
Let me launch an
attack on Assassin.
And then, while I
have him distracted,
you can take out
Lancer's master.
No, Maiya.
I don't want you to make
any moves against Assassin.
We're not equipped to
fight servants right now.
It would be disastrous.
Understood.
(rattling)
(crashing)
There is really no
honor in a battle fought
without a proper
exchange of names,
but allow me to
offer my regards.
It's impressive for a
woman to fight so hard
without even breaking
a sweat as she does it.
You needn't be
so humble, Lancer.
Even without my
knowing your name,
those words from such a master
of the spear do me honor.
I gratefully accept them.
That's enough fun
for now, Lancer.
(gasping)
Lancer's master?
Do not allow this
battle to go on.
Saber is a formidable opponent.
Eliminate her at once.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
♪
As you command, I will comply.
(clattering)
(whooshing)
So the long spear
is his Noble Phantasm.
You heard the command.
The time has come
for me to kill you.
Saber, are you using
focused wind mana
to keep your blade concealed?
I see.
I'll wager that you
have a very good reason
to conceal your sword from me.
I think the sword
reveals your true name.
How unfortunate for you.
I'm afraid you'll never know
the true name of my blade.
I'll finish this before
you ever get the chance.
We shall see about that.
I will discover whatever
it is you're hiding, Saber.
(wind howling)
You've exposed your sword to me.
The Invisible Air
is coming apart.
(crashing)
(whooshing)
♪
(clanking)
(grunting)
What's going on with Saber?
♪
That red spear is chipping
away at the Invisible Air.
I've figured out the
length of your blade now,
so I needn't worry about
being struck by you anymore!
♪
He wields a formidable weapon,
but I still have
ways to counter it.
♪
If I wait for an attack...
...one less powerful
than the rest.
♪
Saber?
My thanks, Irisviel.
I'm fine‐‐the
healing is working.
I see‐‐so this won't be
an easy victory after all.
How could this be?
My armor should've easily
deflected that strike.
So how did the
blade of his spear...
♪
The armor itself isn't damaged.
What's at work here?
♪
The only answer is that
Lancer's spear bypassed
the magically woven armor.
So that's it.
I know the secret of
your spear, Lancer.
Oh?
That red spear of yours
is able to negate magic.
Hmm.
So your armor was
created using magic, huh?
Well, if you were counting
on it to protect you,
you should surrender now, Saber.
You're as good as
naked before my spear.
Don't think that simply
defeating my armor
will give you the upper
hand in this fight.
(shattering)
If I cannot block your blade,
I need only kill you
before it strikes.
Prepare to die, Lancer!
A bold move.
You're betting everything
on a single strike.
You are attempting to
overcome the disadvantage
of your broken armor with
the advantages you gain
by abandoning it.
Excellent.
A courageous decision.
I like it‐‐it's
audacious and bold.
But in this case, I'm afraid
that it was a very
foolish mistake, Saber.
We shall see.
You can tell me your opinion
again after my next attack.
♪
(gasping)
That was a misstep.
♪
A Noble Phantasm needn't
be merely a single weapon.
A trap!
♪
(grunting)
This is extremely bad.
What is?
Lancer has begun
his ultimate attack.
He intends to end
the battle here.
Well, wouldn't that
be a lot better for us?
Ahh!
You idiot‐‐what are
you talking about?
I wanted to sit back and watch
until we saw a few
more masters fight.
But at this rate,
Saber may just fall.
And then it will be too late.
T‐‐t‐‐too late for what?
I mean, the plan was to attack
after they'd fought a few
battles and weakened each other.
I have to admit that
I had really hoped
at least one other servant
would've been sent out
to answer Lancer's challenge,
because, of course,
it would be much faster
to fight them altogether
than to seek them
all out one by one.
You wanna fight 'em together?
Indeed!
Rarely does one have
the extraordinary chance
to exchange blows with great
heroes from another time.
And with a chance to fight
as many as six of them,
I'd hate to miss
out on a single one.
Just observe Saber and Lancer.
Both of them are
strong, valiant warriors
whom I would dearly love
to face in an all‐out battle.
I cannot let either one die.
But isn't that the whole point?
The Grail Wars objective is
to kill one another isn't it?
(smacking and yelling)
To win, but never to destroy,
to subjugate, but
never to humiliate‐‐
that is a truly good
and honorable conquest.
♪
(mooing)
(whimpering)
Now, we will watch no longer!
We shall join the fray, boy!
Let us go!
You stupid idiot!
What you're doing
is totally insane!
If you really don't approve,
then why don't you just
stay up here and observe?
No, I'll go!
Take me with you, dammit!
Excellent, that is my master.
(laughing)
Not good‐‐he severed the tendon.
I can't move my thumb.
Good counter.
You aren't gonna make
this easy for me, are you?
But I like your
indomitable spirit.
Stop talking and get
to work, you fool!
Finish her‐‐what
are you waiting for?
♪
My master‐‐much appreciated.
Irisviel, I require healing.
But I have.
I've already done it.
I mean, I did it‐‐the healing
worked, I'm certain of it!
Saber, you should
already be fully healed!
I don't understand!
It was very sharp
of you to figure out,
that my Gae Dearg was
able to penetrate any armor,
but it was foolish
to abandon it.
♪
Had you not done so,
my Gae Buidhe would
not have gotten you.
I see.
You wield a cursed spear,
which inflicts devastating
wounds that can never be healed.
I should've realized it sooner.
A red spear that destroys magic,
a cursed yellow spear,
and beneath the right eye,
a mole that enchants women.
First of the Knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid of the Love Spot.
Never did I think I'd have the
honor of facing you in combat.
Such is a sublime pleasure
of the Holy Grail War,
but it's I who has
the distinct honor here.
No hero summoned into
service by the Holy Grail
could ever mistake
that golden blade.
To face the legendary
King of Knights in battle
and land even a single
glancing blow is extraordinary.
I must not be too bad.
Now then, since we both
know each other's name,
we can finally conduct
our duel honorably
as knights should.
Or does this displease you,
occurring only after
you've lost use of an arm?
(thundering)
You jest.
It is humiliating that you
would show so much concern
over such a scratch.
♪
Prepare yourself, Saber!
This time you're mine!
Only if I fail to inflict the
first decisive strike, Lancer.
(rumbling)
(cracking)
(yelling)
That's a chariot!
♪
(braying)
Both of you, sheath your blades,
for I am a King!
♪
I am Iskander,
King of Conquerors!
In this battle
for the Holy Grail,
I am of the Rider
class of servants!
(whimpering)
♪
I am Iskander, the
King of Conquerors!
I can't read his
status or anything else!
Irisviel, get back!
That is his Noble Phantasm.
With my Command Seal,
I order you.
Please believe in your master!
At last she has
come back to life!
Nothing will remain
of your corpse!