♪
Aniplex.
(gunshot)
(singing in Japanese)
♪
(growling)
(grunting)
♪
Did you hate me?
Did you hate me so much
that you became this?
(yelling)
♪
Origin rounds.
They cause the target's
mana to go out of control,
causing their body
to rip itself apart.
What?
Time alter.
Double accel!
♪
The origin rounds are working.
No, I understand.
He's using command
seals as his mana source.
By the time the round
strikes and takes effect,
the command seal mana
source has already vanished.
Since he doesn't use his own
magic circuits for attacks,
the origin rounds'
magic won't work.
But if I can land a solid hit,
it'll still be strong
enough to kill him.
♪
Don't think you'll
escape next time.
Now that I know you're
moving at double speed,
I simply need to adjust the
distance to compensate for it.
♪
He's fast!
(choking)
♪
(yelling)
The depth of your
violent madness...
(yelling)
...is that my fault as well?
♪
Is it?
(clanking)
Is it my fault?
♪
(gun firing)
Time alter, double accel.
♪
(gun firing)
(gasping)
♪
(panting)
I'm at a massive
disadvantage at close range.
I've lost my Calico.
My Contender needs reloading.
However, Avalon.
♪
He has healing ability
that allows him
to instantly regenerate
a demolished heart?
Well then, I'll have
to destroy the brain.
But I can't use my right arm.
Avalon will even work
on self‐inflicted wounds.
I have a knife I can use
and two grenades left.
I have 12 blades remaining
and eight spare command seals.
Time alter.
Triple accel.
♪
(bubbling)
Time alter.
Square accel!
♪
(exploding)
(clanking)
But, even so, I
will win the Grail.
If I do not, there
will be nothing I can do
to atone to you.
Even after all
that has happened
you would still
take up your sword
for a reason such as that?
What a difficult person you are.
(clattering)
(rain pouring)
Where am I?
I knew you would
come, Kiritsugu.
I had faith that you would be
the one to reach this place.
‐Iri.
‐This is where the wish
you have lived
for will be granted.
We are inside the Grail
that you have been seeking.
That is the Holy Grail.
It has yet to take form,
but the vessel itself
is more than filled.
All you need do now
is offer it your prayer.
Only then will it be able to
go out into the physical world.
Now, please, hurry and
give the Grail its form!
Kiritsugu, you have proven
yourself more than worthy
to define its existence.
Who are you, really?
I am Irisviel, as you see.
No.
If the Grail is prepared
to receive a wish,
then she is already...
Answer me!
It's true.
I will not deny that this
is no more than a mask.
You see, unless I use
a preexisting
personality as a shell,
I cannot communicate
with others.
However, the personality
of Irisviel that I recorded
is undeniably the real thing.
And so I have
inherited the last wish
that Irisviel
held in her heart.
Are you the will
of the Holy Grail?
I am, that interpretation
is not incorrect.
I have my own will
and my own wish.
I have the will to be
born into the world.
No way.
If that's the case,
then how does the Grail
intend to totally
fulfill my wish?
Well, Kiritsugu,
that is something
that you should know far better
than anyone else
could possibly know.
What?
You learned exactly
how to save the world
a long, long time ago.
So I will do exactly
as you always did‐‐
to carry out your will and to
ultimately answer your prayer.
What are you talking about?
I have no choice.
The only way is to
have you go and explore
that same question
through your inner self.
(gasps)
This is...
Three hundred are on one ship,
200 on another.
‐What the‐‐
‐Five hundred total
passengers and crew,
plus Kiritsugu Emiya.
Let's assume that
these 501 people
are humanity's
last survivors.
Giant holes simultaneously
open up in both ships,
crippling them.
Kiritsugu alone has the
skills needed to repair a ship.
Now then, which one of the
ships would you choose to fix?
Simple‐‐the one
holding 300 people.
As soon as you
make that decision,
the 200 passengers
on the other ship
kidnap you and
take you prisoner.
They demand that you
fix their ship first.
What will you do?
I would...
(gun firing)
♪
You would kill
all 200 passengers.
That is correct, that is
the Kiritsugu Emiya we know.
(cell phone ringing)
Next, the surviving
300 passengers
abandon their damaged craft.
They split themselves
between two new ships
and continue their journey.
This time, there are 200 on one,
and 100 on the other.
But again, holes open
the hulls of both ships
at exactly the same time.
Wait.
The hundred in the smaller
ship take you prisoner,
and like the others, demand
that you fix their ship first.
Now what will you do?
You already know, but you...
(beeping)
♪
(explosion)
Yes, you made
the right decision.
No, that's impossible!
How can that be
the right decision?
Two hundred survived, but
300 died so they could live.
The scales are
tipped the wrong way!
No, your calculations
were correct.
You made a choice to sacrifice
the few to save the many.
Isn't that right,
Kiritsugu Emiya?
You have consistently
chosen to kill those
in the lighter
side of the scales,
even if it meant leaving
a long trail of bodies
behind you in your wake.
If it saved lives,
the lives of the saved
must've been worth more
than those you destroyed.
♪
This‐‐this is what
you wanted to show me?
Yes, this is your truth.
The answer that lies
within Kiritsugu Emiya.
The course of action that
should be taken by the Grail
as an all‐powerful wish‐granter.
No.
No, this is not what I want!
I want there to be another
way to save the world.
That's why I believed
that a miracle
was my only hope.
Your wish cannot include
a method you yourself
don't already know.
If your wish is
the save the world,
it must be done in a manner
that you can fully comprehend.
Like hell!
How in the hell can
you call that a miracle?
But it is.
The deed you tried
so hard to accomplish
and failed to do on your own
can be accomplished on a scale
beyond the power of any man.
If that is not a
miracle, what is?
♪
Father.
(gunshot)
♪
Natalia.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
You truly are Angra Mainyu‐‐
the one worthy to bear
all the evil in the world.
Now, the final question.
♪
Three remain.
Will you save two or choose one?
♪
Welcome home, Daddy!
Oh, I'm so happy that
you're finally back!
You understand now, right?
This is all the Holy Grail
granting your
heart's fervent prayer.
♪
All you need do now
is to wish for it,
to bring back your wife,
to take back your daughter.
♪
I won't be able
to go looking
for chestnuts
with you anymore.
It's okay, don't
worry about it!
I'll be happy just as long
as you and Mother are
with me from now on.
Thank you.
Daddy loves you,
my precious Ilya.
If nothing else,
I swear that's true.
(giggles)
(clicking)
Goodbye, Ilya.
Ilya!
Ilya, Ilya!
Ilya.
(clicking)
But why?
Why would you do this?
My love, you killed our Ilya!
♪
(choking)
My love...
why?
Why do you...refuse us...
and the Grail?
(gasping)
Six billion people on the Earth.
I...
curse you...
Kiritsugu Emiya.
Versus you two.
Angra Mainyu curses you.
That's why.
‐You'll suffer...
‐That's why...
‐...till the day you die.
‐... I have to kill you.
‐I will...
‐And I will save...
‐the world.
‐Never forget‐‐
(snapping)
♪
(clicking)
(sloshing)
What a boring
conclusion to this fight.
Why did you refuse it?
You were able
to see all that?
I thought you sacrificed
everything you had
including your family
in order to make
it to this point.
How can you simply
deny the worth
of something you
worked so hard to attain?
It's so foolish, I
cannot understand it.
The tremendous toll it demands
is far greater than
anything it can offer.
That's the simple truth.
That thing is no
omnipotent wish‐granter.
Then give the damn thing to me!
(cocks gun)
You may not think you need it,
but I most certainly do.
If it‐‐if it is given
the life it is seeking,
then it can surely
answer my every doubt
and finally bring
everything into clarity.
The Grail longs for
a life of its own,
longs for its own birth!
Please, don't kill it, it's‐‐
(gunshot)
No, you are the fool
I can't understand.
(door opens)
♪
Oh, Iris, you...
You're late, Saber!
I realized you were
enjoying yourself
with your old Mad Dog,
but it is imprudent
to the extreme
to keep me waiting like you did.
Archer.
Look at that
delightful expression,
like that of a
ravenous wild dog.
Get out of my way.
You haven't won.
The Holy Grail belongs to me!
(grunting)
Dear Saber, it is
when you are delusional
and crawling in the dirt
that you are at
your most beautiful.
Lay down your
blade and be my wife.
A Grail that grants miracles?
Where is the sense
in totally obsessing
over something so dubious?
Abandon these foolish ideals
and childish vows of yours.
From now on, seek only me and
devote yourself to me alone.
If you do, I swear as
King of All Creation
that I shall give you every
pleasure the world has to offer.
You would steal the
Holy Grail from me
for such utter nonsense?
(grunting)
I was not asking
for your opinion.
I am informing
you of my decision.
Now, let us hear your response.
I refuse.
I would never‐‐
Shyness has left you at
a loss for words, I see.
That's fine.
You may answer wrongly
as many times as you like.
If you would learn
the joy of serving me,
you must first learn the
exquisite pain of it as well.
♪
Kiritsugu!
Ah, then you have
finally made your decision.
In the name of Kiritsugu Emiya,
and by my command seal...
Give me the Holy Grail.
...I order you, use
your Noble Phantasm.
Destroy the Grail.
♪
Impossible‐‐what
are you doing, Saber!
No!
By my third command seal,
I order you again.
But why, Kiritsugu‐‐
you of all people?
‐Why this?
‐Damn you to Hell.
You dare interrupt my nuptials?
‐Mongrel!
‐Saber, destroy...
Stop!
...the Holy Grail.
I remember the look on his face,
the tears in his eyes‐‐
a man filled with joy
from the bottom of his heart.
I felt jealous of him.
He said, "Thank you."