Saki, thanks for
believing in me.
Don't forget our travels.
You can always find
me at our special place.
Say, would it be all right
if we pulled over
there for a second?
Huh?
That's Grand
Central Staion, right?
Yeah, right. Sure.
Whatever you say,
lady. It's your fare.
Ah, thanks.
I've never seen it
in person before.
I just think it'd be
neat to get a picture.
Tourists.
There ya go. Fifty-five bucks.
Oh, well, I uh...
I really just wanted to
jump out and take a picture,
but if that's not okay--
Free country, lady.
I'll get your bags.
Uh, wow, guess I'm
walking to the hotel...
Jeez.
Shit!
What the fuck is this?!
One, two, three,
four, five, six-
What's wrong?!
Are you nuts?!
How stupid can you be,
bringing crap like
this into my car? Huh?!
Come back!
Come back, oh, no.
It's a gun! Quick!
Somebody call the police!
Where did it come from?
Oh, I- uh-
Coming through, excuse me!
What am I supposed
to do with this thing?!
What was that?
What was this doing in my bag?
Oh, great, what now?
My passport, Takky's cell phone,
my purse, they were
all still in the cab.
Takizawa.
Don't worry.
I'll figure this out.
I think I finally
know where to look.
Hey, Saki!
The police finally
finished interrogating me
three days after the missiles
rained down all over Japan.
I decided it was best to go
back to my sister's place,
at least for the time being.
Juiz speaking.
You have one message.
Saki, thanks for
believing in me.
Don't forget our travels.
You can always find me
at our special place.
Takizawa.
I kept to myself,
hiding out at home
until the uproar over
the missile incident
began to die down.
I had a lot of time on my hands.
I spent most of it wondering
about what could have
happened to Takizawa.
But apparently Juiz
had been instructed
to erase any and
all record of his arrest
from police computers.
Takizawa had disappeared
from our world completely.
He was impossible
to find or contact.
You want to become king
of the country, but why?
But a part of him existed still,
in the pictures taken by the
people who were there that day.
He hadn't faded from
everybody's memory.
To some, he would
always be the savior
who had rescued Japan
from the missiles.
When all the pictures
were published
online following the attack,
the mass media reported
that Takizawa was
a central figure
to the terror investigation.
They began searching
for him everywhere.
Meanwhile, because
it was the source
of the Takizawa footage,
the Eden site was flooded
with hits from
all over the world.
Incredibly, Eden of the East
became an overnight sensation.
The image of Takizawa directing
the missiles' take-down
became a symbol of revolution.
This picture, combined
with the slogan "Air King,"
drew more and more attention
as the cause
gained wider support.
After the missiles fell,
our country reached a
crucial turning point.
There were miraculously
no casualties,
but things on the domestic front
were still destabilized
and stocks took a nosedive.
After failing to stop
another "Careless Monday,"
the entire administration
was forced to resign.
The event earned the
name "Uncle Dissolution"
in reference to Prime Minister
Eda's strange remark
during the Administration Audit.
All of these crazy events had
a considerably negative effect
on the world economy.
As usual, the U.S.
maintained its policy
of noninvolvement
and stayed out of it.
Our global standing plummeted.
Other nations satirized us
as "the nation that
attempted suicide."
The missiles may have never hit,
but the sad truth
of it is, in the end,
Japan probably took more
damage than if they had.
But there was still
the country's youth.
They knew nothing of
Japan's economic boom
or the subsequent
bursting of the bubble.
This was the first
time they had seen
their problems discussed
on the world stage.
So even though
they were nervous,
this instability represented
momentous opportunities
for improvement.
No one said so aloud,
but after that day,
our vague sense of despair
became a kind of hopefulness,
a feeling that we
could change the country.
Hey, you guys!
It was in this time shadowed
by both fear and optimism,
burdened by
unprecedented crises,
that Eden of the East took the
plunge and went into business.
I offered to help out too,
though I did feel a bit useless.
Nice business card!
So professional!
So you're "Sales
Division Three", huh?
Just because it's
called the third division
doesn't make me the
third-rate, you know.
Kasuga!
A hard worker like me
deserves respect, don't I?
Don't ask me.
This hard worker's already
got a desk on the main floor.
Come on now, Saki.
How desperate can you get?
We'll see you here
tomorrow, Saki!
It was six months
later--that summer--
that things really began moving.
That's when I finally got
the clue I'd been waiting for.
Hey.
You just made a trip to
Washington in May, didn't you?
I saw you bought
a second ticket,
but what I don't get is
why you're going again.
I didn't realize you knew.
Why go? Don't you feel like
you belong here with us?
No, that's not it, I just-
Hirasawa, you're being an idiot.
Oh yeah?
Don't worry.
You're not the only one
worried about Takky, you know.
Yeah.
Hirasawa hasn't told you,
but he's up to something, too.
He put Panties
to work monitoring
the activity on
Takky's cell phone.
He set it up so any logs sent
to it are automatically
forwarded to Eden.
As for the other Seleção,
they're still engrossed
in this mysterious
game they're playing.
That could put the whole
country in some hot water.
What if we're hit
by more missiles
or something even worse?
Hold on, don't you think it's
too early?
Isn't it about time that
you told Saki everything?
The reason for this company.
The fact that you founded it
as a support system
to help Takky.
Anyone can see
how much we owe him
for all his help.
So the way I figure it,
this time around,
it's up to us NEETs.
We're the ones who
have to save Takizawa,
and the country as well.
You mean that?
Mhmm. Not that we're
actually NEETs anymore,
but you get the point.
Hey, you guys have
to check this out!
The new Prime Minister's
collapsed!
No way!
Wait a second.
Didn't the name on
Takky's passport change
from Takizawa to Iinuma?
I wonder what Juiz is up to.
I may be wrong,
but I'm starting
to think she's trying
to make him
Prime Minister of Japan.
Look!
"Leak out existence
of illegitimate child?"
So does that mean Takizawa
is the Prime Minister's son?
Uh-uh.
It means she's
trying to make him
the Prime Minister's successor.
Changing his passport like this
was part of her ultimate plan.
This is insane.
I thought he was
a little bit off.
Who asks a computer
to erase his memories
and make him king of a country?
Then after doing so
just randomly disappeared.
But Juiz has lost it
too if she thinks this
is the way to go about
filling the request.
There's still one thing.
Just think for a second.
The chronology's off.
Takky's passport changed
over six months ago,
right after he left.
Does that mean Juiz foresaw
all of this happening?
Who the new
Prime Minister would be,
and the fact that
he would collapse
so early on while in office?
Scary, that means
her power reaches
to the heart of the government.
Never underestimate Saizo Ato.
That's the lesson here.
I knew this would be difficult,
but saving Takizawa
might be impossible.
He's in New York?
But I've never been to
New York with Takizawa before.
Didn't the message he left you
say something about
your 'special place'?
Is there anywhere in New York
that he'd think of as
being 'special' to you?
Wait, maybe he-
What, Saki?
Have you got an idea?
Two days later, I was on my way
to the United States,
and New York City.
I believed the
message Takizawa left
about 'our place' was one that
only I would be
able to understand.
So here I am.
But why did everything
have to turn out like this?
Eden of the East?
Saki, why didn't you
think to call us sooner?!
We've all been worried
sick about you.
Sorry.
I've had a lot going on.
It's a good thing
you checked in.
Things have gone from
bad to worse around here.
The Prime Minister passed away,
and there's been more
activity on the phone logs.
Seleção Number 6 and
Number 11 are headed
to New York right now.
And there's still more.
Number 6 made a request to plant
something in your luggage.
Check your bags immediately.
That explains it.
Wait. You mean something's
already happened?
There were handguns
stuffed into my carry-on.
The cab took off with my purse,
and I lost my passport
and the Noblesse phone.
You're kidding me?!
Why didn't you check the
phone as soon as you landed?!
I'm sorry.
I guess my mind
was somewhere else.
Honestly!
Well, I hate to be the one to
kick you when you're down,
but Seleção Number 2 sent
copies of Takizawa's passport
to all the major networks,
claiming he was the
PM's illegitimate son...
The information's out there now.
Which means the whole
country's in an uproar
about how Iinuma's
son is also wanted
for questioning in
the missile attacks.
They're after him
now more than ever.
It looks like the movement
on Takizawa's log
has motivated the Seleção
to resume playing
their game in earnest.
All that in just twelve hours?
I'm looking through these
and from Number 11's logs,
I think she's the one
you met in Roppongi,
but Number 6 is still a mystery.
Both of them asked Juiz
for Takky's location
and were denied.
Which means they'll probably try
to make contact with you.
Actually, they might
already be onto you.
Huh?!
Whoever this
Number 6 character is,
how'd they know about Saki?
Probably because the media
was following her around
for awhile after the missiles.
Either that or because she took
Takizawa's Noblesse
phone overseas with her.
That makes sense.
I wish we had
Number 6's identity.
Not knowing creeps me out.
None of us saw this coming,
but we still have
to deal with it.
You need to get to the consulate
general's office at once.
What?! But--
According to our latest reports,
Iinuma's supporters are flocking
to New York to
hunt down Takizawa.
I know you don't
like hearing this,
but I think you need to give up.
No way!
I have to find him, and quickly.
If I don't, the press
is gonna skewer him
when he doesn't even
remember anything.
How many of our burdens has
he already taken on for us?
I think we owe him
at least this much.
Not if it means exposing
you to more danger.
Think about this rationally.
Where are you going to stay?
You can't get a hotel room
without your passport.
No more arguing Saki.
I want you to hang up and
go straight to the consulate.
You got it?
No, Hirasawa.
I came all the way here,
and I'm not leaving
till I do all that I can.
Takizawa left that message
specifically for me,
and I think
I know what it means.
I have to give it a shot.
If I'm right about this,
I have a chance
of reaching him before
the other Seleção do.
I beg you. Just hang
on a little bit longer.
It's a bad idea.
The consulate general
closes at four o'clock.
Please, Hirasawa.
Okay, okay. But you
had better make sure
you're at the consulate
no later than four!
Understood?
Got it, and thank you.
Hey, watch it, lady.
He should be here.
What kind of lame
hero doesn't show up
when the heroine's in trouble?
Maybe if we'd gone with her,
she wouldn't have gotten
herself into this mess.
Are you going to start
crying over spilt milk now?
Besides, I think
she would've found
a way to go alone
no matter what.
I agree.
Saki's a big girl and
she can take care of herself.
Have some faith.
Her secret travels
have worked out before.
That's how she met
Takky in the first place.
I guess you're right.
I got your voicemail.
What's going on?!
Saki's missing?!
Kasuga!
It wasn't me, I swear!
It was me.
I figured he'd just bitch about
it later if we didn't tell him.
How could you let
this happen, Hirasawa?!
If she gets hurt,
then I am blaming you!
A simple group of NEETs,
and this is all it takes to turn
them into crusaders overnight.
Am I an awesome
producer or what?
Seems like an entertaining job.
One thing, though.
How exactly do you
make money off of it?
Oh, please.
I couldn't care less
about the money.
But you know.
It seems like
Public Security has been
keeping tabs on these
new NEETs of mine.
Level with me.
You wouldn't know
anything about that?
No, beats me.
Of course.
Anyway, it looks as if you've
been playing your cards
as craftily as ever,
for someone who
refuses to join the game.
And what about you?
What change of
heart made you decide
to take this all seriously?
You've never been the
slightest bit interested before.
It's Number 9.
I credit him for my inspiration.
Besides which,
if I don't get a move on,
the Supporter will
eliminate me, won't he?
I assure you, the Supporter's
task doesn't belong to me.
I'm not even sure such
a position actually exists.
But if it does, I would
think he was Number 12.
Well, I hope you
aren't expecting me
to begin trusting you.
You might've made
Number 6 your puppet,
but I have no intention of
letting you do that to me.
I have nothing to
do with it this time.
Sending him after
Number 9 couldn't possibly
do anything to benefit me,
so why would I bother?
I don't much care what you
do at this point, anyway.
You've been quite
busy massaging the law,
rubbing elbows with
your politician friends.
But while you were
otherwise occupied,
I found a way to win the game.
Did you? How interesting.
Was leaking the identity
of the Prime Minister's son
a part of your plan?
I admit, I've been wondering.
I - won't - tell.
Then we have nothing
more to talk about.
We're all done here.
Let's see, next up.
We saw our own Ground Zero.
One of the sites where a
missile hit on Careless Monday.
Okay, so do I have to ride
that boat to find him?
Good. Safe.
Whatcha doing?
I'm not doing anything!
I was just-
You call that nothing? A gun?
Don't worry.
Somebody made you
carry it, I'm guessing.
It happens a lot.
Gun runners use tourists
so they don't risk
taking the fall. May I?
Now run!
Nice! I don't think
anyone saw us.
Take care, okay?
Takizawa, wait!
"Takizawa?" Sorry,
but my name's Iinuma.
Uh. Maybe you could help me.
Mr. Iinuma.
I'm looking for someone.
How can I help you?
Oh, uh, well I think-
I have an idea of
where to find him.
Except, I lost all of our things
when I first got here,
his cell and my luggage.
Man, that really sucks.
I can give you a hand finding
them if you'd like me to.
So where did you last see them?
Back in the yellow cab
I took from the airport.
In a taxi?
That means we
definitely have a chance
of finding them,
so try not to worry.
First off, do you
still have the receipt?
Uh, yeah.
Done!
Finally, everyone's
following the script.
It's after three.
Don't you think Saki
should have called by now?
Don't get your panties in a wad.
There's still time left.
But not much though.
Hey, Kasuga, I think
I'm gonna go ahead
and get outta here, alright?
You're scheduled
for four more hours.
You can't just leave in the
middle of your shift like that.
It's not like there's
a lot going on.
Besides, you guys are still
here, so what's the big deal?
Whether we're here or
not isn't the point.
Let it go, Kasuga!
You can head out.
Have a good night.
Get some rest.
Thanks. See ya later!
Goodnight, you guys!
Kasuga's got the life.
Treated like an exec just
'cause he went to
Mr. Hirasawa's school.
Yeah, no kidding.
Must be nice, huh.
Kasuga.
They're older than me,
so I get why they don't
call me "Mr." like Hirasawa,
but that isn't it.
They come in late.
They won't work the night shift.
They all want raises.
They don't understand
what it takes
to be an adult
in the work place.
I know.
We have a bunch of lazy,
good-for-nothing employees.
Well, maybe we should
just clean house
and get rid of them all.
Huh?!
I get your point.
I shouldn't be complaining
about having people to help me.
I do understand how you feel.
The old guys who take success
for granted should be the enemy.
But I get what they
feel like now, too.
And that's what it means
to be a full-fledged
member of society.
Hard at work stuffing
your faces, huh?
I hope you haven't lost
your NEET spirit already.
You can't lose your drive
just because you've
gone into business.
Seriously, you
don't want to give in
to the man like all the other
lame adults out there, do you?
Yeah, exactly!
Oh, hey there, Kasuga.
What's up? How's
it hangin'? Micchon.
What's this thing?
I took the liberty of amping up
Eden's search engine for ya.
That little baby's
a real piece of work.
It'll give us free access
to data we could
never access before.
There's gotta be pre-Takizawa
info lyin' around somewhere,
stuff from before he
was playing this game.
Let's find out a bit more
about Vintage Boy's past.
Once we do that, we can
stop people from thinking
he's Prime Minister
Iinuma's son or whatever.
Right!
Um, did I take you
away from your job?
Don't worry.
I was just on my way to
a party for a coworker.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, cheer up.
We're gonna find
your bags, 'kay?
Then you can catch up
with the person you
were looking for.
That Takizawa guy.
Yeah.
So, who is he?
An old boyfriend or something?
Oh, no! That's not it.
Takizawa, he was a
good friend of mine.
Six months ago he
disappeared into thin air.
I eventually found out
that he was living
here in New York City.
But even though we were close,
I don't think he's going
to remember me at all.
Wow, that's harsh.
Yeah, no kidding. It's rough.
Follow me.
I found out who
your taxi driver was.
That's him there!
Uh-oh. He looks kinda scary.
There. Stay just
like that for me, okay?
Hi!
Do you happen to
know if anybody left
a cell phone in your cab
earlier today? Or a bag?
I don't know nothin', pal.
You sure about that?
See, I'm a police
officer, from Japan.
You're a cop?
Do you recognize that
young lady over there, sir?
She may not look it, but she
is a dangerous terrorist.
She's a terrorist?
Yes! I finally
managed to catch her.
But I'm still looking for the
bomb that she was carrying.
Did you hear me? B-O-M-B. Bomb!
A bomb?
Apparently it's been cleverly
disguised as a cell phone.
If I don't find it, things
are gonna get ugly quick.
It's really important that you
help me out here, or KABOOM!
You know?
Well, uh-
Maybe I've got the
wrong place then.
I'll keep asking around.
See ya. Have a good day.
Hey, hey, hey. Wait up a second.
Is this the purse
that you're looking for?
Yep, it's here.
I'm just glad we
found it in time.
Yeah, me too.
That was a close call.
Thanks for your
cooperation, sir!
I got it!
Wow, he didn't look
like he wanted to help.
Keep up the good work, man!
He was all right.
I just needed to
explain the situation.
'Kay. Here.
Oh, and I'd avoid
taking another cab back
to the airport if
I were you, just to be safe.
So long.
Please hold on.
Is there something else?
Um, yeah.
Remember earlier,
when I told you
about the guy
I'd been looking for?
I meant you!
I've been looking for you.
Good one! You were
looking for me?
I'm flattered but-
Is that me?
I've been looking for you
for six months straight--ever
since you disappeared.
What d'ya say, my place?
Huh?
Freak out all you'd like,
but it's not going
to accomplish anything.
Yeah, but she's late!
Hey. Saki sent an email.
She says "I found Takizawa."
With his help, I was able
to get my passport and
the cell phone back, too.
So is she coming to his rescue,
or is he coming to hers?
What I'd like to know
is how she found him.
Oh, isn't it obvious?
Love brought them
together, what else?
Is there more?
"For now we're headed
back to his apartment.
I'll write more when
I have time." That's it.
This is so exciting. Right?
Well, perhaps somebody
should respond to Saki's email
and remind her to
use good judgment.
Saki! No! You can't do this!
You can't do anything
about it now, Osugi.
It's time to accept the facts
and move on with your life.
I'm ashamed of you.
You must remember what
the NEET youth stand for.
We don't roll over and
give in to the status quo.
It's our solemn duty
to help Osugi fight
for what he believes.
Am I right, Micchon?
I don't think so.
Yes. Juiz here.
Did you see to it that she
got safely away this morning?
Yes.
I caused a minor car accident
to distract the police from her.
I generally prefer more elegant
methods, but time was short.
I understand.
It was outside
the effective range.
You did what you could.
You're too kind.
Will there be
anything else for now?
No, no. I think that should
be all, but thank you.
Very well.
What's wrong?
It's just that we
haven't followed
our usual routine lately.
That's true.
I haven't set my blade to a
man's Johnny in quite awhile.
Is it me?
Have I done something
to disappoint you?
No, Juiz. It's not you.
I have other business I need
to attend to at the moment.
May I ask what?
This is Number 1,
Daiju Mononobe.
This smarmy, preppy, four-eyed
jerk is the Seleção who hit me.
He left his position
in the bureaucracy
and got an executive job
with Ato and Company.
His objective was to
become the new Mr. Outside,
but he botched the plan.
No idea what he's
been up to since.
We don't know who Number 2 is.
His requests tend
toward the criminal side,
but he's kept his
identity well hidden.
Number 6 is sneakin'
around New York right now.
We don't know
his identity either,
but from his requests,
I'd guess he's some kinda
film producer or somethin'.
In short.
I think we need to view
these three as a threat.
I doubt that they've got
anything good in mind
for ol' Vintage Boy.
And Number 10,
Ryo Yuki, it looks like
he's moved from the 'danger'
list onto the 'drop-out' list'.
Yeah.
His behavior changed
after the missile incident.
He's been makin'
requests to have Number 9
assassinated over and over
but been denied every time.
Three days ago, his phone
finally went completely dark.
That sounds like the same thing
that happened to Number 4.
Yep. No telling yet
whether he's dead or alive.
Number 10 had money
left in his account though,
just like Number 4 did.
So it's possible someone decided
that he wasn't worth
havin' around anymore.
Somebody else's got
me wondern', though.
It's Number 5, Hajime Hiura.
Dude's completely broke.
There's not a cent
left in his account,
but somehow, he's still alive.
I went to see him
to check on his status
and what-not,
but he wasn't runnin'
that hospital of his anymore.
And you know why?
'Cause he'd lost
all his memories.
Even when I reminded him
he owned a huge hospital,
he had no clue what
I was talkin' about.
He was pretty rattled when
I explained the situation,
but the old man
caught on a lot faster
than I would've expected.
It was weird.
When he realized he really
did build a hospital,
he just accepted it, like it
was meant to be or somethin'.
Even with all his
memories wiped out,
it seems like
he'd still rather look
at the positive side of things.
If his money's gone,
why do you think he
hasn't been killed
by the Supporter yet?
These guys don't mess around.
There's some reason
he's still alive,
and the only thing I can
think of is that he won.
But remember what
happens if somebody wins?
The other Seleção are
supposed to be eliminated.
It doesn't make sense.
You've got a point there.
But maybe we've been
looking at all of this
from the wrong angle-Have
you ever considered
that Mr. Outside means to
eliminate their memories,
not their actual lives?
Perhaps. Interesting theory,
but, he said any Seleção who
broke the rules would die.
There're still tons
of uncertainties.
Like, what if Mr. Outside
and Number 12
are the same person?
That'd change up the
entire game, wouldn't it?
One guy keeping tabs
on the other Seleção,
makin' them play by the rules,
and dishin' out
penalties all by himself.
He'd be running around like a
chicken with its head cut off.
But Juiz would help.
That's what she's there for.
Nope. I didn't find anything
in the logs that
pointed to that.
He's the one who
organized the game
in the first place,
so maybe he's been outside
the rules from the beginning.
If so, then why would he leave
a record of transportin' Juiz?
If you ask me, old
Saizo Ato's gone batty,
but he's still run a consistent,
streamlined game so far.
The geezer really seems
to know what he's doing,
even if it is nuts.
Think about it.
He's got this
crazy idea that no one
in their right mind would
willingly go along with.
So, in order to motivate 'em,
he invents the
role of the Supporter,
and he makes them all think
it's a life-or-death game.
Which also increases their
suspicion of each other,
like when they thought
Takizawa was the Supporter.
Of course, it could be nothin'
but wishful thinkin' on my part.
Well, it'd be
good news for Takky.
He's burning through
his balance quickly.
I don't know how long
it'll last at this rate.
We shouldn't jump to any
conclusions yet, though.
She's right.
We've gotta be careful
not to get too optimistic.
Huh, so I'm in this
group called the Seleção,
my code name is Number 9,
and I'm wanted for questioning
about that big
Japanese missile crisis.
It's kinda like that movie,
The Man Who Stole the Sun.
It's not a movie!
It's true, I swear!
Hey, don't worry; I never
said I didn't believe you.
Well, this is our stop.
A hotel?
Heeeeyyyy! Air King!
Hey there!
That happen a lot?
People calling you 'Air King'?
Yep.
People I don't even know walk
right up to me on the street.
That's part of the
reason I didn't just
blow off your story, no
matter how weird it was.
It might be true.
Without my memories,
how can I say that it's not?
Hell. Just looking
at this picture
makes me believe
I'm the real thing.
All right, they're in
room 801 of the Gramercy Hotel.
I don't care what
you have to do...
just make them take a shower,
then do exactly what I told you.
I'm sorry, but I'm
afraid I don't understand
the point of your request.
Come on. Think about it.
In every great movie
featuring a couple on the run
from the authorities,
the two lovebirds inevitable
end up in the
shower at some point.
It's a classic motif that
I can't simply overlook.
Classic motif or not,
not even something
as powerful as
the Seleção system
can control the human will.
Besides which, you're at the
edge of the effective range.
My scope is limited.
No, no, no!
Hold on a sec. Not fair!
I know for a fact
you're supplying Number 9
with cash from a bank
account that you created.
That's totally against
the rules, and you know it.
If you're doing it for him,
why can't you bend
the rules for me, too?!
That's different.
It's part of Number 9's
request to become king.
As such, it is perfectly
in keeping with the rules.
Oh, all right. I get it now.
Then I want you to
make me a king, too!
The process of becoming a king
is different for each Seleção.
You may not be eligible.
Please wait while I confirm
if your request is possible.
This may take a moment.
Do you really have
to be so difficult?!
Will that be all?
Fine, then just
do what I told ya to
in the first fuckin' place!
Can you handle that?!
Accepted. I pray that
you become a savior
who knows how to
watch his mouth better.
Damn her; she's becoming
more of a smart-ass every day.
Nice room, Mr. Iinuma!
How did you pay for all this?
Wasn't me.
Oh, and feel free to call me
Takizawa if you'd prefer.
So do you remember
anything that's happened
since all your
memories disappeared?
It was strange.
The cops up and
released me outta nowhere.
They gave me business cards
and a passport in Iinuma's
name and all these keys.
Then I got a phone call.
It instructed me to
go to the movie theater
where I first saw Dumbo.
So I came to New York
and found the theater.
I've been waiting ever
since for my mom to show up.
You're doing what?!
People usually go to see Dumbo
with their mom's, don't they?
So I figured that random call
I got probably came from her.
But after everything you
told me, I'm not sure.
I mean, didn't you say I haven't
seen her since I was five?
Mhmm.
I guess that "concierge"
lady on the phone
is taking care of
this room for me.
But I don't remember seeing
a request for a
room on your log.
Really?
"Given the situation,
it's too dangerous
to come back yet."
"You and Takizawa
hide out in the U.S.
until the dust settles.
We'll back you up from here.
Wait for us to call
before you move."
What do they mean by that?
Your request to become king
is complicating things a bit.
There's no way you can go
home without being noticed.
You'll not only be the Prime
Minister's illegitimate son,
but the main suspect
in the missile attack!
Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't I see if
I can cancel that request?
It's gotta be
worth a try, right?
Huh?!
Hello, Juiz speaking.
Yeah, hello?
It's been such a long time!
I haven't heard
from you since I called
the police station while
I was having you released.
Oh! So that was you.
Funny story: I actually
thought that you were my mom.
Since you're back in touch,'
I take it everything's
been going well
these past few months?
That's good to hear!
Yeah, well.
Uh. I had a question about that.
I was wondering if
it would be possible
to cancel that request
to become king.
What?
But I thought you'd make
such a splendid king!
I must admit,
I'm a bit disappointed
about this, Number 9.
Wow.
Thank you, I guess.
It is technically possible
to cancel the order,
but if you choose to do so,
things will remain-
as they are- at present.
Do you still wish to proceed
with the cancellation?
Nothing'll change?
That isn't going to help anyone.
Even if it doesn't, I still
think you should cancel it.
Can I have a little
time to think it over?
Huh?
Yes, of course. Noblesse oblige.
I pray that you continue
to be a successful prince,
er, rather, savior.
Why not cancel?
Well, I figure
I've come this far,
so I should probably
see it through.
You sure? Really?
I can't really
blame Mrs. Iinuma.
I'd feel the same
way in her position.
Dear. As expected,
yet another unusual request
from Number 6.
I wonder if Number 9
knows what he's up to.
We don't have to eat that stuff.
We do have other food, you know.
What happened to
your NEET spirit?
Life isn't all about fancy food
and nice things, you know.
This from you?
The same guy who could
barely leave his house
for two years
because he was living
on an allowance he
got from his parents.
Don't you get it, man?
That's what being
a NEET is about.
That's easy for you to say.
You've had a good time
of it as a NEET
so far since your
parents are well off,
but that isn't gonna
last much longer.
It sounds like the changes in
the tax laws are going through.
Like the one that's gonna push
the death tax up
to a hundred percent?
This country gets threatened
with a missile attack,
and we're the ones
who end up payin'.
It's nuts.
How can such a crazy law
possibly pass so easily?
The youth don't
take it seriously
since they have
nothing to pass on.
Instead, they see it as a way
of leveling the playing field
by taxing the rich, but most
older folks have already started
depleting their savings
so they can avoid the tax.
Yeah, it's true.
Even my old man's doing it.
He intends to make damn sure
that he's not
leaving me anything.
The law's supporters
say it'll be a stimulus
to speed up the
economy's recovery.
But if you ask me, what
they're really trying to do
is stick it to the NEETs,
and from the sound of it,
Hirasawa, your father is
playing right into their plans.
A stimulus? Oh, please!
What they're doing is
stealing the taxpayers' money.
Why can't the government
get anything right?
Hey, check your phone.
I don't think you hung
up after the last call.
That doesn't make sense.
I'll get it for you.
Looks like Number 6
just made a move.
That's hot! Why did
this thing turn itself on?
Yes, hello?
Number 9?
Who's asking for 'im?
You really don't
remember me, do you?
Huh?
Well.
I only called to see if you
were in the shower yet.
What? That came out of nowhere.
A 'yes' or 'no' will do.
Okay. No, not at the moment.
I suggest you check your
cell phone immediately.
Who's that?
Beats me.
That's good stuff.
Small explosions always
play more realistic on film.
This is right up there
with Spielberg's Munich.
No way!
They got out of the building?!
Juiz, what the hell?!
I told you! All great
movies have a sce---
My research hasn't turned
up a single classic movie
that ends with the leads
being blown up in a bathroom.
That was my own
personal touch, thank you.
Fine, I'll let it
slide this time,
just get them for me, will ya?
Request denied.
You're outside
the effective range.
I cannot pursue them
in a timely manner.
Why, you little-
Yeah. Don't worry. We're fine.
Someone warned Takizawa
about the bomb,
and we were able to get out
of the building just in time.
A warning? Who'd it come from?
I have no idea.
In any case, we'll
come up with a way
to wire you some money tomorrow.
Take it and then
get out of New York.
Right, thank you.
So what now?
Do you have a place
to hide until then?
We're headed for the place
where Takizawa works right now.
He says he has a key.
So, this is the theater where
I saw Dumbo the first time.
That wasn't a lot to go on.
But you still found it.
Crazy, huh. Here, take this.
They always crank the
AC up way too high in here.
But what about you?
I'm gonna keep watch.
It'd be bad news
if someone finds us.
Shout if you need
anything, okay?
Hold on!
Are you gonna leave again?
Hey. Do you know
what I was doing
out in Brooklyn today?
No. What?
I've lost almost all
of my memories,
except for the ones that're
associated with movies.
For some reason those stuck.
That's probably why I was
able to find this place.
But there's this one,
a movie I can't seem
to remember no
matter how hard I try.
It's about this couple that gets
temporarily separated
from each other,
but they took a picture of
themselves in the middle
of 9/11 with Ground Zero
in the background.
That picture becomes the clue
that ultimately brings
them back together.
I was so desperate to remember
the movie's title that I
visited Ground Zero every day,
but now you're here,
and it turns out it wasn't
a scene from a movie.
Wow, you mean you
can actually hack into
all those peoples'
personal networks?
Shouldn't you
be careful snooping
into business
and school records?
That'll get you in big trouble.
Little late to be
worrying about that now.
We're runnin' outa time.
We need all the information
that we can get
on him, and quickly.
Hey, I found something!
Now I get why we
couldn't find his data.
Damn Juiz. This is her work.
She's erasing all of the "Akira
Takizawa" info on the net,
and replacing it with
"Akira Iinuma."
Hey, Micchon!
Did Number 9 send out
that order himself?
It doesn't say anything
like that in the logs.
It's gone?!
So she's erasing more
than Akira Takizawa's
history on the internet.
She's also deleting all
the names in his log.
That's crazy!
You mean Juiz has been
making data disappear
all this time and
we haven't noticed it?
Eh, don't have a heart attack.
I made a plan B in case
this kinda thing happened.
I worked it out so
the phone's activity
is copied to my PC,
where it's saved.
You are so awesome!
Aw, stop it.
You're making me blush!
Impossible!
A firewall that's got
the ability to attack?
What is this? You ever
seen anything like it?
Micchon, try scrolling back
through Takky's detail log.
Stop right there. Look.
Yeah, I see it.
"Hack into Eden of the East
and use the image system."
Your plan backfired, Panties!
Now Juiz can use Eden
for her own purposes
since you beefed up
the search engine!
She's usin' it?! That bitch!
At this rate, it won't be long
before Akira Iinuma replaces
Akira Takizawa completely.
They're called roving bugs.
They're used to control
cell phones remotely.
With these, you can listen in
on surrounding conversations.
From what I hear, FBI types
use these things all the time.
Is a Seleção behind this?
No clue. What do you think?
Is it one of them, Micchon?
Probably. It's here,
in Number 1's log.
"Have Public Security Division
investigate Eden of the East."
It's four-eyes again?!
What is he up to this time?
And what does it
have to do with Eden?
Takizawa?!
Hey, what's wrong?
Don't tell me you thought
I'd taken off again.
I know this poster.
You had it hanging up
in your theater, too.
I guess it musta been
really important to me
at some point for it to keep
on popping up like that.
So, what now?
I'm betting it's still
gonna be quite a while
before the money comes
in from your friends.
I've got enough cash for us
to take the bus to Chinatown.
I have an idea.
Why don't we take a walk
and explore the city?
Wait, explore?
Why not?
This neighborhood
is familiar to me,
like I lived here as
a kid or something.
Plus, there are still some
things I need to know.
Some things about my past.
I want proof of who I was
before he's gone for good.
Well I can think of one thing.
Before you left,
you said something odd
about there being
no "gold ring."
I think that's where
we should start.
Juiz speaking.
Yo, No-obli.
I'm up to something interesting.
You wanna hear?
Certainly. I'd love to.
How's this headline:
"Late Prime Minister's Son
is the Missile Terrorist."
That should cause a good amount
of chaos, don't you think?
Unfortunately, it won't be
enough to save the country.
To do that, we're gonna
have to go further.
We find a way to make
all Japan's citizens
feel victimized.
They need to be
motivated to stand up
and bitch at other nations.
Are you feeling me, Juiz?
Yes, I feel you, 2G.
These days, the victim's
the one with all the power.
Think about it: We live in a
time where all you have to do
is spill coffee on yourself
and you can sue
for pain and suffering.
So I say we buy us one
of those victim tickets
and hop on the train
with the rest of 'em.
I'd hate to waste
the NEETs' sit-in.
Let's orchestrate a nice,
painless destruction.
Magnificent, 2G! Truly inspired.
I know, right?
The Prime Minister's son returns
to Japan in an Air King T-shirt.
The rest of Asia
promptly flips out
because they're
afraid that we're going
to turn militaristic
and nuke them.
Then the Air King is gunned down
by a foreigner shortly
after returning home,
and from there,
it's a done deal.
Yes, 2G.
I pray you shall always remain
a forward-thinking savior.
But how do we get him
to wear the T-shirt?
It's over there,
on the merry-go-round.
I think that's the gold ring
you were talking about.
I didn't know what you meant,
so I did some research.
Japanese merry-go-rounds
don't have gold rings.
That's what you noticed on the
day of the last missile attack.
Apparently most of
the ones in the U.S.
don't have them anymore, either.
They did up until
around the late eighties,
though, and sometimes,
you'll still find one.
You're supposed to
try to grab the ring.
If you catch it, you get an
extra ride on the carousel.
That makes sense.
I must've been here
sometime as a kid.
That explains why I know
about the gold ring.
That was a nice try.
It's over already?
That was quick.
You take another spin.
I'll watch you ride
from right over there.
When did you get that?!
This place does
bring back memories.
Mom was always sending me off
to the theater to
watch shows by myself.
So when she actually
took me somewhere else,
like this park, I was ecstatic.
I'd reach for that gold ring
with everything I had,
hoping I'd never have to
get off the merry-go-round.
And when I caught it,
I'd wave to her and shout,
"Look, Mom, I did it!
I got the gold ring!"
She'd be sitting here,
just watching me go
'round and 'round again.
She hated movies.
There was only one she'd
ever watch with me: Dumbo.
You should come out of the rain.
You're gonna get soaked!
Don't worry about it.
I'd rather watch you
from here, if that's okay.
Target sighted.
He's in front of the carousel.
I finally got 'em.
They better not have
gotten too friendly
while I wasn't
there to film them.
Hey, what's this?
Thanks to you I was
able to get back some of
my memories from the
time I spent in New York.
Hurry up. Get in!
You're the one
who called to warn me
about the bomb yesterday?
Yes. Prime Minister Iinuma's
wife wanted me
to fetch you.
She insisted I use
the utmost secrecy.
The other Seleção aren't
the only ones upset
about your request
to become a king.
Thanks to you, Mrs. Iinuma's
pride has been damaged
and her husband's
good name sullied.
It's no surprise
that she hates you.
If she's that mad,
why are you taking
Takizawa to see her?
She'd like to
meet you in person.
She wants to assess
your intentions
regarding the leadership
of the country.
As for me, I'd like to see
what kind of king
you'd make of yourself.
What do we do now?
I erased the new search engine,
but I don't know
how much it'll help.
The next step is shutting down
Eden of the East completely.
At the very least, that should
buy us some more time.
Huh?!
Panties, how much
longer will that get us?
It looks like we'll have a
little over forty-eight hours.
That's a decent increase.
It's good to see how
well our system works.
Think about this.
Eden's been growing so quickly.
By now it's practically part
of the public infrastructure.
If we shut it down,
we'll be affecting a lot more
than just twenty-thousand NEETs.
I know. Well, Micchon?
I switched over to the local
area network.
Here we go. Goodbye, Eden.
It's really shut down?
Relax.
I know you're the one who's
gonna have to deal
with the ton of complaints we'll
be getting about this.
But it's only temporary, so
don't freak out.
But what about Hirasawa?!
I mean he's spent so long
pouring his blood,
sweat, and snot
into Eden of the East!
It's 'tears', not 'snot'!
And Saki?
We can't support her
and Takizawa with
the system down.
What're we supposed to do?
I have an idea.
Our current location is
under strict surveillance,
which limits our capabilities,
so I propose that
we move headquarters.
Where are we supposed to go?
Sir, I have our
club room at the college
on reserve in case
of an emergency.
It's not as nice
as the new place,
but the old Eden
system is still there.
It's settled then.
The club room's the perfect
place to help Vintage Boy from.
Yeah, I think you're right.
An email from Saki!
It says "We're heading
for the airport.
Sorry for the sudden notice,
but Takizawa is
coming back to Japan."
What the heck's she thinking?
Sorry, sweetie.
I'm afraid this is as
far as you can come.
Hey. What does
this new log mean?
Number 1 is launching a missile.
Juiz?
Get me a report
of what's happening
at the coordinates
in Number 1's log.
Now, Juiz.
Launch the other missiles
as we previously discussed.
Accepted. Noblesse oblige.
I pray for your
continued success
as a "raze and rebuild" savior.
My number's been blacked out.
Hey, hello!
Juiz! Can you hear me, Juiz?
Mononobe has to be behind this.
I wonder if he located Juiz
and blew her up
with that missile.
But at least half of my request
has already been accepted.
You're too late.
Besides, Mr. Mononobe,
what you have planned
isn't what this country wants.
Yuki!
But I thought you were
eliminated by the Supporter!
Actually, I "eliminated" myself.
I destroyed my Noblesse phone
so I could get the
revenge I wanted.
Hello, Juiz.
I need you to do
something for me.
It's urgent.
What is it?
Can you move the third trailer
in the convoy to
the front of the line?
Yes, of course.
Then please do it. Quickly.
Accepted! Noblesse Oblige.
I pray you shall still be
my beautiful savior tomorrow.
Hurry, Juiz. Please hurry.
Just in time.
You were the most brilliant
assistant I ever had.
Thank you for everything, Juiz.
This is it, Number 9.
You're on your own now.
I can't be your
guardian angel anymore.
Number 1 will be wrapping
up the game any time now,
but I've already
placed my bet on you.
You will keep your
promise, won't you?
What promise?
I pray you never
forget your true self
when you are king.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Go to him. He
needs somebody's help.
I've done all I can do.
Thank you, Kuroha.
All right, well, it's
about time to go home.
Ato is so difficult.
If the public
finds out about it,
the political fallout will be
the least of our problems.
Yes, sir.
The repercussions
would be quite severe.
That's one of the reasons
we need to sacrifice
Mr. Iinuma's son.
You've proved your worth
before by stopping
those sixty missiles.
I have every confidence
that you can handle
this situation neatly.
It's been sixty-five
years since the war.
All that time, we've let other
countries call the shots for us.
I will break Japan free
from that culture of dependence.
You have a talent
for gathering information
and intimate knowledge of
the bureaucratic machine.
With you on our side,
I can almost see the old
Ministry rising back into power.
I'll even say "uncle"
again if I have to.